What's that? Hold on, hold on, you put the light onto the fucking tracking thing.
Ah, it's blinding! It's blinding, it's looking good.
Me? Hmm, why do I need to wear glasses? Also me, because blasted.
About, like, one minute late, she hates us.
You stop that, you naughty Nellie.
You naughty soft fans.
You naughty ballbags. I actually don't say that word, that's fine.
Well, I mean, that's another word.
Uh...
Um...
Are we here? Hello? Hello? Hi! Hello America! Hiya! Hiya!
Oh my god, what's that?
We get to do another full day of Assassin's Creed.
And I get to, yeah, ease as much as I like.
Uh, I do want to say I am very thankful to PayPal support.
Yay! PayPal unblocked this.
Because if you didn't know, yesterday, you guys unanimously, at the same time,
supported, like, everyone with donos.
And PayPal was like, halt, halt.
This account has been paused because what on earth are all these things?
And we literally had to go, oh, hello there PayPal.
Uh, we're streaming.
Uh, we're beach homers. Please unblock.
So you can support my daughters.
Uh...
Good morning!
Good evening!
And most of all, good afternoon reeflings!
Are you ready to fuck up your sleep pattern?
Do do d, d, d, d, d, d, d.
Do, d, d, d, d, d, d, d, d, d, d, d, d, d, d, d, d, dd, dd, d,d, d, d, d, d, d, d, d, dd, d, dd, d, dd, d, d, d, d, d, d, dd,
How are you?
And you did? It was Aisy looking after you.
Did anyone touch your tummy?
Don't lie, Aisy's best design element is her tummy, her navel.
If you didn't know, a belly button is also a refer to as a navel.
I understand you can't hear the background music, oh I've seen some creepy brotherhood right now.
Ask that memean, erm.
I apologise for being a whole 60 seconds late.
Do you want to know why I'm 60 seconds late?
Cos I was trying to arrange another Ace Markalab.
Um, I've recorded one with Mimosa, I need to edit it.
I do not know how long today's stream is gonna be, so feel free to strap in.
And if not, I'll be the one wearing the strap in this relationship.
Ah, that's terrible, absolutely terrible, just started.
Erm, but it's been fantastic.
I should hopefully not miss any freaking donations.
Like I did yesterday, cos I was absolutely awful.
I just kept missing everything left and right.
Everything left and right.
Left and right.
Oh, that's not how I can read.
Okay, there we go.
Woo, five hours of sleeping, eight hours of work, and we're so bad.
Oh, please rest, okay.
I can, I literally, I brushed my teeth, I had a shower.
Right, well I'll tell you something gross whilst we jump back into the action.
I'll tell you something nasty.
Why can I not hear my game?
Hello? Headset?
Headset?
Headset, I know there's, hello?
Okay, I cannot hear any sound and the game isn't coming out of my fucking desktop.
Are you fucking serious?
By the way, this game lives up to the test of time.
Are we being true?
Why is it not coming out of desktop?
Is this a fucking joke?
How could this have been so scuffed?
I can't hear the game either.
Okay, fantastic.
Fantastic!
No, seriously.
The tips link is messed up again.
Are you joking? God, I'm so scuffed.
Um...
I am speechless on why the game is not playing through the desktop audio right now.
Hold on, let me start clicking stuff and see what happens.
Okay, I need to start clicking stuff.
Why would the game not be detectable via the desktop audio?
I am totally not raging right now.
Let's check, let's check.
Right, okay, okay, okay, hold on, hold on, hold on, let me click.
Rule one, if something doesn't work, close the game and open it again.
Because why would it not be detectable on desktop?
That's rule one of gaming.
Okay, so I've closed it.
It's now closed, you can't see none of it.
Also, I listened back.
I was watching a bit of my own brotherhood gameplay.
My voice actually doesn't sound that messed up,
but I can hear it and feel it myself how messed up it is.
Yep, again, no audio.
If I have to go offline to troubleshoot this, I'm gonna be so mad.
Why? I didn't do anything.
I, Mercy, has literally made a short about this exact scenario.
I cannot make this up.
Mercy has a short coming out later about this exact situation.
Game, audio output settings, hold on, hold on, hold on, manage input devices,
output devices, sound mixer, is it sound mixer?
Input, yep, output, yep.
Why the frick?
Why the frick fracked Italy deck, tic-tac, petty whack?
Would this not be coming out?
I think I actually have to go offline to frickin' jumpshoot this.
I'm not even kidding.
I can't believe this.
Are you joking?
It only took me seven minutes to start the stream!
Oh, 49% total synchronization.
Oh, I guess we are doing 12 hours then if I'm only at 49%.
Let's go.
Literally, Mercy made a short about this.
I cannot wait for the short to come out so you guys can be like, oh my god.
Oh my god, she was right.
If you are not up to scratch, please do not worry
because we have successfully finished campaign mode.
We are currently playing Landlord Simulator 2 by all of the buildings at the moment.
We are now doing the kind of side quest-esque missions.
We are about to do a very sad mission for the auditory family.
Me, I'm still here.
Good morning, good afternoon, good evening.
I hope all is good.
I believe Asakul is the only other member live at this moment.
But as always, when another member goes live,
I will force you to go insane to her stream.
Okay, here we go.
I do not normally do this so I'm not too familiar with what happens next.
I think Asi is going offline.
That's Leonardo.
That's Leonardo's voice.
Desmond's heart rate is increasing.
I'm administering a sedative.
No, the missing data may be there.
The piece of Eden is useless until we have-
Oh, I don't remember much of this.
Yes, William.
Yes, William, congrats if your name's William.
Any Williams in her?
Eh?
The Da Vinci-
Eh, Da Vinci- I'm sorry, I didn't mean that.
The Da Vinci Disappearance.
Did you know?
I remember.
Leonardo.
Good friend.
Thank you.
I see you're reading Super Chess at the moment.
Wait, she got monetized?
She couldn't have.
I didn't link that.
Did you mean Donation?
No, they were doing- I was gonna say.
None of us have monetization here.
Uh, I think one of my assassins came back for success.
We're from a mission.
It's gonna be da Mona Lisa.
And that smile.
Overdone.
I'm so sorry, AC, I never managed to catch any of the-
Snowberries!
Any snowberries?
Hi, Snowberries!
He's a part of the campaign.
Get raided, get raided, get raided!
Get plopped, get plopped, get plopped.
Are you squidding me right now?
Ah, thank you for the 20.
Bajinga, what the fuck?
There's no way that says Bajinga.
Did I read that right? I read it in the top corner.
Thank you Bajinga for the-
What? You didn't even leave a message!
Why are you called Bajinga?
Oh, now I can't read chat.
Oh god, I'm so brain dead.
Hold on, hold on, hold on.
Bajinga?
Good morning.
I'm glad you like icicles.
Ah, it's the woman.
Did you see the guitar AC design?
No, I didn't manage to catch her stream.
I was uploading everyone's Patreon audios.
Did you know?
Honestly, me is real.
I'm good to go.
She designed one for everyone.
Oh, I need to watch that VOD then.
No, no, there's not new audios on Patreon.
Sorry, I scheduled up everyone's Patreon audios.
I'm really struggling to know how to tag though.
If you didn't know.
Of men?
You worship their misery?
No, mate.
I actually prefer
holes and no poles.
Then he's swinging that way, but
I actually need nothing against a mate.
Wait, is this DLC?
Yeah, I think so.
My main quest stuff, this is side stuff.
Okay, ready to kill.
No reactive model today?
I never put it on.
I've got this though.
That's if I make a joke, I can do that.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, combat.
Hold on, hold on, get the wee knife out.
And let them attack you.
Oh, I can call them assassins.
So if I make a pun that I like,
I can literally do that.
Okay, the assassins on the horse, I'm happy.
Can you get off the horses?
Oh, that was brutal.
You can attack me then.
Whoa, I missed that.
Okay, there we go.
Please, God, do that.
It's hilarious.
Yeah, so if I come up with a really good pun,
all you're going to hear is that all day long.
Right away.
Casually kills a dozen people.
Zoom, my man.
Apologize.
Any apologizers?
Me, man, let me burp.
No, sorry, let me raid the horse.
Geez, I didn't mean to say that.
Literally what I was about to do.
Why is he running?
Why you won't?
I drink honey tea.
I have a lovely honey tea.
Just for me.
Some honey tea.
And a game
full of nostalgia.
And I'll play
and ramble all day.
So I can
enjoy
the game with you.
I'm not even, I don't know
what the tone of the song is after that come with me.
Yeah, there you go.
Wait, so what are you?
I am a cuttlefish.
I'm a siren
and a cuttlefish.
But the problem with being a siren is
I can't sing.
I can't lie on my hypnotic abilities
to steal the hearts
of men
and then perish them in the war.
I did not make
my lore, by the way.
But in terms of who's the most
evil
out of all of us in Vealor,
I'm pretty evil.
Then it goes Emi, but Emi isn't inherently evil.
She just really wants her brother back
and she does stuff to entertain herself.
Okay?
I drink some tea, so if I
start hypnotizing it's because I'm drinking tea.
I would, oh you'd perish
in my water, willing?
Follow me!
We are following
the leader
trailing behind the leader
going ahead of the leader
the leader
oops
oops I don't think I'm supposed to be at this section
because they could spot me a mile away
but hey ho
somehow things work out in the end.
It speaks volumes about Vealor
but the most evil person is not the goat goddess
but the fish.
No! Azura created you
she's your literal mother
she created humanity
as we know it.
Like
so Azura is like the kindest
Mercy's just
misdirected, okay?
She just doesn't understand
because she does genuinely
love
but sometimes that love
results in
your expiration date
which is a shame
but she doesn't mean it, okay?
She's wholesome
She's like a dark yandere
She lures your guard
and then before you know it
the finishing act
the guard will discover
and then, yeah
he found the entrance to a temple
oh we're learning about catcomes
that we can go in
oh this is the DLC called Leonardo's Diaries
I just remember that literally
right now I thought it was an auditory
something discovered by some scholar from Lechia
in fact
taste my blade
taste my
oh no we're just
for size
oh I got double ear assassins
Rick, wait I'm going to take a quick
drink of my tea, I apologize
don't like her to see views, I'll just part of her plan to lure her in
to her watery graves, oh my god
that was such a hard word to say
watery graves
terrible, here again
we are jumping into the DLCs
of
Assassin's Creed Brotherhood, we've finished the main quest
we are going to try and 100% this bad boy
I think I can do it, I have no idea
I did not look up what the tank mission is
so I'm getting scurred
DLCs
delicious
not neutral, well maybe mainly
a honey is very good for
avoiding illness
put antelab
and take back cereal
sorry that guy's talking
at the same time and it makes it hard to
talk and think
wow, AI
I'm a beautiful fish
oh we should watch that movie
that the song is like
I'm a little little fish in the
deep blue sea
somebody
help me
no help
whoa whoa whoa I've gone too far
I'm about to desync
oh no they're just walking past
walk on the
high
out my way
I'm on the floor
no help
strong evil intentions
through kind acts
Amy kind intentions through evil
basically Amy just wants her brother back
and she kind of has a bit of fun
with the spells really
that's how she was contemplated
oh the young Leonardo
the temple he discovered
where is it
Leonardo
Salahi you want to save
and tell me where the temple is
I do not know
cazzo
etcher
something is written on the floor
what does it say
I cannot read
Leonardo
but now
painting
he wants us to examine art
I remember when Leonardo
Leonardo
you're the cuff
you're the cuss
hey thanks for doing the watch alone baby
god I can be the cuss cull fish that ever did cull
hope you're doing well thanks again for doing the watch alone
appreciate you
winking at you right now
you got 3dio
you want to do some art together
you want to slay down on my twitter dance
that's terrible
that's absolutely terrible
please do not feel put on the spot
anyway I'm just meaming around
many this time I took back what was stolen
hi hi
I'm such a fiend
I'm a little ASMR fiend
right we're going to keep doing a Leonardo situation
so if you didn't get any of that put
Leonardo has been yoinked
and he discovered
some sort of advanced
advantageous
things that would
pardon me excuse me come through
I was reading chat excuse me
excuse me sir
have you heard about this
have you seen this about chat
oh my god
slay them right now yeah slay them
my deans
and then I'll do the rest of the work
okay I got you covered baby
baby
oh Catherine
Christina is coming up
alright we'll do Christina
okay so basically we
stalked her home
and then we got a kiss
so
surely this isn't going to get weird any further
reading chat obviously was a mistake to do
I know literally doing it like in a game
is so hard
let strongy lead my pleasure
I remember that
I was a bit sus
I have to admit it's you
now we
the girls can do it to you
that's fine
yeah that's fine
other way around
Christina we're in
Farenzy
oh this is so sad
oh
this is so sad
in Assassin's Creed 2
your family get hung
due to treachery
this is
really sad this
I don't like this one this is pretty
freaking sad honestly
I can't remember the past though
this is very sad
so the girls yeah yeah so we can do it to you
but you're not allowed to do it to us
come here you fanny
oh I missed
that was really embarrassing actually
imagine someone coming to punch
I did it again I'm like punching the air
this can't be one air that's going on with him
Assassin's Creed 2 is actually very beautiful
considering how old it is
I don't
want to speak
because I don't know for a fact
this might genuinely be the imported map
from Assassin's Creed 2
where the heck am I trying to go
swinging it
his family's
to be honest it was
his first day
I don't know
unquestioning me
that's a very hard word
that's a big word for strongy
right if I remember correctly
I can just do this
and there's one patrolling
guard
that will
desync you if you're not
aw he's up there I can see him
aw this is so sad this is
literally the bodies of my
frickin family
aww I desynced already
wait am I not
to kill these people
wait dad desync if I kill them
Chris
without killing any
right how did I do that
wait he
perished because he went in the water
come in the water
good boy be a good boy
you love water don't you
you love it into the water
come on
there's a good boy that wants to come in the water
yes no
jump in the water
oh wait can I knock him out
does it count if I knock you out
let me knock you out boom get in the water
yeah good boy get in the water
right in the water
you too you're next in the water
don't be throwing rocks at me that's no nice
ha ha ha ha
get pulled get pulled in the water
go good boy
in the water you go okay we did it
we did it
okay now back to the sad part
this is my big brother
and yeah
honestly it's pretty messed up
all things considered
put me down there
oh his
his body just kind of
ragdoll and
it's still leaving their deaths to fate
once again bro literally
oh no
this was your wee brother
it was actually so freaking sad
in Assassin's Creed 2
so your mother
Maria
she doesn't talk until you collect
100 feathers
because Pietro
the wee little brother
was collecting feathers and once you collect
all 100 feathers she finally speaks her first words
after the death of everyone
and it's just like
a freaking sad thing genuinely
and then this is your dad
oh it was so sad
literally so freaking sad
yeah the feather quest
that's why there's 10 feathers
in this game
I guess it's in memoria
oh
me
actually so sad
she doesn't
ah
she doesn't come with those
in
Christina's Etsy was like
true love
and then so sad
she's feeding corpses to the fishes
oh that's true
and there was no in-game map for the feathers
do you want to hear the worst part
about the feather quest in Assassin's Creed 2
so my
Xbox was in a different room
from where the computer was in my house
so I would have to
scurry to the living room
and memorise a location of a feather
and then scurry back through to
my Xbox as a child
my mum was like
what on earth are you doing
I'm getting worried about you
and I was like the feathers
mum the feathers I need the feathers
what do you need the feathers for
I was like scurry and back and forth
like
all of that
and I did it once
I've never done it again
but we'll probably try and do it when we play AC 2
these are DLC
I
allegedly like so the way I memorised
things I don't have a very good like brain
so I had to
open my eyes really wait and
oh it's the crit sale
wow
so after chaseries
date with bait
the crit sale got married off
and Chanel is on the countryside and hiding
but yeah I used to like have to
in order to memorise stuff
I had to open my eyes really
which I know seems bizarre
but it's the only way I could do it
I just had to go like oh
and then like I wouldn't blink and then I'd run
to the Xbox and like where the location was
it sounds really dumb now that I'm saying it out loud
but it was the only way I could do it
like the like phones weren't
like well I didn't have a phone
it was
because I was a child and like
yeah phones weren't like that
um
wee
this is
really dangerous because I actually don't know which way
okay okay that was lucky
eyes wide must take all information
I was literally like sorry can't speak
don't talk to me
and then I'd get another feather
and then come back through and look at the next one
and if
you like pick up feathers on the way
it actually makes it a bit harder
where is that heck am I supposed to go
there are guards everywhere
Lecretia is
is that just a straight jump I think so
okay
you don't hear a grown man
fall into here literally
oh my back
yeah
yeah you don't remember
which feathers you pick up along the way
so it makes it even harder
because if you go to the area you think
it was that
um
sorry I got nervous I'm about to go the wrong way
I can reach that
jeez
Skyrim logic
best logic
sorry is there
I think
no there can't be flags on the DLC
that's not allowed
wow that camera angle change
sheee
wee
although I will say one thing
about this DLC this is so satisfying
because um you really won't get caught
by the guards doing this
you can literally parkour your way through it
and the guards don't actually catch you
which I see is very
satisfying gameplay wise
but it's satisfying yes
um
I do like the idea of like it's
he'll be able to like completely sneak undetected
without the fear of being detectives
wee
oh my god
ugh I have terrible news
aren't you pee already um
yeah like see I love this
this is like so satisfying
like I'm just quietly
sneaking around
ooh
we're in the gardens of
whatever that goddess name is
and I've already forgotten
what the garden's called
okay this is the bit where you can
lose
I think
right you can't climb the hedge
I guess
okay
as if they don't hear me
fucking
what was that supposed to do there I have no idea
oh I just went for it
they are so dead
honestly this outfit they're gonna
kill me a nice
gentle
or should I say
a borrowed
title bestowed by my husband
ill-fitting and barely concealing
the truth
you can keep your life
I am here for the art on your walls
I'm redecorating are we
I'll redecorate that win
I'm sorry
if only it were that easy
my birth place
she is home
and you like her haze
I do not believe you
frightening is it not
you have lost so much
perhaps
we can comfort you
we are really a ladies man
where are the paintings
sold to Francesco Colonna
and one to someone who was special
to me patricio
he spends his time near ilvatica
not gonna lie reflin if you did that to me
Edmill
give it to me
guards
place the winch's
in a cart
leave it outside the walls
no
no gobbene
now close your eyes
I don't remember what's happening
there's no way
we killed her brother
and forgive me to Kessa
what for
no man can heal your pain
you must do so on your own
no we won the scene
say hello to the duke for me
guards
see all you had to do
was put your pole in the hole
and now the guards are on us
it's so it was that simple
come on
you heard that doctor at the start
there's a cure for syphilis
I don't know where to go
this is the most logical reason
because why would you put the stairs at 12 o'clock
I don't know where to go
there's a timer
there's so many guards
inside
ok
ok across the chandelier
unfortunately
don't look down
ok
sorry I cannot reach
I'm getting stressed
there's a freaking timer
ok and then we
and then run across
ok we can do it
come on I say
scared
oh sorry I didn't mean to whistle
I just whistled because I was breathing
with the small mouth
my pardon
your pardon I beg
I don't say my pardon you beg
but you don't need to ask me
oh did we do it?
I was actually really quick
1 out of 5 paintings
ok we nailed that
we nailed that
we absolutely nailed that
who's pardon now
that was
scary but we did it
only 1 minute and 57 seconds
is fair
ok
that went so well
honestly can you distract on a horse
can you distract with me
wait whoa whoa whoa camera angle
relax relax
this is terrible but can I go for a pee
already
I need to tinkle my winkle
please get up and stretch
and get a thingy I actually generally
pee
it's like so quick but I just
noticed it and now I'm like
ok I'll literally be a minute
stretch your legs and get a war
oh I have a war already
so I don't need anymore
I'll be 2 minutes ok
oh I'll just smash my cheek off if you hear that
ok
I'm so sorry
I'm so sorry to do a pee break so quick
it's a shame normally I'm more organized
I do apologize I was a bit
scarabrained this morning I like
put up
so Shibi
as much as we meme about Shibi's
concept art of her looking like a horse
she is a work horse she's already got
like 2 months of
audios like
scheduled up and I was like dealing with all
of that so I'm taking painkillers
oh
uh tummy hurt on ironically
ah
um
uh
and then I had to record
I could you know I recorded like a really quick
ASMR audio
like 2 minutes before the stream
where do we post art
on Twitter
ok I'm just taking some war
I still think I can like
100% this game um
unfortunately
oh right ok let's see what we're working with
here we've got 30
thousand hmm
it's not really enough to invest in a landmark
at the moment we'll keep doing the Leonardo
DLC I will say one thing
about the DLC
was it worth the money
like
back in the day when it came out
when did you last hear
where the heck am I supposed to go
I'm like all over the water
should be should be should be
you know also be apologizing for burping
I feel so bad
about people who like can't stand burping
it's just
like if you've been
like kind of raised that like
you know burping manners like
obviously in like in person like
if we ever do like a convention
or whatever I'm not gonna burp
in your open mouth
but like
I am just quite comfy
burping on stream
like I'd rather not like do a throat burp
because it's like uncomfortable
I don't know we're getting into the physics
why not no you're not
gonna ask me to like
like give me fizzy juice at a convention
about please strawnee please
burping my mouth
burping my mouth strawnee
lol
but please
no you guys are actually same please
but my burps
always taste like whatever I've eaten
would I have to
like eat something that you guys like on purpose
like fried chicken and chips
so like my burps are extra yummy
that's disgusting
I am so sorry
oh
yes please
burp on me
lol
up up up up up say pop say
let's go
garlic oh you want garlic
you mean to have garlic fridge
excuse me
I need how you say
checkpoint
can you burp back
mmm
no
you're not allowed to burp on me
only analyte burping
are you Irish or Scottish
pick one
I genuinely want you to pick what do you think I am
Irish or Scottish
oh it's a tailing mission
don't spoil it
don't spoil it let the gate
Irish
close but no cigar
I am Scottish
this is what Irish is
in the name of the
dear father
we are gathered here today
in the name of the father and the son and the holy spirit
we are playing it too old
oried off our inzu
and we are enjoying our game
I actually don't know if I am going to desync if I get caught by these guys
what am I supposed to do
am I getting caught
am I supposed to kill them
lol
what the heck is going on
oh
what is going on
I am so confused why aren't they attacking me
are they scared of me
I am tailing
we will be glad to add it to our collection
as agreed
I got you a fresh and cool iron bridge please
she thought I would be pleased with such a gift
after she married another man
you're alert literally every enemy
was looking at me
and nothing happened
both may be brought into harmony
doubtless
I think I thought you were going too far away
literally
I don't know if that was just like streamer buff
or something
is there a group ahead
other than that group there
I feel like they are about to stop and turn around
so I am hiding here
they are behind guards
can I climb that
oh it's a three storey building though
can I climb here
I will climb this
oh whoa
I am sorry
oh don't use the brief tops
how is that
what is going on with this mission
why isn't everyone
so unresponsive to me
genuinely like
what is the game like
being nice to me
take this
I wasn't to be detected
I was literally going to smoke bomb them
and walk past them
oops
I am not to be detected yet
everyone is refusing to detect me
what
okay
and I have already failed it
yeah so I can go on the roof top
right I am not to be
detected
okay so I will go around this part
of the street
am I going to run out of time
because I can't see them out my way
that was
smoke bombed yourself out of a whole mission
literally
I cast evasion
and I completely I roll the one
how
is this how
is this such a
rather confusing mission
I have to admit
I assume he is going to come out here
so I am not going to I just want to look at him
so I don't oh it's a bit too close for comfort
I am a lady
I like shopping
hehehe
I like getting my nails done
make up make up make up
boys boys that's terrible
I am allowed to make these jokes though
why is he coming backwards wait is he coming this way
no
no he is not coming this way jeez
jeez
you are scaring me
so don't get
detected
oh you are so talented
refling is looking cool look at that
flexibility you will never guess
what I can do with that
I cast itchy
that's a nasty one
what is that
a little
brit
what
oh a little britain ref
sorry
what little brit
I have already forgotten what I said
going to be honest truth you are going to need to
sub quote everything because I always
forget what else I see
okay okay
oh I knew you were going to turn around
that's right I got the eagle sense
no
okay he is going
oh no
okay okay okay
let me get up
this is like very close
I wonder if they are going to turn him around again
like they did earlier in that section
because I am getting nervous
I do not remember playing the DLC much
pardon me
excuse me
oh we did it
success
cast
your voice
you will complete the sale
of course
hello hello
the error lies in your spanish blood
I know it
such untruth you so casually utter based
on little more than a name
these countries these groups
make such easy targets for the lazy
and ignorant
you should tell her that the high
and mighty duquesa putana
I have changed my mind
that painting does not deserve to belong to anyone
take the painting and examine it
for clues
be careful
human hands aided by a fierce intelligence
made that
treat it with respect
go
he casted London experience
no
oh I am to destroy him
refillings
destroy that man
what he is so fast
how am I desyncing
he is literally faster than the speed
that I can run at
I am not sure why the game is telling me
careful you are desyncing
get arrow stormed
you deserve it
stinky
leave the Vatican district
working on
there was a pole there that you could have grabbed
to save the health of your ankles
I am not going to take responsibility
for you being sore
that was point blank
no excuse
I am trying to escape
this district
it puts you all the way into
a certain section of the map
by the way go all the way out of the section
shake all about
you do the hokie pokey and you run around
and that is what it is all about
hey
that is green
let's start watching
I am suing viewer
your pentas
have you drawn your pentas a little too much
the funniest thing
I got a few maros
I wouldn't say anyone was like disgruntled
I think they were surprised
so out of all the four audios
for sheebie
three of them are her in control
and one of them is her not in the controlling position
guess which one you all voted
well the majority voted for
the one where she was
and then I got a few messages
and I am like ah please
I kind of maybe need to explain it a bit better
we are working on
making graphics so you know
what content is coming up
it just takes time
we are settling into everything
obviously emi got a warning recently
in sheebie's
lower video got 18 plus
so I think we are actually debating
about deleting it to try and
ensure she gets monetization
I would be mortified for the girls
if they didn't get
like they were rejected from youtube
monetization because of me
because member the girls didn't pick their designs
and I would feel like so upset
like don't get me wrong
there's still stream elements, there's still patreon
there's still tips on stream in general
which is perfectly fine
heck am I supposed to go
but I would be mortified
for the entire month for monetization
streams all because I didn't think
I had to get a toggle to cover up
the cleavage
hmm
what do you normally need to do to get monetized
500 subscribers and 3000 watch hours
but your channel
can still be rejected
which is understandable
they need to go through the content
but I'm hoping
all things considered
if the girls are sitting doing game streams
and all of that it's just another
they're just gamers pass it on
obviously before we could launch
I could only spell out so much
don't be silly
of course
the girls aren't going to be
am I not to be detected
don't detect me I'm scared
get in here
who dares approach the veil of hey
right we're just going to go for it
cause there's no need to
assume we can just run
right those guys are bugged out
cause that guy
literally couldn't give a left boot crack
ooh I'm going to hurt my ankles
thank goodness we have the armor
cause yeah
I'm just going to run
for the objective there's no point
to stopping and fight cause it's one of those ones
where they just keep
spawning in with more guys
and it's just a waste of time
we're trying at 100% this
I say that as if we don't have to
redo all of this again probably
to get 100%
I actually don't know what
oh no 100% was don't be detected or something
that is impossible if they're going to just
constantly spam enemies
may I sit on the bench please
oh
it's him
he was rude to claudia
is he
he's the baddie
from claudia
he used to harass claudia
our sister
didjo that's a thing
we hate didjo
he insulted claudia
we are only talking are we not
I see this place has
worked its magic on your sister
she did not want to open her legs
in ference
but now she is the madame
of roma
katso
why are you just standing there
eat him
no
good luck didjo
you're going to regret this buddy
but that does not mean
they will take you back
he counters me you know what time it is later
we're going to remove his ability to have children
I cast no children
I cast no lineage
I cast no bloodline
I cast the end of your family name
take this
this is for claudia
get back here
he insulted my sister
get back here didjo
I'm not done with you
but you can get it
take this
give me those balls
your father
intended to be one of us
but we all knew you were outside
a templar
templar identified
lineage deceased
timstones erased
women forbidden to marry
it ends here for you buddy
the history books burned
and most of all
testicular torches
nice try didjo
not today
terrible
absolutely
you hired these people
you should try and get a refund buddy
he ran away
I can't see the tree you're in the way tree
sorry no
not had enough
that's right insult my family will you
yeah that's what you get
how should I know
go ask your whore of assistant
I am sure she has slept
with a couple of gardeners
oh yeah
yeah
that's what you get
I'm also feeding you to the fishes while we're at it
who's targeting me
someone's targeting me
right how do I feed you
to the fishes
to speak things up I'll just jump down here
excuse me ladies
got some business to attend
to an ever
insult my hardworking sister
she is the madame
of a brothel
and high ranking
enjoy sleeping with the fishes
hey
disgusting
you will not insult the auditories
am I not to be detected
well this is given don't be detected
wait
don't be detected just feel synchronized
the truth
do I kill them one by one
right in my mouth
come back here
come here
right there's two of them
so I don't think I can do it
right next to him
I mean there's we can almost come back
and redo this mission
you can just
can I just arrow storm them
I can
okay so there's literally one more pair
okay I didn't realize I could use arrow storm
for that no no go down please
I'm just gonna make sure
the
I think I'll just send an assassin
on this guy because I don't want to mess up
if I can get 100% right off the bat
no you won't
wait it's already filled
because I failed it earlier
okay I must have already failed because I failed it earlier
okay there we go
yeah okay it's fine it's fine
my apologies
made a little oopsie
oopsie
the pink
I didn't realize there was like one big continuum
nice my bad
I'm gonna apologize for that one
okay we'll definitely have to redo that one
later time but that's okay
we're getting close to finishing the
painting
oh wait
thanks I appreciate it
a 500
500 floor in
a bribery is actually
a lot of money
you could like buy a lot
back in then
surely
I swear I could fish Duccio out
just to punch him again
literally
in assassins creed 2 he was
really horrible to Claudia
so I'm glad they brought him back
but I didn't
expect oh that happens
every time I launch off the boat
I never
expected
what are you
hello
what
what was that
what was a jester
why was a jester attacking me
is this like a secret thing
kill
jester
well I did kill jester but
multiplayer character
possibly I don't think I've ever seen that
before
Elden Ring mentioned
he literally as
I thought he was going to be like a fight
fight but I just swung once
and he was gone
we can't really continue the game
if we kill jester
sorry traveler
we cannot progress if we kill him
don't just
don't
okay
the jester is killed you cannot progress
bye
literally
just slapped him and he spun into the war
hello my lady
hydration check
so is this before she's an assassin
or no this is after
okay
we love cloutier
girls will accompany you
bonafortuna and don't get caught
bonafortuna
do not let guards discover
any dead bodies inside the restricted area
these are
I'm starting to get worried about me 100%
in this game
I'm getting nervous
I'm getting a little shaky what have I gotten
myself into
now
now I'm confident in like playing the game
in general 100% in it
I have to admit my confidence levels are diminishing
the further into the game we get
because it's starting to get pretty
like the ones where it was like
don't take damage fine I can do that
please leave me alone
no
they're so aggressive
watch out if they pass
with their camera and their glasses
and they can't keep
a lid
da Vinci
says
what am I supposed to do over here
I hope it's not get caught
oh I've gotten sheepen
mate you guys can all attack each other
smoke bomb
that was cool
I don't want to stab him
oh I
am to talk to this pretty lady
hello lady I would like to talk to you
hi darling
you must believe she through
promise me over here
we believe that you can beat this
oh you believe in me
oh
I'm getting nervous I'm getting
shaking
I'll try my best
I mean it's not like we've like
hashtag failed or anything
in all honesty
don't let a guard see a dead body
so if I kill everyone
can I be the tip
oh I can't be the tip
I always do that I'm like
okay
don't let a guard see a dead body
right okay let's try that again
so guard no
detect
oh
I'll try it but I feel like
this is most likely a try hard replay
section
because yeah his
dead body is like literally ready to drop
unless I can drop it in the water oh no
right we're gonna put it in this
okay let's try that again
we did get caught red handed holding a
dead body okay one more time one more
time one more time for the back
getting from the baby
can't believe it after one
twelfth ever session I'm washed up
I can't be right
you
perish first
then you're next
cause you spotted me
whoa
you climb fast
please don't
oh come right
we'll come back to it children
me first
if I do not successfully do
a double air assassination
that's not gonna work
I can do
this
but did it get
the car
it did get that guy down there
okay we're safe we're safe
tiny spiny hey scrawny I'm off to
working I'll be back in a few hours hope
to catch more later good luck with the game thank you so much
enjoy your work and thank you for the tip
did you guys hear that notification
I never really heard it much
and sentence but as long as you guys can
hear
oh I've been stood up
not another chase
no more are you
squid me right now
brah the finalized
voice line that I
use was horrific
and there was one before
on that are you squid me right now and I was
so monotone like I was like
are you squiddin me right now it was
terrible absolutely
horrific
am I supposed to just grab him I'm
I'm not to kill him I'm to grab him grab grab
grab no you're wasting
time
it's you
wouldn't be real for
a bit away you bams
oh my way oh my way no
oh yeah
they wonder the target was lost I was
busy getting blocked by everyone
oh my god I'm a terrible
brotherhood player
okay I should
reclaim right let's try that again
and let's not grab random
citizens right we're locked in
right so
mm-hmm
right okay mm-hmm people are in the
way that people
are in the way but that's understandable
hashtag jump
open
come
on
am I allowed to
just send the recruits on him
there's no
and I'm gonna lose him again
I'm out of time
I'm running out of time
gotta go gotta go gotta go gotta go
I know I know I know I know
what am I supposed to do
dev team
wonder if you parkour across the water
at the start I also thought that
we'll do it
we'll do it we'll do it we'll do it
we can't do it there's nothing to
parkour off of
merda
putana
ah
okay
please work with me
etio
stop jumping on people
please
am I allowed to kill him
I know he has a yellow symbol
but etio
I'm not even chasing him across the bridge
what's the point
etio
I've never struggled with this
you guys are wondering why I can't play
rage inducing games
I just start screaming
I'm not sure anyone wants to listen to me screaming
be miserable
in case someone really does want to
I'm here with you brother
sorry
everyone's dying
he is literally coded to be faster
than me
is this where I'm supposed to stay on the bridge
you're the freaking ghost
I know I'm happy again because I got what I wanted
so annoying
literally
now don't just stand by the need to chase mission stuff
but
bruv
I have zero faith I'm gonna be about 100%
in this game
if that chase sequence
included don't be caught by a card
is it on the bridge
my apologies
are you sure you played this
completely 118
yeah that's why I can not play
rage inducing games
because it's a miserable experience
I do have one donathan reward
but like you guys are literally
gonna hear me like miserable
I'm gonna be monotone I'm gonna be mumbling
swearing cursing everything
if you didn't arrow storm
you probably would
no I got caught at that earlier like grab the letter
you need to not get caught at any stage
which is insane
it's your tackling random
citizens basically when you see a refund
me at cons just jumping on you
and just like that we sneak past
wait
hold on a minute I don't have to hurry
good evening evening
I'm here to see the page
I'm gonna run
or a dagger is suspicious
evening
hello I too
I'm a connoisseur
target located
target acquired
oh this is a
oh my apologies
my apologies sorry I was just
oh no no no no no
he's pushed me wait the people don't like
me
I have not seen an
from this angle before
the composition suffers I feel
the light of God is not properly
supposed to mark it if I literally can't
hey do we
my apologies I was just so
what was it
hello
how am I supposed to do anything
if they're both looking am I going crazy
does he not
like move at all
oh no
hello
I'm so
interested in this painting
stupid
hey boy
what am I supposed to do
look I'm just really passionate
about this one painting
they need to like get on
to do this
hold
so I can't be detected
but he pushes me off the painting
oh come on I'm having a stroke
another good time trying to figure out this
what's going on
can I distract them
I don't I don't have
access to my
I'm like not being funny
do I need to look up a tutorial or something
I assume if I do
can I put money on the ground like a weirdo
and then everyone looks at the money
oh excuse me I'm just
a rich
philanthropist oh excuse
me
no
oh pardon me
oh I'm just coughing up money
okay
what on air
excuse me a shoe
a shoe
no way that was it
I thought it was a small ball
I was like no way I go a shoe
and I can do it
okay
guards
shovels are the most OP enemy
literally they distract
like literally coughing up money
what am I supposed to do
did they play test this
use eagle vision
okay I comprehend
okay mark the paintings without the guards
I just stand here and wait for the guards to move
oh gorgeous look at the detail
wait this isn't it
wait
there's more are over here
it moves every time
oh
a shoe oh pardon me
no
I don't
I'm
I'm being branded can I
can I get a handheld moment chat help
help any help
can you I'm trying
to draw them like am I supposed to do it
where he pushes me and then
a shoe
right am I supposed to annoy him
and then like bring him over here
and then as he walks away
whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa
don't touch me don't touch the goods man
don't touch the goods
oh I'm just
are you putting me into this
wait
throw money in front of the
guards so they're body blocking
okay
okay you can try and poison them
I do have access to poison darts
hold on
cause technically that's not killing them
and I soon I get the checkpoint
I'll poison
and then I'll get the checkpoint
and then
we'll take it from there
okay okay we know where it is this time
which is fine
right
the one guarding
this one is this guy right
okay
I'm sorry
excuse me
pardon me
excuse me come through
yes poison worked
thank you refling poison worked
oh my god
oh my god checkpoint unlocked
oh wow that was so hard
that was so hard
genuinely I had no idea what to do
thank you refling for helping me
you guys were fantastic
that took me quite a hot second
to progress
enter the castle
how?
the front entrance?
any front entrances
or are we back entrances
online
no more hand holding
no you're allowed to hold my hand
because I actually
don't mind it
some streamers like really don't like it
and I'm like but I'll miss things
if I don't get help
oh
okay okay
weird goal
eh
this? this? this looks right
I have really
not done this much I do apologize
so the Leonardo missions
and the DLC stuff
yeah I not really
had my time
okay
please don't turn around
asking a lady for
unprotected hand holding
are you allowed to do that in conventions?
I've seen Japanese conventions where
I fucked that up so badly
no it's you
jeez eyes
we almost got caught
I
I've seen like the Japanese
idol stuff where you can just like straight up
talk face to face with your idol
and stuff and I think that's a really cute idea
there's an enemy up ahead
sorry
there's no weapon 100% in this stuff without using ranged weapons
this isn't say hey hey
like genuinely the same
uh
fuck off
do I need more enemies?
whoa whoa that's a big pain
sheath
there's someone in here
no no
it's not true
escape
without being detected
okay
why am I supposed to not be detected?
there's two
and a freaking guard up there
hello
oh I can be detected
I'm sorry I'm just really dumb
I don't know when I'm not to be detected
pardon me coming through
excuse me
where did he go the guy says
cause I'm still literally out here killing
where
am I just to leave the castle in general?
I have no idea
if we're looking north of the castle
I need to go south of the castle
this is brutal
I'm rubbish at the DLC honestly
yeah I'm gonna
literally 96.96
I'll take that cause
yeah there's absolutely no way
wait I'm still gonna be outside the walls
if I claim to the top of that
is it gonna take me outside the castle if I jump down?
cause I'm 99% sure you can claim the top of this
so we're just
gonna do it for the yolo
be on the lookout for a thief
me I'm the thief
oh wait no I can't be detected
silly me
jump it's okay
well don't jump then
fine let's just fight
we're gonna jump off the top of the castle
cause I think it takes us
out of bounds of the actual area
hello bye bye
that thief me
I'm only not dying on site
oh boy
here I go killing again
oh wait
hold on this isn't a jump point
I don't think
I see a flag up here
yeah I'm gonna be honest I don't really want to jump
into a balahee from this height
is that a feather or a flag?
the flag
I'm gonna be honest as
oh that's the hay bale
I'm supposed to jump into
whoa this is a big map
oh look there's the thing
and you can see the colosseum in the background too
honestly this map is humongous
do you remember that?
okay
right let's try
this again
I don't really want to be on the site of
the castle but
it's where it's taking me
so
there's really more jump points
oh it's the courtyard again
okay okay
the humongous oh it was crazy
humongous what?
what are you on about honestly
where the heck am I supposed to go to this castle
I'm so like swapped about
I know there's a ledge
okay I'll get down
get down
left or right
okay this way
jeez we got there in the end
I have not woken up clearly
I think I might need to get a call
or something like I don't feel like I'm here right now
this is the most pathetic
wait
it made me go out of bounds only to tell me the map
is right
why would anyone
stop I don't need the lore and the paintings
I need the map
can I have the map please
map map map
map I need the
oh wait it's straight ahead
oh
oh it's because of the bridge
you're really good at this game
maybe yesterday
yes but today
rough very rough gameplay
I still don't think a man can jump 100 feet
maybe I'll be fine honestly
game please I don't care about your stinky pay
I literally I do like that they genuinely
put like all that lore and I'm sure like others
appreciate it but I'm so sorry I'm very
like them
I can't be in there's only
so much knowledge I can inhale
not PewDiePie not the bridge
that's terrible
yesterday's Nike Daily
before we set which is 4pm
and that's kind of annoying
is Nike Gacha
I just know it's got pretty girls
and people like the pretty girls
use your head more than your brain
I'm literally like
use your head however we're gonna solve
this problem to open the door
yes you're right use my head
I'll ram it against the door until it breaks down
that's how I am
we are gonna hire because we are gonna try and get the
favor of everyone at some point
so we're I'm gonna take that money
at the bank because your bank interest can
actually get full
and then you're kinda wasting
that income
free money
actually the hay bale
this should be as high as the jumping point
to be safe to enter
I don't wanna use my head
okay last one
of the Leonardo mission
not the war machine mission
oh sorry I just need to click with it
I think it was like 5 for the core
did you see get busy as distraction
that's a bit on the nose don't you
look
now we need a
did you know strongy
no
I always think watch someone forgets a pitch fork
in that hay bale
as if he knows it's going good
we're finding Leonardo
he's been taken we need him back
strongy's a hammerhead caught a fish
wow
use your ego sense
ooh
discovered the location of the catcoms
oh no
wait interact
zoom
oh shit
for real for real
look for something clues
what am I looking for
hello
oh
okay
we were right scanning scanning scanning scanning
scanning scanning scanning as fast as I can
scanning scanning scanning
ooh we did it we did it okay I understand
I understand this one has been searched entirely
five minutes five minutes five minutes let's go
zoom scanning
we'll just do oop one already
oh my god I'm actually so
Scanning, oh, oh
Where's the others? Where's the others? Where's the others?
Use your eyes look alive look alive. Reflings. I need your eyeballs glued to the screen right now
Scanning scanning. Oh, was that one? No, I'm dumb. I'm dumb. I'm dumb
Do not scan do not scan. It was a mis-input
Rubber shit this honestly
Okay, okay, uh-huh, uh-huh, okay, we can start from the bottom
Okay, okay, okay, left right left right. Oh
Okay, okay, three more three more eyeballs eyeballs eyeballs get your eyeballs up. We're the head card. Where's the other one? Hello?
Why would you hate it? You did the on purpose. Oh, this is my oh, okay. What can't be that one?
Haha, what was that? What was that? Analyze? Analyze? No, you're right
Uh-huh, uh-huh up and hey, hey, I'm actually doing these one as well
Okay, okay, last one last one five minute timer last one. Where is it? Why are you hating them from me?
Oh, it's the girl with the ferret and
It's schnozer. It's Emmy with her rat
plural
Wow, wow, wow, wow so fast so fast so furious
We did it I found two drawings
Checkpoint reached give me that hundred percent
No, no, no, no, no, I have found all the images. They seem to fit together
Bring me paper and ink
We get to find Leonardo and save him
Where's nickel cage really?
Is this how museums work scanning scanning scanning show me the end
It's not over. Oh, no wait
What about the burn paintings? It's not over. It's likely they missing parts will not be needed
Care to bet on that
No
I'm gonna have to use logic. Oh, no. I suck at this. Ah, okay
Okay, possible outside right corners start with corners whenever you do a puzzle starboard corner
Miss input. Oh north north corner. We have a north corner. Let's go right north corner. So you can't be a north
Hold on. What are you? I don't know. Well, right. You're a middle piece. You're an outside piece
Put the outsides on the outside, I guess
Okay, you have to be a bottom piece I guess
Okay, you're a corner piece. Oh, there is here. I see I comprehend my apologies
Right, you definitely do not go there. Whoa. Whoa, you fit you fit you fit
That's good. That's good. That's good. How about you? No, no five-minute timer. Okay. Wait, where's the corner pieces?
Am I going crazy?
No, some of the pieces were lost in the Villa fire
What do you want me to do about that well you can't go there you definitely don't leave
Oh, but that could be a bottom corner
Could it? Oh
No, wait, how did I do that?
Okay, I comprehend why this is a five-minute like timer. Oh, you definitely don't go there actually you fit there
Okay, okay, okay, okay
No, maybe this pull plausible that I believe no, no, yes
Uh-huh. Oh, yeah, uh-huh. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah
Maybe maybe here. No. No, you have to be an inside piece. You can't be there
Uh-huh. Oh, yeah
Uh-huh
Yeah
Wait a match is gonna do in five minutes
Yes, oh
There's no way that was so good
I'm so proud of myself
I was like, huh? Where's the other corners cuz whenever you do a puzzle you're to start with the corners and the other side pieces
And then I read they're burned in a fire. Excuse me. Oh
Can't believe I did that. I'm actually so smart with a heck
I deserve all the headpats and preys and a tummy stuffed full of who goes there I don't find yourself
Wait is
Wait, what?
Where am I supposed to go? Am I supposed to go for you? No. Wow. It's actually overlaps perfectly
Hi, I'm back you we're currently rescuing Leonardo da Vinci they have kidnapped him
And we're taking him back. He belongs to us. Okay, one of us one of us
We're about to grab him I may get a cola. Oh, we're going to a layer of
Romulus I might get a cola as a reward for being so smart
Oh
There's no cutfish, but it's good to do. Yeah, they're both cephalopods. Oh, you're gonna pet the cephalopods
Okay, we're definitely in catacombs
Um
Time
It's been an hour 30 already with the heck I was about to be like oh she be is gonna be on in an hour
I thought 30 minutes have gone by
whoa
That's scary how like potent you guys are holy crap. That's scary
I
Believe she becomes online or she already online is she be online?
Or just come online in 20 20 minutes
In 20 minutes, okay a warning for
The fan concept name was love bunnies, but I don't know she
How dare you do such a thing to Leonardo
You disgust me
And I'll make it hurt
Normally I am merciful that Leonardo is a dear friend of ours
And you hurt him that is foolish. I'll make sure your death is as long as painful
Nero, thank you very much for the tip low reward for having solved the puzzle
No, don't give me money because I did I played a video game
Thank you, though, I appreciate it
The reeflings have a mascot design absolutely today I'll show you I
Didn't show it on the debut you absolutely have a mascot design
I've only made freakin
Wow
Yes, you have a mascot design you have a little love heart on your tent cause you have a nicotine patch on your head
Oh
My goodness the door I might go get that fail like right now when I go get that cooler
It may be on discourse
Oh
Kicking him or would you rather I used my knife on the contrary there is nothing I would like more than an amiable solution
Help Leonardo see reason with the Patigarian Unifier. We will remake humanity together not under my
Then the revolution will begin without you
Oh
Bring it I dare you I dare you straight green
I'll strike heart in the fears of the man. How dare you hurt my friend Leonardo?
Take this and this you're next don't grab me don't touch me the goods aren't for free in this place. Ah
Hey, it's so fun watching them fall on by one
This is what you get
We're hurting Leonardo. Don't do it again. I'll make you regret it. Yeah, you better start panicking
Oh, yeah, I
So
You'll never guess what my daytime job is
killing people
You want to beg for your life now should have thought about that first before hurting Leonardo
No, no, don't let them talk just
Me of knowledge
One must choose to search for truth
Forcing it on others accomplishes
These lost people
Warring kingdoms I
Would have ended there's I know your element is what we're going down women. You have fire
Like grass it today
Mmm, I will pay anything for your goods. Well, they're free. Um, I
Keep saying I'm gonna make an audio. I'm gonna make an audio. It's just that so busy
I'm a busy busy be come. Let us leave this come. Oh, we can get you
Not without reaching the final room of the temple you are hurt
Leonardo you have two black eyes right now. You did not look good. Come on
Go to sleep Leonardo. You need to rest
Oh
He looks so being off. I hope he's okay. Why are we getting locked in we literally just walking into our tomb, I guess
Thank goodness. I sent Massimo to look for my paintings. It delayed their progress significantly
Why is there a random treasure box? I honestly don't do it
Whoa, I really don't recall much of this
The Pythagoreans
Like a beam of light ignites fire which symbolizes knowledge
Wow, I'm gonna say something controversial this reminds me of the blades
From Skyrim quest when you enter their place
Now before you're like brain rot gamer brain rot. Yes, I know stone and leaves don't equal
Level thing, but I'm just saying my brain is tickled
That's cool
I
Yes, I know where to go
This stat you okay face stat you
Okay, okay, the camera angle is gonna help us out. That's what I like to see
Do we need a bit she goes live in 13 minutes? I repeat it not love bunnies because I'm pretty sure the name's being changed but
She be warning in 13 minutes to my
The blades you mean the organization we all kill
Her fans are called Haram wait for real for
having
Like a Haram
Thank you for cheering me on Leonardo
I'm gonna do it. Oh, I need to come up
Oh
I said here I'm not Haram my apologies. My apologies. I hear them. Okay. That's genius
Little bit to the left wait if I just go down back. Oh, no, no, I'm supposed to go here
It's pretty clever, honestly
I'm like you guys are named after Lord of the Rings. Let me be happy
Why the half
Why the refling I do not know
Maybe it is because they give me courage we must continue onward
Hmm, I suppose Salah is out having fun spending my ardent Florence
He is safe at home. I'm relieved about the Florence, of course
You do not need to lie to me
Salah if you give the blessing I am
Leonardo da Vinci and a loss for words
That is a burst
Also M for
Masked this room could use a little
Leonardo a kudibaturi
He is soupy now the sound of wind
You hear that sound of wind
Wow
Okay, I said these DLCs maybe weren't worth that. I don't know what their base price was but
Leonardo just casually talking to us while we're literally doing like the
Just jump on the face. Oh, yeah. Yeah, dude
Here rabbit aim
Whoa, that's really smart, okay
Must have been the wind
Now I can get back up here. Oh
I didn't even I was like where the heck am I this camera angle is wild
Oh, hey, so we're getting a bit dangerous out here. I'm not gonna lie. I'm gonna be nervous. I'm gonna be shamed
A
Little bit windy up here. Yes, I'm a tummy's rumbling. I forgot to eat
I
Maybe we finish
My father, uh, maybe we get cooler and I'll get my snackie wackies again, and then that will refuel me
Why
Oh, there's a bar right there, I'm very struggled with the DLC. I can't believe it. Where's where's the yellow paint?
I
What snack time snack time is the exact same as yesterday I am going to have I have one egg
Today because I forgot to boil more eggs before stream. So I have one egg left over
I will have two meat sticks and I will have pea snacks as well with a cola and water
Um, I don't think I'll make another tea. I'm not really feeling like a tea right now
I had one before I did my very quick ASMR recording session. I had one when I started to stream. So tea maybe not right now
Wow, I hope this is the right way. I've just launched myself down there without actually checking
So anyway, when was the last time you had vegetables? I actually do struggle to eat vegetables. The problem with
streaming long is
I need snacks
But on short stream days like I can make myself an actual meal. So don't worry about me
I know I had takeaway yesterday. I have my chicken burger on my chipies. I
Had
Breakfast English tea, I believe it's called. Oh, she be eight minutes
Haram, Haram hair and
She be eight minutes
Uh
But yet for long day for long streams, it's much
I am really struggling. You can tell I've hardly played the DLCs. My goodness
Oh, it blasts into the campaign, but then the DLCs makes them possible
Me clings and worrying is like people breathing honestly. Whoa. Oh, that's cool
Wait a minute, didn't this not happen with the blades as well?
That's good help. Oh, we know Skyrim came out in 2011
Yes, how enlightening very funny
Jump oh jump cross. Sorry
Confused and it's like, uh, what do you want me to do me? This is literally a wall and I'm like a jump on it
Wow
On a scale of zero to one how good of a cucumber? Um
For the foods that I like hundreds for the foods that you guys might like, uh, not so good
Hey, oh, I thought I was having to jump on the fire there. I was like this is gonna be good
Oh
These sound effects are so different from regular assassin's feet as well
I am enchanted the music is different as well for the DLCs
I'm very much enjoying them
How good am I King Ting, uh
I have an air fryer
That means everything
It's he was currently setting up the most intricate game of the floor is lava honestly
I've like really blown away right now
Like I keep saying to myself like this is such an old game like it's it's 2010 like
And all of this is in the game
It's fantastic
Fantastic fantastic
All right, you can just pre-mix this
Oh
Beijing girl, thank you for the tip go go bed. I enjoyed you. Thank you so much. See you when you wake up
Can you bake as well? Yeah
I have my unity is achieved, but the door is not opening my favorite thing to bake is apple cinnamon muffin
Because I like apple cinnamon. Oh, pardon me. Let me touch this
Let me commune with the post
Leonardo come here
Why don't keep the light source with us Leonardo? Yeah
Recognize these symbols
No
Wait, these are the symbols that were shown to me by the apple of Eden. They are in the wrong order
Bacon stream when oh
If you want
I don't remember any of this
I like smiling like an idiot
Wait
I
Is this the room
Those are not Pythagorean symbols
43 39
19 n
75 27 42
W
I miss Brian
The number is meaningless
You are leaving it's not for
It's for Desmond
I must be in the chair that I go. It's the the vault and assassins creed three locations
What are you not telling me?
Well, I have begun several dissection studies. Oh my god. It's for dance man
Oh my god, I literally have tears in my eyes. That's so cool
Salah you would model for it again, of course
Then perhaps I will study a woman with gentle and see how her body changes
Interesting
Tell me more
No fucking AC
When his body's all mangled, it's where they take him
You can sedate Desmond now. Yes. Oh my god. It all makes sense
Yes, and then you're broken in revelations
Oh
Oh my god, I get it. I understand
Ah
That's right. Oh my god, it's like all clicking like a like, uh, uh
Oh my god, that's so cool and revelations Desmond's broken. You're stuck in the animus
And they can't take you out because you're so mangled
And it's you understand that he's a vessel for Desmond to get information in present day. It's absolutely crazy
Oh, that's so cool
That's so cool
Oh spoilers. Yeah, I'm sorry. I'm just like I'm like re
Like putting it all back in my head because I've played brotherhood over and over and over
But I didn't always have access to the dlc's whenever I played them
And then it's all clicking in Assassin's Creed revelations. You're mangled in the animus
And we had to go like in present day your dad William takes like Desmond's dad William takes him to the thingy
To that location because it's a safe haven and it's where one of the gods
Uh, like the building things were and
Ah, it's just so cool. It's so cool
Oh
Desmond's stuck in the mangled in the animus
I have no idea who Desmond is but i'm happy you're happy. So we're playing xio Desmond is his and
I
Like blood lineage offspring and we use Desmond's dna in present day to look back at xio in the past
Christina oh, we just jump scared our oops
Of nothing
My father kept asking me to choose I thought I would never see you again
It's manfredo he's going to kill him what?
In tally he lost money. He's dragged them out to the end of the new bridge. Who the hell is manfredo?
No
Save christina's fiance manfredo from the freaking gamblers
I'll have a freaking minute. No. I'm just gonna let him perish so I can take christina away with me
Come on. You've got anyone to hang a bit with look. I've got 10 k florns on my person's christina. You just come with me
You want to lay let him perish to the gambas
Do not gamble
Do I kill oh I kill okay, let's do it
Sorry mate, but your time's up
Wait I have assassin signals that's not right
Oh no, I'm so sorry. What?
The woman you're about to marry. Yes, I do. Hey, I swear I do kill me here and I will die still loving her
You are never going to gamble again
Never the same
You will be a good husband to her
Oh, why is this game so sad? What the heck?
I can't handle this
All right, she's a wee bit of a slag, but it's fine
Wait, it feels really not going like I know like he never ended up with her because of revelations
But why is this game so sad? Why can't it feel have a freaking happy ending?
He tries so hard
He's fine. He'll make a good husband
I made sure oh
What
Even christina's confused
It's you you're supposed to take her away. You're supposed to whisk her away
Oh
You're crying. I've got tears in my eyes. I'm just like can it's you have one like happy ending
So I like I I'm really invested in it's your storyline
I don't get it give this man catch a freaking break. Is that the end of christina's story?
I don't see a broken heart on the map
There is no way it ends there for chris christina
That's it
That's freaking it
Oh
You can't do this to me you be soft. Come on
Oh for folks that we're gonna have to do the plane. I don't want war machines now
No happy ending for the best character literally like
There must have been more written
I'm so sorry, but I do not believe for a moment the development team ended it there for christina
Literally it's you saving him from gamble and going do you love her?
Do you love her and then that's it? I do not believe one second the writers left it there
If there isn't more it must have been cut because I refuse. I refuse. I refuse
But it's you will have a hell of a happy ending. I can't remember what happens at the end of revolutions
I really did not play it as much like I know he was sweet on a girl and then she got kidnapped
But that's not the true love christina was
Like
Ah
They saved it for the 20 bucks DLC honestly, isn't that song misery was I have no idea
I just if it remain
Never my intention to brag it was never my intention to mine. Oh, I can probably renovate this aqueduct while I'm at it
I'm like right next to it
I mean, I don't know I simply saw it it took revelation
I
Took revelation. Look to this one. He if you want the christeners, you just get somebody's I feel sinking
There's more wait. What's her DNA sink?
Uh 100
Oh, that's very low in the batter on the va
right
Oh total sink
Oh
Okay, okay. I get you come on. I get you come on right. We're gonna do Leonardo. I think that brings up her total sink
surely
No, it doesn't it didn't we were like unfortunate right hold on hold on we're steamrolling this right in memory
We only have one thing we failed. Do not drop below his
Huh
Is this this one where they jumped me out of nowhere from around the corner
Okay, okay, let's try again. Oh, we're going to shoot him for that deja vu. Okay. We need 75 percent sick
We need more. I just felt like that was such a bizarre thing to end on
I think it's when the guys jumped me
I
I can't skip this
Didn't know you could do all this in a sense people
Uh she be is alive by the way for anyone who you would like to watch her
Modes you have permission to speak
momentarily
Oh the music. Oh, okay, let's just play it all over again. Why not?
So good
Oh
Left of it since the borja came to power
He cannot see it from here
Well, I had to google why the Christina mission wouldn't show up in my game. So you're welcome. Oh, literally
First and only girl in the series. I still doesn't realize literally
Okay
So someone said I didn't take the medicine like a dum-dum dummy dum-dum-dum
Jeez. Oh wow because I'm
Okay, I know I'm replaying it. I didn't know it did it like this. I like fully armored up fully healed up
Uh, okay, I'll take it. I'll take it
Oh
Okay, let's do this the totality. Hello, mr. Doctor may I please have oh my arm
I need to find a doctor you're 100 health mate
It's just faking it. Literally. He just needs a bit. Honestly felt that I needed a bit attention
I felt that
But they have not proven effective against such things
However, I can recommend several good colleagues around the city. Do you need anything else? No, sir. Thank you very much for your help
Right checkpoint reach of north
I think it was the guards
a
The guards hit me
Remember when the guard hit me around that corner? I think this entire section is for that
I don't have climbing gloves. Okay, so I don't have what abilities I don't have at that time
Chad doctor not prescribing leeches, honestly
Right
Um
Oh, what's my opinion on satan food? Hey
It was a game. Yeah
Okay, it must have been because they hit me around the corner when I wasn't expecting that
Literally arrow storm would wait this
Yeah, it was definitely because they hit me
We'll try and finish Christina or maybe we should do Leonardo
It would be nice to finish Christina, but then we're having like backtrack all this way
Right, what weapons? Okay. I do have my fast knife. So hopefully none of them like
fly out of the corner and attacked me because that was
What happened the first time like they started attacking me way before we even got to the
Gallo
Which is where it's supposed to start. So I'll definitely hold back a bit more
to be cautious
Like I didn't dislike Assassin's Creed 3. Well
I wouldn't play it on stream though. Like I definitely wouldn't be like as excited and happy and all of that
and I
Really love how forgiving the counter controls are in brotherhood
In revelations, I think it's roughly the same
Um, but in Assassin's Creed 3 onwards
They like change the controls and I am definitely if it's not broke
Don't fix it. And if you fixed it, it has now made like gameplay
Frustrating like I really strongly dislike when gameplay gets interrupted because of like
Oopsie. Whoopsie. You forgot to dodge this attack. So now you're desynced and you have to repeat this over and over and over again
Uh, because we've changed the controls and we knew for a fact that the controls on brotherhood were received so well
Because it's like our best well received game, you know, like that stuff just makes me perish
Right, we're still gonna stay back. We're not quite at the gallows yet, but I don't want anyone reaching
To attack me and I definitely have time to react if I've kind of got this distance on them
Ah
Sorry, excuse me. Pardon me come through
All right, take your time. Actually I have smoke bombs. I'm wondering if that's probably the safest method maybe smoke bombing them
If they turn on me
Are we at the gallows yet? I'm like getting scared. I do not want to replay this
If it's literally gonna be like this strike from okay here is where they kicked off
I don't know if I should claim, you know that
Whoa, that's okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay
I have access to all my long range. I am using it
Please citizen do not walk in front of the crossbow bolt my goodness
Oh, wow, this is did I just
Citizens, please do not walk in front of the crossbow ball. Okay. There we go done 100%
Yeah
Okay, this is so much easier. I did not realize we'd have access to the older weapons for this stuff as well
This will make it easy
That guy had a death wish literally like thank you for
It's you did not kill civilians. Well because civilians certainly pop themselves off right. That's fine
Uh double
Oh, we've got one missing from this one as well
Do not be detected while reducing to a right
That's like super easy. Why have I failed these ones?
Fake game are clearly
Uh, right
Oh, I need to do the whole thing over again. Oh, it's okay
I'm surprised to see you 10 out of 10 reeflings recommend strong for this reason
Was this the game that had the terror defense? No, that was revelations
She was super excited and borrowing them to a barrel
That man is a traitor to our order your character design romance of mesmer from subnautica
Is there mpc's in subnautica? I thought it was like you versus all that
I know
You run into guards. Well, oh, that's right. That's true. That's true. Really. Really. Yes. It's true
The mesmer is a fish
I'm a fish too. I'm a photo fish
Oh, I didn't sink my my cheeky iPhone. Hold on. Let me calibrate myself right now
Okay, I calibrated so now you can like really tell what I'm looking at you
Okay, we will rock you for one
It's a scary little fish that hypnotizes you stop is actually okay
Maybe we will have to play subnautica didn't realize I was in the game
There are mpc messages, okay
that's cool
Right how much ammo? Oh, I need a restock ammo
Okay, I'm actually going to do the
Pouch upgrades so we can like hold a lot of stuff because the pouches increase
your ability to hold ammo like a lot more and
It'll definitely help out in these kind of rewind situations
Wait, you've never played subnautica?
I don't remember. I think I've seen people play it. Which is why I say like I don't remember playing it
um
I'm in
My tummy's wumbling. Okay. Okay. Okay after this one we go get food and fizzy juice
Wow that would hurt
We can play it together and stream as long as you guys hold my hands through subnautica because I have no concept for what to do
My son Claudio has been injured they are going to shoot him
Not if I shoot first get the others because I'm a I'm a quick shot
I may not have an automatic, but I'll I'll do it anyway. Oh, whoa. Whoa. What are you doing?
Yeah, yeah
Whoa, they're like destroying him
Oh
Why are you just accepting gunshots? Oh, okay. We did it. We did it quick. I'd run the guards. Can we hold hands anyway?
Yeah, I subnautica multiplayer. Imagine if you guys can come in and help me
Oh, we should have more games like that
Uh, right. Don't get caught while reducing notoriety. I'd like to see you son
Oh, my tummy's really yumbling. Whoa. That was a good switcheroo words. My stomach is really rumbling
Okay
As soon as I notice it all of a sudden it's a big problem, but I don't notice it for like hours on end
Are you sure you guys aren't the one hypnotizing me because I'm starting to feel like it is going that way
It's single player. Oh, that sucks. It would be so fun to play
There is a mod but
I don't know if I need like
Whoa, what's going on? There's like three groups here y'all shouldn't be inter clashing
The tree someone's taking the tree
Okay, okay, we're good. We're good. We're good. We're good. Yeah, we're good. Yeah, not suspicious at all. Nope. Nope
Mutual hypnotizing
I'm stuck
Okay, and then we quickly run ahead and then we don't get detected whilst reducing our notoriety
Can I just say shout out to the word notoriety? You're so satisfying to say no, all right
No
The gods are looking for your word. Good one. I see there's subnautica and subnautica below
It would look into it and see which one
Subnautica is easy when she spawn in just swim the deep part of the ocean
Okay
I've had it. Oh, I guess because I'm a colorful shed
So straight down
Right, don't be detected
Stinky stinky me got detected
Okay, there's no guards here. So I'm sick. Hello. Goodbye
Is it literally this easy
I know it is
Yeah, then go back to the thieves skill. Wow
I suck at this game
But it's okay if I suck because you swallow. Hey, oh
Literally
Oh, there's a horse waiting on me get back to level three
Ready up bill say ready up giddy up giddy giddy. What strange word giddy up
Any giddy uppers
Did you know
The hit no
Oh, look around the eyes. Don't look in the eyes. Look look in the eyes. Don't look around the eyes. Not around the eyes. You're under
That was ridiculous. That was funny
Hello, love. Oh, babe
What we didn't have hungry. I'm so hungry. I could eat. Oh, right. Okay. Okay. Okay. Know what we saw
But you have nothing to fear from markie valley. I am sure of it. I'm a switch. Hey, I have you to thank
Switch is probably
Have a best of you believe markie valley remains loyal to the order. I trust you
So what is one of the girls dm'd me on discord if someone's freaking account just blown up
Oh
One of the girls sent me my reeflings. They linked me the reeflings when I posted it in chat like a dumb dumb
Um, right. I can show you reeflings
R E E F L I N G
And then let's pick the picture
Pretty pretty reefling. We're the heck did I just save the picture?
Yeah, there you are
Okay, why isn't on screen?
Ah
Look at my pretty pretty reeflings. Look at you. You're so adorable. You're just like mommy
Look
Look at us together. We both have our little tippy bits at the side
And look at your front facing tentacles if you look really close. Look there's a little hit a little heart
But these are my reeflings
But frunk, I will tweet this out because I'm a dumb dumb and never tweeted it
But you guys are adorable
And you have a head nicotine patch on your head because we're addicted to each other. Don't worry. I've got one too hiding under my bangs
um
But yeah, this is you
You have
eight arms
You might think you have eight legs, but actually we have eight arms a cephalopods
Wait, so are we reefling or humans that you're hypnotizing so you can be a humanized version of a reefling
So if you wanted to draw a human reefling you'd technically have like a nicotine patch on your head
Um
type thing if you wanted to be humanized
But this is what you are. You're my perfect little reefing. You're quite small
I can't remember your official height and centimeters, but you're a small baby. You're a small baby
Um, your size is pretty accurate to the loading screen
um
You can fit on my head and you can um
Like fit under my armpit or in between my butt cheeks
Um and I can caress in love on you all I want and your um arms your front two arms
You can make them nice and long if you need to for whatever nefarious acts we might be doing together
But you're you are very
You can be very big if you want to be
Yeah, this is you
I will tweet it out after the stream because I can't believe I was a silly billy and forgot to show you what you looked like on debut
I knew I was missing something over here, honestly, but that's who you're so cute
And look at you getting all angry like me. Oh, this is such a cute face. You're like, mm-hmm
Mom, hey, mom, hey, it's been four days
Okay, we finished this mission and then I'm gonna get my tummy rumbling
Now that you and I are working together, I would like to know what you think
Reef flings and a manifold stay away
Perhaps it would look like an E unless I miss something
Sometimes all the guy needs to feel cute in his subtleties a little
Cephalopod that looks like him. Wait, the quest is still going. Talk to the architect. Oh wait
We'll finish this. No stop summoning the horse. We did that last time as well
Mummy give me I'm bro
Actually, do you know that really funny?
Japanese meme where that guy looks like oh
He's perishing and then the girl's like smiling and all smug
I want to do that. And then like I've got I'm bro on the side to like perk you up again
There's like so many memes. I want to make of us together
So fun. I cannot wait to do my donor thon
Like I don't obviously donor thon's really good for like
Like making money back or whatever if you want to see it like that
But like I'm like, yeah, I want to commission this artwork and then this artwork of this
And then a meme of this and then us together in this scenario and then this plot like this is amazing
And like make this audio and do this
Ah, yes, I forgot. We also have gambling. Wait, do you mean the guy in bed like drained him thin?
Like the girl looks smug and I think there's a rapper in the meme
And she looks so smug and he's like oh and death looking like he's being trained
More
Okay, it's done
Strongy she what strongy wearing one of sheebie's tops using two reflins to fill the gap. Oh true
True. Okay. That was really good to get. We're actually gonna go get more
um
Ammunition for these
Uh, so far we're actually not doing bad for the 100 run don't want to drink it but hey, oh
Uh
There are so many anime. There are so many anime edits to
She's doing peace sign
Oh, is there there's more of it? Oh, I just saved my ankle so much damage there
I am gonna go get some food
I'm gonna try and go to the bank. Wait, why the bank money for
Money for pouches so we can have more ammo. I remember got there in the end should be
I tired after
We are in the
1498 or something like that right on the cusp of
Do you have ammo in here? Or is it the other place that has ammo?
It's you that has oh wait, we know I should buy the pouches first and then go buy the ammo. Yes
That is a smart decision. Please do that. I will
Get on you. Oh, uh, one of the challenges is to grab a guard
No into the scaffold then you twat bag grab him into the scaffold and there we go. That's what we needed
Okay, there we go. Yeah, one of the mission things is to do that. Right. Okay. We need pouches my
I'm very right. What right? What do we want for medium quiver?
And then I guess just all of this
Okay, and then heavy complete a shop quest
I
Whatever whatever don't know what that meant. I don't really know what the shop quest meant, but that's okay
I don't have to know everything. I'm munition. Yeah, give me all the knives. Give me all the billets
Give me all the crossbow bolts and then we are stacked for
Uh, wait is assassin speed two that had the bug that made archer spawn in death. Yeah, that was assassin speed two
There is like a really major click about it. Good night. Rest well. Thank you for hanging. See you when you wake up
I'm kidding. I don't know how long we're going for today
Oh, we've got like tons of level names. Okay. I completely forgot we had done that
Oh
Okay
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, we need like yeah, we need like heavy hitting contracts because we're getting to the point now where
Like I'm needing you guys to like level up and take these ones with you
Yeah, I do that
Wow, it's only 22 percent rate. Whoa. Um, I don't even want to do that
Take you two together to get leveled up
My internet just died. Hello
Ah, hello. Are you guys there? Did I just disconnect?
Hi, are we checking? You hear it? Okay
My OBS literally just said disconnected
Monka is please don't do that again. That wasn't very nice OBS. You scared me when you did that
You wouldn't want to scare me OBS
Don't do that again, please
Wow
Okay, I've sent all the assassins away
She be said that you're butt superior
I show it. Um
I may or may not have showed the girls
my my butt
In the discord, I may have showed them some photos of me
Um
Like it came up in conversation. Please don't think I was just like here you guys take this
No, I came up in conversation. We're all just kind of like, oh, this is how I look
Oh, this is how I look and this is how I look and I was like, here's my butt
Um
Yeah, basically
Showed them the moon. Why am I not surprised literally like everyone's like
Oh, yeah, these girls gonna hate each other and all of that and it was like all of us like, oh my god
You're so cute. You're so adorable. Oh, this is so good. You look so good. Like your hair's this
Like, oh, we just love each other. It's so nice
Not fair they get to see it
How exactly does that come up in conversation? Honestly, it was just kind of like
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, is he gonna attack me?
He is he's an enemy
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, I can't counter his punches
Wait, someone in chat earlier said five Harley Quinn's
And I didn't understand what you meant. I think I understand what you meant
There's five hidden on the map and I have to eliminate them all
I'm happy you're all bonding. Yeah
I
Got a big butt me too. No way show me basically like
so
Yeah
At boys sleepover parties
It's like video games and all that girl slumber parties. Oh, here's a picture of my bud
So, yeah, there you go
Um, I'm gonna see if I can buy these goodness gravy. This is so far away
I'm trying my best not to take too much fall damage trying to get to this place
We don't
Uh, when guys have slumber parties they do soggy biscuit when girls have slumber parties
Oh
Where the heck am I trying to go?
Sorry, you guys are distracting me. Stop being so entertaining
Stop being so nice to me and gets me so distracted from the gameplay
I've been told that I inherited my supposed to be very nice
From my mother's side of the family. Oh, well, do you want to know?
What's funny?
My mummy has
big
bazongas
Do you want to know what cup size my bazongas are?
My mom's like freaking double g's or something
And I'm a cups. I'm like, thanks mom. So it all went to my butt instead
I
Don't know where they went literally
You know it all went to my butt instead
so
I don't know how
You got your yiddies from your father, honestly
When can we get mum on stream?
Stop she'll actually talk about it. She'll be like, I
Just never grew anything
um
Like I remember when she got me a training bra
Like so if you didn't know a training bra is like to get you used to wearing
One because it's actually really uncomfortable. Like I know I know it doesn't sound like it's uncomfortable
But like having something to strap down
moving parts
um, it's kind of cut
I
How much am I missing? Is that like less than 500 Florence roughly?
Oh
Um, and like she got me one and I was like mum. What is this for?
And she was like, oh well
I've got big gibbers. So you're gonna get big gibbers as well. And I'm like, um, okay
So like I start training and then nothing happened
Oh
No, not like a sports bra like just like a thin fabric to like get you used to it and then yeah, none hand
None hand with me
But I'm not mad like I quite like my
Uh aesthetic
Some people like have struggles with their bodies, but I am really lucky because I I prefer being
Uh, not having much up but having a lot down like I really like my body
Yeah, like small buddies don't get in the way either
Like all I hear like my mum will complain about like back pain and I'm like
The only pain I get is like
I don't get any pain because of my physique
I would say that sorry. I'm trying to like think and do things at the same time and it's not working out. Um
I would say like
My physique just means like I'm always good to go basically
Uh, right when we do another dna
Do you know bro, but do you know? Okay, there's quite a lot. Um, oh
Oh no, only two only two
Castlecrasher, no, I don't want to do you the burdens we carry
No, I don't want to do you either right. I'm gonna avoid any don't be
I can do it in this one. I know how to do that one
I
So I just went on a massive ramble about that
Milk milk and dump truck as I go. Oh mini milk is uh, yeah mini milk
Oh, no, we don't have our assassin recruits
But we should at this point
Hmm
It's going to be a bit painful
At the meeting find them on the computer wait, where are you gonna get some food? Oh, I was
Okay, we'll do it after this one. See you guys distracted me
They alert
You feed
I forgot to get up
Wait, I have one assassin recruit thing
Is that because I only had one at the tank?
Oh
Oh, no, it's because they're all away on missions right now
Okay, so if my assassins are way on missions, they're not available during recall that's
Yeah, I understand that's probably like programming would have been a nightmare
So, yeah, no, that makes sense. Okay. I won't send my recruits away too much anymore
If that is the result I can send away the lower level ones because they do not count for the assassin signal
I'm just gonna do this right now. I'm pretty sure it'll count
towards my hiring the
to lure the guards
At the end of every week each one of us I'm starting to get lightheaded oopsies should have got some food
Yeah, you put everyone else on quest literally
I need to go around and find all these gestures. I don't know what happens at the end of the gesture
Thing like they're getting money or just something happened
Wait, is that senator?
I'm wondering should I stall right now so all my recruits come back for this mission
Right. Yes, we're going to do that. That's probably the best idea right now. So I don't mess up this mission
I'm actually going to go out of range just so the event doesn't trigger
and
Please get off. There we go. We're just hiding here. Why not?
I'm going to go get some food. I'm going to get a drink as well
Oh, did you see that street performer fall over there? Oh dear
I'm going to go for pee and please do get up and hydrate and stretch your legs
Because we do not have hemorrhoids in the reefing gang
Hey, I'll be back very shortly. Literally. I just need to like put it all in a bowl and then
Uh, that's it really
I don't recall if I need to do anything else
Maybe make a hot water bottle because I'm a bit chilly
Bit chilly. Right. I'll be I'll be like couple of minutes
I would hide there
He could be in here
Hey, you'll need a beating
Oh
I think it's a good idea to do a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little
bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of of a little neutralization.
Come on and play.
You want to take a picture?
Were we not in a haybill when I left?
Am I going crazy? Did I not put myself in?
Let's see if I can just go play on his own there.
And break the fourth wall.
My god, the shuby stream is hilarious.
Hell yeah, it's how you go watch her.
I could have sworn I was in that haybill, but whatever.
You were, a guard shoved me out.
I got bullied.
Yes, all your florns.
How dare you.
A guard attacked me. How am I alive?
Did the mission just reset?
Right.
I can see that I've got three sassan signals.
So this is going to make things a heck of a lot easier.
I completely forgot I bought chocolate covered raisins.
And I have chocolate covered raisins.
And I'm sorry, I had.
No more arguing.
Your bill has come to you.
They just pushed me out, I guess.
No, the banker sent us to play.
Make an exception for her own mind.
Momentarily.
Not good enough.
Right.
Oh, am I allowed to be detected at this stage?
Do not be detected while escorting the senator.
So I'm not escorting just yet.
I know I said that wrong, so I repeated it.
It seemed like I said on purpose, but the truth is I didn't.
I like how the senator couldn't, like, perfectly see through it.
By the way, sorry, I just know it's a mean tag in the reply.
Under your schedule is Cephala Fogo.
Is that correct?
Have I spelled it wrong?
I probably spelled it wrong then.
This is what you guys need to tell me what to do.
Because I don't know what the heck I'm doing.
Friends these days.
Unfortunately, I am not one of them.
Cephala Fogo.
He fights the guards and gives away money.
Where have you been all my life?
We better get out of here.
Cephala, please.
So, honey, someone on Twitter made a VTuber food tier list
and they put you in impressive.
Oh yeah, they like my fringe tipped.
You're going to have to protect me though.
Hold on, I'm taking a sipping to Nicola.
Did you guys get up and start to leave?
I'm so sorry.
I don't know what's going on with my tum tum.
I'm having to take more painkillers,
but I'm having them with food,
so it's not going to hurt me.
I promise it's not going to hurt.
Not long.
Cephala Fogo, honestly.
I mean,
I take a little nibble out.
Oh, burp warning.
I burp a lot when I eat.
So, please brace yourself.
If you're not...
Not that you're not into burping,
but I understand that some people have been raised
that burping is very rude,
but I...
Oh, I liked her scream.
Okay, if you look away,
your assassin recruits will despawn faster.
And then they'll
start reloading quicker.
Did you see the art of food?
Art.
I've been locked out of my Twitter.
I keep getting locked out of it
to the point where it's inaccessible,
and it keeps telling me to do these
like, stupid capture thing.
And it keeps saying
um...
No?
Well, I did not
see them at all.
Um...
So, it says like,
verification complete, you're human.
And then it says,
error submitting.
I can't do anything.
I don't know what I want to do.
Um...
So, I've been locked out of my
alt one.
I've not had a chance to check out
my current one.
That is the music so loud in my ears.
Sorry, I need to turn my headset down.
I'm gonna have to get this stage.
There we go.
They're gang violence and I'm right now.
Barpeous, more wind.
Um, am I allowed to confess
I've already recorded it?
I sat in my recording booth
for 15 minutes.
I had one bottle of water
and one can of cola, and I felt ill
after recording it.
But, I already recorded it.
I'm so sorry.
If it's not your thing.
But, it's the truth.
I already recorded it.
I thought it was funny.
But, I don't really have manners.
I was raised in a barium.
I've just gone...
Oh, management
unlocked my alternative twitter.
Okay, I'll go. I'll look after stream.
And then I'll see what I've missed
because I think it's very possible
I've missed a lot of fanarts or clips.
Someone clipped me.
Plain Assassin's Creed.
Someone clipped me
when me and the horse
were beating up the captain.
I was like giggling my little
bottle off at the cliff. It was so good.
I'm gonna tweet it out
because like it was just so funny.
I really appreciate anyone that clips me
because clipping takes so much time.
How long will the audio be?
I think it's roughly 15 minutes
after editing because
I'm doing a lot of
what I call live ASMR
where I don't edit out all my mistakes
and stuff.
I know this sounds a bit funny
saying it like that.
But...
Sorry.
What was the name?
I'm sorry.
My brain's too small to think and talk and play at the same time.
Oh, yeah.
Live ASMR.
I've really been enjoying doing it.
Instead of the super hyper edited approach
if I make a bump
then I just lower the volume
so it's still acceptable for ASMR
at one point my cat
came in
my recording booth
and I was like, do you want to do ASMR with me?
And my baby boy was like
so I'm just like gonna leave it in
because it's just so precious
and I really like it.
I've really
enjoyed doing live ASMR
instead of like try hard even more.
I've done like
scripted ones as well
where I'm rambling out my butt
like so much.
If it's not scripted
my rambling ASMR is ridiculous.
Like it's not even ASMR honestly.
It's just me goofing off talking about whatever I like.
Um, whoa, whoa, whoa.
I've accidentally hired
this group
when I'm...
How is the senator under attack?
I don't even know how he's under attack.
There's no one that patrols that way.
As long as I don't get discovered
I could be
here. What happened?
We're addicted to the yapping.
Where can I hear the ASMR? It'll just be on YouTube.
I do need to edit it. I've got a few things first before
I start doing my
1000 subscriber
thank you ASMRs.
Like I've got a few collabs that I need to focus on first.
Like I really, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Why did all of that...
Did I not
perish you guys?
Can you look at those
guards maybe?
Okay, there we go.
They're gonna fight each other.
Wait, what?
Yeah, so this is true.
Taser ASMR unlocked by she-
What? Is she doing ASMR right now?
But yeah, my rambling ASMR
always end up, like non-script
always end up in a massive ramble. That's not even ASMR.
There's so many things in it
because at one point during one of them
I was like, do you want to listen to how much
ASMR tools are on the floor right now?
And like I kick my feet around the mic
and stuff so you can hear it.
It's just a scene.
Am I silly Billy, honey?
Wait, whatever.
100%
We get Taser in
the actual Taser.
She's trying to make an ASMR game.
What did you want again?
Like I did an ear cleaning thing.
Like an ear cleaning role-play.
And like the first sentence I said
was like, oh, the STD clinic's down to the left, mate.
I was like, oh, you're here for your ear cleaning.
I'm gonna start cleaning your ears.
Like I'm just...
I don't know why, I'm just like having such a good time.
She said drunk ASMR.
Oh, she's drinking, I hope she's careful.
Okay, I'm gonna eat my egg and meat
because
I don't like
when
eggs are out of the fridge.
I don't want to get sick.
So, eggy and meat stick.
Oh, she's steaming.
Oh, is she steaming?
Oh my god, did you hear the egg just bite me back?
It's just full of the money.
I can do that one easy.
Easy.
But I can 100% this one.
I just bugged it.
Bugged it.
It's so good.
It's so easy to make as well.
It's literally boiled egg.
I look forward to this drunk ASMR.
Shibi's doing it right now.
YouTube moderators, you have permission to link.
Please consider supporting Shibi Cottonbomb.
She's doing live drunk ASMR.
Shibi, how's it going?
We're trying to finish Christina's frickin' story line.
There we go.
Bancum on the way home.
I'm a bit worried.
I don't have a napkin again
and I've just touched egg.
I'll just wipe it on my hoodie.
Sorry, I'm gross but it's true.
Look at Emmy's alt.
Bancum.
Can I see it?
See it?
I think I'm following it on the memes.
Where is it?
Is it hidden?
And you can't see it
unless you search up for it?
Where the heck are you?
Oh, there it is.
I got it. What did she post?
Oh, her tummy hurt.
Is that what you mean?
Do you have a favorite streamer snack?
No.
Let's eat anything.
Oh, why did I feel like I've heard it before, Strony?
I'm Strony Cuddles now
and I'd like to remain Strony Cuddles.
Thank you very much.
Underneath the tummy hurt message.
Me when I can't kiss you 600 times a day.
The retweet or her tweet?
Tight.
You up and whispering in your ear
that if you can make it to 30 seconds
without I'll reward you.
As fast as you can.
I'm watching you struggle not to.
But in the end, you'll still fail.
Please give me a kiss with what?
Oh, I never read the full thing.
I just read that her tummy hurt.
Oh, my God.
Emmy.
That's outrageous.
That's so good.
Emmy.
That's funny as in.
You'll never guess what.
H.E. Girlfriend in my DMs.
I was right.
There's my clubs happening by hook or by crook.
I'm so bad with Twitter.
I'm supposed to tweet like when I'm going live and stuff.
But I just can't even ball it.
I just can't even ball it with Twitter.
It's for looking at pictures and then doing your thing
and then going off again, you know what I'm saying?
I only got to the tummy part.
No, I didn't read ahead.
I just saw that she had a sore tum tum.
Maybe like,
all the girls run their own social media.
I told them do what you want.
Because like, I'm so bad.
I know you're supposed to tweet like oh, I'm going live.
I'm doing this in an hour.
And I'm like, I feel like those who want to be here
already know the drill.
But I do get that reminders are helpful.
And say I'm going to use it for like, oh,
my YouTube video for 1000 subscribers
is here. Take thing.
I don't miss the strong 10.
That's so good.
Self gatekeeping.
Are we going to react to the Xbox showcase stuff?
What's my stream on Sunday?
I don't know.
I can't, I think
my stream on Sunday is
the sweets.
Hmm.
Johnny is cute.
Cute. You're cute.
Reflink cute.
Okay.
I shouldn't munch too much, but I'm so hungry.
Born sweet.
Okay.
Hmm.
I kind of plan to do like one endurance
game stream a week.
So next week is Skyrim for endurance.
Then we have Elden Ring
for two weeks in a row
after that.
So I'm playing the DLC
with you guys first.
And then I'm playing multiplayer
with sin sister.
Um.
And we also have shot callers
and heart rate winners and all that jazz.
Um.
Thankfully sin sister is an
endurance streamer. So like if you ever
get annoyed like, uh
I hate it like when
streamers like don't finish a game.
I don't like it either.
Which is why I would love to get
endurance streamers for Borderlands 2.
I would love to do a VTuber
playthrough like you know the VTubers.
The problem is
if people aren't endurance streamers
that's like
so long.
Whereas if you can find endurance
it takes maybe three streams max.
If you want to just blast through the campaign
maybe even two honestly.
Uh-huh.
Bye.
What?
I'm sucking my fingers.
I don't know why my tongue's coming out.
Oh it thinks my fingers are my tongue.
Uh-huh.
That's so cool.
I love this.
I don't know if I've ever been
Borderlands 2 is like a hoot in a hole or
it's like a fun game honestly.
Oh maybe I should look at Marshmallow
while I do this.
Yes I will look at Marshmallow.
That's so silly.
Oh my goodness.
I have a hundred more questions
than I did yesterday.
Oops.
Any chance there will be a full body
pillow for sale in the future?
Yes!
Uh-huh market
are like absolutely amazing to work with
or like whenever a girl has a birthday
please tell us and we're happy
to do like a new thing for you.
Um so the more support
like they get on UwU market right now
the more favour we have
to like produce something new.
So for the girls' birthdays I would love
to do um
at least booba mouth
mouth mat
and
also possibly their mascots
in a plushie.
I don't know if the designs for the mascots
might be a bit advanced
um or they would come out
quite expensive that's the only
um issue.
Hi!
Good to hear you. Yeah it's good to be heard
isn't it? Um
100% open to any merch.
We are going to establish ourselves first
and then I'm going to reach out
to a very unique merch and dice
line because I have no idea
how to bridge a connection between that
for sure. You know you can only
do but ask. If you do not ask
you do not receive so I will ask
I will see if it's possible. If it's not possible
then we tried.
Um
would it be um
I'm not going to let you know what those type
of mousepad designs would be for the others.
I know what mine is
my big badonkadonk.
I take a bite of my muffin
and
mmm
I'm just, hi strongy I really like the
Assassin's Creed streams. I wanted to give
you uh feedback that I've tipped in
the stream elements page around five times now
between the two streams
but it never came up!
Oh no!
Wait wait wait wait
why would it not come up?
Why would you get filtered?
I don't
It was broken before
it's fixed now but why
would it not show up?
I have bejinga narrow tiny
spiny and bejinga again
for today. It broke yesterday
please tell me
if your money didn't go through
or did go through.
The paper was broken because
you guys gave us so much money you broke the
cricket paper but it's unbroken
that's what's fun.
It is a legal requirement
of all reeflings to love strongy stuff.
I also was
thinking
I need to find an artist to do this
one that's good with all body types
I would love
for our six month anniversary
to have a mouse pad
of all of us together like one of
those big flat mouse pads
I would adore to have us
all together. I absolutely adore it
but I would need to get
a really good artist for that
I would not want to waste money
dicking around with an artist
I would want an artist to
smoke it
I would adore it
Since there's a notification discord server
would it be possible for you to
upload the unarchived stuff
to the discord like a thread
unarchived stuff?
Do you mean like karaoke stream or the ASMR stream
that went kapoot?
I think because
we shouldn't
really host it because I got taken off
so I don't want to be the ones
responsible
does that make sense?
Like archive annons shout out to archive annons
for saving everyone's butts
For me
I am open to suggestion if you don't like the suggestion
please you're more than welcome to give me your opinion
again on Marshmallow but archive annons
if they broke don't fix it
they've been doing fantastic
they've been catching
what's been put out there and
hmm
Are alternative streams
going to be free to access? Yes I do
not personally
believe in paying more than
like 10 us dollars
to like fully support your oshi
and get everything that they put out there
and the girls have shown an interest
in playing alternative games
and doing some other stuff
but I
would not
like them to charge for it
I'm going to say to them like let's not charge
but obviously I will never hold you back
from giving any tips to the girls
you can always tip as a thank you
to content that you enjoy
but that's with me
like someone said
hmm
do I plan on raising
the prices of what's been established
no I don't
I think
I think 10 us dollars per month for all the
content that the girls put out is fair
and I think it's
good value for money
and I think it also
shows that
like
the end goal isn't great and again
like 820 split comes into it type thing
and it goes up in their favour next year
type stuff if they want to hang about
like
I think if it's more than 10 us dollars
you're
not taking the piss
but
I very much push for
value for money and
I hope
I know region
doesn't always
change the price of membership
regionally
which is obviously a big thing that's hard
to overcome
because we don't set the price
but if the website doesn't do
an alternative payment style
then
you're getting shafted in other countries
there is a
streamer that talked about selling games
and it was like oh
Brazil because they lowered the price
in Brazil like it was fine
and all that jazz
I'm sorry I'm rambling I'm not making any sense
um
by the way
cuddles I sometimes make a lot of clips
as you probably remember from back
then
are you goober?
we may be goober
I'm happy for you to use my clips
with whatever
you want whenever but I would
prepare to keep the clips of you as
gay cats as possible
and I only share those with the reeflings really
and I post a group
clips of the other girls
I'm happy for the clips of the
other girls in the group clap to be used
to monetize the shoot oh that's so nice of you
whatever you want not like it really matters what my opinion is
yes it does you mean
you goober
and I would like to keep comfy streams
as long as possible while you go naturally
and share well I've got good
news for you
the nature of my
content gate creeps me automatically
do you want to hear why a little reefling
my goal of a ASMR
video every time
I get like 1000 subscribers
the reason why that naturally
gate keeps me is because
someone will come into the live stream
after consuming that content and they'll go
when ASMR, when ASMR stream
and then when they see me rambling
my head off about a 14 year old game
having the time of my life
they're gonna get bored aren't they
they're only here for ASMR
5 head
I'm playing chess
and for D
already
I already did it myself
they're weak they can't
handle the scrawny they want the
they want the stealthy ASMR whisper in ear
they can't handle the rambling
they can't handle the accent they cannot handle the
errrr
so by default I naturally
gate keep myself you're welcome
love you reeflings, always had you in mind
Only the strongest roofling can survive on this level.
First time doing this, listen to your audio through- oh wait I don't think I can read this
one out loud.
It's a video link!
Oh am I watching that after this game?
Hey I did a Scottish game show.
Show them the name of places in Scotland and ask how to pronounce it.
That's such a good segment, love that idea.
I'm stealing it now, my idea now.
They tune into a stream expecting like a soft whisper with an accent.
I just sound like a bagpipe.
I can't handle the Scottish ramble.
Also check to see if you're still subscribed to the other girls, some have been called.
Oh I saw that I was like really YouTube you're calling us after like literally a 12 hour
stream.
Go and calm down.
It really should start to calm down now that we're streaming.
There is no way you're telling me like it's gonna keep continuing because this is getting
outrageous now.
Like I'm not laughing, no one's hee-hawing.
Strony it's not fair, you give the burp-huffer so much good stuff but what about the burp-huffer?
Oh stop it!
Is it terrible I have a Donothon reward where I took out my boot?
There's a really funny ASMR outtake and I laugh and then it comes out more with my laugh
okay?
So I'm thinking about you, don't mean I'm necessarily- and I swear if anyone starts
complaining like oh my god it's literally just a 10 second audio clip of me laughing
and releasing air.
Like do you think I don't have a digestive tract?
Do you think that I'm- oh I'm such a gamer girl.
Ehehehe.
No I'm Scottish for one.
I take big Steven jobbies, no such thing as an idol meeting and my piss is neon.
Alright let's- no let's get it right, let's get it right, right off the bat I'm no having
none of this.
Eww you?
No.
I'm Strony, I'm Scottish and I was raised in a barn when they manners.
If a little 10 second audio clip of me laughing while I tout filters you, my guy.
Enjoy the oo-woo because that's what you're looking for, no me.
You're not looking for me.
And that's okay, if you're not looking for me I've got 3.3, I've got 5 adorable doors
waiting on you alright.
Hi.
Ahem.
Mmmmm.
Sup.
Oh I'm gonna choke.
Sup lass, I feel they need to say something after that Brotherhood part 1 stream.
What are you talking about?
Why?
You don't think you could be considered- or oh she why?
Because there are creators out there who are more experienced, who you think are better
so clearly would prepare them?
Have you not followed- have we not followed and supported you for a while heck?
I've been listening, laughing, relaxing, sagging and straight, jorkin' his pentus.
For many a time now.
Why do you think that is?
Could it mean we adored this silly Scottish gremlin who's not afraid to be herself and
treat her with love and respect?
No lass, kick that impostor's syndrome to the curb, we love you.
Oh you're her or she, case closed, doofus, oh thank you Evelyn, I love you Evelyn, oh.
Is that a bag of chips?
No, it's a bowl, like the pea snacks are really hard, I can like dink them on the bowls without
them cracking.
Crack.
Oh there was a marshmallow you wanted to talk about on the other stream but I forgot.
Oh my god right, hopefully I don't forget this time.
There's a really brave wreathling who messaged me, well he's not a wreathling but he's asked
for help's wreathlings okay.
I'm gonna paraphrase it because I can't quite remember exactly what it said okay but basically
this person is struggling to brush their teeth and I think it would be very nice if we brush
our teeth together after stream, like when stream's ending we'll brush our teeth together.
I know that sounds silly however it takes 21 days to form a habit and I think it would
be nice wreathlings if we could encourage and help people that might struggle with that.
So if you would like to brush your teeth with me at the end of stream I will give a roughly
30 minute warning so you don't have any sugary drinks or any food before because that's bad
for your enamel to brush and I think it can be a really nice thing wreathlings can do for
someone.
Even if together we help one person hopefully if we consistently do it for 21 days we have
helped that person who was very brave by the way that was a very brave message to come
out with.
I won't say too much about it but you know you were very straight forward and said that
you don't you know consider yourself a wreathling and that's okay and you know we can't promise
that we can help everyone but we would love to maybe show you a way that we can do something
nice together and it's a lot easier when you do something together with someone.
So yes thank you for being very brave and reaching out I would like to brush my teeth
with you when I end stream I don't know if you're out there or not but we can definitely
do that together yes I see no problem yes unfortunately I don't have the consistent time where we can
not brush your teeth it would just have to be roughly 30 minutes before my stream ends
sorry I'm pushing in my chair you're pushing my chair.
Hi strongy congrats on debut I was wondering um nope you're done any games coming out that
you're excited for multiplayer the binding of Isaac apparently someone went data mining
and saw that there was a new repentance after plus or something so there might be patches
to current items which would be very interesting forming new habits with my oh she sounds like
a tuition name honestly join oral improvement she's getting closer to I am the urge to crack
a british joke oh my teeth are mangled honestly my teeth are mangled I'm like they're healthy
but they're just all squint and it's like I like the look of oh my god there's apparently
a pandemic happening in America with veneers veneers are like these fake things you put
on top of your teeth that are shaved down and it makes them look perfect but I feel
like teeth have personality like I like my wee squinty-winty teeth um I just I've never
seen myself any other way so it's me oh yeah I do understand for people that do need braces
like there's probably something else going on but I like I was obsessed and I never got
braces um and yeah I just have naturally squint teeth like they didn't come out perfect and
that's fine that's just how it is um mommy I really need a hug debut has made me really
emotional oh a little reflame trust me I know this isn't about me but I'm talking to you
now you should be so proud of what you've accomplished I am the girls have done fantastic
and I'm having a good time with my weathlands you and the girls but I feel much more lonely
than I did before oh watching everyone interact with each other the girls respond into mario's
ma rose and such I don't even know why I suppose I'm just envious of the attention that everyone's
getting I feel so out of place I'm so sad I haven't even been able to listen to your
audios to sleep I'm sorry for being selfish I feel selfish at all are you are you maybe
one of the lurkers that are shy to say anything or have I managed to successfully accidentally
dodge all your messages and stream and I would be a bit upset too if you were talking away
and I accidentally never read out any of your messages so I do apologize if that happens
and well I'm sorry real little reflame I never want to make you feel lonely if you are a lurker
and you're a bit scared to talk that's okay whatever your comfort level is you're allowed
to be that you can always say you can always be at arm's length or you can always be attached
up my head you can sit on my head if you like and and it's okay but just I don't know hopefully
it doesn't make you feel lonely like we vibe and I get to show you my childhood game you
guys get to show me you get to suggest to me your childhood game I want to something strong
yeah lurkers are beloved yes I understand for lurkers sometimes it can be a bit nerve
racking as well to like be perceived with my eyeballs and like I I read out what you see
and stuff but um literally uh if you would like evidence from my autistic diagnosis please refer
to my first stream which was 12 hours long and the only reason I went off instead of 14 hours
of full gameplay is because of bod okay I'm usually playing something and lurking yeah like
it's perfectly okay to lurk and just do your thing not wrong with lurking absolutely not
um don't be shy reflame strongy isn't always reading my comments but yeah it's um a guberrino
so I do apologize I've ever made you feel left out um and hopefully it doesn't happen in the future
I can only apologize
uh sometimes hi strongy want you to know what I think it's very cute when you narrowed out about
sassus gree brother it well I'm getting rolled in the dlcs clearly I'm not built for the dlc
I have a little sip of cola a fizzy juice I lurk when I'm at work mm yeah a lot of people like
lurking and listening to strongy podcast wait if you don't see the screen when I'm streaming and
like I'm beating up bad guys and oh you hear us huh oh take this oh like are you like oh what's
going on or can you use context clues I like to have the stream one in the background but I do
like to interact I'm like yeah don't feel don't ever feel forced to interact I know some people shy
like that hi goddess just wondering if you could forward something to management I know
viola or not on holodex but you can still view the stream of the URL
but I think the girls have something set that prevents their streams from being viewed through
third-party sites well mine is fame I can't be right it's true screen off pretend and strongy
physically throwing the refill and then around for sport
to be honest you talk enough that there isn't dead air so I don't have to wonder about what's
going on yeah I can't believe it wait was there really no dead air in the last stream I must
have been quiet at some sections there's no way I had the video playing I just can't fully watch
the whole stream yes the streams are a bit too long for the average adult uh okay management's
gonna look into holodex I think that puts all their streams together we were thinking about
hosting a website that showed all our stream schedules but it cost like more money and it
was just kind of one of those things where look holodex does it for free we're just gonna let
holodex take over who goes there I died for yourself there is almost no dead air outside of breaks
I may wonder my throat is sore honestly after uh after I've been done with you
I've watched for about five hours and wasn't any dead air you talked the entire time I do I'm
very passionate about this game very very passionate uh sorry if I missed it but what are we
yes your reeflings I was very dumb and never showed you what you look like that's you
I've lost some gnar twerk of nature of us together and what's the old twitter check out
who I follow on stronycuddles on twitter I don't use twitter much you're much better given a
like and a subscribe to this youtube channel I am not much of a twitter person okay in a gush I
use twitter now pretty much to reach out to other vtubers and be like hey want to make a samar
hey sweetcakes want to make a samar basically that's what I do I think your longest dead air
was the sprint section where you were against the clock and you're still monologued more like
monomogged because I'm just that good at being a yap or ooo hey strony loving the assassin's
greed I was wondering if you have ever seen or played lost planet one or two I haven't there
are fun games that I think you may like even if you don't play them I still appreciate you for
beating this message I have not I've never heard of them or I can't remember them being on the cover
of an xbox 360 so probably not have I ever played dragon age I played the demo of dragon age
one I think uh where it's like brother and sister at the star and then one of them perishes if I
remember correctly yeah that's how much dragon age I've done I don't know what it's like um
but yeah yes one take flamboyant cuttlefishes are highly poisonous okay well I'm a flamboyant
because I'm a watermelon candy here someone described as watermelon candy and I'm like
honestly true true uh will there be streams on other platforms okay
congratulations on your debut I'm looking forward to supporting all the talents I must
apologize I said that's so wrong I must apologize but I find myself confused what you meant by
vealers collab restrictions and I'm looking forward to clarification you describe the
collab restrictions as the unwritten rule through other information do you mean for me
my collab restrictions are um I'm like if I don't know that someone is like me mentally
then I can't stream with them because I'm dumb I can stream with the girls though that's fine
and the girls can stream with whoever they like other than males they're not allowed to stream with
males or interact with males or follow males literally that's the only rule and so far so good
literally none of the girls have broken that rule strongy slaps of each of us behind I can make you
a star yeah um it seems odd for me for them to be rules I've never heard of any other agency that
has an outright rule against them against who sorry I'm not read this properly uh especially
value in freedom doesn't that apologize if it comes off with really critical however I think
clarification word on the issue oh and they can freaking go wherever they want
oh this is asking about male collabs the person has said wrestle tube collabs were like mixed
would the girls be able to do that I mean I would never stop them from an opportunity
like would they be on the same team as a guy like I don't think I don't think that's like
advised if it was like that like I wouldn't advise it however none of the girls have given me an
indication to ever even do that like I think we would be like sorry but uh we can't uh we are
following Japanese idol culture and uh no male sorry sorry we sexist out here
which is terrible don't say that I learned don't say that part I learned keep burping don't apologize
hello again friend of a friend I knew you well
no true it's just a rule that you can bet sitting my love on
I don't remember the words pick it up every time
hi strongy I think you've been one guy what does that mean saying names is okay as long as it's not
too much oh no so the way I I've been taught V tripper culture I'm so sorry but I've been taught
by the majority V tripper culture I'm not allowed to say your name unless you don't know
or membership however because and the reason why I can't do it when it's like just saying hi section
or in general is because like people think favoritism is forming or jealousy and I really
don't want anyone feeling put out um wait that's exactly what you've just said to me
we have just agreed okay we've just agreed yes we have agreed um at the start of the ASMR stream
I am going to try and say people's names just as a special thank you for showing up how do you feel
that you're no longer a v-tweeter well hopefully my first stream length really showed how much I
enjoy v-jobbing sup cuddles was thinking of a tag uh I've missed the tags I kind of finished them
oopsie uh please do give us a guide for those script writing yes um I'm currently getting a
new manager on board that deals with all the scripts and thank god he is a male because he
can actually write scripts that guys want to hear because I can only guess what you want to hear
and so much. So like roughly the first three months of scripts are me, and then it goes
to other script writers, and then it goes to the script manager, but we're a testing
script manager. But if all goes well, my responsibility is less than so much, and I can stream so
much more! Well at the start of the stream you were at 3.5k, now you're at 3.3. Heck
yeah, that means I don't have to edit the 4k thousand any time soon. That's fine. Hey,
I have to say that I think you are amazing. I don't get to interact with many Scottish
people online. That's because a lot of things had to go wrong in my Scottish life to become
a VTuber. That's why there's no Scottish VTubers. Do you know how? Oh no, I've hurt
myself. My finger is bleeding. Why? What did I cut myself on? I've not touched anything
sharp. Is there anything sharp in this room? Ouch. It stings. Hopefully I can still keep
gaming. Scotland only has one computer. No like genuinely, there's a reason why there's
not a lot of Scottish VTubers. If you genuinely like grew up around, well like grew up around
like normal friends, you would genuinely be like bullied so hard. Like bully culture like
in America and Australia and the UK is so prevalent. Like if you show any enjoyment or being slightly
different from the status quo, you get sicked on like a hound like sickum. It was crazy.
Pour some Azura milk on it honestly. I don't know, I can't remember how I cut myself. My
finger. I'm okay though. Someone says, hi Strony, I missed all of your livestreams,
rip. But I do have a few questions. What happens if one of the girls wants to leave? They leave?
Question mark? They get to go? We don't have a non-compete. I don't believe in them. I don't
think they're nice. They are not kind. If you no longer work for the Vealer agency, why
do you prevent you from making money elsewhere? That is called being messed up. Will you retire
the character? Yeah. Also if you can, what are the plans for Gen 2? Will you bring in
6 new girls and retire the other? If Gen 2 is the thing, there will be 6 new girls on
board. When Vealer agencies come out with Generations, everyone can be active at the
same time. It's not a problem. So Generation 1, all 6 active. Generation 2, all 6 active.
So that would be 12 total. Then if Generation 3 and everyone's happy with their cuts and
things are all nice and swimmingly, then Generation 3 and there will be a total of 18
Succubi and V Succubi. Wow. That's very daunting to think of but thank God I'm not the script
master anymore because if I was the script master, I could not stream. I genuinely could
not stream. There are absolutely no interest for any Generations after 3. No spin-off Generations.
No secret plans. No save for work Generations. None of that. I am exhausted. I took insane
amounts of HP damage getting Gen 1 out. I am ill. I want to get myself better and I'm
going to stream and I'm going to enjoy every second of it. But yeah, we are not having
to retire Gen 1 to get Gen 2 out. No. Sorry. Lastly, and this may be Taboo to ask. I'll
read it in my head. That is controversial. It's not controversial. What's an item you
would copy and steal from the other girls? Succubi's not. I will be taking no further
questions. Why is everything in Japanese? Are you weeb? Nothing's in Japanese. Actually
this is a fully English stream. There's nothing in Japanese at all here. What's going on?
How am I supposed to support the girls when you keep pulling me in? I'm pulling you into
my gravitational pull. Can't escape this gravitational pull. The website? Oh why Marshmallows
You'll never guess what country Marshmallow was made in. It was made in Japan. It's all
Japanese so Google. I use Firefox which does have a translator thing. Someone says please
William Wallis all over me. Oh yeah you like that. I don't know if this made it through
into twice. It's a PNG. Do we open it? Are we going to open it live on stream? Oh it's
me with my autism hair. I thought it was going to be something else. I had my autism hair.
I thought it was going to be something else. But I saw it was a PNG and I was like I'll
go for it. Okay I just quickly refreshed. We've got a few more and then we'll jump back
into their pay. Someone says check Smuttlefish hashtag. Hashtag is on safe mode. Show me the
goods. Smuttle did I spell it right? It's been hating? It's hidden for me? Check your search.
Hate sensitive media. Absolutely not. Show me the goods. There's two goods inside. Oh my god I have
faith. And my hair is so big and I'm sitting in a clam. And there's a second one. Oh my god there's
two. In the second one I say come closer to me. Have I got hypno eyes? Oh I've got hypno
eyes in the second one. Oh that's so good. They're so good. I love it. Thank you. I cannot
react to it because I'm on my minicum. But they're so good. There's three R's. I can't
see the third one. I only see two. Some accounts seem to be muted for me for some reason. I
can't see the third one. Only see two. I don't see it. It's not displaying. I don't know what's up
with Twitter. It's like really having a hard time. I see it. I have a tail. It looks like
three. Girls and viewers have a tail. No I have a tail. I have a leash. I have a leash. Oh
my god. Oh my god. Thank you. I love it. I have a leash. Oh it's so good. And the tail goes
green at the tip as well. Just like my horror. I'm going to stare at it for a very suspiciously
small amount of time later today. That's terrible. What are you doing to me? I should be the one
saying this to you. I accidentally... Thank you very much for that fanart. I like all fanart
actually. I need to put it in my folder. I have a folder of all the fanarts in so far.
Someone says, I loved your audios in the part where you talked about... Yeah you let me talk
about her baguette and go squishy with it. It's the nicotine patch under the bangs for
real. I don't actually have it. However I quite like the idea that we both have the nicotine
patch because we're both addicted to each other as we are each other. Yes, yes, yes. It doesn't
show up on my... Yeah it never showed up on my face. Hi strongy. I just want to say that's
really great how much you care about the progression of the other girls and your inspirational
speech in your first AC Brotherhood. You're a really cute person. I hope you have all great
and long careers. Also now I have a thing for the Scottish accent. Oh I do you like this big man?
Oh I am pure coming over to you like a satyabas coming to your house. You'll be sleeping in
your bed and then you'll feel my hundle over you. That's right and before you know it you've
popped abowny and it's all that funny. Is that what you want? Is that what you want?
Because you got it with me baby. Is Daystream another endurance stream? I have no idea. I'm
a bit nervous. I don't know if we can do 100% Assassin's Creed so we're just having fun.
Strongy is just an industry plant from the Scottish tourism board. Don't fall for it.
Don't fall for my tricks. You shouldn't come to Glasgow and spend all your hard earned money.
There's totally no amazing lovely tourist cafes in Glasgow.
Watching Austin Powers is going to hit different. I've never seen it. I'm so excited to watch
Austin Powers you guys. I think that's all the lovely Maru's I have. I is 411 Maru's.
Okay who's ready to replay this memory? Weirdly I haven't had an urge to visit Glasgow.
Scotland has turned to hypnotism. Wait did we not finish that memory? Oh we didn't. I thought
we did. I went away and got food. Nori nori.
Okay are you trying to get achievements? I'm going to see where it takes us. I don't know
if I can do 100%. My confidence as we played some of the DLCs has gone down significantly
because I don't know what the solution is to a few hundred percent. So if this game tells
me I have a new outfit unlocked one more time I'm going to cry. It's done it so much. How
does my browser all come to die directly to stories? Oh that's terrible. I need to start
retweeting stuff. Like I want to rule play with the R. I'm sorry I said it I don't care.
People find it cringe. Yeah you know what's cringe? Your VTuber never had any good time
with you. That's cringe. That's different. Hypnotic Scottish assessment.
Forbacione is such a specific word. Oh we are like that.
So we don't actually want to kill this archer because if we do his body is going to drop
down. See how it only got out. I'm going to pray the body doesn't fall right in front
of me. Don't do it ragdoll physics. I'm going to be mad. I might actually have to try hard
during this segment. I'm not to touch the ground and I'm not to get detected. I do have
issues. Are you trying to give me a heart attack because it's actually working me. You're
getting me concerned. I'm getting a bit concerned about how much you're launching. You're launching
yourself. He's at a rooftop. I have no idea if you guys can understand me when I start
doing that on purpose. Like being super scots on purpose. Or does it just sound like it's
just kind of like pleasant noises for you. I think we're just going to do that. Yeah
As long as his body doesn't go sliding down off I'm fine with everything that goes on.
I understand it. No it's pleasant. Oh my god you guys are so scots. If you can you're
actually getting pretty scots. Is it? Wait is that your literal translation of scots
there? Stop. What does that say? I'm like trying to reach out and play the game at the same time.
I'm actually such a skilled streamer. Sorry I played this game so much I couldn't do it.
There are some bits and pieces here and there but it's mostly understandable. Ah, tu comprendes?
Fuck it let's just go French. I'm surprisingly soothing. I'm definitely going to do a hard
Scottish accent ASMR. I don't know what I should do with it like tingle wise. Or maybe it should
just be like go to sleep mate. I'll get these. These are really coolant on your face and they
go bloop bloop bloop bloop. And it'll be really nice. It'll put you to sleep real quick. Oh
you still don't want to sleep right? Let me get the ear cleaner and snake. I think you
call it a Q-tip but it's actually called ear cleaner. That's the kind of ASMR I want to do.
Yes please. I'll just call it super scots ASMR and then people are like don't be silly.
There's no such thing as super scots ASMR and then they click the listen and they're like
they click to listen and they're like I understand now. I get it. Oh please don't ragdoll physics.
Do no drop. They cannot get past those cortisans huh? I feel like there's definitely more on the
map. I think that person yesterday was actually correct and said the more favour you gain with
the factions the more they appear on the map because all of a sudden I'm seeing zans everywhere.
His body is tempted to fold over. Literally it's like giving me a mini heart attack. Can I aim on you? Aim, aim, aim.
No aim bot, aim bot, aim bot. Just don't want to do it for me. It's really annoying when it does that.
That's not good. I really do not want that guy to be able to see me.
Oh no, no, no, don't, don't, don't. Yeah, didn't think so mate. Right, he's just discovered that body.
Do I desync because he sees the body or am I? I actually think I'm safe. You know that? I think I've done it.
Even though he sees the dead bodies of I, that's fine. Okay, we did it. We just have to hang out on this little edge.
Oh no we don't because there's freaking guards right there which I don't like. Hopefully we don't have a problem.
Scotch, want me to speak calmly while you enjoy a heart meal? Is it weird being the Scottish accent? No, it's not weird at all.
It sounds like home. A body? Just another day in the room. Honestly, if you've totaled how many SEOs joined, I feel like it's a really considerable number.
Wait, can I move on this? Do not be detected and do not touch the ground while tail in the centre.
I can touch the ground now, right? That's definitely not, I'm not. I swear if this is like we're broken it.
Yeah, okay, I was gonna say I was like that's the silliest thing I've ever heard if it's like you're not allowed to do it.
Celtic language is just assistant to me.
Oh, there's Scotch, there's Scotch. Can you get up please?
It's not mysterious.
Video embedding issues should now be fixed for all channels. We're not on Holodex, are we? Did you guys already get us on Holodex? There's no way.
Or are we? I thought it was like a view thing like you needed a certain amount of views ourselves or something.
Thanks, we suck.
There's an endy say. Ah, I confirm. Okay, okay, okay, okay.
Hopefully everyone's viewable and you can see what's up. Shibi's still alive, I believe, and we don't have a zero today.
I think it's a rest day for a zero if I'm not mistaken.
Okay, we're done. We did it, 100%. You're not, but you can still use the zero to create your own.
Not views, so I've got a 20 key average on channel, yeah.
It means about to go live, heck yeah. What's it mean to do in the day?
I would highly recommend in and out.
Yeah, the court is blocked us from being able to do the bench thing. I know how to do the bench thing, it's not a problem.
Oh, she's meme reviewing.
Come on, come on, come on.
Scots East, more strongly misunderstanding the listener's lack of accent.
We can't go in.
Fitty land, boy. Fitty land? Fitty land? Fitty land?
Well, you've succeeded in confusing me.
I'm back. Take a break to listen to music.
Hell, Claudia, the banker is here.
Oh, I have so much money to hire these lovely ladies.
I'm too good, literally.
Okay, Emmy live in... when? Soon?
Can't take the name of the music, so...
Beautiful.
Ciao bella.
Che cosa.
I don't want to get them on that sofa.
Oh, he's staring around.
No one's actually named it Luigi.
Darling Bratter sister, Emmy.
Darling Bratter. Darling Bratter sister, Emmy.
See, that five times fast. Darling Bratter sister, Emmy. Darling Bratter sister, Emmy. Darling Bratter sister, Emmy. Darling Bratter sister, Emmy.
But they are giggling away and won't stop losing.
Right, so take them and then go back to the full stack.
Because I don't want to get in any trouble.
I think we just got 50% DNA, so I think we might actually have...
I think we might actually have a new Pristina memory unlock.
If it's 25%, then 50%, then 75% like that reason said, then should we help?
I can protect you.
I can protect you?
Speaking of smoking, you're fortuitary friendly.
You want to go for it? No, nothing for me to say.
I'm trying so hard not to lose them to a guard right now.
I think we're okay with the render difference.
I have no idea what we're missing and not done yet.
We're replaying easy missions that I failed in order to get higher DNA sequence.
Pristina's story doesn't unlock until you have high synchronicity, so I'm having to go back and redo missions that are easy.
And that will raise our overall percentage.
And then we should be able to finish whatever happens with Pristina because it ended and it didn't make any sense at all.
We're done this part, we just need to do the benchmark now.
How far are you planning on taking Viola or dominating?
No, not dominating.
I just want the girls to achieve their dreams and achieve what they want to do.
Have a good time.
It's kind of like what are Viola's dreams?
Viola's dreams or whatever the girls' dreams are because we want them to be happy.
Interesting what about alcohol?
Oh, I can't have alcohol.
Have you guys drank its fine?
I'm going to stop you.
But yeah, alcohol and me don't go well.
It speeds up my heart rate, it makes me feel uncomfortable and I get...
I'm very late wait, even though I'm Scottish.
I'm so freaking late wait, it's so annoying.
I'm stinky, like why?
So I just can't really handle it.
I don't do it.
Also there's been like tons of reports that come out where alcohol is really bad.
But I'm not going to say no to like drunk karaoke streams or something like that.
I kind of learned that...
So when you feel a buzz from alcohol, you don't have to drink any further than that point to keep the buzz going.
That's not how alcohol works.
I only recently learned that back anyway.
But I won't be shy of doing like drunk karaoke.
I'll drink for the both of us honestly.
There's less of you to fill alcohol with.
Oh, please excuse me.
I'm holding B, please excuse me.
Ladies, ladies, sync with me my goodness.
Work with me here.
No Guinness for strong.
I actually like drinking beer.
It's probably the only thing I can handle at the moment.
Please remember to drink water if you do drink it.
Yes, I did not want any issues.
What's the way to celebrate my birthday?
Than to join in the brotherhood of man.
Soon, we will be here once more.
Celebrating a new night.
And then the feasting will last for 40 days and 40 nights.
Not even the girlies drink?
I mean, Shibi is live right now doing drunk ASMR.
I don't know, I just never...
I never had like going out friends.
Let go like...
Like nightclub or rave or any of that.
Which is where a lot of drinking culture comes into play in the UK.
The aim when you go out with your friends is to get plastered.
Which is just not very pleasant.
Chesering full plated armour.
If only we had a very strong kneecap.
Sure would be a shame.
Oh, I did a challenge.
Right, let's do this without getting in trouble this time.
You go away.
Thank you very much.
Right, and then you stop so I can go in this blend spot.
No, you're right in front of me. This is what we didn't want last time.
Half my friend group loved getting hammered and half did not.
Yeah, like I didn't really experience any of that.
So it just never really became a thing.
And like obviously hang up.
Right, I definitely can do this thing.
Yeah, okay, easy peasy.
100% right there.
I was the Disney driver on my 21st birthday.
Oh, that's right. 21 is a drinking age in your country.
Honestly, I'm going to happy here.
I'm going out or getting good at it.
It was going out or getting good at AC Brotherhood.
Literally, I like just play video games all day.
I'm sure it is fun if you're into it, but like I just have no interest.
I have an interest in like doing like tipsy streams or like drunk review of movies.
Okay.
Not again.
Did it twice.
I'm sure there's a freaking hay bale down there or something.
Drinking with good family friends is probably getting me.
Well, you're getting hammered.
Well, you were out there getting hammered.
I was exio al dottori himself.
Right.
Wait, those missions only went up to sync to 51%.
So didn't you, Christina, get unlocked at 50%?
Oh.
What do you mean?
I've only done 50% of the game.
Ah, right.
Those ones are difficult, so I actually don't want to do them.
What's this one?
The Baron de Voix.
Gatekeeper 50-50.
What are you?
Don't lose any health squares.
Okay, this one's super easy.
We can do this one.
I'm literally doing it easiest to hardest.
Then we'll get hard at the end.
How should I beat you first try and get clues?
Sorry, I need something like that because it's not very nice.
Because like I completely understand that.
I did it again.
It makes that noise.
I think that must be an audio mistake or something because...
Your men can overpower the camp's patrols, correct?
Yes.
I was studying the hidden bleed.
I was such an Assassin's Creed fanboy.
I used to think it would be so cool if I got like the Assassin's Creed logo branded on my finger.
I was so impressionable as a child.
You're truly a man after my own heart.
So impressionable.
Not very smart.
It's kind of character.
I will get the armor.
My troops will gather it from the dead.
The stream tomorrow is a native streamer overload.
Native streamer overload.
It's actually a pretty good pill for me.
Next, small fish, the AC logo in tattoo.
Only refilling Assassins allowed inside.
Okay, if this is just don't be...
Actually, well, I am here.
No, not while I'm here.
We have to do it outside of the mission.
No, I always go that way and it's like the longest way to find anyone.
That's a good reason that young people can't get tattoos.
Yes, I would like to be sitting here with like a freaking branded fingers.
Probably the Sega logo on me at one point as well for...
Don't get detected.
For Sonic Heroes.
I always loved it when it was like Sega.
Did that not alert anyone?
They're actually so efficient at fighting that it didn't alert anyone.
What do you guys get?
Okay, Assassins are pretty high level.
I'm pretty sure they can handle what's going to happen.
Oh, there's a patrol route.
Oh, there's a big old fight going on.
Okay, we're at five costumes.
They're still going for it.
Whoa, they're getting beaten up by the big guys.
Oh, they're fighting back.
They're beating them up.
Four to two.
Oh, she lost the health bar.
Wow, I actually thought the...
Oh, they're going for this.
They're doing it.
They're going for the patrolers as well.
Oh, we got ten in that one.
That was a really good one.
What's over here?
Another French battalion thing.
When needy streamer overload, okay.
I think that's definitely going to be a shorter stream.
However, when I do have shorter streams,
I'm going to be working on ASMR collabs and stuff,
so there's not going to be more content coming.
I'm going to cry here.
Let's see.
Oh, that's actually for two assassins
to take on that big old group.
That's quite a lot.
Yeah, one of them just lost a health bar.
I actually think I'm going to have to send in more assassins.
Oh, they've lost two health bars.
This is getting juicy.
Oh, the other one's lost one as well.
Oh, it's getting juicy.
It's getting juicy.
Oh, there's losing three.
I don't want to get detected because that will ruin this little sequence,
but I will call in the next card.
There you go.
I have no idea what's going on over there.
I don't want to get detected to ruin it, but...
Oh, he's on two.
Okay.
Help him!
Freaking...
Ah.
Jeez.
Okay, I definitely need to level up the gang
because they are still not strong enough for this.
Stop.
Oh, my goodness.
No, don't pick on a guard, please.
Oh, right.
Everyone despawn right this instant.
My heart.
Right.
They'll heal up.
Whenever your assassin is low, they'll heal up.
I thought we lost them.
Oh, my goodness.
I thought we...
I was like...
I called in another assassin on that guy
that was in particular his harasser.
I was like, where are they?
Where are they?
Like, where are they going from?
And I was like, oh, wait.
I can shoot off my horse.
Like, I can still attack, technically.
I just need to not be discovered.
That's all.
I'm gonna wait to call in my assassins to do this.
I really don't want to actually get caught.
I'll be annoyed at myself if I do.
There's another guard post all the way over here.
Excuse me.
Pardon me, come through.
Oh, wow.
Yeah.
There's a big one over here.
Maybe...
Big like mine.
Okay, let's just send in guards.
Eh, guards.
And like this.
Fill health already.
There you go.
Hold on.
Super simple.
Super easy.
Got 100%.
Literally, that's all I had to do last time.
I wonder if I didn't have all, I say,
a...
Signals?
Um...
Doing.
Oh, no, my track is bugging out again.
Please stop.
What's this one?
Don't take any damage.
Don't lose any health squares.
That one's not easy
because of how many enemies can just swing at you.
And that first one...
I'll try it.
Do I plan on unlocking all the endings on Needy Streamer?
I don't know how much I'm gonna like it.
I'm gonna play it for the first time.
I think it's like a click game, which honestly
might make it super simple.
If I like it, then I'll try and get all endings
if I don't like it.
And then I'll probably just do a few runs and then
have a short stream and then I'll work on ASMR.
That sounds like a deal.
Surprise me.
The French puttane have us under pressure.
Tell me about their general.
These...
Baron de Valois.
Some major is just the, like,
the hmm option.
And over and over again.
Where can I find him?
To watch the bed.
Wait, do I need to censor the stream?
Is it safe to stream it?
They seem to be getting closer.
The situation is under control.
Close the gates!
Needy Strony overload.
Oh, I should have named it that.
I'm taking that.
Thank you.
No, you can do it.
Okay.
Right.
Don't take any damage.
I'm gonna do that.
So that stops them.
Okay, that's what I'm nervous about.
Them doing that.
And I don't have a freaking smoke bomb.
I have...
I don't have any more smoke bombs.
Right.
Oh, I think I might need to...
Oh, I can call in my recruits.
Oh, my God.
Please don't attack me.
I really don't want to lose health over this.
I can't see because of the camera angle.
I'm scared.
I'm going for it.
I'm sending it.
Please don't attack me.
Okay, my assassin recruits are going ham.
That's what I like to see.
They're stuck outside.
Assassin, please.
Jeez.
Are you trying to make me lose?
Is there anyone else?
Wait, what?
On air?
I've never seen this before.
I guess I'll just...
Wait, they keep seeing me, though.
I can't...
So the AI can't actually see me,
but it keeps claiming it is.
It's not.
I think I'm just going to shoot them.
I can.
Oh, I can.
I'm getting them.
Okay, that was...
Okay, we did it.
We did it.
It's just heavily implied.
It's more of a win-win-win-nothing.
Okay.
He did it too well.
He dumped people in us.
Blame them with your ink.
Maybe I should have had an ink toy,
but what would have been funny is anything.
Like, I'd just go...
And it was all in screen.
Oh, no!
Didn't the developers also make another game?
A whale after?
Oh, I think so.
Hello!
Hello, everyone!
How are you?
Today...
I...
Yeah, I can't speak none of that.
Okay.
Okay, I think we just need to go back and forth
and not get attacked by anything,
which is super simple.
Oops.
Maybe part of a 2.0 or a new output.
Why is your French so good?
No, it's nothing else.
Don't understand the French.
No, I don't understand it.
Oh, no, my eyes.
Sorry, sorry.
Sorry.
I actually don't know any French.
I literally know phrases.
And I record to take the same phrases.
If you would like to order a ham and cheese baguette,
you say...
I forgot what cheese is.
A baguette.
Well, that didn't...
That didn't work out very well.
No.
Baguette.
Well, it sounds good coming from a French speaker.
Oh, thank you.
How are you doing?
How are you?
Huh?
Are you okay?
Oh, wait, that was for a joke.
What's the French password?
Hmm...
I don't know.
One...
Two...
One baguette.
And one...
Ramon.
Who wants me to play with you?
That's like, I'm literally just regurgitating.
Do I have higher education?
That sounds like I have higher education.
That's just new.
Reason of barn.
Uneducated in the barn.
And became a gamer.
Hell yeah.
Ray.
I'm a bit scared of this one.
Don't lose any health squares.
I actually don't want to do that one
because it takes too long.
Right, we're at 52%.
So every time I do a memory,
I'm getting like up to 5%.
Use assassin recruits to do your targets.
Okay, we're actually factually
going to upgrade our assassin recruits.
Which...
Sorry, I just closed this,
but we actually needed to open it.
If I do this, they get...
Okay, we just need to send them on missions.
If we get 5 assassins level 10,
the assassin's recruit signal
replenishes so much faster.
I think it takes off like 20 seconds.
Which, in the grand scheme of things,
like adds up so quickly.
How much money do I have on my purseings?
13k, right, I don't have enough right.
We'll just go and...
We'll send them on...
Missions.
Like the pigeons.
Oh, it was like dead ahead, dead center.
I remembered an Italian swear.
I'll use it in a sentence.
I didn't even know that.
I know catso.
And merda.
Oh, we put 50 grand in the bank?
50 smacaroons.
Right, we're going to send away our agents.
Because I want some of them to level up
so then we can get faster.
I have no one at 10 yet.
What?
You guys...
Oh, you're getting close.
Right, I just need to send them away.
Maybe do a mission that doesn't require them.
And then we can get the...
Upgrade.
5, 1, 2, 3, and 4.
If you guys all go...
I think...
1, 2, 3, 4, 5.
Oh, I don't want to risk the room.
If it fails...
I'm like 99% sure they come back all perished.
If it fails, which is like pretty unforgiven.
Honestly, your openness and no manners
is one of the reasons why I like...
Oh, that's funny.
Right, missions, missions, missions.
Wait, they don't have...
17 minutes for that mission?
Is really not.
Is there not another level 5 regular contract?
There's no...
Oh, these are all level 5s.
All four of you go together.
And you're humble, little thing.
Alright, as an Italian myself,
I have to say here in the dub for Italian phrases
another language is cringe.
Oh, you don't want to hear me say
Spingy, Spingy, Ayuto, Ayuto!
Ayus meus, Dios me...
Wait, no, that's Spanish.
Right, we're going to go to a bank.
Ummmmm
the Bangkok, Bangkok, Bangkok, Bangkok
As in Italian you tell, please say more Italian words.
Ayye, Ay... Ayus, meuls!
To say...
I don't think I have any Italian word.
I'm ready for a little nap after eating all those little snacks.
I still have P-Snacks left over.
I forgot to eat any of my rice.
I'm gonna have to put them back in the fridge. Oh, I need to buy paintings wait the paintings question mark and go to DNA
Fifty-two four seven fifty-two four seven fifty-two four seven fifty-two
Four seven fifty-two
Spend all my money on London, oh, excuse me you're in my way
I
Just need to access the bank over here. I don't mind get a little wet. Why not we
That's my favorite food chatting has to be chicken
It's too tasty, I don't know. I just did something. I like savory foods over sweet foods
Savory is just dab on
Flags feathers and chest today
to flag go to the percentage because I feel like the DNA sequence doesn't is like so
Rough colonel standards use that something I can't do that. Just yeah
Don't be detected like I don't like the
Beat Chesery to the apple of Eden. Don't hurt anyone
Cuz they're all attacking you
Beat Chesery to the apple Eden don't hurt anyone
Mmm, I have my hand over my mouth thinking I'm oh, I don't have any smoke bombs
I don't have any smoke bombs on my person so I can't get away with that fried all fried by far
Yeah, for sure, would you like if you heard an Italian speak your navel image sure might not be some bad
But you know the accent can pack a punch
Oh
So
Okay, yeah, the layers of Romeo the war machine. Oh, oh
Wait, do these have a percentage
No, these don't have a percentage
Oh
Okay, this is why our thing is so low
Okay, okay, we're gonna do assassin's contracts wherever the heck they are that's why the freaking percentage is so low
these
symbols
the pigeon
Like these ones is it that assassin contract, right? Okay. Okay. I
Was gonna say because it's not making a lot of sense why the percentage is so low
There's only a few missions that haven't done a hundred percent on
I'm gonna be honest and I don't think we're gonna hundred percent it
But we definitely finished the game and I'm sat aside
That after like the stream, we don't need to hop back on black a on black ops on brotherhood
Hey, cuz I'm satisfied with the play through
Cuz yeah, I don't actually have much me okay, so I just need to kind of do all the
Black markers on the map really maybe factions also half of it if I get like a hundred percent favor in the factions as well
Okay, see yummy, honestly
It's been very close it's it's more of a cozy day
I think yesterday like I used up a lot of my energy on a rifle
Just like being like gushing about this game and being like it's getting so cool
Today it's like it's definitely cozy. It's definitely have a little blankie on you and make sure you're comfy
I
Yesterday I was screaming my head off like just loving everything and so energetic
But like that get to be like that unapologetically cuz like nothing's worse than like
being excited for something and then
Someone's like, oh, you're being really loud and obnoxious. So just like kills like oh, this is a lot of me
Like I'm having such a good time. You never met someone who's like genuinely excited for
Yes faction challenges are also part of the percentage of the contract no not like contract
Mission
Chesery hopes that our rebels will stumble into his line of fire his expected come and wait instructions
Kill the three targets in two minutes. Oh my god. These have freaking things as well
Oh, okay, I'm starting to understand why our DNA think is so unbelievably low
Oh, he's just that range
Wait under three minutes three gunmen and under
They're not that far away. Okay, I guess the assassin's contracts are super nice
Because this guy's on that far away. Oh like that was like super reasonable
Oh, I can't reach that
Oh
That quick
Okay, I was like, oh, oh, oh, oh, I'll I'll I'll meet ankles
I'm out of medicine. Oh and smoke worms
Oh, there's a doctor over here. That's perfect
Oh
What was out of medicine
I've seen the thing is I don't look soldiers bodies so I don't get anything from him. He'll heal me. You should heal myself. No
Do the feathers count as DNA or possibly
You don't need ankle
Right, so literally just do the pigeon clips and then it's going up
Oh, yeah, 53 percent. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Let him get up. Let him get up 53 percent. Uh, how do you go up there?
That looks like a hell to me. It looks like a bit of an in slope a bit of an incline
I
Think tomorrow I'm going to say
Which means I need to take a shower put deodorant on
I need to pretend
I'm a normal person
I'm teasing. I do not stink all the time. Wait. What was 100 percent?
Assassinate three guards with a hidden blade. You do not have to tell me anything more. I assure you
Hidden blade is wiggle
Oh
They're on horsies
I love when they're on horsies
Hello, would you like to die? I oh, okay. Hold on. Let me try the game. Would you like to die?
One
They're all on horses. No wonder the game's like do they're all on horses. How am I supposed to do this?
Hello, would you like to die?
Hello, would you like to die? No
Yes, wait, I did it 100 percent already
Skill okay. Wait. Wait. Hold on. It's fine. Don't panic. Don't panic. Don't panic. Don't panic. Let him get up
Let him get up. Oh, no, no, no. Don't spank the horse
Wait, wait, wait. Get him because he's got a bow
Why does it not? Do I need to like jump up onto the horse?
Ow, you're hurting me
Okay
Okay, okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Let me cook. Let me cook. Yes. They got off the horse by automatic
Okay, easy peasy lemon squeezy. You're next
No, you're not
Are you coming?
Yes, there. Get him. Three, two, one. Oh, oh, I missed it. I missed it. I missed the timing source
It's never too late
Hope the weather's nicer for you. It's mild
33 degrees
That's too much for me. I'll I'll pass right. I guess we're gonna do Leonardo as well
Oh
Right, there's another one if we do that the assassin mission seemed like super fair
Some of it buys for them right now and we can generate more money by sending
Are we assassins to get more exp? I'm gonna need a horse for this
I said I'm gonna need to wait. I'm blind. I just passed off on the horse. Sorry mate. My apologies
Uh, if it's super easy to do the assassin contracts, we'll just do them get them out of the way and then
Hopefully that's like our percentage raised by like five
That's pretty good
Uh, actually I could also use these mercenaries
Well, I can't right now
Uh
We're just
Trying to do what we can. It's very unlikely. We're gonna 100% it, but I'm enjoying myself thoroughly
Uh, I'm actually gonna go get a blanket because I'm putting my legs on the table and I'm killing circulation to my leg
I'll just be a second. I don't need to mute so you can
Uh, was it
I
Have my lovely blanket to protect my leg
Because the circulation is dying because I pressed them so hard against the table
They ain't sitting on my feet. I'm cutting the circulation out of my leg
All right, my chair is like so quicky
Right have we got any level 10? No we don't. It was a smaller mission
I
Screen shot that
That's an interesting
I'm supposed to close my eyes before I leave like so the thing looks right, but
I'm just gonna keep sending people to
Do more um
Oh wait, I'm a dumb dumb. I was supposed to accept uh, assassination contract
missions
The ball on the
Choose company kill both targets for your hidden belief. You do not have to tell me twice
I'm loving these assassin missions. Are you joking me?
I assume I don't have to get on a horse to reach them
But we're getting pretty far
Uh, I can't tell which one's closer
Eh, what is this?
The wheat. Oh, wow. They're like, okay, actually it's closer to a door than four. Let's do that
By Austria and Switzerland just 26 right now
Oh
Literally the assassin missions are like so easy and like um, um, we might be like 57
Once by the time we're finished them if they make them this easy then
Yeah
If you die
Your assassin rule before promoting them a max their cape match will be that color. I have no sense
Wait that
Assassin contracts are so easy. I love it here. What the heck no like don't be detected and there's 18 billion like guards looking at you
Shout out to assassin contracts. Hello. I can't believe how easy these are
Oh, excuse me mr. Horsey yet in Maui
The 68% finish is that where we'll end on 60% I'll give the Leonardo missions ago
It would be nice 100% but my goodness, I didn't know
I'll see what happens by the end of this stream like I didn't I thought I was only going to do six hours today
Hi, I'm sorry
Bye
Um
What percentage are we now in like 54
55 I love it here says 55. Oh my god more contact. Please. They're so easy. Is there any more?
No, but there's
Templar agents
Okay, we're going to do Templar agents. I'm totally not stalling on the Leonardo missions because I know they're a bit tricky
Last Christina needs 75 percent. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. We're gonna do it. We're gonna do it
I mean, honestly, it might be one of those things where I'm like
We'll do what we can
I actually don't know how long we're gonna
Like stream today. As I said, I was only planning on doing
Six hours ish, but I mean we're already getting close to that mark
It's already been four hours and a half. Yeah, and I'm like I don't really feel like I'm out of stamina right now
for stream
so
Yeah, and like especially tomorrow
Depended on like how much I like the game. It might only be a tour stream which kind of is a bit meh
um
I believe
Anything called love just listen to the rhythm of your heart
Da da da da da da da da da
Yeah, literally it may be one of those things where I end up actually getting so close that we do just go
Oh wait, the bank. I can collect money from it
Eh
Oh, no, I've already collected my money. Oh, please
I suppose once we buy the last, um
how you call them, touristic locations, then we'll shall.
I'm trying to do the faction challenges, like on the way there.
Yeah, like I need to hire thieves to lure people away.
You need to do it 10 times like through their quest then.
I just need to find enemies
Yeah, just like that
We need to complete Christina literally
Right, what's this? Hi. Are you okay? Oh?
It's not looking good
She's beating up
Don't
I will not touch you what happened here
He owns this neighborhood that border I have given it to him
He once made signs for the shops in the district
But now he post lies for the border and hurt those who stand in his way. Wow
Where is he? He spends his days locking his workshop, but I may know how to go them out
What we're doing kill your target with the hidden blue. I love these missions. What the heck?
Yesterday said eight hours on the end of being 12 it would have been 14 I
Don't know maybe one day they'll fix the vod issue if the day comes where they fix that vod issue
Please let me know because it is over for your sleep schedule. I'm talking we wake up
We brush our teeth. We get our food and then we stream 14 hours
Wait, it's the doctor what was to do? Oh, no, it's the same
Interact oh
We're pulling down propaganda my apologies. I
Didn't know
Can you at least reserve the weekends? Yeah, oh you need a break from my stamina. You're so adorable refling
There's no breaks on this tree. I
Was gonna say something else there
We're pulling down propaganda it's useless posters
Sleep is already ruined what's a lot more room
I
Like I'm trying to do this like obviously they did the poster grab and things
When you've got no right, but I didn't realize they like we use that actually like the concept because obviously like whenever you think of the
Past you're like, how did all these people like even get caught for crimes like it just seems so
Oh
Kill your target with them
Can I rip it down or are they gonna be mad at me? Okay, that's exactly odd up smoke bombs
We're just so that length
Well, whoa, whoa, I wasn't even yes
See that's what I get annoyed with if you don't enter combat before they whack you you can't count us
And I look you can't see one boom, but yeah
I might be able to get a smoke bomb off of this guy for a little which I would actually really appreciate in case
Ancient room graffiti you see the walls the Pompey. We're at oh, yes. He does give me a smoke bomb. That was lucky
I'll definitely try and remember to oh
So when we pull this down I assume we get to meet the guy
Oh, we lure him out of his workshop because we've filled all those posters down, okay
We can definitely do
Other fan bases be looking at we feel like a man dying of dehydration watching another man drowning
That's so good. What I
For goodness sake, I'll get Santa my
At least he well in this house
Like I do feel bad when like people have a streamer that maybe like struggles to stream
And I just find they're like a really good time poke it down
Is that a multiplayer character it kind of looks like it might actually be
If it is then that's like another
Complement to the game would be in like how they incorporated multiplayer characters into the game
campaign between
Drowning is standing
Did you ever play the multiplayer for this game I
Don't
I
Think I was aware of it 56% okay hold on. I'm starting to have hope
I'm starting to have mild hope. I don't want to get anyone
I
Don't want to lead to anyone on
But it might be possible it might be for the hundred percent run
Because that's going up way faster now that we're just sorry I should be re-riding horse right now and
Because that like literally I was so confused why like the percentage was so low okay
So let's let's see what happens. Let's see. We're at 55 percent. I believe I've gone
Oh, I remember this one is that stupid
You go all the way around in order to oh, actually I'm gonna send off assassin recruits
Need to level them up and we need money money money for tourist attractions
I
Know I know
Knowing that a streamer you like is on most of the days I got time from yours
Yeah, like I don't really get born out like I'm happy to talk about it, but like I
Just don't seem to experience like so don't get me wrong. I absolutely can have days where I am
Like ready to go to bed, but like I wake up on the other side of bed, and I'm like
What we doing like let's go do this. Let's go do that. Um
Send them off for 200 type thing
But like actual burnout like I always wake up the next day like wanting to do something more
Oh, there's actually a contract right here. We is that inside?
Oh
It's fantastic there. Hello, Madame Madonna Madonna
The pigeons deliver the names of key paper agents the Jubilee has brought the hard part will be the last 5%
Exchange for up solution
Threats of damnation terrorized those reluctant to pay the agents collections go directly to Chaldery
I will make money the least of their worries
What's the hundred percent
New assassin contracts a lot
Say no more my lady. Say no more
Okay
Let me get up. Okay. We've got more assassin contract, which means the percentage will get even higher very shortly
Send away my assassins to level up and
Well, pardon me, excuse me come through my ladies. Would you like to distract those?
More ladies would you like to come and distract some
There's any guards ahead unfortunately, I'm on a horse so much faster than them
And the horse is stuck on the hill. That's the only thing I don't like with a game
Right, uh, there's no guard. So we're just gonna we'll be fine. It's okay
Where's this guy? I'm on the wrong side. Hello. Oh, there you are
Oh
What are these contracts doing
Just one shooter it will be easy to overtake cannot be very accurate
Oh
He's swinging a huge person and
Kill the target using the head and bleed within 45 seconds
Don't like change both try it
45 seconds run run run run run run run right he's gonna close that. Okay
Okay?
45 seconds hidden bleat.
45 seconds hidden bleat, 45 seconds hidden bleat.
45 seconds hidden bleat, 45 seconds hidden bleat,
hidden bleat, hidden bleat, I love hurting people
with a hidden bleed, okay we did it.
Oh. His name is Laquac. Okay, we did it. What's your take on the best AC game regarding
story-wise? Exio's story-wise? Like, all of Exio? Uh, like, especially Revelations, when...
Whoa, why am I under attack? What's going on? Give me a run. Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, where
did you even come from? I didn't want to hurt anyone, though, as you're doing. I saw that,
so I'm gonna grab it. I didn't even know where those guys came from. They're no
stationed here, right?
Oh. I'm not having a good one around. Hmm.
You know if we're part of these, Exio's killing a lot of the multiplayer characters. Yes! Definitely.
We'll go get this assassin contract. Well, can I just spin around the map again, like,
how we did when we were renovating everything? Spin around the map. Why is he
whispering in Italian to a French? I don't even know how you'd say rest in peace in
French. Dormez-vous! Dormez-vous, mate. So, la-vous. C'est n'est pas la vie? No, no, it's not the life
anymore. My French is awful. I get very confused with how they structure, like, words in French.
It's true. It's true. Do you ever think about if Exio was really here to be an insane serial
killer and probably the highest kill- Oh, yeah. Actually, who does have the highest kill count?
Oh! Don't answer that, actually. Yeah. Not necessary. Thank you, guys. Hmm. I'm gonna grab
this flag right now. Yeah, no. I, like, I asked the question, and my brain then flashed up
that answer, and I was like, ah, hmm, hmm. Like, I've run out of this. Uh, nah, we're just meming
along. We're not really talking about much. I've discovered why my percentage was going up so slow,
so we're currently in the question mark stage of, is this gonna be a 12-hour marathon to 100%
the game or not? Because I couldn't figure out why the frickin' game. Oh, we need... Okay, you guys
are, like, so close to being maxed out. It's crazy. I'm not gonna send you away for 20 minutes, so do
you max out? Yes, we do. The other two, we don't even need to send away anymore. More. Do you need,
like, 24 minutes? Nah, you need a bit more XP than that. Got a level 82 XP to it for you. Yeah,
that looks like quick math. That looks good to me. My brain was still explicit in the context. No, no,
I don't need it. Oh, I need to accept the contract. Actually, oh, I'm gonna send the thieves on this
person over here, actually. Actually, factually, as long as you set them on someone, you don't
actually have to stick around or anything. I'm gonna grab this feather while I'm at it as well,
because I'm really close to it. Right, as well. It's also a feather in the coliseum that you go
That's 6 out of 10. Wait, why are you guys still following me? Did you not lure the guards?
I guess they didn't activate because they weren't close enough.
Wait, do you only lure away stationery guards? Can he be? Oh, wow, I did not know that. I thought
you could lure anyone, so I have to pick stationery guards? I have not bought the coliseum. I actually
might have enough. Right there. Right there, luring him away. I'm gonna go and get this nation. Oh,
a maestro. I saw that. I saw that. I need five assassins to be maestro, and then we'll do some
more reblet. You just have to be good at the game. I say you're done. Wait, is this funny? I'm coming for you.
Right, I'll send them two together, because they're not ready yet.
Uh, no, I keep forgetting to accept the fricking contract.
Hi, hi, hi. Yes, yes, yes, but you don't need to tell me. Right, what's the mission assignment?
Make a nice and easy peasy. Finish the memory within two minutes. Where am I supposed to go?
Do I need to go by horse or not? Yes or no?
The thing is, you take, like, if you just directly sprint.
Yeah, see, this is the problem. All this stuff is in the way in order to get to them in under
two minutes. Right, gallop, please. Yeah, okay, okay, faster, faster, faster. Yeah, okay, the horse
was definitely the better bet. You could not run that. And just says do it in under two minutes. So
yeah, what are you? Oh, they're on horseback. No, that makes fighting so annoying.
Oh, sorry, I've got an itchy nose, so if my tracking goes away, it's for my 90s.
Okay, okay, so glad I took the fricking horse. Holy crap.
Okay, that's it. It's just so easy. It's just so easy. It's so good. Like, I love these
missions. Holy crap. I had no idea how easy they were. Oh, excellent. And it's like that.
Literally a minute to spare.
Another one. Another one. Oh, do you want to come with me? We'll distract some guards.
I should be so close to doing the distraction on.
Okay, there's a guard over here. Actually, I need to walk around. I might distract.
I didn't do anything. May I ask that? Time to perish. Are you ready?
Oh, is it because I had the weapon out maybe?
Yeah, I literally did not know.
So the good thing with the mercenaries, if you walk around with them to the next location,
you can keep setting them on new people to attack, so I'm just going to bring them with me.
And once they've attacked 10 people, then we have done that section of the mercenaries challenge.
Do you think Margaret Thatcher effectively utilised girl power by funneling money into the
game? I'm just here to play video games. I'm quite happy to admit that this topic of conversation
is completely out of my knowledge realm. No, I've never played it with monsters. I
always play vanilla. I prefer to play games vanilla to appreciate the way that the development
team made it. A lot of people don't like vanilla Skyrim, and I'm so sorry, but I just enjoy it.
I didn't know because I played on Xbox. I didn't know that on vanilla Skyrim because I was on
Xbox that the little dots on the floor were daisies and grass until I played on PC for the first time.
Oh, oh, oh, is it, am I pooping or is that mud?
Why are they insisting on walking into me, honestly?
I just tried to watch A.G's stream, A.B's stream, but I'm deaf in my left ear,
so it went silent for 10 seconds in my right ear. But you heard that? I'm like, I don't know.
Oh, bless you. What happened?
Were you born like that or did you get tiniest?
Are they still not done with that fight? Oh, the guy went back on his horse. I was actually going
to send him on him. Oh, they're still fighting. Come on. It's just one guy in armor.
Oh, come on. You can do it. I believe in this.
Horses kicking. Literally. I've never, I've never had the horse being pushed into the floor.
Come on, mercenaries. Come on. One of the, yeah, there you go. Geez. Right. We're going to set him
on this guy now.
The Guardia. Oh, they're beating that horse up.
I don't know how many mercenary challenges are completed. All their stuff is like
weapon based or doing something impressive or winning. We're going to say, do you guys need help?
I think they need help with him.
Okay. They definitely need help with him. Yeah, from done. Thanks guys. Glad I hired you.
Bought some bought things. Taking so long. I know.
I've almost done like sending the mercenaries on people at least. Is this like five maybe?
If they could just perish them a bit faster, you know, we can be there.
Literally, I'm like just hooded man on horse since four men to fight.
Ten years working around engine rooms. Oh, no. That's like the quickest way to lose here.
It's like works like that. Okay. Maybe not.
Why are messages disappeared? Mozio feeling okay? Am I going crazy?
Rubber room. I'm rubber room through the rest.
Oh, right. We're almost there. We're almost there.
Right. Fight him.
Fill them off the horse or something.
This is going to take forever.
Is there like another mercenary group right here? Yeah. Okay. Can I have you?
And then can I send you to fight this group that's already fighting?
It works. Okay. Now they're completely outnumbered.
That must be what? Six now? Only four more to go.
I'm born deaf on my left ear. Perfect for sleeping because I sleep on Marisa.
Okay. Now, follow me. So this will be seven?
Oh, for goodness sake. That's taking forever.
I'll do that though. Because it's when you send them, they don't have to win the fight.
It's just when you send them on people. Actually, you know what?
I'm just checking. I'm just checking. I can't take this anymore.
Gale challenges. Mercenary? Nine? Okay.
Guards killed Will on horseback. Brutes killed. Scaffolding.
Guards on horseback. Ares assassinated? That must be done from a certain location.
Yeah, double assassinations. Three out of ten. I can hardly get it done.
Court is on. Nine. Oh, guard's poisoned. It's 15, so I do need to go poison a ton more guards.
I assume if they hate each other, then I don't care. Okay, thieves on our entrance.
Leaves of faith, I need a 20. Guards are assassinated from a mini.
I just need to find one enemy. Hello, you are enemy. And fight. Okay, finally. That took so long.
Hiring discount earned a little bit. Hello.
Man, look at his fresh cut on that beard. Look at that angle. Is that even possible back then?
I was really dumb, but like before razors were invented,
did guys just like shave their beard on rocks and stuff? Like, I know that sounds really silly,
but did they like fashion a rock to be sharp? And then that's how you got rid of your beard?
Or did like everyone just have beards back in the old days?
The razors weren't a thing.
Maybe glass. It was 100%. Kill by air assassination.
Sheave with swords. Not like before that kind of thing.
Oh, wow, it's such a good far way. Maybe a horse again.
I'm tired of thieves. They may be able to keep up. I'm fucking do a lure away the guards.
Thank you. We're getting there. We're getting there. We're getting there.
I'm getting stuck on a rope. They shave with knives. They just go to homies to scratch their
beards off by hand. That sounds painful as anything. Shave with obsidian.
Guys still did.
Okay, what am I supposed to do here? Oh, air assassination. Okay, I'm gonna go out on a limb
and see the guys probably up in this building then since it's all red.
Hmm. I'm not gonna be discovered, am I? Hello. Goodbye.
Actually, I need to start looting bodies because I'm getting low on supplies,
because I'm wasting them all.
Okay, air assassination.
Let's give it a shot. Where is he? Gee, I wonder where it's air assassination.
Oh, I just called him a horse doing that.
I need to get away. That's why I called him a horse.
Gee. I haven't drawn his mug on two monitors as overwhelming.
Wait until I make hypnosis. I'm so excited to make my first one. I don't know what to do.
I was gonna do a like free thing.
God, these missions are so good and easy. I can't get over it.
I'm not doing the Naruto. I'll keep doing the Templar Agents
because it's starting to get like less and less.
Copernico is a nightmare. If I remember correctly, Copernico is like throw yourself
across the city as fast as you can type missions, which I despise.
And like it really does not give you like much time at all.
So I'm not looking forward to doing Copernico.
No, I don't need the body, but thank you.
Hello, horsey. Are you ready?
Mount. Mabos. Mabos. Well, the horse, please think of Mabos.
Speaking of, are you going to collab with Secret Subject?
I haven't reached out yet. I know Secret is like super busy.
Like she's got like the new VTuber model and everything going on.
And I don't want to be like a bother, like harassing anyone.
I might get the boss to reach out, but at the moment, like I've actually got quite a lot of
people that are interested in collabs with me. And I'm going to try and like not take too much
time. Like I say, she says that she plays on stream for 12 hours and literally has like folk
waiting on her right in the script. So it can be sent off. Well, that was.
But I don't want to send you away. Can I send?
I'm so sorry. I think I need a drawing.
I think it's time. The problem
is that I take like five minutes to generate one. I really don't want to go.
I know it didn't happen yesterday, which I'm really happy about, but I think it's happening.
Oh, wait. Sorry. Oh, sorry. I need to go into an emergency meeting with one of the girls over
something. But I'm like 90% sure I can feel my organs shifting around.
I have no coin on my corpse. I can hear them behind me. That's actually pretty scary. No.
Oh, no, no, no. I mean, doing this, I will take advantage of the smoke because we need to kill
enemies in smoke.
Right, they can all just fight each other. Oh, I need to go through the most.
Any idea when the first hit in the stream, I'll do my job.
It's time is my biggest problem. Like if we end up doing that 100%, I don't know if it's possible.
Then I probably won't do it tonight. Needy streamer. I need to go out and buy American
sweets for this hand cam stream and clean up my desk because it's an absolute mess.
And get like a nice cute outfit and all that.
It's just time, honestly. I hope it doesn't sound like I'm not interested in making it. It's just
time. I've got these Ace Mark gloves and girls are waiting on me. And then I'm sending away
shorts of the girls to be made to Clippers because I didn't want them being stressed out,
having to organize this stuff. I guess it's just trying to settle in right now,
but I hope to have some consistent stuff. That's free to access. I do want at least
something decent free to access on the alt because I don't think it's fair, especially for
people that just simply don't have the money. I completely understand. Don't ever feel bad
if you're unable to just straight up give money to streamers or anything like that.
Like any of the viewers. I am 100% can say right now that all the girls feel the exact
same way as me. If you can't afford it, please don't feel bad. Literally watching,
liking, commenting, flipping if you want, liking a tweet. All of this stuff is free to do.
Like that helps us beyond words. So don't ever feel inclined and like thank you for
respecting that there like is a paywall and some of the content because obviously the girls need
to eat and they need to thrive because if they don't like thrive monetary wise, then obviously
they're not going to stick around a veiler. Why would you? So like I do appreciate everyone's
like complete understanding around it. Um right, where's the source? I am actually
unironically stuck. Where the heck am I going? Over the bridge? Over the bridge? Over the broken
breed? The girls are doing great. Don't worry. No, not over the broken bridge. Don't be fooled by
the map. It's not that old. How do I get down though? I always have that problem whenever I come
up to this section. You have to like all of your breath around. We're already lucky and spoiled
with what you've done for us already. No need to rush, yeah. Like I know some folk are noticing
like oh all the girls aren't posting anymore and it was like yeah the girls are live streaming now
they're preparing for streams. They're thinking ahead like they got stuff to do now. Before the
only stuff the girls could do was meme in the discord with each other and muck about on twitter
and pre-record audios you know and now they've got so much to deal with and contend with so yeah.
What am I doing? What am I doing before I mess up? Kill your target? Why is this game so good?
These game missions are so good. It's actually making me angry. I have nice
interfaces. No, I do understand that some people like complain to complain. That's okay. That's
just how some people are. Like it's how they like get you know like stressed out. It's therapeutic
to kind of have a mooper whatever. It's a lady killer. Okay I need to chase. Stop chasing me.
No you like it you little rascal. You're teasing me. You're a leaky. I don't know what that means.
They didn't put the subtitles in. Stop it. I love a good glitch. I love a good glitch.
I love a good glitch and that helps me get the objective. I love that. That was good. Just do
that again. Honestly renaissance outfit starting to grow in me. It's kind of renaissance influence
outfit maybe. Someone suggested a design which was uh was it an aristocrat? Vampire?
No it was a smug aristocrat. I'm very like posh hoity toyy looking. The only problem is they
would have to be brish because if there were any other I was about to say if there were any other
gender it doesn't work. If there were no brish I was like oh Christina available. Wait what's her DNA
if Christina is available? I'm not questioning it. To Christina we go. Any other gender than
brish? Well that child was like okay thanks brain. Strony. Yesterday don't follow lady who
and also me. No no no no I like that. It's a lady assassin though. Only I am allowed to
raise lady assassins. Okay I'm coming Christina because I have no idea what the heck that you're
freaking storyline is. All right I need you guys because you guys I need to lure away guards with
can I technically get you guys to- well why am I- right I guess not. There should be some guards
coming up. Good they can run fast they're keeping up with a horse practical.
Thank you.
Lure them away.
Aristocrat with a Jordy axe.
Wait how is this all spun about when it comes to the section of the map it's terrible.
I think it's on the side.
Stuck their anger.
Goodness me. I just can't even get this right.
I cannot have gone there on you.
From the rang way? You rang? You're the one that's now- oh excuse me you're in my way.
I could have sworn there's a cape that makes guards ignore you unless you like
straight up attack them. I need to put them to that. I don't know what cape that is.
Oh wow I think that's five one two.
I'm just gonna send them away for money because I think we actually might have enough now.
For- for what? For buying everything yet.
Right Christina my love thank you for unlocking because we were genuinely also confused on what
a bizarre ending your storyline had because that didn't make any sense and you know it didn't so what
on earth are we busy? Oh no.
Oh no I think we're going to the fair.
Do you get an EC mod for your pretty extreme? Maybe put like an assassin screen hood on me.
So there's gonna be an assassin screen. I've never thought about that. Maybe I should get
Ezio's outfit and like- but like you know get the- get like red lacy underwear and stuff.
Leonardo.
Perhaps it would have been better not to tell you. She's with her husband. She may not be too happy to see you.
No it's wonderful. It's carnival. With these masks she will not even know it's me.
I know just the way to draw her attention.
Oh he's not over her. He's heartbroken.
That's so sad.
I can't remember what we have to do here though. Oh there she is. I'm to tail her.
There she is with her other hussies.
I'm just so interested in these masks.
She just got to circle? Wait what was it? Am I supposed to do something?
Oh plan a letter on her. I beg your pardon. I was like why did she just go on a circle?
Okay that makes much more sense. Way more sense.
Okay the rendezvous. Don't mind me.
Wait she reciprocates.
Um
It's you that's wrong. This is it's you.
Oh
It's been eight years? I was afraid you wouldn't come if I just asked.
It was the right thing to do. We loved you. Who cares what he wanted? I love you.
You had your second child. Please that's it.
It got worse. Why did we do this? Why did we play that memory? It got worse. Is that where it ends?
That was even worse. Why did we go away? Why did we go further? There has to be another one. There's
no way. It got so much worse. That was terrible.
Oh
Shot through the heart. True. That got even. I don't know why. Like I don't know why I thought
that memory would like oh that's gonna be so much better than the last one. No.
No no no no no. That's terrible.
Well she said don't find her again but I'm left unsatisfied. I feel like that's such a short
memory that's not like the true ending. Right we're gonna upgrade our assassins just because
we have the thing. I'm not bothered about the thieves honestly. I have quite a lot of money though.
Good on Christina for not being a cheater. Literally like when
when she was like oh husband's name. I was like wait Etsy planted the lair and like
ah what a mess Etsy. What a mess you've got yourself into in a pickle.
Yeah he sucks when it comes to romance. Like everything is permitted.
Goodness gravy.
Welcome to the Brotherhood. Yes.
Did I get the thing?
Hmm. Suspend points.
Assassins Guild challenges complete. Okay.
Uh oh Guild crest stop. Is there something new around here?
This? We get little things. We get trinkets. Oh my god this game. I'm sorry this game was
made for girls. You're telling me. I get a little sim and I get to put it in my little house. My
little assassin house. Okay sorry I love this game so much. How did it know? How did it know I was a
girl? Good night. Rest well. See you in the morning.
Gender norms go hands my goodness.
Ah right I don't really want to start Copernicus. We'll go buy the Pantheon.
We'll go buy this because we literally do have a I'll check the bank in case any interest is made.
Accessories clear. I can't believe it. I can't believe I get to decorate those assassins freaking
hideout with my guild crests for all my hard work. Ah. We know the target audience. Honestly
is Assassin's Creed Brotherhood a girls game? The only reason I say that is because it's like
such a good game. Like it doesn't it's like so hard to get like genuinely to get stuck in like
at any part is next to impossible. Oh I need poison guards actually.
I'm just gonna like muck about and I don't want to poison like anyone in front but I think they
need to like pass away from poison or it doesn't count because I'm pretty sure of poison quite a
lot now. Game's so good it breaks the gender barrier. Why is this one so goofy looking honestly?
Wait are you saying if it's easy to make friends? I mean I don't know. I feel like whenever I see
like a guy review a game it's always like I love the challenge of this game. I love having to repeat
the same thing like 12 times over until I got like unspanked and like I figured it out and I'm
like I just want to chill experience like make it through the story mode and have a good time
and like yeah I'm just a bad gamer that wants indie games.
Not a free game journal. I feel like Brotherhood is such a great game that boys angry.
My little cousin played it after watching me play it so there it is.
Then you gotta love Dark Souls. I mean it's basically what you- no Dark Souls is the opposite
of what I described and I know for a factoid it is because I have had the pleasure of playing
Elden Ring with the Reeflings and the truth you want the truth I don't think you can handle the
truth. I would not have been able to complete that game on my own like I just don't see how
I could have done it without all the help of the Reeflings. That's the truth you think you can handle
the truth. I'll just poison them one at a time. I think I need to wait until they expire as well
which is the biggest problem. You're just like your hand being held didn't you? What do you mean
that like all these people are being so nice to me and helping me through my game and I get to
reward them? Maybe I should do that like every time we do like a game where you guys hold my
hands like I do a reward audio for it and then like my set like when I'm you know doing the
ending part of the reward I'm like thank you for helping me thank you for helping me thank you
for over me and then then I pop. You know that's terrible I know.
Can you poison on horseback?
It says shoot. No you can't poison on horseback.
Spank in that horse jeez. I'm not gonna hang around until I need him to expire.
I wouldn't be opposed. Wait we played what? Uh Elden Ring. Elden Ring's a really good game to
carry. I think I want to carry you. It's a beautiful stream and strong ease so dumb to play.
Hey streamer I think I want to carry you.
They're all looking in opposite directions so I can maybe do two.
I can maybe do three if I get this guy. Oh no I can't they're both.
He does his hands. They'd be amazing.
Games should have some challenge though. Yeah no I do agree there definitely should be like
some consequence or else if you don't feel like any pressure to do anything then you
don't enjoy the game like it's really hard to nail what kind of dynamic that you wanted.
Like oh I'm in trouble I'm sorry. I am a naughty assassin. I didn't hate well enough.
Unless don't don't don't. Oh don't push me. Get poisoned.
Plap plap plap. Get poison get poison poison.
Everyone's getting poisoned around here. Oh please spin that pole around. There we go.
Okay I managed to replenish a ton of poisons which is good because oh hello.
You're going in the well for thieving from me. Goodbye.
Um you can come out now. It's okay I'll come get you. I did not mean to do that. I don't think
his life should have been forfeit but I mean was it kind of deserved? I don't know.
Everything that was a bit morbid I'd say I'm gonna be honest I actually didn't expect that.
Please mummy don't poison my iron brew. Have a can iron brew in the fridge.
Right it ages ago and I'm still not sipped up. I need like the perfect meal. I miss
British fish and chips so much. I'm sorry to any Aussies listening. Your fish and chips are rank.
Okay I did the courtesan. Can I poison?
Can I like poison all you guys and then push it all away so you don't do that fighting thing?
I hate when they do the fighting thing. I think if they like hit each other with
the swords it doesn't count as poison so I'm gonna try and separate them. Oh he just did it there.
No I tried. I don't want to leave the vicinity too quickly for the poison but something.
Hey I'm not gonna find it with fish and chips around here. Yeah Aussies use shark and like I think
it's called gummy shark. It's not actual shark meat it's just a fish.
How do you call Germans Scottish? Oh there we go we did the poison gourd. Rank five courtesan.
Did I say courtesans poison people now? Ladies. Am I in Australia forever? I highly doubt it.
It's very good to run a business from Australia compared to the United Kingdom but oh no you're
saying get down to me but not to this wife over here. What's he gonna say? No are you doing me?
Um yeah it's good to run a business in Australia but I can't see myself being here forever.
I've fallen from my share of rooftops. I'm waiting for my lance. Up here. He left me after our baby died.
Joined up with the Chento of Keegan. They say he kills now pushes men from buildings.
I tell them I don't believe it. The British use haddock is a delicious fish. What will you say when he comes?
Are you in Australia? Heck yeah I am. I'm doing uh I'm making a call. My death will remind him of the
man he once was. I'm gonna do a VTuber meet and greet in Australia.
I did not look at what the hundred percent thing was. Oopsie.
Hold her head a guy. You will travel you no more Madonna. Madonna. What's hundred percent?
Kill your target with a hidden blade. Why is this mission type so so perfect?
So Imburgh was well with fish and chips then. Kind of. I don't know what the best takeaway,
maybe unironically a Chinese but like a British Chinese. Oh I think I need to chase this guy
from the rooftops. I think yeah. It's giving chase from the rooftops.
What do you mean merda? Get bonked. Hidden blade hidden blade. Lock on to him at least.
Exhale don't be afraid. Exhale water. Exhale.
The only thing I despise is when you have to do like assassin. Can you come here? Yeah? Yeah?
Yeah? No. No. No. Come back. Come back. Come back. Come back. Can I knock him off?
Why are you trying to hit the ear? You know full well what I'm aiming for it. So like genuinely.
Oh goodness sake. Stop moving a bit. Just accept your death. It's over for you buddy.
Stop it. I'm actually getting teased. Stop it. There we go. My goodness.
My tummy hurt. No more food. No more have you eaten too much. Can't forget.
Have you had any encounter with the local fauna? Ah magpies. I have befriended wild magpies. Although
I saw my first snake in a cockroach. Oh my god. There's no such thing as cockroaches
in Scotland. And I met my first and a possum. Oh my god. Possum are terrifying. I don't like.
I thought they were cute. The noise they make at night is like
a very scary. Not a fan. Not a fan. Yeah. I had my first cockroach encounter and I'm like I want
to go back to Scotland right now. Thank you very much. Because oh my goodness. Possums
are harmless if you leave them alone. Yes. I accidentally ran like into one. That sounds
really dumb. But my cat escaped the garden and I had to go into my neighbour's garden.
And it was one o'clock in the morning and thank goodness I'm no in America because I probably
would have got shot on sight. Oh I'm in trouble. And it was absolute nightmare. It was freaking
so dark and I had to run around to get into my neighbour's garden and there was a possum that
was eye level on the fence. And both of us basically like both me and the possum were like
but yeah I had to dive into my neighbour's garden. I'm wondering to throw my cat back over the fence.
Yes Gimli. I'm talking about you. Don't do it again. I never want to be in that situation again.
I had to stick a letter through the freaking mailbox being like I am so sorry if you heard any
of that. Ruckus last night. That was me. No one tried to steal from you. And like I had to sign it
with my freaking address and everything. Her name is Gimli. Yes. Because she's Ginger.
She's got ginger on her so I named my cat Gimli. So when I pick her up I go that's my wee laugh.
Gimli.
Excuse me. You said well the thing what it was literally 1am and like they're creak they had the
creakiest gate ever and I'm like I'm like Gimli. Gimli get here. Gimli get here right now. Gimli.
And because she had never been outside the garden before and she got really confused and was meowing
at the door of the neighbor instead of coming back over the fence to me like I had been calling on
her for ages and I was trying not to wake up any of the neighborhoods like the neighborhood area.
Donut was the man that I met him a long time ago.
I was like Gimli, Gimli, Gimli, Gimli, Gimli, Gimli, Gimli, Gimli, Gimli, Gimli, Gimli.
Kill only Donut though. Big Donut. Where can I find you?
Thank you. Nobody. No, like unironically I had to toss Gimli back in the garden.
And yeah she's not here and the music's gonna do the thing.
I love the pickup of the music.
Oh my god veterinary care though in Australia is so fairly priced and so good.
My baby boy he ended up injuring himself on something mysterious and he had a cut on his leg
and I phoned up a vet and they were like oh we offer up a pickup service
for animals and I'm like well I don't drive so that's perfect thank you.
I don't understand how you can do that though.
Wait I need to kill all my him.
Simple.
You can bowl a cat.
What? Where are my field workers at?
But yeah they phoned up I'm like my baby boy's got a cut on his leg I don't know what happened.
Can I book an appointment? I was gonna have to put him in a taxi with me.
Wait wait wait just becoming almost.
None to miss.
Don't hurt anyone.
Excuse me good sir I need this horse.
I need the horse.
Please give horse.
Horse now.
Thank you.
Bye.
Ow ow ow.
Horse horse come.
Let me on you.
No don't hurt anyone.
Don't don't hurt anyone.
Don't hurt anyone.
Nice I'm coming in my own horse this is gonna be ridiculous.
No don't run away.
Don't run away.
I need on the horse.
Right let's go.
Okay we did it.
We're safe.
Oh we're safe.
Are they chasing?
Oh they're chasing.
Oh okay okay I've run.
Sorry sorry sorry.
I know which way to go.
Pardon me.
Excuse me.
Come through.
Uh right.
Which path does indices not normally take?
Like this one I guess.
Okay.
Have we lost them?
Like we're we're going pretty far now.
I'm still going.
Still going.
Can I go down here?
Oh we did it.
Okay I'm fine.
We took a neighborhood cat since you're going to fight in Toro Fathom.
Yeah like literally the health, the veterinary care in Australia is so cheap and good.
And they were like oh we can like pick up your animal and I'm like oh yes please.
And I was expecting like $800 or something and it was like super cheap and they were so nice
and like it was so quick into when I adopted him that I was like I'm so sorry I have absolutely
no idea what the temperament he's going to be like please be careful he might be aggressive
like I don't know how he's going to act and they're like oh he was just like a sweet little angel
and I'm like oh thank you I'm so glad.
So what happened next with Gimli?
Oh well through back over the fence and now she's not allowed outside without me being with her
because she's a silly silly sausage and gives me a heart attack.
I unfortunately live like on car roads.
Actually one thing I'll complain about Australia is residential areas don't like have a speed
limit or the speed limit is ridiculously high and I'm not being funny the speed of freaking cars
is ridiculous over here it's very Americanized sorry sorry to like be mean and stinky because
I should be really thankful like that I even have like the ability to like basically like check out
another country and type thing like I should be grateful and all that but it doesn't mean I'm
not allowed to complain so I will complain um but I'm trying to think that once hold on.
So you did literally what she did was climbed up a tree and jumped over a fence so I basically
now she didn't get hurt before anyone's like oh my god you're was it a linear whatever her name
was 2.0 or whatever no I put her back on the tree like I like shuggled her back on the tree
and then I knew she was back in the garden and then I had to run around and go back in
like in a my garden and bring her back into the house and obviously she was on time at like
she wasn't not allowed outside for a couple of days after that we know you never helped me yeah
oh sit in the chat for me while you go home you go into a car crash listen to she be you're joking
you're joking you're in a car crash you heard it here for
violor is causing people serious damage to their health you've heard it here first
I've done all the missions so we can do courtesans we can do these
the Copernacle what's our DNA percentage now 62
okay
wait the treasures count as 100% I've been ignoring the treasures
I am no was listening to she be an SUV incinerated my driver's side mirror
thank you hope you're okay did you have to like call the police I think you have to report it to
the police if you get hit and I'm gonna cry I'm gonna cry you oh okay
okay
why are they doing that okay Leonardo says 18% I think that is holding us back on the DNA
right we're doing it we're doing a Leonardo
oh no Majobi's came back
you know sometimes if you hold it it like goes away again it's coming back
uh
where's caca anon when you need him I had a really funny story for him but I don't even know if
he's here anymore and it's the one that wanted to hear me fart in the toilet I don't know if
he's still here but if he is I'll tell you a really funny story and it's really gross
hmm
yoyoing your poop but no no a little bit though I feel like oh I think I've said this before
and this is the dumbest statement I'll ever say but I feel like if you're a guy if you yoyo can you
not like stimulate your pee doing that use a smoke bomb to stun the overseer sure I can
100% that easy peasy yes I do have a stun bomb on me
locate the overseer what no comment literally like isn't that a thing that guys can do
still surprised no one said I'm doing it right now right do that and then oh we got a double
fascination at that oh the others just disappeared okay right we'll do a Leonardo
I've never felt good from well aren't you in luck I have a four-part trading series
see if it's for you and if you finish the series then and you you don't like it then
actually you were right it really is a preview
whoa that's a lot money
so
you stay away from the back door I mean I don't know if once you've done all those things
if there's really much of a point of sand in the movie other than
one three three and four yeah let's go
did she be heck on wheels not yeah I may not have even done it I know honestly
oh I think I need I think I need toilet time but it's gonna take me five minutes because I'm a
nervous poop oh I'm a nervous poop oh when I sweep for some reason like I'm flying out of me now
I've never felt more embarrassed by a streamer in my life because SUV man went what was that and
I just went listen to a podcast oh are she bees in your ears like yeah I like like spin on you
and that I'm like weren't you listening to me flying oh I think I picked like the hardest one
do do not get shot while using the bomber okay the bomb de la caca
um do not get shot while using the bomber
do not get shot so am I allowed to be spotted or is this a classic warning being detected
because desynchronization okay I need to go poopy I'm nervous I'm scared of this part of the section
do you guys want to what happens if we all take a job at the exact same time
I'm having lots of war and you make sure the the organs are already for this ball man I'm about to drop
okay I'm gonna mute I will be a few moments so do forgive me for this he
who said link up or put mods no I'm just gonna
okay I'm ready to poop
okay
I'm going to do a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little
bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of of a little bit of a little
I don't know about you lads but I keep flying over me.
I'm grabbing my cup of tea and I'm going to make a honey tea, I'll be back in like literally
a minute.
I think that was already boiling.
I'm going to make a honey tea, I'm going to make a honey tea, I'm going to make a honey
tea.
Well, I have absolutely horrific news, I've not got any tea bags left, there'll be no
honey tea for me and this has shot me, that was a moment for me to, I'm so sorry if you
dropped in on that moment, we all collectively went for the adjubi, I can't believe I'm
freaking out with tea bags, I'm so annoyed at myself, I'm going to like, the one thing
I do like about Australian supermarkets, they have big like, eh, stuff, oh my, calibration
is off, hold on, there, that's my calibration, I don't know why I was looking all the way
up, I have no idea if we're going to be able to do this, do you want people to tell you
when the other girls go live or when you ask for it, please always tell me when a girl
goes live, I can't always keep up and I suck, right, I am not to be tech tech, interesting,
if I'm not to be detected, wait what am I supposed to do though, locate the architect,
but don't be detected please, okay, um, I, there's two together, how am I supposed to
navigate, hmm, you play some games where you versus a chat and hypnotise and so you went
honestly though, I wanted to do an IQ test and then I want to chat to do an IQ test,
like we would do a poll for what the answer is and see what like the results are, I am
very confused, are they going to spot me, wait, what, I love all the bugs in this game,
full stop, I just love them all, game, don't be detected, then hmm, why is that man on
the roof, how bizarre, wouldn't work, we make you work for victory, oh no, you guys are
allowed to win, I wouldn't cheat to do it on the IQ one, but I forget it's a stream where
I make the album, where the heck am I supposed to go, I assume I'm allowed to kill folk,
I feel like I need seven bolts, am I going crazy where, is he over there, is that him
over there, I'm, I'm having a, well, I don't have a choice, yeah I was going to say I don't
have a choice, because he was coming into the hay bale anyway, lower score is better right,
I'm going to be number one, chat's IQ is room temperature, but that's why we're so good
for each other, we're so bad, am I tracking funny with you, I think, oh my tracking is
funny, I fucking hate this iPhone, for some reason, sorry that got really aggressive out
here, whenever it is horizontal, it does not track me full stop, horizontal, vertical,
no, when it's vertical it works, when it's horizontal it doesn't, but I need to charge
it while I stream, and it's awkward to put it vertical doesn't it, is my tracking being
rubbish all day, I'll just over enunciate my word, though you guys, I don't know where
this enemy is, genuinely, I guess I can do this kind of stuff, and loot the bodies, could
you get some sort of tool to grip it and hold it in there, oh, so it's on like the world's
tiniest tripod which is adorable, I'm so confused, honestly, I don't know where this person is
I'm supposed to be trying to find him, I'm going to loot these bodies and hopefully get
more supplies, because one poison, one medicine wasn't as cool, please expire so I can loot
your body, sorry, okay there we go, to be honest it's hard to tell if the tracking is
off or not, since we don't have a reference, alright let me build my webcam let's, where
is this overseer, is he like in, is he below the church or something, is he in it, is he
the one by the hay bale, he can't be, um, have I been everywhere yet, I don't know, so those
were the ones that caught me on the outskirts, is he in the center and that's why, no, what,
what, did I just, is he like walking around and I just can't tell, yeah the game's telling
me to stay in this section, I'm on podcast unless as long as it's your birthday, love
cuteness is smaller they are, the cuter they are, true, I'm, I'm one confuzzled girl,
look at that, I think we're just going to have to literally go around the map and clean
it up, because this is, use eagerness to differentiate, yeah but I don't know what to tell you, nothing
is being highlighted, oh there's guards coming, no they stopped, we're checking the hay bale,
they're like, those guards from down there coming closer or no, yeah, we will shoot them
with poison, oh like the game keeps telling me but I don't know what to tell you video
game, I've literally been to all sections of this map, wait that didn't happen, okay,
I hit him that time, I'm going to loot their bodies to get all the supplies, we'll meet
them first, closer to the larger area, is your target in the building?
more poison there, the one thing that I'll say is a bit funny in this game, NPCs will walk
into guards that are like flailing about and it's like bro, hopefully I can get more ammo
off these guys and I'm not spending more, I'm getting more poison back which is fine,
I'm spending poison, it's good to get poison back but my goodness, okay, so he does just
roam the map, okay, all those guards, I don't want to be these things because I stopped,
I didn't realize he turned back, I'm very confused with this mission so like I had to find him
walking around and there's guards everywhere, I'm going to go on the roof because there's
that rotating jewel here, there's, oh maybe a desync if he notices that people are ill
with poison, I don't know, beat up the architect, hopefully this gives me a loading point, give
me the plans right now, oh yeah, honestly me, that took so long to progress, I do apologize,
that must mean painful, right so what happens now, I'm notorious, okay I can deal with that,
I've definitely progressed to the next loading screen so again we've not failed 100%, do not
get shot while using the bomber, surely I will do this first time when I get on the bomber,
surely I will not have any issues at all and I'm not going to be frustrated with this game
mode, I'm already preparing for it, can I launch on that, oh it hits you over there, oh sorry,
I need to impair sleep right now so don't get caught, now I have the interest, surely
absolutely helping copium right, next loading point please, oh I'm at, I'm to not be detected
by the two guards that are across from each other, yeah I'm not to be detected by the two
point blank guards, I can do this if that citizen doesn't get in the way and then he will be
distracted by him, I said he will be distracted by the poisoned guy, can you, oh and now everyone's
in the way, get the fuck out of my way, Jesus, I know why they make the minstrels like that
but they've made them a little too well, okay they've made them a little too well, okay yeah
my tracking is like bugging out because it's horizontal, I despise you, there's no way
or maybe it's the iPhone, hold on, let me cook for the thing, I'm trying to see if I can stand up on it
so I have my elaborate setup from yesterday because I removed all the cups from my ring
look at the mask, when I have the perfect setup, that looks much more, okay and then we'll look
for supplies, the per NPCs, I just know we're gonna fail this and I'm gonna be so mad
because I don't know what to expect
these poison darts for distraction is absolutely gorgeous, these NPCs in my fucking way, not gorgeous
okay he's gonna start attacking, I can see the ones coming down the hill
I don't know if they're gonna, oh no, oh no they got attracted, I'm just gonna hide in here
unleash the archers, you're evening skulls, I'm nervous
I don't know what to do here
I'm just kind of waiting around, like waiting for the EI to kick in so I don't know what to do now
oh yeah, that
must have been drinking the good stuff
okay, we're just gonna poison them both again, like literally poison darts
don't be afraid to lock onto them when they can see us, no it's fine, honestly don't be afraid
no, miss, shit, we cannot be missing poison darts, no, next one, use the other guy
okay there we are, we're gonna loot these two bodies so we can refill our poison
we're taking it nice and slow, should charts start logging every bird, nah
okay these are both poisoned, again we're gonna pick up, we're just gonna take it nice and slow
you know, we don't need it too fast, just relax, calming, cozy atmosphere
but remember, don't get shot when we are in the glider and I know I'm going through these things
I'll still finish it anyway but
oh yeah, wow, you get a lot more from them, okay I'm quite happy with that
she be redirect, oh no, they're all gonna see my terrible gameplay and me getting mad now
they're gonna know I'm a terrible gamer
nice cozy atmosphere, remember the guys gagging and choking on the background, literally
I'm gonna just move a whistle through my teeth there
your gameplay isn't terrible, it's rough on the DLC stuff cause like
I don't know, there's anyone up here
oh my gosh
I've just remembered how humongous this is, we have to get up there but we have to go like
and do all this dodgy stuff constant back and forth
oh no
no, he can't see us again, he needs to forget about us like right now
he needs to like, okay
wow, that was dangerous
hold on, I think we'll be in best, get by another guard
there's one in there
yeah and he's moving out, oh there's two of them, we're investigating the bodies
I don't want to go down, I'd rather stay on the walls and go around to this tower stuff
oh my goodness, she be caught and bummer self, thank you for the wade
how is your stream, are you steaming, please drink water
please drink lots of water, my dear, we don't want any hangovers
she be and Emmy
wait, both Emmy too?
you both ended stream at the same time, oh my gosh
hi guys
oh my god, you both ended stream at the same time, I don't know maybe you should like kiss or something
please, I don't know maybe you should give each other a little kiss
if you're just like so in tune with each other
please, Emmy riddy she be, she be riddy due into cycles, please get lots of water and food, she be
don't want you having any hangovers
hi Emmy
hope you both enjoyed your stream, hope you enjoyed your stream
we are currently doing Leonardo's missions
and I'm currently debating if I'm actually capable of 100% in this game
unfortunately my answer is, it might be a no, I don't actually think I have the thingy
just guarantee the vods getting nuked, okay
guys, I'm trying to get you monetized on YouTube
right, I can get him in time, fine
him, I need this archer over here done, yeah
okay, I'm glad that looks
that's good
is that a flag over there?
I don't know, maybe just a treasure
sorry, it's fine, I'm teasing, you guys can do what you want
I need to go there?
what?
oh goodness me
what is that?
I actually think I want that guard to forget I exist
she seems so worn out, it's fine
we're playing Assassin's Creed Brotherhood 2
which is a very beloved childhood game of mine
I believe Mercy is coming online in 1, 2, 3 hours, just under 3 hours
so if you are a snippet, you are welcome to hang about till it's Mercy time
that's very, oh that guy up there, I don't like him
I think I'm gonna have to start looting bodies as well because I'm running low on ammo
so that was actually rather cute
oh what a post to be left in
POV, you're a harem
that's the position she be gonna leave you in at the end of the night
yep, no bod, it's already dead
wait, it already got a warning?
that was pretty quick
that was pretty rough, Jesus
I private it over for you, ah, I should have gone
let's see, let's do poison
oh let's not do poison again
she be making a smart move, 5 head now
this is so sad, I'm only good to see half of it
there's always more ASMR streams to come in the future, don't worry
it's not one and done
we ain't one and done around these parts
hopefully YouTube gets her stuff messed
there's a few things going on with YouTube right now
this is a very slow based mission by the way
because every time we poison, I have to wait until they're perished
and then I have to loot them and then I have to go for the next part
I don't know if I can reach him from here
just out of sight, but I need him gone
I need him gone or I can't be jumping around this tower
he's got a range of these guys, but I'm not with him
Strani, you're always streaming, are you okay?
ah, yeah, it's called
I am sharing my childhood games and I love them
and I want to share them
it's a bit more cozy the day yesterday
I was a bit, can he see me?
he can
man needs glasses
I mean, whoever will literally leave you up
true
lovely, lovely stuff
we will be taking this very easy
I am not sure how to get down
out of safety, we're going to be doing a lot of poison right now
I don't know if I can leap from there to that
and I don't want to risk it
that looks like a leap over, definitely
like that 100% looks like a leap over
they're currently poisoned below me
but I should be safe to make my
there's a lot of red there
I think this is definitely what I'm supposed to do though
a 12 and a 6 hour plus stream on your first week is awe inspiring
I just really enjoy these video games
I definitely will be focusing
please don't think my streams are all going to be 18 hours
tomorrow's needy streamer overload
I've never played it before, but it's definitely going to be a shorter stream
because I don't even know if I like it
and whenever I have the
what happens if I spin around
a beam
and a
neat poison, these two down here
not risking it
not risking it at all
we have come too far
right onto the beam
I'm just going poison route
because poison stops them from being able to see me
I'm going to loot this guy's body
because archers normally have a lot more stuff on them
cuttlefish are venomous
there is one cuttlefish that's venomous
but my ink isn't venomous
it's an aphrodisiac
it puts you under my alluring spell
what is bro doing with poison though
the lead artist for needy streamer overload
is one of my favorite artists
I'm a sucker for
oh his son
she booties
stuff
right we need to be super careful
because this is the most ridiculous
thing for trying to spot enemies
there's like guys all the way up this tower
and it's so hard to know when one's about to see you
and I'm not freaking redoing this all over again
but I'm getting scared
okay I can see one guy up there
it must be they're all on the roof
under your lure
not your resa...
you might have a streaming edition
I can't believe it
oh almost fell there
you said you might not be able to 100% it
there's a few 100%
that I genuinely don't know
and I'm worried about
not being able to do my
like I just simply cannot do it
and I can't like call
I can't tap one of you guys into the game to do it for me
so I'm still
I'm still not sure this is going to be a 12 hour stream or not
I can hear the music
how am I supposed to hurt them all at once
I don't think I...
is that a flag this way?
no what? the sun's getting further away
uh...
why?
what am I supposed to do?
no!
okay
I understand
I thought I was about to be exposed right at the end there
right
in order to 100% this mission
do not get shot while using the bomber
okay
we have been at this mission for like 20 minutes now
all I have to do is nail this off the bat
and I don't even remember freakin' doing this
I'm going to start sweating
okay
don't get shot using the bomber
why can we not get like a little tutorial first?
destroy the workshops
I can do that
it's fine
tactical camera
no not tactical
that was awful
don't ever do that again
press retreat to fire
R2
oh no
oh my god I'm going down
this is not good
oh my god I don't know the controls
I don't know the controls
oh I don't know where the closest one on the map is
it's the one...
if I take her right
I don't think I'm gonna make it
just go for the one that I'm hitting at
oh my god there's archer towers
no no no no no no no no no
how?
how were you not supposed to get hit by that?
oh I didn't even hit that tower
yeah see this is what I'm afraid of
I can't 100%
I'm under the impression I now have to redo this entire
entire mission again
I missed that again?
I'm trying so hard
I think I'm gonna have to like go further away
I don't think there's a checkpoint
I never gave an indication
wait for one
okay there we go
shoot workshop twi-
whoa whoa whoa my controller Jesus
oh please my goodness
I almost didn't make it there
alright do that
okay then do this
and I missed so that's okay
we just need to do it
go around a bit
oh well maybe we're gonna just straight up attack this one
I missed
hopefully there is checkpoints
cause this that does seem very harsh
I completely I did
I will admit I twided off
I need a fire like right now
oh goodness me
goodness gravy
they didn't even make this game easy
there we go destroyed that one
honestly this section was a lot harder on paper
I think
there
right now what?
only if you die you have to repeat whole missions
a checkpoint at the start of the bomb
destroy the bomber
where I see
speed run over there
can we aimbot it?
three two one
oh I think that was a miss
a swing and a miss
swing and a miss
hold on let's try again
oh wow
I cannot control this right now
I'm completely looking in the wrong direction
I
bruv
bruv bruv
yeah
okay
controls please thank you
oh no there's more
okay okay it's okay it's okay
I'm just trying to set a fire along the way
I am hello game
respond please
I missed and it's okay
it's okay
we're gonna bomb that get a bit of speed
whoa
whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa
hello game
relax
game
what on air I thought I don't think
whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa
whoa whoa whoa whoa
bruv
game
what was that velocity
it was completely unnecessary are you sure
game
put me up
put me up put me up put me up
I went ups so I can aim
a miss
oh wow
I actually hit that
wow
that was crazy
I don't think I was supposed to fly that high that was
Oops played out of order
Where's this a horse? Okay?
turn around
Every now and then I get this. Oh, I was too early. Hmm. Maybe there then
Yes
Yeah, okay. That wasn't bad. That wasn't horrific
Wow
That was a crazy boost. I don't think I was supposed to go that high. I think the game mathematics
It's weird
Okay
There's cool guys don't look at back at explosion
Well, we did it
That was not easy. That was not fast
I am going to open it up in the dna sequence to see if it's like replay that section
If it is then a hundred percent, it's still on board if it's not then a hundred percent
It's like a much less likely because this is getting hard
This is getting tricky
It's tricky tricky tricky tricky
Rock around rock around just right on time. It's tricky
The whole thing I was worried it would say that
I was so worried it was gonna say that
Look we'll do what we can
We'll finish the other like Leonardo missions and that
But yeah, this is gonna be I don't
That has just like dramatically decreased the odds of being able to a hundred percent it like to go through all of that section
Again, like I was taking my time like poisoning guards along the way so I didn't have any issues
that
That one attempt and we got hit immediately that was the only time we got hit as well
Which was just so unlucky because I wasn't sure what the controls were
Like that was so rough. I just jumped us. Come on that horse
And that is why late game gives more check literally that is so
Um punishing
Wait, can you a hundred percent this game without being online?
Yes, the dna sequence is what we're a hundred percent
It's like doing a hundred percent of the memories and stuff. I'm currently
63 percent, which isn't bad at all
however
I was under the assumption the game was a bit more forgiving. However, we've just kind of discovered
The replayability checkpoints aren't necessarily all there on certain missions and that is just so
I don't know. I don't know
Let me see that
Okay, go. Yeah. Yeah. Remember trying for
platinum to give
Achievement wise
I don't know if you need a hundred percent dna for the achievements
War machines are infamous for a reason. Yeah
There's a difference in a hundred to give a hundred percent achievements. Um
So, yeah, I thought we could maybe attempt to a hundred percent the dna sequence, but yeah
It ain't looking good. I mean, how long oh, it's already been six hours. What the heck?
Okay
Yeah, I didn't like I thought I was only gonna
What was I supposed to do?
Use a kick attack against over here. I literally thought
Um
If you don't do it now move these kids should be a thing you come back to at a later time
I think so. I think three days of like Assassin's Creed brotherhood in a row is a bit
It's a bit too much, but I'm perfectly happy to like come across the save file. That's not a problem
Um
Oh, no, no, we're not doing this
We're not doing this horse feature, but leave me alone. You're scaring me
Oh
Oh, whoa, I actually dodged that successfully, but the game said no, so
I true love with this game with a hundred percent. Oh steady on have you seen what the requirements are on some of the missions? Oh
That a wee bit of a
That a wee bit much for me honestly like I love this game
But I think, um
Definitely
Wouldn't mind coming back to to attempt it, but I think three days of Assassin's Creed brotherhood in a row
Maybe ain't the choice. We'll try and needy streamer and it'll be a smaller stream tomorrow, which means I can go get the
Sweets that I'm using for that hand cam stream. I need to like prepare for it and saw
I don't even know what to wear. He he I'm actually gonna have to put clothes on for one
Uh, I don't even know
And one achievement requires you to reach level 50. Oh, yeah, no, no, not those achievements like the dna
Are we going up?
cancer crime, which we
Have to is a strong word
Open one of the first three game the bourgeois have constructed a deadly naval war machine base on the in our design
It must be destroyed before chesery
Good dreams. Talk to Eduraro
Ed Uardo
I assume this is a don't get caught. It's giving don't get caught. Yeah
That only
I'm just a little fish
No, I'm a fish. You didn't see me
I'm just a fish a fishy fishy fish
Swimming in the deep canal
Fish fishy swim
Um, actually
If you hold the block button with the sword ball in the horse coming out, you can knock the raider then
Oh, it's it was gasman prayer me
Clothes strong a have six honestly
Baby, it's you
Hello, I would like you to take me on the canal. Oh
You are the assassin, am I right? You must stop chesery. I will help you. Let me take you to them. Oh
Grazie
Like I said, I chose life today. Thank you
Uh interacting with the gondola will cause desynchronization
I
I scratch my nose
How taller you 162 centimeters
um
taller than
Smoke bomb disables guards assassin or sleep before it wears off
Um, excuse me, but the actual phone am I not allowed to kill? Oh, so why not?
Uh
The gate
There's nothing oh, he just jumped on I saw that I thought I saw that
Oh
Okay, okay, okay, we're getting taller than a smoke ball
What's that banana freedom uh five three
I've not played assassin for the origin
You're like me also have issues wearing clothes. It's just no fun me. Okay, something's a fun
Mmm
I just put I just pushed that man in the water and he drowned
I will say one thing though, if you're a gondola pusher and you don't know how to swim
Isn't that a bit dangerous? Isn't that a bit silly?
I don't even realize I was supposed to be up here
Whoa, wait, why can't he see me? I thought we purposely put these beams here so you can't get seen by the guards below
Oh
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa my part in my bag
I'm gonna do that just so you know, where is it? Oh
Pitching wasn't the problem is that you touched the boat. Oh, I can't believe it finding Nemo. I touched the boat
How many slower me
Oh
The freaking twat from across the street saw me
Hey
Yeah, you do that on the way again
You'd be surprised I was in the Navy and only passed the swim test because
Proctor wanted me to go home. Jeez
And
I think if you're Scottish you have to learn to swim like you're forced to go to swimming
Yeah, let's just run ahead of this guard because he can't see me at the corner of his eye, but I get out of range
Which is good
Gondola logging
I've only got five poisons
It probably just
Man, I've got 19 crossbow bolts. They're quiet. I don't get
So it's all good
Uh, right
That's fine
It's fine. That's fine. So who
Okay, so this time the freaking guy doesn't notice me. Yeah, that's what I thought me
Doesn't even spot me this time sting
We'll set the stall and we go
Oh, I need to go up
Uh, so you're gonna see me he is so I kind of need to deal with you. Sorry if you're in my way son
You're in my way. You're in my way. You're in my way. You're in my way
We
Oh
Poison him just to get around the corner successfully
The bluetooth device is uh, why did you not go up?
Go up
Oh another there we go
How's your gaming going? Uh, we mlg gamers out here. Um, unfortunately
I believe the 100% will not happen this stream it I did not I did not anticipate
How hard this game is
Because I've never attempted it before like I genuinely don't know how it goes
Um, right. I'm gonna poison him and the other
Oh, hey, where where where
I almost deseed but I think I hit a checkpoint
I don't
I got so now I'm gonna just go in
I don't even know how you saw me. I'm up here. They're not supposed to be able to see you from up here
Yeah, like that guy really there's like more cool. Oh that
Get me in the war. No
I like that
Oh
Okay, that's pretty good detail
No, no
It feels literally drowning right now. He needs to catch a breath of freaking air because I keep making him go under
Oh, goodness me. I don't think we make a
Oh goodness me. They're not making this one easy, aren't they?
Oh
He took a sword out. I heard it, but he needs to breathe or else he pops up for too long. He needs to breathe
I need to breathe just thinking about how long he's holding his breath honestly. Um
Please don't do the animation where you can't breathe. Please
Oh, we did it
Oh for goodness sake, there's more
Breathe
One
two
Reeve
One
Okay, I think maybe I can kill those ones because that was really rough, right? So that was too much bright olden
Any breathers in chat we stay driven
I'm going to scotland into the whoa. Wait, how far back are we?
Huh
That's pretty far back
Okay, like I did here
Oh, I've just wasted so much time dropping myself back here by here. I'm breathing is overrated honestly
I
Know the game's telling me to swim under this but like
So much freaking time like that guy is going so fast and as we gondola like he knows that I'm literally trying to swim behind him in time
he's such a lot like
You know, I'm freaking behind you. Slow it down
Literally, I'm trying to like silently swim is not even possible
I think if I just hang off the pier and assassinate him, this is the best way forward for this
Sorry mate, but time's up
Okay, yeah, that's far more easier. I just need to do it to the other guy on the pier. Sorry
Oxygen addicts honestly can't get enough of it. You're so greedy, huh?
Okay, let's die
And then breathe and then die and then breathe and then yank
Ezio, please do not go on the platform when it comes to assassinating freaking gods
Ezio
You knew fine. Well, I was asking you to pull him into the water
Not get on the platform
Where the freaking AI is so sensitive and on the lookout on freaking
You freaking freaks, right? I'm just a sir air assassinating spam. Honestly
Game knows. Oh and he's gonna
He's gonna
And I'm out of honey tea and I'm sad that I can't have a freaking honey to
Gonna have to go to the shops
Right, I can take my time to this segment. I've never been caught out of here. So let's not go caught in there
Um
We swimming
Any swimmers you got any swimmers for me? I don't know
Shopping
I feel like if I fast swim I might alert him
Now if I am correct
What the problem was is I assassinated here. I need to hang off and then assassinate. Yeah
But you knew exactly what I wanted to achieve it. So so don't even look at me. Okay, right don't interact with the gondola
I
Me swimmers
Nice choice
All right, let's
Why isn't gulping I'm not even diving me
Okay, hang off the ledge, please
One assassination, please
Back in the war
dive
Dive over the ropes. Don't be afraid. Don't be afraid of the ropes. She be uh, is very talented
Wow
Oh
My life flashed before my so I'm gonna say ropes. Hey, she's still alive
Especially not past that drunk. I don't know if you're drunk. I don't know how to. Oh, I was not supposed to be okay. Detections now permitted
That's all I want to see baby
Detections now permitted yee-haw time to perish boys
Ha
Yeah, yeah, yeah, you want some of this
Actually, I need just disarm guards and kill them with their own weapon
So let's do that. Oh, give me that sword, please. Thank you very much. And then drug
And we did that automatically drop object and then we're gonna do it again. Can I steal your weapon?
Oh, not fighting over the weapon
Okay, there we go. He wouldn't like over honestly. I wouldn't like all my wife into if I had one
Now I'm chilling cleaning up and watching because I love easy to do
Azura said she watched like she played it as well. And me said she got it as gifted, but she never played it
So
Good night those who rest. Thank you for hanging
I love when I can be detected. It's so fun
Come on who wants to first then
Okay, there you go. Oh, no, don't grab me who wants to first you
Take that and this and you're another one
Oh, I love the crisscross kill is so cool. Oh wait, I'm actually gonna look because those were pretty high
guard
Oh
These guys act like they understand you're the main character on a little
Uh, okay, I thought I got more poison holdings
Uh, once we've done other Leonardo missions, I think we'll do all of the factions because I want to dress up my assassin's creed gild
gild
So it's girly pop, you know what I'm saying
How'd I get up there? Or did I just leap?
Did I do a leap? Oh, that was a big leap. It's so on the side. I don't think you should have been able to do that
But hey, ho
You can't see me because you're dead by the time you process. It's me
Daddy's home
Let's look he may have poison on him
They accepted that they were dead
I'm gonna go see you in the morning. Oh, that's hilarious. What fuckers saying that now literally good night. See you in the morning
I'll still be online sweet dreams
Have a good rest. I'll still be here on assassin's creed on my knees
Drive home
They're more like guidelines than actual rules
Oh, I do love this game
So that's fine
That reason I did go watch and I get him out of it live
Oh
Let's see if you can fight your master's hand shall we oh
Oh, what's this? I don't whoa. Whoa. Whoa row. What switch?
Oh
Wow, I have to switch between rowing and and aiming. I mean, I guess I comprehend that but sheesh
Oh, we're taking down ships
Boo Templars stinky Templars, uh switch fire
Oh my gosh, that's so cool. Okay sales destroyed that makes sense
I only hit one of them there. I'm getting rigged right now
All done. Bye. Bye. Okay. Okay. I like it. I'm digging it. I'm digging it
Oh my gosh, they're like ragdolling off the ship
Okay, that was cool. I enjoyed that
Yo ho ho it's a pirate's life for me
A tweedily dum a tweedily dee tweedily weedily wee. I don't know the words. I just know the shiny. Oh, yo, yo
Okay, it looks like there's just three and I have plenty of health. So that's fine
Give me fuel in my fire give keep me burning
Put some oil in my land eye-free
Can I do it from here? Mmm, baby, just gonna clean that
Possibly can I do all three though?
I think I'm gonna have to row a bit closer to this one at the back here. I think that's it. That should be good
No, I didn't hit it. Oopsies
Oh
I don't think you can go back through so we're just gonna
Do a thing
You're now notorious guards are on high alert. I should hope so
Because I'm still here me it's you. Oh, they knocked me off my my gun
I don't even know what you're doing. Hold on lads. I need to rotate before I destroy his
Do give me a second
You just need to rotate. I actually don't think I can hit it from this distance. You know that
Ow, I'm
Wait, whoa, what's happening?
Okay, hold on. Hold on. We need to like do a big old circle around because
That I'm like too close to even hit this stuff
Honestly black flag for all take for real
Going reverse so so can you go backwards? I don't even know if I can
I don't try it. We're just in the old spin around
Did that hit I hope so
Almost there we go beautiful beautiful
And last but not least let's not get too close now. Let's not get too close
Still got some momentum
Oh
One more rule should do it get us front row seats to this pirate ship going down
Oh, they're hurting me they're hurting me
Just a range hold on
I'm like just there no more. Oh you guys are hurting me
You're giving me a booboo
Just just a range that was so close
Right a little bit of a push
I just don't want to get too close to the point where I can't even freaking aim
There we go we got there we got them
It literally is your tank in all the arrows. Okay, that was kind of for me. Take the way they are jumped off the ship
However, they don't want you on you. Honestly, there's literally cannonballs
Literally be a BRB. Sorry. I can't aim at your shills. Let me just do a little spin around. Oh
Oh, we're shooting at ourselves
Wow
Oh
We actually go 100 sink for that. Okay
I used to love this game then you have fantastic taste because this is my number one game of all time and I suck at it
New
Right, hold on. Is there one more Leonardo mission? Yes. Okay. Okay. Okay
Uh, how are they always on the opposite place?
Right, we're finished this Leonardo and then we'll get the gales faction
In
Tank tank tank you are good at sucking
Sorry, I'm making an animated shot of your reference sheet for the meme tag
Should I uh bring in the tweet?
Um
I don't know if when it comes to memification of something you don't have to credit the original rs
I don't know. What do you guys think you're probably better know than me like
I did credit her like right under the
Thingy so like people know it is by her under the reference sheet like at all times. I don't know
These hay bales were soaking
So
One of the games are the most uh called dynasty warriors ac brotherhood was the last game I truly played in the series
Yeah, revelations was all right
but
It wasn't brotherhood
If I had to rank them it's brotherhood then ac2 and then revelations for exo storyline
I went on an adventure trying to beat up all oh to beat all of this asca games, but I stopped at syndica. Hmm
I think I've played assassins creed three maybe unironically three times. Um
It's just no fun
ACR had uh fucking turret defense literally the turret defense
Do slash credit. Yeah, maybe do slash credit just so it's not like
Bothering but the credit is there for people who do want to
Yeah, people say they love black flag I struggled so much to get into it
But I'm wondering if it's just because I'm like a little cry baby because ac wasn't like in the series anymore
Which is very plausible. I wouldn't I wouldn't mind to try and get black flag one more big hood. Uh
Um
But I just
Really seem to struggle with the controls, but it's probably because I'm doing the well
I've already played assassins creed. So I don't need to sit and read the controls. Well, obviously they have changed the controls
So
I'm you've been a quiet boy, baby
Valhalla
I wish they would make more like story multiplayer games like
It takes two
It's like such a good story thing
And I would absolutely love to play games like that on stream and be like, okay after the first chapter
We'll get someone else in okay next chapter. We'll like get someone else in but like they just don't need to do that. They just don't need to do that
It's annoying
So annoying
I can't believe I can't play video games the exact same
Exactly the way I want to play them
It's such a baby
Kill the template overseer to recover map use the pistol a
I can do that
Oh
No, yes, no, yes
Yeah, I was gonna see you sure you want to fake this. Oh wow, it's always you guys that want to fake stop this
Hawkins and not really I'll see if I can loot a smoke bomb back
I've been having a blast watching a veteran in a newcomer play the hero
That oh, yeah, the halo campaign is gonna be playable
Okay, last one question mark, I think
You
That's the other mission
Halo 3 plugin
Is it like safe to do a halo campaign?
That would be really cool to do a refling. It's not gonna lie. I'd be pretty hyped for that
But I don't know how safe it is to like add people
Because I don't think I can just instance and have you guys in
It would be pretty pretty cool to like I don't is it joe only or is it four man?
Favorite game combat of bill is it evolved or yeah or evolution
Oh my gosh, it's john halo from fortnight
Lean out his tank is an ambitious and devastating war machine capable do not take any damage well in the tank
Yeah, good luck for that. We're not in the fun
Have name poison which is decent
Yeah, we're not doing that. Um, literally everyone's getting poisoned. I don't care
We have name the wash to bought some more at a healer
Yeah, maybe if it's safe to add people like on halo then
You could do playthroughs of that, but I guess you
We could only do a mission by mission. So like we would do one mission and then
Kick out and then add and then next mission
You know
We see nothing
How did you guys not sure it's a poison dart so it's supposed to just be like a little swing
And no one knows
Literally poison is so peefer like when it comes to don't be detected because you can walk right in front of them and
Obviously the crossbow does the exact same thing
Yeah, poison's cool
Oops. Sorry. Sorry. Oh
I was pulling down my sleeves. I'm getting uh, that's right. I'm wearing a hoodie
You'll never guess why
Wait, how am I supposed to get
I
Love how as soon as you go sideways, they just don't care anymore. They're like and
Beat up the architect. Oh, okay
Hello
What are the plans for the weapon? You're so aggressive. I feel like goodness. You just ask before beating up
I am not sure
But you need three people to work. Come with me. They know we we captioned three soldiers
They're in a cell across from the plans. We will help you. We're helping people. Yeah
Go home
Uh checkpoint reached amala to be seen yet
No
This music so dramatic
You can go first
Sucks to suck. Sorry, but if I'm gonna have to bear
Uh, we could do two poisons here just to be doubly sure
Uh
Oh, it probably does. Can you know I really
Oh my god, that alert him. No
I need this guy to pair
Stop hurting and then in order to unsheathe my
Right, you're next
You're freaking next now that I can see you. Jeez. There's such a pain in my butt
Not the good kind
You're next
You're all done and everyone's perished and my ankles are sore, but
Here we did it
First thing I checked was she's still screaming for me to do it. No, I would have gone the 14 hours, but it didn't work
Three of the mercenaries can I still be can't be spot?
Which
Uh
So anyone even here
Doesn't look like it. Hi mercenaries. Hello. Where is Dabin? She's machine. Follow us. They have hidden the path, but we discovered the entrance
Do you come lads
Eh three mercenaries. Oh not two
Follow and protect them. Uh, well, maybe if they didn't jump right in front of the enemies, then sure
You frick wait, wait, wait, you're done fart. I'm farting
You're done
Oh, it's good to see me
Hopefully they can actually fight a wee bit. No, why are you fighting one of them guys? There's
I've got them in the oh and yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Stop it
Ah hate when they do that right where are you taking me?
Step eight riddle fart in the guard spaces
Get him first get him first. No, you missed him. You were supposed to get the other card right right. We're farting again
Oh, I should have got that guy first actually
Oh, and he's right around the corner. I'm just attracted to the tent. Please just perish your one HP in a freaking dream
Uh, and it's not even registering my kicks lovely and that guy's getting beaten up by a brute
Yeah, they're done. Oh
Now looting time for another fart bomb because
We're needing them. I've got one. Okay. I actually got one needed
Yeah
For a surprise assault on sigilia, we will stop the attack
We need to open the gate. I will find a way
You guys hold still you just wait for me
A little bit parkour a little bit parkour momentum
Okay, there we go open for you open sesame
Did I just say open sesame
Remember that time I got asked about open sesame
And I said open cumin
Good
I don't know why my brain blank
I think it was the way the question was worded
The bridge can I lower the bridge? I guess
Open sesame or open cumin. I know which one sounds better than me
Uh
Oh
The way you record that literally my brain was like recalling memory memory loading memory loaded
It's open cinnamon
Whoa
Music
Oh my god, hello
Can I run people I must be able to run people where there's no way in heck
Oh my god, this is adorable
Oh
Yeah, POV come take that and this you stinky stinky pins and that
Oh, this is like so cool. Sorry. I love this POV
Oh, maybe not
I don't know what's behind
I assume that's what hurts me if I take damage. I don't know. Maybe I'm maybe a little hundred percent of it
Oh, that's unlucky. Oh well
Hmm. Oh, sorry. That's a lot easier to tell what's coming up. Okay. I'm sorry. I have to change camo angle
Uh, I apologize
After the hundred percent are you squiddin me right now? Oh, thank you for the tip. What did you see?
Ah, hold on. I'm destroying things wait, wait
Thank you for the tip tiny funny
Ah, why are you? There's no way someone is standing up to a tank. You have to be crazy to stand up to a tank
Do you did they even do damage?
Wow
Oh, so you can dodge
But let me pause because uh, I don't want to miss that don't know because I'm really dumb and I'm gonna forget
I don't want to forgo
No way. Okay
Tiny spany goes. Hey, Australia. I'm back from work. Well, first of all, it seems like I've tank tank. Yeah, I got tank tank
Thank you for the tip. I appreciate it
Oh, man, just tank that whole cannonball
I need help setting up alerts they barely work
It's a bit of a nightmare to instrument elements, but once you get it set up, you never have to change it again
And you can set up custom
things like if someone
Donated like 69 dollars for example, you can get it to do. Are we going in a battle dome? Yes. Yes
Oh my god tank battle dome
Take this and this
Hold on. I'm reloading and this
Is oh my god, I love tank battle dome. This is amazing
More tank battle dome more tank battle dome. It should be a game mode or something
Let me in
This is why I think of your factories take this capitalism
Um
Tanks tank battle dome
No, no, you're not allowed in the tank. You're not allowed in it tank battle dome tank battle dome
Tank battle dome. I'm stuck on the
Cylinder box tank battle dome tank battle dome
Oh, oh no, no, no, no, no, wait, wait, wait. Let me in. Let me in. Let me in. Let me in. Let me in
Okay, there we go
Tank the battle dome battle dome battle dome battle dome
Yeah, I don't know how I'm gonna feel sink that I'm not gonna lie
I ain't going there's no way I'm 100% we can try and layer
Streams, but uh, yeah, there's no shot. I'm doing it tonight
Arrivederci
Little tank
I wish I could keep you
I see we're surreal for that. That was fun. I like tank battle dome
Just don't take damage five head
Some of the ever played the game modded before me who mods it so I can't take damage sucking because there's no damage hits
runs
Some of the freaking
100% are a bit outrageous, honestly
Rest builders who have to go if you need to go sleepy. Bye. Bye
Stroney, I'm up for almost 36 hours. I'm gonna get some shy. How are you? Oh my god, that's dangerous
Definitely get some rest my goodness
And yes, we will have a wonderful stream
It's news I spread that all my inventions have been destroyed
The disarray allowed me to work on something just for you
What is this story underwear to drift slowly from any height? It is not as cumbersome as my flying machine
You can take it everywhere
Okay, I think I know what we do with that
I think I know what we do with it
Uh
99% sure I know what we do with it. Y'all don't mind if we go do it right now
That was Leonardo da Vinci, you're right. You're not wrong. You're right. Oh, maybe I could have gone off that surface. Oh well
Um
I think it's just one of the guild requirements
To use the parachute
Whoa. Oh, there's a bank actually. I'm gonna take my bank money out because it looks cool
I can find the bank
Good evening. Good afternoon, mr. Bankman
Can I have my landlord simulate? Whoa? Where the heck is this bank?
Oh, it's out. Can I have the landlord simulator part of this game?
Is he counting coins? Why is he leaning over like that? He looks so insidious like volume
My coins
12 never came so mean as we just went away lol
Oh
Hello bank. I was like one million. I want one zillion dollars
We're it we're it
Right next we're gonna do challenges
To get our guild
To play decoration to play room decoration
So I've done landlord simulator. We're now doing room decoration
Uh and then after that
I think we actually have done like the main we're gonna take some of the layouts of this place
He actually just gave you sheets to take it's it's his laundry. He's like here it's all for you, buddy
Why not jump with me and why not jump with me? That's such a smart. I wonder if he only says that line
If you jump here
Butcher, it's not a butcher. Why do you keep saying butcher? I don't know
They both begin with letter b
So
Yeah, maybe that's why instead of blacksmiths I say butcher
Up next animal crossing decorating rooms
I
Personally will never stream animal crossing
I don't know if I why what whoa, they boarded me out
Ah
bridge
Like I don't know if I can make uh animal crossing fun
like
Maybe it's um
I don't know. I couldn't make it fun. I don't mind watching other people play it
But me I'm like I ain't that creative to make it in our game
I love all the games that start with ac on full
Right, so I guess the only way to get back into the castle is this way from now on
Whoa, we have over a hundred thousand forums
Uh
Right I can
Can I walk through that gate? No
That would be too easy. I wonder actually probably post game. They should actually open that gate
I said what said because like chaseries no longer a thing
Yeah, okay, so I've got a dm
I'm getting nervous. I'm like, oh no, is there something wrong with my babies if I've got a dm
Everything is cute
Oh, we have the thumbnails for our first group collab
And that is what I knew how how interesting I'll let it be a mystery
Rest well those who have to go. Thank you for hanging
Uh mercy is going live and two minus
one hour and 45 for
of
How the heck did I get up? I've completely forgotten all over again
Just go straight up like that. I guess
I do have my assassins. I suppose I can just signal them to go get rid of them
Yeah
Wait, wasn't there
This way over here
Do me sick
Uh
Relax hen
Why are you moaning about the place my goodness gonna alert the guards?
Good night. Sleep well those who need to sleep. Good morning. Those who are good morning
We should get me acting up a little I don't know what that was
Okay, this is what I was on
Let's do you
No, that guy actually can see you here if you get really unlucky, but you know
Morning, then uh, Europe's waking up
Whoop whoop you're coming to Europe
Okay, yeah, okay, the assassin signals being able to that is like
It's 3 a.m. In Europe. Oh, I'm a bit early for european streamers. I'll pull it out
Can I not go up there if I go up at the next one? I don't want to walk and go too far
Okay, it's the next one I go up
I need to go down in order to go up
Europeans perishing right now trying to
Wait, I'm losing it
Yeah, go down to go up. Okay, I'm starting to kind of remember but
So I was three a.m. somewhere
Last and ESP
I have no idea what time zone I'm like perfect for
But then again, am I technically not perfect for all time zones if I stream really long, huh?
Yeah
I don't think we're doing a 12 hours before anyone is strapped in
So some people will be relieved to hear that we're not doing another 12 hours at the spotting home
Uh, I think when we do Eldon ring it will be a few back-to-back 12 hours
Yeah, you fit all time zones, huh
If I had a healthy sleep
You'd be perfect for New Zealand
I thought it was 4 a.m. I was sorry. I didn't have my wife. No
Sorry, I'm not paying attention. I'm Jerry chat. Why have you got your
Put away the thing all my things glitched out. It's like
What are you doing? It's yeah
Oh, that was kind of badass
You know
Something's not add not pure that was that was no my assassin. What are you doing lady?
Classic woman moment can't make up her mind. That's terrible. Don't don't make yourself
Don't do that. That's my name
He is too gay
Oh
We're doing it. We're doing the thing
What was on the wrong side my sassen still haven't despawned they're freaking out. I don't like it
Ray
So I don't mess this up. How do I tell the parachute to come out?
Uh, I'm being papaga. How do I tell the parachute to come out?
Dad just launch and press x
Right, I don't I don't want to go that way because that won't activate the jump
Yeah, they the assassins are really struggling should prompt do a flip. Okay
What we did go to go that way
No point in going in the back in the street
Uh, uh, whatever the prompt is bloody hope it comes up because
It is not on the wheel
Oh, there we go. Oh, thank god, right. I need to do like a ton of distance. I guess I'll just go over the war
I was really worried that prompt wasn't gonna come out
I think I need to glade like 500 meters
Uh, am I gonna make the glade?
Am I gonna make the glade? Hello
Oh, am I not gonna make it come on pop pop pop pop
No, I don't want to claim it again. Please pop. What was that supposed to do?
Why did that all pop? I was supposed something was supposed to pop there not the achievement
What was supposed to what did I do wrong?
I wasn't assassins
Was it thieves because they're agile?
Glade and a cumulative total of 500 meters. I'm not to turn at all
Okay
No, I hope you guys have the same patience for me because I need to do that all over again. I don't know
Cumulative
All right, I'll just do it again because I should pop then
Just do it multiple times. Yes, right. We're gonna zoom it because at least I know exactly where to go
Wait
You can do it cheeky from time
I thought you could do it in one jump for some reason
There's not a star in heaven that we can't reach
If you're trying
Oh, I'm breaking free
I can't remember the rest of it
Does it still a parachute? Yeah, I have four more inventory
Ah, all the guards have been spawned. I can't believe it. I can't believe this castle is full of guards
Shorting behavior
Get out. Anyone wants you here? Oh, my ankles. I didn't take any fall damage. Okay
I love your sit. Yeah, you're like when I burst into scots. I'm with my wee accent
I should do a scottish song cover. I don't know what to do. I wanted to do an m&m one
But I was like, I don't know if it's like bordering on cringe
I was like, I don't know what m&m song I wanted to do. Well, what a fun effort all
I've got
You got any clue what's going on? Do you? No, you didn't. You've spawned. That's all right
You threw me. I don't know what one to do
I'm beginning to feel like a wee bit of a rap god
I don't know what I'm doing
Yes, who's back back back back again again
Strony's back back back
Tell a friend. Oh
Everyone report to the dance floor
It's your season to be butt squeezing. That made me snore. I'm so sorry
Touch my body. I mean, was it boy? Just touch my body. I mean girl. Just touch my body
Because this is the part where the rap breaks down. No one moves. No one makes a sound
I'm just mixing into a ton of different songs. I think
Okay, that was very lucky you can actually go backwards
Are you a big fan of him? No
Not like
Oh, I know like all the albums and stuff like it's just the goofy songs. I like it. I can't believe it like the
I love Scottish Eminem
Like the
That one's good
The spaghetti on this shirt, bro, does vomit on a shirt mom spaghetti
I'm a jukebox
Okay, now we need this as a carry, okay
Oh, there goes gravity. Oh, there goes a rabbit. That's not the lyrics. You're teasing me
Scottish Kendrick Lamar win
I am the one the only one don't need a gun to get respect up off the streets
My enemies your enemies we wet them up like a canteen. Hey
Well, the head is straight
Hey
The day that I bet I don't know the words. I don't even know if that was Kendrick Lamar. I'm gonna be honest
No, that was dental what no
Wait, hold on
Hold on brain farming sitting here repeating you to work on my Scottish accent
I really know many other
right
I was in the 212 on the uptown a
You know, what's up or go to you? That's not really
500 accumulative meters 500
Accumulative meters. I don't want to fly up off that freaking building again
500 accumulative meters, please
I can't believe it
That's it. Put the tunes on we're rapping in scots
Because how on earth was that not 500?
Accumulative meters
Accumulative meters. I only ask for 500
meters
Talk to my assassins because it's so eatless
Go
We suck at rap battle you want us to rap battle each other honestly
All right, right. This is gonna be really obviously kind of spoilers. I should be here
Well, it's not really spoilers because it would have to be discussed anyway
I really thought it would be fun to like have distracts made like make distracts on each other
like so obviously they'd be like
Strony cuttles can't even see your name right because your Scottish
You know miss
I don't know how to do that. Like I would have to unegronically commission someone to like
This each other, but I think like a diss track on each other would be so funny
Like I know it's brain dead, but it's like, I don't know. I just find that content like funny like interact with each other in that
kind of way words. Yeah, like
She be cotton bum. We're like
Pretending to be our mom
Oh
You know because
You know, she's a mill, but
Uh, she hasn't spawned in a child from her loins like oh
Like oh what this what this but I don't know how like this tracks work. I don't know how you make them or anything like that
Um and like azura duly more like azura duke. Oh
I mean be zoom more like I mean your brother's dead. Oh
Oh
Acy snow paws more like a brat with just claws. Oh
This is awful
Mercy modest. Yeah, nothing. Yeah, your dress wear isn't muddy modest at all. You're just like you dress like a slag. Oh
Like how do you make this tracks? I don't know
Huh?
Oh
That didn't even rain
I just don't know how like how do how do people think of it like you have to go right away and right? So
I was like that. I don't know if you've seen the meme where it's like you're deadly
Your dad like snails out of the garden the scruffy
Oh
Like that's how I would end up doing a distract because I feel so much pressure to like say something
That's like
It just doesn't make any sense like
I just don't know how people come up with like actually like, you know how epic rap battles is like so good like
Who's rap flows the dopest Marilyn Min roses
Upthrown pharaohs like opposers like Moses or something like that
um
Like that is so good. And I'm like, how do people who've neared that we can do epic rap battles vtuber style. Come on
I'll stop reading my mind literally though
Literally though
I said
Yeah
Yeah, they spend more times on the like get idea of
Maybe vtuber should do rap battles
But like the problem is I don't have any music or lyrical thing
So I would have to like go out and commission to do it and then I would need to grab vtubers
I'd be willing to like let us diss each other like
Oh
I don't even know how I would diss myself
Oh, I don't know
I'm probably like oh schizophrenic personality disorder. Oh, but you're like
That's probably how you get me. She's been streaming seven hours. I sleep. Heck yeah, yeah, right
repeat after me
500 accumulative mirrors 500 accumulative mirrors
500 accumulative mirrors
accumulative mirrors
500 please
Because I don't want to I don't want to do that anymore
I'll probably do something else if we don't hit it this time and that's okay
But we're asking for 500 accumulative mirrors
Yay, we did it. We did it. Okay. It takes three times to jump off to get it. Okay
Well, let's do a cheeky ear assassination. Oh, I can't I'm hurt bones
Sorry, just dropping in for the third time today. Oh, I just looked up my own skirt there
We did it. We did it right now. We need to figure out what on earth these guilds want from us
Uh, let's see guild challenges assassins like fully done. Yeah, okay. Okay, so
Cheeky plant we cheeky flash right brutes killed scaffolding by guards paypal guards
The paypal guards are back there. Um
Guards killed while on horseback
Guards on horseback air assassinated double assassination
Five guards disarmed and killed with their own weapon. I'm gonna be honest. I've actually already done one of that
I know for a fact have have a five-man kill streak. Mm. Okay. Is there anything easier?
Oh, we've actually done quite a lot evade enemies using the crowd or other hiding spots
Enemies stationed at a guard post while using a crossbow. I actually know how to do that. Um
Horses belonging to guards
Common-deared without killing the rider and guards killed in a smoke bomb, right? We'll do that right now because we can do the smoke bomb
Hello
Oh
Right take your time it seal the name
Right, and then I'm going to get rid of this one. Oh, well we're going to get double assassination and then I'm going to take his sword
Oh, he can't he's not weak enough sugar
Uh, right we did the smoke bomb which is fantastic. Um
Um
7.68
Is that actually
No, I killed actually I did the coppers kill that terrible
Kilty-kilty cold bum. Did you know when you were killed you're not supposed to wear any
Beaks under it
Hmm
I need to write these on a note. I think I had to
Uh
I think about yeah
This is like so much right the papal guards are
Actually back across the bridge, you know that
Excuse me. How about your horse? Oh, thank you. I'll call him on
Um
What I am just you from the other girls oh I answered oh I answered that but it's a bit inappropriate
Right here these are where these guards these ones spawn
So we're going to need to like come back and then
Oh, don't shoot me. That's not nice
Whoa, you weren't even aiming at me bro
I don't want it. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa, right. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. You're done. You're done. Alakazam. You're dead
Don't waste my time
stink
Take that
These are the only location. I know these type of guards spawn. I'm like 99 percent sure
I don't think anyone others spawn here
Hey
Right, and then you here you go. Here's some money
Me here we go. That's my money. Uh, I don't know
Belize
I don't know how to respawn those guys in without like going on doing something else
Do
Um, I need to do a lot of horse activities that sounds bizarre out of context. Um
Have I got a pen and paper for my brain?
Uh, hold I'm literally gonna write this on the discord
So the girls are like, what the heck are you typing about?
Uh, right, let's see. I need to
Right, I've killed four multiple
I have to like open it and then show it in the next kill streak and then
I need to evade
I
Invade
Invade four times or something. I've already forgotten the other freaking thing I was supposed to do
One enemy stationed at guard post. Okay, we're actually gonna uh
Stations guard post we're actually gonna do that in a memory because there's a memory that enables that
Horses belonging to guards commandeered
Horses yoinked
Without killing
Um
Do you want me to screenshot and post them to the third? I just need to do the last one
Oh, I can screenshot. I don't even have to type it out
Can I screenshot it? Did that screenshot work? I don't even think I did
It did
Okay
Okay, that worked. Okay, I worked it worked. I am so smart. Yes m r t
Okay, let's see
Put that there so I don't miss any donations of someone tips
And then put the discord there
And now I can oh wait. No, I can't see it. Oh the screenshot makes it so tiny that I can't see it
I need to type it out right six
Six thieves lured. I did it for anyway. No, it's the picture
It's because if it's a picture I need to have like discord and small sprint uninterrupted sprint
four three hundred
21 leaps of faith. I need to 40 leaps of faith
So you don't really do leaps of faith anymore
Guards air assassinate from a beam guards air assassinated from a beam unless, but certainly not least
Jump from a horse to a beam
Jump from horse
To beam. Yeah, there's actually like so much horse related ones. This is surprising
Uh, I didn't actually expect
Oh, is there a just message me? Oh, we should see
Ah, okay
It's m r t. Oh my god. Oh the girls are posting in the not say for work section of the discord now look at it
I think it may be oh actually maybe my gifted artwork
It's m marty. Oh wait, I've just closed the discord. Oops
The discord actually holds everything that I need to in order to play the game. Look at dum dum
It's m marty. No, that's smarty
Wow, I can't believe it. I might unironically need a third monar for this kind of stuff
Okay
Someone at our ubisoft is really proud of the horses honestly probably took like a heckish
And hellish. Oh wait a freaking dumb. Why must we don't?
Okay, wait, hold on hold the freaking telephone
Okay, there we go
I definitely need a third monar. Honestly. I felt that right now as I'm currently trying to like arrange so many things
Okay, hydration check
I am going to do one
Yeah, one of those portrait monars. Yeah, definitely like chat orientating
Right, uh because there's so many horses ones
I'm actually going to take us to the thieves district if I can find a fast port which I can
Uh mercy
One hour 20 minutes mercy
Mercy modest more like mercy
We're like mercy didn't know what countdown was. Yeah
We're like all our all like mercy senpais are more deceased. Oh
Mercy just catches straight a little
Oh
Well, I'm dissing my
My fellow gen mate, but I'm so bad at like dissing because I just like I
Oh, I need to put you in the scaffold and please let me grab you
No, no, no, I don't want to fight. I don't want to fight. I don't want to fight. Please. Can I grab you?
Can I grab you? Wait, I can't grab them when they're in
Right, that's two of three
I'll leave me alone
Uh, is there any more scaffolding if there's more scaffolding now's the time to reveal yourself
Oh, there is uh, um, um, um, um, um, um, um, um, um, please come this way
Please come this way. Oh, look at this lovely scaffolding that someone's put up for them. She cooking mercy. What's she doing?
I'm zero. I'm trying to do this tracks. Well, I'm absolutely rubbish at them
And I'm like try to pretend I know how to do this track with the plausible
Now you're not coming over come here right now come here. Come here
I'm wondering uh, it's terrible. This isn't gonna work out. Well, I don't think
Kill these two right. We've got a double assassination out of that. No
It's you. You're a bit too efficient at your job. I didn't actually want to assassinate them
Talk about a third monitor and I still only have one
If you come to be sure you might need three
Moment and mummy are you? Yeah
Or mommy
Uh, wait, what I needed to I need to go do horse missions
Right, we're gonna go to the thieves guild
Which I totally know the name all
The thieves guild
Why is it all the way down here?
Is that like the last one? You know what?
Yeah, you're dumb
She would never diss me. She loved me
Oh, I can't remember what my diss was on you. I've already forgot. I thought I was like a zero duly more like
Oh, that's what I was like a zero duly more like a zero duke
That's really like the most rubbish things like nonsense
I was trying to do like visual number of horror games. Are we allowed to recommend? Yeah, you can always recommend stuff
Isn't that probable right? Uh, horse activities
Right, I need to run 300 meters and interrupted you can do it at this section super duper easily
Uh, definitely recommend going to the thieves guild in order to this
Is there a delay more like fun to the bosom?
Your third monitor should be used exclusively to ignore chat. Why would I ignore chat? It's literally the best part of streaming
Other than like when the gameplay gets intense then uh
I'm thinking for that
It's really like a perfect circle here. Can I just come circles?
If you get motion sick close your eyes mercy. Look away. Don't watch stream here, man
What would happen if it's the oddest time of each of our I think you'd have a lot of fun girls
Hey, hold on
Uh, right. What do I need next?
Do
What
How have I got the thieves guild crest? I didn't do it
More like stacey these milk retains literally
She'd be
She'd be calling herself a dom when her prototype name was literally cotton bomb. Yeah get wrecked. Yeah
Uh, right, okay
Your dedication towards it so it's highly
It's a good game. What can I say, right? Am I supposed to kill from being on a horse?
Guards killed well on horseback. Let's go
Oh, hold on. Let's try again
Oh, hold on. Hold on. Let me get back on the horse. Sorry. Sorry. Let me quit
Excuse me. Excuse me. Let me literally get back on the horse. I could you literally let me get back on the horse
Stop I know you're scared, but we need to try that again. I messed that up like really badly. Hold on
Okay, let's try that again. I've been destroyed decimated
Just like
How decimated your skin is when you interact with rabbits because you're allergic. Ha ha ha ha you're allergic
Yeah, I'm so good at doing this
Awful. I'm so sorry. This is absolutely horrendous. I'm just gonna stop talking
Oh
I'm a horse
On an old space commercial
Wow low blue just like the height of rabbits. Oh
Oh
They just make my throat close now literally put you in anaphylactic shock. Oh nothing measured though
Yeah, okay retconning
The model we gave you like right now. Holy crap
Double air assassination. Whoo. Oh actually worked. Wow. Okay
Alley wait, hold on horse come back stop being scared. Where did the horse go?
Is it all right fine? I'm just calling my recruits and I'm not doing this
No, no, no, no, no, no, we don't do this. Give me here. Give me
Yeah, yeah, yeah, the people are fighting back take that and this
Stinky stinky wait that missed
Oh, well, I like this. I can do with it. Where's my horse? There's one
Okay, we did the
We need to just go around killing more guards from horseback and then once that one's done, we'll move on to the next
Hello, are there any guards?
It's you quieter. Hello. Are there any guards?
I get turned into a horse
because they get oh
Would you want to be a horse feature?
If I would change into another animal
I'd maybe make you
What would I make you?
Thank goodness. I'm not on the development team anymore when it comes to that shiz. So don't worry. You're not getting any more bad names
No, no
Uh, hi jack. I'm to commandeer a horse without killing. Okay, so that's one for the commandeering
Oh, my horse has like a little backpack now. Oh
A little backpack on the horse. Okay, so that just need to like keep running around open to run into
Okay, here we go
Okay, that was one more
Okay, we're gonna call in the assassins
As soon as they get on a horse. I don't like it. I get scared. Oh
Oh, that was guard on horseback assassination. That was good. That was good. There's only been like three surprising ones
Hmm
Let's see if we can do another double. Maybe yeah, okay nice double. We're racking up them numbers really quick. We are we are
Uh, I'll let the assassin feel with this. I'm gonna get this guy. I'm getting out of here. No, you're literally in my way
Horse features also have a very big buff because of course
Mm-hmm
Uh, right we need to get back on a horsey horsey
Hello
And then
We're getting there. We're slowly, uh whittling it down to not much. Oh, I'm stuck on a rock. Mm-hmm
Oh
Right enemies enemies enemy. Oh, who we got who we got? Uh, I just need to hijack without killing. Thank you. So that's two for 10
That's two for 10 for common deer and a horse
Uh
I need to do the hide spot things. So maybe I'll go into the spale here in time. I don't count. Oh rubbish
What was an enemy back here? What was it? Oh, right you right you're three of 10. Thank you very much
Appreciate it
Actually, I'm gonna go for these guys because we're just easy
Oh, pardon me. I'm just calling this ass and zoom
No, stop running away. I know it's scary when I start. Oh, uh hijack. Thank you very much
Wait, if he keeps going on horses, can I just farm him?
Oh, no, my sassons are gonna get um, okay, I have learned today I have learned let me get this guy here
I
Think I can just farm him over and over again and because I jump off my horse to do it
He jumps on main automatically
Right what? Uh, what was that like five?
So he's gonna get on the horse
six
Okay
Oh my goodness
Seven grand theft dressage, but I didn't get the thing yet
That's funny as anything though
Oh my god, this is actually really funny eight. I think eight
Nice
Oh, no, no, no, no. Hey, there we go. There we go. Beautiful beautiful
Oh
Right a few more kills from horseback
That was good. All he wants to do is ride the horse on his way. I just get yonking over and over again
I mean, did he really want the horse if he just made it that easy for me?
Okay, we're at the bath house. I recognize this part of the map
Uh, I think we're gonna have to go in a bit more to find more guards. We've literally just gone on the outskirts there
of the map
Uh, a few more assassinations from a horse while on horse back
Well, oh no, hold on. Let me check
Very quickly
Stoney has d need d need
Is this the horse one guards on horseback air assassinate guards caled whale on horse whale on horseback
Okay, I'm gonna get my crossbow out and we're literally just going on a spree then
Uh, I need to stay on horseback now
Oh, I'm going the wrong way
I need to go to the wards the coliseum, which is this way
What's that you played assassins creeds so much that you recognize which way you need to go
Maybe maybe not. What's it to you?
Right, there should be four enemies here. Okay
I'm surprised how casual this is
One
Two don't pull me off. Don't pull me off. I'm scared. Stop. You're scaring me right
That's four
Okay, there we go
Oh wait
We need to do the beam trick. I think this is the beam trick
Oh, that was the beam trick, right? We need to do that 19 more times. I'm not even hitting hold on and we need to lure the guards
Come here. Come come come
Lure these men away
No
Lure them away. Yeah, there you go
Uh, right. We basically need to go back and forth over and over jumping on this beam
No, you didn't do it. See oh that wasn't it. That wasn't the trick
We needed to do that flip you saw literally 19 times more do a flip. It's you
Right and I want to know it see we'll try again
They need to jump a specific
Jump holds flip. Okay jump hold flip
So I need to tap a and then hold it so 18 more time
Jump hold
No, okay. I think we needed a bit more speed that time a bit more give us a bit more energy a bit more energy
little
Little bull's eye a little horsey-worsy
Do a better run up for it hold
And that horse just blocked us and jump and hold
Why did that not work that chain?
I'm not sure why that didn't work
Yeah, but we'll talk with those. It's not bad
Didn't in the corner my right and uh jump
Okay, I purposely did that a bit later than when I would have selected a so it's 17 more
I can do it
Uh betley. Oh, no, okay, right
Are you gonna have to bear with me bear with me I see is in this room right now because you're gonna have to bear with me
Bear with me
few seconds
Steady jump and hold. Yay 16 more times. Let's go
I definitely seem to be able to do it come in from that way. I'm wondering if I can't do it this way
Maybe there's like a hidden bug and I jump and hold
Maybe it's the one way type of
We're getting there
70 more. Let's go. Literally. It's like, oh, I'm so glad you guys put this really arbitrary arbitrary. Okay, really
Really premature with that one. I'm not gonna I'm not even gonna. No, no the horse
That was uh
Let's try that again
Yeah, literally. I wish the NPCs would actually calm down about my rely. Oh, no
I honestly, I'm not sure how I'm getting it sometimes and not other times
My only guess is that an NPC is making it so like
pathing mess up
Jump hold
What is going on
What is going on? I'm not actually sure why sometimes I'm getting that right
We'll do a really big run up just because we can
Okay, so run and then stand and then jump and hold. Okay. Okay. It's speed. It's speed. We need it
We need a bigger run up 15 more times
15 more times. Okay big big long journey one two three four five jump and hold
15 is still the number. We can't do it. This is not at all
A bit of a grind. I don't know why so a bit more of a grind than I was expecting. Run
And jump and hold
I honestly don't understand what's determined in
a
Maybe do the middle one like jump lay
I think you may be right. We'll jump lay on purpose this time. Okay
Not doing it. Not doing it. Not doing it. We'll jump now and hold. No
Thank you for at least coming back
15 is better than 20
And 14 is better than 15. Whoa. No, no, no, no, no, no
No, no, no, no, no
No is the appropriate response after seeing that out loud
Oh, all right. No, that didn't work
Uh, I think I'm getting speed blocked or something
Because this is what we're on 14 or
13 no, not 13 close to 13
We can do it. I literally feel like Bilbo Baggins when he's like
Uh, he's like trying not to be like a bit. Um, just growing old with like the door showing up
And I'm like, oh, it's fine. It's fine. No
This is very
Maybe you have to be under the beams. Okay, I'll definitely like I'll super delay at this time like genuinely super delay
No, he just he just jumped straight on it if you do it like super delayed. Okay
Curious curious, right? I'll try again because 14
Like I can do this honestly. It's just so
I'm trying to avoid that guy. I try to avoid that guy. I think
I just need to let the horse maybe
Directly steer even if the horse is a little off because my the steering as soon as I stand on the horse's saddle the steering
Oh
So I just realized since you're in Australia, does that mean you've been streaming 3m? 4am is my stream time
Daylight saving and stuff
But it's healthy
It's healthy
It's it means I can do stuff during the day. Oh 13 13. Okay. I don't know. I genuinely didn't do anything different
I think it really is just luck of the draw or something because
I did not do anything
Ah, I was gonna say hopefully we get to in a row
This is such a bizarre like challenge type thing honestly
No, why why why?
30 no, not 30 13
Spreads build up just straight up and uh
All bits are so like
He acts annoyed in the moment. See. Yeah, that was like hardly any build up
So I think that's why that one's in the one
Mmm, um, let's not be knocking down women. I only want to knock up women. Thank you very much
Oh, wait, I don't want to knock down women. I only want to knock them up
Please laugh
One more time without doing a massive thing
Uh
Yeah, I forgot I forgot I had it too. Okay. I forgot legit. I'll need to add a laughing track as well. Oh
Brother this guy's thanks. Yeah, I'm gonna have to add uh
Um, I'll add a laughing track. I should add a laughing track
That's like one that's good and then one that's like
Uh, I gets a few coughs and like a giggle. So it's like a bad joke. I'm definitely need to get that
Hmm
I need to hydrate my goodness. I'm like trying so hard to figure out like what's determined in this jump or not
I need some crickets. Yeah
Do the joke again. I let my laugh in my other jacket
Oh, you left your laugh in the other jacket. Ha ha you spelt it wrong
Everyone pointing laugh you spelt his thing wrong and I read it out and now he's embarrassed
Ha ha ha streamer read out your message with a spelling error. Ha ha ha ha ha ha. Oh that that was just gross
Right, okay, we're gonna try gallop now
The only issue with galloping is if you gallop through a crowd too much
No, that was far too early. Okay. I'm kind of struggled with it. We'll try the gallop from this side
It's over. It's over. You'll never recover. Your social credit has been determined
No, okay, that gallop doesn't seem to enable that jump whatsoever. I like how the horse is so responsive
It's like where'd you go? Please come back
Oh, is it the digration?
Degoration degradation
Degration degradation
Degration sounds correct
Instead of degradation. Oh 12
I'm just so surprised when it does happen. It seems to happen in that direction more than it happens in this
No, look close it's over not quite
I do want you on the beans, but I want you to do that
We fancy flip that you do they should have made it 10
No, they actually shouldn't have done this all because literally how would you have discovered that it so can even do this?
I'm sorry, but I would never have naturally discovered that he could do this
Good night. Rest well. Thank you for hanging
We're uh
Oh, I actually can't see how long I've been streaming for I've accidentally covered it up with my uh
Little list of things that I need to do. Oopsie. Whoopsie
Oh, that was like really
It feels like has cooled down honestly
The brain rot took over. Yeah, it took over long ago. I apologize
Eight hours. I've only been streaming eight hours. I've got a few more in me
I want this one over because I never want to have to do it again
Like I don't want to have to come back to this
I but I know you guys have been literally watching me do a backflip on do a flip on a horse for like 10 minutes
Now it's gonna be just no one's laughing
Getting aggravating it right. I am running. I am running. I'm holding
Oh
Okay, I think it's 11. No, I don't know why right. I'll run up for ages. Hold. No
Oh, we're almost 50% of the way there
Absolutely
Only
Oh, well, you guys are gonna feel at a place when you see me only only for like two hours tomorrow
You're gonna be like, what's wrong? Is she sick?
Oh, I'm sorry. Oh, no, you have done
10 10 right. I feel like it always happens come in this direction instead of the other direction
I feel like you can't even do a flip. We're not flipping out on you. You're not flipping out on me
Insert laugh track here that I still haven't added yet, but I will have the laugh tracks into him
Please get the heck out of my way. I'm trying to do
You
Can you leave me alone? No
No money is worth this he said I do need to kill from horseback. So maybe just do that real quick
We'll just do this one to add to the horseback one. So we're still making progress even though it's
Okay, that's that's the sound I need to add right now
But if I do the flip it goes
Don't worry, I'll get a little bit for you. I'm dead
Flipping on a beam off a whole horse this sucks and I don't know why they asked for 20
Stop taking people's horses. It's really not
No, I
I'm looking to see if there's like a prompt that's like double tap to do a beam or jump or whatever about
No happening, it's no happening, but we're halfway there. We can do it. We can do it. We can do it. We can do it
We do it. We uh, well
That's probably not gonna work now. Is it? No
I have lost my mind literally I've been doing flips for thanks for so long
Please
Free me free me from the beam
Oh nine finally
No, it's you below the beam you could have easily sat back on the horse. I'll be honest
The skirt looks so funny. You mean has killed he's killed to kill to pull fun
Eight eight eight eight. Okay, that was actually
I think I need it. I think I can kill him and it'll count for the horseback
Oh, I'm getting a spank. I'm getting a spank. I'm sorry
Actually, I should probably do these guys from horseback as well
And there we go one
Two
Three or I'm going to throw rocks through your window
All right, let's try this game
Oh, no, don't jump no stick
Try going try going
You mustn't offend the last
You wouldn't you like me when I'm angry you can't you oh seven seven seven seven I think seven
I still have yet to figure out what determines it but once it's over with we don't have to do it again
We got a double. We got a double. We got a double. Oh my god. I've not done that. Can we do a triple?
Can we do a triple is like my subconscious understanding what I need to do even though my brain like my actual
conscious doesn't
No, we got a double though. So it's six only six more to go. I've never done back to that. That's fantastic
I was literally I'm like is my subconscious knowing what's up, but my conscious is like
Can't that was far too early me put my glicks on for that one. That's terrible
Wow, oh baby
Top 10 moments
Welcome to watch module. Well, we wait the work. We rate the worst
Little side quest things that assassin creep brotherhood randomly give you because it is a bit arbitrary
Only six more can you hold on for six
I'm starting to lose a little bit, but that's okay because we got five we got five
I was gonna take it will be be a triple get out of my hand
Look, I wasn't kidding when people like why would you just grave she be is like everything you should have been
I wasn't kidding. Was that kidding?
I was oh four four four
You
Or
Oh
We're sounded so country
Wow the sound of the ice cream
Three three three three three
Oh
The people listening in right now that are like waiting on mersey start they're like please for the love of god mersey start
One more one more one more one more one more
One more just one more time. We've got to celebrate. Oh, yeah jumping on the horse beam
Do the random say thing for the guilt
Oh
Don't don't ever be such a silly sausage again and
Your daddy your dad says they've gone
Don't ever give me such a silly thing again. That was absolute torture
Lure guards leap of faith guards air assassinate from a beam
No guards
Okay, the only thing I can think of doing is attracting these guards over here to no because they would have to be below me
Where is a beam that a rider goes past?
Because I think that's what I have to assassinate
So now forcing around no dive on I
Think if I do this I might get the horseback kills
I
Please come under this beam over here, please harass me under this beam
Please harass me under this beam. I can't believe the game literally just train me for this moment
Please come under the beam. Please come under the beam. I take all back. I'm sorry these skills
I'm sorry
Where the heck is this mystical beam that the enemies pass under I don't know where it's located
It's not up here doesn't feel like it's up here at all
Mission failed you get them next time literally where the heck are these beams?
Hardly any beams anywhere
The only beam around here is me having a beamer because of how freaking embarrassing this gameplay is
To have a beamer means that you are embarrassed and have scarlet face or a red face
Oh
Just to be
Volpe does have missions. I am going to buy ammo and
I'm gonna do this stationary guy one because it's really easy to do it in this quest
So I'm gonna go by ammo and we're gonna replay a mission that gives us one of these skills
requirements
Claudia yes, she does as well
I'm
Try to do sorry who goes there?
I think I'm actually gonna have to get rid of my rating
What is needy smart overload it is
Unfortunately, I actually don't know too much about the game
But it might be a good thing because we get to play for fun for the first time
I don't think it's gonna be a very long stream if you're wanting an endurance on that
I
Need to go to the shops to buy the sweets for the hand camswing stream
Why am I here?
Yeah, sure
Well, you're no cheap. Oh, I need to buy are I just realized that yeah, I need to buy like tons of art in all the different districts
To three hours. Yeah, that's like the perfect stream
Deep gargling didn't overstay as well. Oh, okay. Okay, I did
young man with an apple man
He's so done. He's like I have enough of posing. Oh, that's a cool one
But what art for here, oh wait, I'm like 90% sure you sell failure locations
Can you please resell me then
No
Yeah, the feathers. We'll grab the feathers. I'm sure another's one on the Colosseo
Are you gonna hundred percent avatar? No, I've never played the RDA side of avatar. I don't like the RDA side
Can I still visit Leonardo?
And I don't play the RDA side only play the Navi side and
It will just be done the Navi. I think the campaign's like six hours on that one if I can remember correctly
We'll be strange not seeing you before bed and waking up after yeah, it's gonna be an interesting day
But I do have endurance streams every week kind of planned as long as all goes well
I'll see what the clipping situation is
Hi Leonardo
It's you the people apartments are in turmoil. Yes, it is ill and the pope dead
It was your doing was it not Leonardo? I swear to you did not die by my end
This world gets stranger every day. I shall have to focus on my painting
I work on the small portrait of a woman. I'm growing rather fond of it
Do not let a beautiful girl distract you from constructing my designs. I have no worries
Women provide little distraction
Wait, I don't get it
He's a gay boy. It's you. Oh, it's pride month. Can he be like that man?
Can he be like that? That's nice. Oh, I have everything
I
Don't have anything to purchase Leonardo about everything wait if I talk to him again
You have all that I can give now. You're on your own. Ah, Leonardo
Get back you
Give me some of that
Good day for catching up on cooking balls and things and no engineering. Yeah
And so the clipping situation I don't want the girls feeling stressed out thinking like I have to clip like and stream at
The same time and like deal with all this and try and do collabs all the girls and all that
And deal with the audios and blah blah blah. So I don't want to stress them out
So when you guys like do a make a YouTube clip
I can go on their accounts and see what someone's clipped and if it is like clippable
Where's a I can then send the timestamp onto like an actual clip editor
To make clips for them and I just need to see how it works out in theory obviously when I do endured streams
I can't do any of it like right now for them and
But we
Will see how it goes
I don't know if I need to like put out a little ad saying like I need more clippers of this particular style
Because there's a particular clipping editing style
That I'm looking for the most recent mercy shorts the blonde hair short
and the other
short of forgotten
And is the clipping style so if you really can do that in style
You know, don't be afraid to help the website
Because that's kind of what I'm needing at this point
Good thing. I've got a few clips already
My job is not necessary. If you're a general clipper and we do I'm still interested in doing the clipping
Enterprise that like I don't end on which is really good
Obviously need to get monetized first and set up and see whether my funds and the money looks like and all that and
Because will I tell you a really embarrassing fact, you know the earlier like
The earlier
Clips that came out shorts that were on the girls channels
and
Amy made two of her a couple of shorts on her own actually
But I was editing them and I hated them so much and I was so embarrassed. I was like, I'm so sorry girls
This is the best I can do because we had a quite a few issues behind the scenes production wise with timing
It was a freaking nightmare
and
so like all my attention was elsewhere and
Like I didn't have time to be like hi clippers. Here's this these files like please wait at them
Which that's where I did fail like looking back like obviously I'm happy like talk about like where I failed the girls and like I
Definitely feel like I've failed with them on the clips because the actual plan was the count school life for two weeks
before stream and there'll be a clip uploaded every day and
Like I kind of failed the girls like doing that and I feel really bad about it. I feel wrong
But like the dust is kind of set of already done this but the dust is like kind of settling
The only bad thing is that for now time zone only you and I see stream at normal times, okay, you may be not in a normal way. Yeah
You
Do you know like it definitely went well like the absolutely no denying like
And I'm definitely not denying like
debut went well and everything
Just like I had planned things to just be a lot better and obviously it's not realistic to be like all my plans are all
I just realized I need to leave the face. We're gonna be jumping off this building for quite well
Like I understand it's not possible for everything
For everything to like come out the way of my head and
Like the girls trailers didn't come out the way I wanted them to
And but because of like production issues, I couldn't get things like fixed or altered in time for anything really and it was just like
But yeah
Yeah, are you winning strong? Yeah, absolutely. Um, are you winning?
Excuse me, I'm using this cable. I'm so sorry if this makes anyone motion sick
I'm needing to do leaps of faith and if you jump off a pigeon thing it counts as a leap of faith
No, it's ill into the hay bed
Yeah, it was a timing issue and we love artists in this house we do but and I
had given
Very I feel I had gave incredibly fair deadlines for what I was asking and
Pretty much across the board the majority went over and if you are an artist that worked with me
And you did go over deadline like please don't worry and
Like it's not like a big deal anymore because obviously now everything's out there and everything's all good and we debuted and like that's
That's the facts
but I
had a lot of delays and
Basically, I had planned every month in advance
Being like this month. I'll be focused on this this month. I'll be focused on that and what happened was
Everything had to be done in May and
Like I'm not gonna lie
I like cried a few times out of just like pure frustration of like feeling I can't do enough
because I have to wait for
Someone to send something back in order for me to progress and give feedback like I had a lot of
Like issues with
People not checking what they gave me the first time around and being like hey the reference sheet looks like this or hey
Like the subtitle that you put here and like it's quite clear that she didn't say this
But you've literally put it in for some reason or like hey the audio
Literally cuts out in the middle of this. Can you re-render like I don't know what like
it was
It was rubbish and at the same time like obviously the girls know a bit more in detail exactly what I'm talking about and
Because like I showed them like we are
Like I'm constantly sending back like please fix this please fix this please fix this and the days are going by and the
Fixes are taking 24 hours the fixes aren't done within 20 minutes and I get a new rendered version of something
It's like no 24 hours. I'll do it in the morning. I'll do it later, and I'm like I have paid premium rates
I shouldn't be the one who is quality checking your work. You should quality check it before you send it to me and
Like it was just a cascading effect, and it was pretty horrible
And
But yeah, but we're here now. So and there were so many lessons learned like
Rip to future artists if you're interested in working with Veeler, but like everyone's getting contracts like conscripted and stuff like
And being like if you miss this deadline like you know
it's
Just there's just it's not fun being like that like I love giving artists the benefit of the doubt
But holy is this even counting for leaps of faith?
Yeah
Like deadlines are so important and having that like
My heck are the leaps of faith here. Oh, wow. We're one off of leaf of faith
Literally in the end we made it everything worked out fight. Wait, did that guard hurt himself?
and
Like we made it in the end, but yeah rough rough
Not fun, but I'm now
Like I just want to stream. I just want to have fun. I want to show off my games. I want to have a good time
I want to make ASMR. I want to do everything that I wanted to do
While I get to do it alongside like these amazing girls type thing
And I want them to see them achieve their dreams and see how it goes like obviously the the the current goal is
YouTube to please stop calling us and like admit that we're real
Like streamers and stuff. You don't need to call us like there's plenty of content
On channels now
But yeah, like it definitely like everything works out in the end
Absolutely is everyone max level
No
Three people aren't max. Oh, I didn't mean to do that by a whole
Yeah, like the worst part is over
Wait what the heck
Oopsies, I'm to kill
the mailman
Not to be confused with the Sandman that blows literal dust over your eyelashes or some shiz. I was ridiculous
Never heard of the first time I've ever heard of that nonsense before I heard this song
But like what?
For goodness sake
I
Love how easy that stuff is
Oh, excuse me, am I not your mentor?
Oh, no, the PayPal got fixed and so you can support any of the girls like right now
I think I need to update my link or something because people say it no work or something
I don't know
Oh, you're using the new info
YouTube on soft as it's old European folklore, of course, it's nonsense. True a
Literary tree
Right, I don't really know what the plan is
Okay, we'll finish the guild people's requests, but I have to admit I'm a bit lost on what next to do
Get all the guild crests by everything and then I think we might be done maybe the feathers
And
And we'll revisit
Mercy 30 minute
Did I get the feather from this location I must go
You did
Cause a little chaos why not
Christina, oh I forgot about Christina. Oh, right. Okay. Okay. Okay
Oh
I've completed all the renovations
Wait, so what's my DNA?
Must be high enough seriously 68
Is there anything I could do that's really easy
No, no
I don't want to do do you know be to take it
Wait a minute did this one
That was rubbish that one don't look I discovered no that was rubbish as well
That was rubbish as well rubbish and maybe the missions
I've never achieved that
No, these like so aren't possible
Well, maybe I need to do
Wait the assassinations are only a oh
The assassinations are like only a 41
Okay, okay, we'll do assassins that'll raise us that'll raise us really quickly like they're super easy super nice and consider it
So we'll do that
I
Climbing up letters, don't mind me
Y'all excited for my first day some ice cream
I'm doing something
Mildly special in it. I'm a bit concerned after what happened to me, but he will
Apparently she was jumping up and doing on the bed like a monkey
Yeah, were you there? Did you hear about this? Did you see this?
What was my cute little sister doing on the bed hello?
Mmm
One little in me jumping on the bed and she jumped off and bumped her head
How is your
Oh
Let's see the board to have unleashed their interrogate if they cannot find us we realize people do not let your targets call for
reinforcements. Oh, I don't know what that means
kill
Wait, does that mean like don't get detected?
She had to fall and land on her ear somehow. Yeah, I remember reading someone's review on it and I was like
Now I want all my children to succeed
but apparently
Apparently we were spitting and licking it back up
How do you plead to these accusations? I mean, how do you plead to such accusations?
Actually
Pin pals
How do you plead to the accusations that you egged your little sister on?
To do such devious acts
I
Guard is running for backup who who they're all highlighted
Got kill bruise
I don't know where that guy ran. I'm not really mad at it because I'm still gonna get DNA anyway, but
Oh, there's scaffold in there I could grab them
Not guilty I plead the fifth egged in me on all that's funny. What is she egging you guys on?
Oh these accusations against my little sister. I will not stand for such things
Right, okay, let's keep doing
These
She knew what she was doing my innocent little sister has no concept of
What even a double meaning is
You are looking at her through your your lusty eyes. How dare you?
No, how dare you labeling on the innocent the innocent turn yet it because that's what the name of her
So true
She's always egging his own
Right, I'm gonna send away those assassins that aren't ready to level out properly
Thank you, I'll send you on a big big contract big big big big contract
One two three four five of you
She turned a guy into a tree like he was asking for okay
She needs to level up. Okay. She needs to be experienced with what she's doing
It's not hurtful
Right, we seem to be about 42 percent use assassin recruits to assist in uh
diversion
Kill the merchant while remaining undetected
He's peasy lemme squee
Gotta get that xp somehow
You know what you're right. Her latest
Alt tweet probably is a misunderstanding exactly. You're just reading it wrong, okay
Uh
Can I like lock on to the guy
Well, let me recall my recruit
Is it bugged out? Oh
Oh
Wait, what was the mission use the session recruits to assist tonight diversion
Oh, well
That was easy peasy lemons wheezy. What's going on here?
We are discussing how
Pin pals have you so misunderstood
They're looking at you with
This
They do
I'm trying to tell them that you're innocent. Okay, and that they're not comprehending
That the you jumping up and down on the bed during your ASMR stream is completely innocent
And you were literally just singing that song
Three little monkeys jumping in the bed one fell off and bumped its head first game the doctor or something
That's not anything fun though. Sure
All right, I don't get
We'll do the feathers
I'm not innocent. That's for e
Who among us is innocent truly? No
If I were making an among us reference that it means Lord there
I was like, did you like that? Uh, and wait, I don't need to go off on it. Okay
I
Really suck out of this, you know, it has potential don't tell me otherwise. I won't accept such
Right, you need to jump up here in order to get this flag
I need them to come across more thieves to do the lure. I think I have like two more
Thieves need to lure the guards away. I'm sad. I missed on these. I mean
I don't good
It means probably gonna do it
And ASMR streaming in
Just uh, maybe a little less
Uh a little less, perhaps
You know
We can't escape
V suck it could be another brand of ruler. It should be for the the innocent
The innocent side where I just make them do like
Girlfriend roleplay audios or like that kind of stuff. But like it's nothing. It doesn't like go any further, you know
Safer work side that people have been asking for I did get a few emails
um
Management showed me them and people were like, uh, is it required to do that?
and it was like
Very sadly kind of the the whole point of the agency. Um, that's where the money is
Oh, oh wait. No, there's not boarder people here anymore. I was getting nervous. So I was gonna get caught and I'm like, wait, man
There's no boarder
Oh
Eye contact roleplay
Teaching you eye contact proof. Oh, I don't know the best way to climb this. Maybe on the outside of the policy
Give me that feather
True love
Ruffin
Yeah, like so I did have a few variations of like
Would there ever be a generation that didn't require that part and it's like
What's the point? It's just a really agency at that point
Um
Where the height was that other feather?
Oh, it's literally
split perfectly
Uh, where there is the
Jump off point. Oh wait. We have a parachute. All right. We'll just use the parachute off the coliseum
I
Come pop off in real food where you can hear audible call. Oh, and me
All right, we're just gonna do this
Your assassins
You
There's a few uh group roleplay is actually seventh as well. I'm coming out
Uh, I just can't any time to settle. I only want them to come out once the culling has stopped because literally it's like such a
shame
That it is still happening
Even though like we're like getting into the studio. It's like, yeah, we've like got proper streams now. So I'm not really sure what the deal is
Like the meme asmr's are literally i'm too scared to even upload them at this point because i'm like
What's going on with asmr? I think there may have been a stealth policy update or it's about to be introduced publicly
Feathers up here. Um
This is a little sister you argued has an innocent mind. Yeah, I'm not arguing in what's innocent of
Okay, right. We're gonna use the
Yeah, there's definitely something going on at youtube headquarters when it comes to asmr because
There's a lot of channels left and right getting yanked for content that previously was fine
and they're
my guess is that youtube don't want to publicly say it because
Asmr is such a popular category on youtube like it's an insanely popular category
And they don't want to come out and say it
So they're just tackling it like silently basically
So it's not arguing
um
I think I think the uproar if they publicly said like we're doing this would be so much because asmr
I think they like said it's like one of the top four categories
Sorry, like in the top 10 searches a variation of either like food eating or asmr medicines
Like whatever you want to kind of really get into it
um
It's like such a high
Watched category that if they publicly said like hey, we're drawing the line here now
I do think there will be a post at some point
But at the moment it's kind of stealthily being done. So the content is no longer
Available. So when they do go publicly like hey, we've actually changed this people are like, oh, that's fine
Because like no one's been uploading it anyway because you know, you've been deleting channels less than right and
Handing out warnings willy-nilly. So
Yeah
That's my guess by the way. This is absolutely not factual. This is like just what my genuine like
What I think is going on
um
YouTube is just like I see. Yeah, it's literally just my guess what's going on. It seems the most probable to me
So unfortunately, I think like you're looking content's just gonna have to be like
Just straight up upload it to twitter or
Put on patreon
Yeah
Solution and I know a lot of people are like, oh like just put it like not behind a paywall on patreon
Unfortunately in order to link your patreon successfully
Um everything must be behind the paywall
First like even if it's a fine audio that is not wrong with it
Um, it has to all be behind a paywall. It's bizarre
It's bizarre the rules get very arbitrary in memoria
Now you're wrong YouTube's drunk
All right, let me see we've done the feathers. I have no idea how many
We've done right we're getting close to doing the courtesans
So
Yeah, like we're so
Uh enemy stations, right we're gonna do that now because I know how to do that. You have to replay a memory
from
the french one
No
Yes, this is the one
Can you stream to x? I wouldn't stream on twitter
No, you need money on it
Like I hate to I hate to be that one. I know it sounds really sucky where it's like money money money, but it's like the
Obviously the girl's name is ported and the thing with youtube boards is like
Uh, you always like make money on youtube boards and like always look up and yeah
Once inside your men can overpower the camps patrols, correct?
Yes, I think it's fine saying like yes, we're not an agency for greed, but at the end of the day
We need money around
And the youtube boards is like a fantastic way or the youtube ads on like a small video for example
Like this kind of stuff is like free to make content like it's free for me to stream right now, you know
My troops will gather it from the dead and people underestimate the value of ad revenue the uh
Advertise like the free
The armor has to stay clean
Right if you use your crossbow ball in this mission it accepts that last thing like oh, there's a horse right there
Oh, there's another horse right there
Yeah
Businesses move can't do everything for you. Unfortunately, yes, the world is run on
All right, I'm not going now because really peace forever to get to these guys there
Um, we'll go this way instead. Yeah, this way's like so much better
You basically for some reason if you snipe the guys in this one
um
They count towards that cortisone thing, but if you snipe in general it doesn't count
Oh sugar. I'm sorry
No, I didn't want to do that
Actually, hold on hold on when the disarm and kill with his own weapon. There we go one of five
I don't know
99% of all my problems come silver money. It is a terrible way
Okay
We might have to do this twice twice. I'm not sure. Well that guy's coming over to investigate right here
Another free kill
Is that guy coming to investigate? Oh these guys are
I'll take it
I will loot them just so I can get some of them back
And that's how the next one might be
We appreciate that thing but please do always consider supporting the girls
We should get crossbow bolts from this. Okay hydration check hydration check. I've been yammering but I've not had much water today
I don't know when we can submit for monetization yet
As I said the stats like are not updating so it's kind of just uh
I
Very casually like
Oh, excuse me. Sorry. Oh, excuse me. Sorry. Okay. I'm gonna help
I'm calling the assassins and
Oh, I just teabagged him as he died. Okay, that was rather unique
Let's not do that again. That was uh, really not a move
But yes, once the youtube calling stops then please do look around uh for
Very fun ASMR collabs coming out. Um
Very very large ASMR collabs that cost a lot of money put together by hey-ho. Um
Um, sorry, I'm like trying to bramble and think and
Get this done
I like how he's suspicious even though I literally just perished that guy right there
God I wish there was a way to pay for all the girls patrons
I once I just got 16 months back to back. Oh, you support them as patrons. Thank you so much. That's very kind of you
Thank you. Yes, actually special. Thank you to literally
um
Anyone who's supported the girls on patreon. I understand the patrons will have one audio and it's very kind of you to like
You know reach out and do that even there's literally one audio
There are coming because the audio is released on the first
The girls are gonna have a consistent day that their audio in particular comes out
I really hope this is counting towards the challenge actually
um
I think this
Grave I'm having to go all the way around
That was it right I just need to redo that and then I think that'll be it for the mission
For the the crotch is on
right, let me just
Check the DNA sequence. I say that as I literally just goes that
That should have counted quite a bit towards that one
Two
That came it is two
Oh
Why did that not work is it because I kept getting detected
Oh brother
Oh
Guards on horseback air so guards killed well on a horseback
PayPal guards I need to go all the way
Guards air assassinate from a beam actually we're closer to getting the thieves done
I need to find a beam. I don't know where the beam is
Yeah
The mercenaries one is like absolute killer
So you go patreoner just paid for you. Oh, thank you so much for the support. I appreciate it
Y'all are I expected way more hate
Honestly, I think we all did but like I think everyone's just on the same page of like, yeah
You're probably tired at this point of like your vtuber just like teasing and teasing and then never giving anything
And then it's like, yeah, we're just having a good time meemen
If you want the goods, you know where they are. If you don't there's also free stuff coming out
a free video game coming out
like, uh, yeah
I think it probably helps without the greed out. I think if it was like a greedy
looking corporation that probably wouldn't help
but it's like, yeah, everyone's just
Right, I'm gonna bump into guards and they'd run away from them and hide in spots
Great
We'll do the bump because there's a hay bale right here
Hey, excuse me. Don't you be?
Oh sugar. Oh, uh, I don't think I can hide in this
Okay, let's see how
Can I hide now?
Oh, oh no, oh no, they're right next to me
No, don't check it. Don't check it. Don't check it. Don't check it. Don't check it
That shouldn't happen. Oh, there's more guards up here. I thought this district was like there's no guards here at all
Oh
Oh, yes the bench the bench of safety
Okay, I can't go on the bench because it's not like oh for goodness sake. How many of you?
Oh, right. I'm hiding in here can't get me
Does that count
Did it count you seem to be still annoyed at me?
I'm just gonna check that counted because if it does
Uh, not the poking if that did count. I'm literally just gonna keep upsetting those guards over and over to do that again and again
I think it should have counted those
I did right time to keep bumping into them. I'm gonna kill this guard up here though because he's gonna keep ruining it
Oh
Yeah
You smell so bad. No, you have to chase me
Miss me miss me now you have to kiss me
I was supposed to jump up
Where's the bail hey, oh there is
A six
Oh
I've got to get out of here
And then we just open dive into this again
Oh
I'm not sure that counted he was like so close you guys should know
No, I'm sorry, please excuse me. Ah, please excuse me. I'm scared. There's a table in the way. I got nervous. I'm sorry
Oh, no, I can't climb this way. Okay, he jumped on again
Ah
He's got a long lens. Please leave me alone. Let me out
Jump
They're like instantly given up. I'm like really worried that's not counting but
No, it is it just doesn't look like it looks so silly
And mercy online heck yeah mercies online. Let's go
Uh
If there's any mods still even I'll awake at this point. You're gonna look link
mercy
Uh, and please enjoy your stream
Uh, I think we're gonna wrap up the guild challenge. Oh, it's seal. It's supposed to go in the hair bill
Oh
See in the flip
Can you hear that or am I going crazy?
Am I going
Did I hear that right? Yeah, okay. I'm good. I was like, um, are you all hearing nothing?
Well, literally
I wonder if it's leftover ambience from the party sequence with the banker
Last one
Okay
I hear it again. Is there like people here or is it just SFX?
More like SFX
Yeah
Yeah, there's not even coded people to be here. I must just be background ambience
That's leftover from the party sequence with the bankers
All right, let's get notoriety down a little bit because guards are getting really worse
They're still asked it literally the party ended many a day ago. They just played operation
Hmm crazy, that's crazy right
I'm starting to get a bit delirious. Oh, I must switch the body though
I don't know why that did so little
I
Watching all the girls straight a long watch starting to move off isn't it not too much noise like there's too much noise going on
We're all blabbing away at once
I'm not sure what to do. I'm kind of getting I'm not like stuck. I know we can do those things
I'm just like, I don't know where the beam is for what we want to do
Um
I'm just like
Do we call it and then the next thing come on
I'm not gonna I like I'm like I'm saying to myself. I'm I'm gonna be annoyed at myself if I call it right now
is one
think I'm
I think I'm in back yet
Oh 19 seconds to come back
Right, let me find a group of thieves to hire at least so I can get rid of that
I can only focus it's hard to multitask that I'm watchable script right
But mercy live if anyone would like to watch mercy modis
Oh, I saw that. Okay, there are there are thieves somewhere on the verse up here
No
I see why they fear you
I'm forcing
Um
I
Think for simplicity will just teleport to the thieves guild in order to hire them. I struggle so much to find thieves
I understand their own rooftops
But they make it so freaking hard
run wads
Run wads of all six at once and let it just fry your brain
Most of it's four, but only one audio
Yeah, like I understand maybe for like a collab stream you like meet everyone but one person and then get to see everyone's POV
Mmm, I have teleport to the wrong place. I was not paying attention. I apologize. Oh wait, there's somewhere I can buy hello
Would you like to be purchased?
It would be a shame not to do Christina though like we're actually so close
Ah
What's the percentage we need for Christina?
Oh
Why is your accent so cool sponding Scotland?
and
always be scottish
It's very hard to unlearn that accent. Hmm. I even think it's possible
Truly out there now
Um, why was I here again? Oh to hire thieves and there's literally no thieves hanging out here
I need to hire one group of thieves. Is this for real for real like for real for real?
Uh, well, I need to find a beam that enemies pass over
And it's kind of in these general area. I'm uh
Unbelievably I'm at 69 percent. Um
Like
I don't know why
Locate memory in world insufficient data to access locate memory in world go to memory start point to synchronize with animals
Gotta go to work have fun at work
If you could have any other accent, what would it be?
Ah
Copernacle might have a lot of percentage in it. That's missing. We'll do Copernacle. Um as for accent
Can't imagine myself wearing her now. So honestly
Like to pick one
The Italian accent can be really nice
Although the Japanese like but Japanese voices are like so nice and like pitched
Um, which I really enjoy but I guess it's pitching no actual good boy
Uh
Her accent
Honestly, I don't actually mind
a
Polish accent if you've ever
Listen to a sweet Polish accent. It can actually be really soothing. Um
Just a little a little hint of uh their words and that's pretty good. Apply the Scottish accent to any language
Oh, you might apply to it
It calvane
It will sex
I
Was he believed
Volgmae
That's Scottish touch
That's pretty awful
Pretty rough pretty rough right. We'll try Copernacle, but if this doesn't like dramatically raise the DNA
Think I'm gonna I think I'm perishing
Unfortunately
And it might be wiser to
redirect into mercy and kind of have a break and
Deal with uh, these a smart collage and see what I'm looking at because I think someone might be waiting on me to edit
Scottish is the best accent as much as I was
Who is this man? He comes from Russia. I hear studies at the body count, but his words are unlike any that issue from that place
I don't buy it for Scottish accent's first
Scottish is magical hearing German speaking with songs that weird
You know, you have a good source accent when people can't even understand you
Perhaps to disguise a myriad of contradictions
I could use an excuse to go to bed. Yeah, I'm kind of like I think I'm actually lagging. I can't believe it. You're injured
Me saying I'm an endurance streamer. I'm a liar. The master wants all the scholars silence by nightfall
How long did we make it?
And so am I
Take no damage during the ambush right get the wee knife
Two minutes
Let's get to me nice
No
Yeah, that's what am I I'm gonna call in two of my assassins
No, it was like way too early that you saw the way he was wiggling that knife up
Whoa, why are you you know the guy that's like right in front of us maybe focus on like
Oh
Okay
Okay, my assassins are sticking around which I'm quite happy about I don't want to call in the last batch of assassins
just because
If they kill them too fast, they actually might all be spawned and not help me at all, which is quite funny to think about
I do wish citizens would stop running into the middle of the fight or near it. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Don't hurt me, please
If I take no damage, I win
Oh
I'm scared. He's got such a long freaking pole. He's gonna hit me with it
My assassin is trying to chase them but it's not happening
I'm just hiding. I'm letting my assassins do it. Copernico is fine. His health bar is fine
Oh, I've got fun. Oh, they caught me
Uh, I don't want to get hit. I'm so close to doing no hit. Please. Please. Please. Please. Literally 13 seconds is all I ask
Don't change up. Don't do anything else
Four more seconds
Okay, we did it
We did it. We did it. We did it. We did it. We did it. We did it. We did it. We did it. We did it
I think we came to do it. I'm still running away in case it counts. I think it counts
So I'm just gonna keep running running and running in circles around the fountain
Okay
Yeah, that's right. I did that
Right, I have terrible news
Fake endurance streamer. Absolutely horrible news 100% poggers. Yay. You said 100%
Wooo
Now we may genuinely return to brotherhood again at a later date. Um
But I'm actually quite satisfied. Literally, we did the campaign. We've done all the dlc stuff now
You did that so hard that other people didn't
Strolling it if you don't finish it just
Means you need to do it. Yes. I actually wouldn't mind revisiting it at a later date
I would like to play a bit more variety at this point. Um, I'm going to redirect into
um
Mercy so we can all enjoy her
I I can't believe it. I'm not a real endurance streamer. I only lasted
Nine hours this time. Gee willacrus. Oh, I'm kind of basic
I can't believe it
Oh
Uh, please do consider giving a like and a subscribe. Uh, if you enjoyed youtube may have unscripted
But don't worry. Uh, I'm going to redirect you an emergency
An emergency
Uh, redirect select stream. Oh, she's playing. Oh morey. Oh morey
That's oh morey
When
mercy, please
The tippy tippy day
That's pretty good. Yeah, that's pretty good
I got a copyright on my assassin's creed playthrough a game yesterday
Uh, sorry, I just spotted that right now and I'm like, uh, what I apologize. Uh, thank you
So so much my lovely beeflings for watching
Um, literally, I just I just checked it out. I'm like, I'm pretty sure the game has no copyright
So it's a false copyright thing going on. But thank you so so much for hanging out. Uh,
Yeah, maybe not 100 for the first time, but we'll give it a shot
I think we'll come back and we'll feel refreshed at a later date
Um, because that was a lot of jumping about. I think that's brought 20 hours
Combined at this point. Um, so thank you so so much for hanging. Uh, tomorrow we're playing needy streamer overload
I haven't played it
So i'm not quite sure what to expect but is a shorter stream for me
Um, so for those of you like the endurance side of things, I apologize, but my stamina is lacking tomorrow
Um, but nevertheless is always fantastic. Thank you so so much
My little reeflings or those who are watching and I will
See you tomorrow and say hi to mersey. I will talk
I will talk in mersey's chat for a little bit, but uh, I do need to go for a big pee
Um, I'm not even gonna pretend otherwise and you may pass
So I'll see you tomorrow. Okay. Bye. Bye
Bye
Bye. Bye now see you tomorrow