He's not happy with me, you know.
Yeah, I'm the life on, what life on that could be?
All right, I need to get a chance screen. I need to get a chance screen.
Why is my iPhone, whoa, my iPhone bugging the fuck? Oh, relax. What? I'm bugging out.
Am I getting a challenge screen? Get a challenge screen. No.
No, hold on, hold on, hold on. Scuffs already started, boys. Scuffs already started.
Look, he's a, he's the same, he's the same. One man, one mop. I was there, doing some,
some business things. God, the frickin scuff is a thing. What the hell's going on?
The tracker is hating me right now. Can you hear me? Have you all seen this? Have you all heard
about this? Okay, I think I'm gonna have to move the iPhone about because what the actual heck.
Can you guys hear the background music? I'm new. Okay, you can now. You can hear a bit of Assassin's
Creed. Good morning. My iPhone is bugging out right as a, I'm pretty sure this can do horizontal,
so not sure why I'm going to absolutely not hold on. I'm just calibrating, testing, left.
No, what the heck? Can you not see my face? Sorry. Blame the technology. What's that? I
should have used my loading screen. Sorry, can't relate. Couldn't care less. And something, something.
Oh my God. Is it because it's dark in this room? I can't believe it. I can't believe being a goblin
in the dark is a terrible idea for freaking tracking reasons. Hold on, hold on, I need to
come literally on my hands and knees to plug in this light under my PC. This is nonsense. Honestly,
why can't you see me iPhone? I'm out of the port? There are no keys. Oh my God.
All right, anyway, I've got some good news.
Well, the good news is I've got my first ASMR club coming out. Right, I've got to lay on.
Right, I've got to lay on. Here we go. Here we go. Here we go. Here we go. Right, back and back
Yeah, that's snuffing those. Why? Can, can be chip studio not handle?
Why is that going? Right, I don't think the chip studio works at all horizontal. Fuck you.
You stupid little twat. First of all, you little prick. Can it hunt? Can it know it can't go horizontal?
I'm confused, but I'm ready. You know what? Fuck it. We're just jumping in. I'll,
I'll deal with the tracking issues once. Hold on, hold on.
Fuck it. There we go. I'm actually normal. I don't know why the track and bugging.
I'm covering up too much on the screen now.
Who's ready for someone's house and screen now? I do believe ASECLE is still streaming,
so please do support ASECLE. She's still streaming for a white Christmas.
Let me just check before we jump into that. I need to make sure I've got suit titles on,
spoken language, English subtitles on. Oh my God, I'm such a real gamer. Are you ready?
ASEA is just ending. Oh, does she be next? I think she'd be moving on.
Her God's EPS soldier. Yeah. Right, okay. Oh, actually, this is some, oh wait, no.
I did all my latest, like, tipper and all that if you did a donor link to me.
Oh, no. Oh, you know what? Fuck it. We're playing Assassin's Creed, man. Fuck the money. I want to
play Assassin's Creed. I wanted to say something. I don't know if you guys would like this, but
whenever we play a video game, obviously there's names in the video game, and it's rude for a
feature, but to like name people and chat. So I want it to be like special congratulations
if your name's Desmond, if your name is Sean, if your name's Rebecca, if your name's Lucy,
if your name's Ezio, like, in the video game. I don't know, like, maybe only the guy names
make sense, but I thought that would be a bit different. Um, yeah, special show if your name's
Desmond. Uh, wait, that's right, you get a name by me. Eh, there we go. Eh, Desmond, that's right,
your name is Desmond. Okay. I don't think anyone ever expects to wake up one morning and find
themselves caught in the middle of a war between two secret organizations. I know I did, but here
I am on one side of the world. Can you guys hear the game? Better known these days as exturgo
industries. We're in the business of control, politics, economics, technology. I school hope
you enjoyed your, uh, Tomb Raider, more like Whim Raider after I'm done with you.
That's terrible. It's terrible. Friends will remember we don't have HR at, uh, you,
did you enjoy Whim Raider? Your little EP Polar Bear? I caught the start of you swing.
Don't worry, I'll tell you the lore that you're missing out on because I'm rambling on the top of
it. Oh, oh. Oh, my god. I'll tell you.
Not here.
as a piece of each of it go out right now you're done go away manager actually scare
me yeah they actually can make me graduate I always have to be like my
views are not they do not reflect the agency because my views mm-hmm they
shouldn't reflect the agency I was hoping that would be the end of my
I have honey tea how are the snowberries piece of Eden
even these nuts okay my ancestors from their instance searching for a path
forward but me I'm still here
it's you and see you on the tour and that's from a South Street too we're
gonna play that Lee are okay we're playing brotherhoods first take one
between the views of the town's this narrow flight agency true oh my god
ready I'm so excited I'm sipping my teeth tell me if it's to load or I'm too
load so let's be honest I'm almost to load if I'm too big I may need to make
myself smaller you know that
would you let me small ewe me this is a police dog from Mario let me hear that's
actually the full dialogue we got it we did the quick time thing the bigger the
me oh my god it's a horse feature bird
oh my god it's us we're it's the old
serious hooded man watch this
technical difficulties oh my god I couldn't this isn't on xbox game pass so
we're not getting any gamerscore from it what's that another reason to play this
game later she will occurs you don't have to tell it's general fun fact
oh
so excited blue who is this I don't understand
please wait so many questions
il vaticano December 1499 hey should I do not tell you next in this entire time
right man oh wait that's not telling him Italian speak I'm here me it's your
victory
this is my favorite bet cuz they always glitches out the fabric always glitches
out on his knee in the scene it doesn't matter how many times you play through
this game like it is instance of new glitches gonna occur during the cut scenes
but it always glitches out on the knee at that cut scene to the matter how many
times you play it Mario what are you doing here better to be left in the hands
of the earth than in the hands of man I can't believe the Pope fucking vanished
where's that bloody popcorn sorry I'm drinking and then it makes me do hypnosis
I'll just get so excited okay
I'll be swallowed alive as a giant test for it's already occurring
are we ready are we ready are we ready for the best freaking voice line for
Mario it's such a good freaking quote
it's an entire area I was worried quick we have to get out of here okay so you
can actually jump up if you do not engage an eagle vision so we're already in
tutorial mode if you do not engage an eagle eagle vision the game will not let
you climb up at all and but until you engage it so we're playing it's your
auditorita friends it which means he was spawned in frenzy we are already an
established assassin okay we've just defeated the big bad evil and assassin
screen too I'll shut up
oh my god right okay and so yeah we're Italian so Baba the boopie all those
jokes this up next part section so we're still in tutorial mode obviously the game
but the reason why I want to mention that we're in tutorial mode is because the
game perfectly is structured
oh that's another good like you can damn what you do not understand now right so
we can push people out the way it my way it my way it my way rosary beats up your
arse leave me alone away you go Mario will actually get caught on those people
which is quite funny that's your uncle Mario my arm is attacked now I want
you to remember that pineapple for no reason at all remember the pineapple all
hail the pineapple all hail the pineapple okay this next section is how you get
one of the easiest achievements in the game and it is perfectly sequence for
you to do so so look alive this is how you get the you haven't you're not to get
hit you're not to get hit oh shit he knocked them over right hold on you
wait for them to attack and then if you perfectly execute all these men then you
get your first achievement which I believe is frenzy but if you do it
perfectly Mario shouldn't unfortunately the camera angles are a bit no I lost
the street because of the freaking camera angle anyway your first achievement is to
kill 10 people in a row you could easily do it at that section of the game but
don't worry if you miss it there are many opportunities to do so the camera
angle will make mess you up I was gonna say make you up
and the camera angles a bit funny especially when you're in between
buildings like it's telling me to follow Mario you must also trail behind
Mario a couple of meters if you are right behind him you will knock him off
his coded path the AI will fix itself and he will go back on the path but you
must give him space or you will knock him off the rooftops and then you have to
wait even longer for this section to occur but it's fine it's not bad section
this is to learn mostly rooftop moving about how to get your agility sorted
you can't get used to holding down I recommend oh see that's another thing
sometimes it say we will do something when you tell him to jump in a certain
direction it's fine this game has aged beautifully
and I believe this game came out 2012 Skyrim was 2011 again you can knock Mario
off this if you're too quick you must be careful
it was 2010 oh my god I was a baby I remember asking my dad for this game
and um fun fact my dad bought me the special edition sasa's crude brotherhood
and it came in a special box and if you opened it up I had the sasa's
a logo on it and you opened up the box and the game like pops up and presents
itself man it was freaking good here's another section if you if I
continue up he does not move are you ready for this I'm gonna
oh no like you can't progress like you have to go to the side he is in a wall
right now in the tutorial phase
yes my dad gave me it I was so happy I was so lucky
well I'm a sip my fish
we're holding the apple of Eden
jump the page doesn't load if you
click the link in the description did I mess up my own donation link
oh this is a beautiful song
hmm
oh the theme song I think that theme is called uh family auditory
if I could it's such a lovely ball it takes you to just your profile but not
the tip page eeps um
can management can you update my link live on the stream
nothing that will come come time far in the future
better thanks management we need not worry about see
have our work is finished put that be so funny
so we are now going back to Montregion which is the home of the auditory
family we upgraded the arsenal while you were away
and we've been introduced to cannons customary for you to fire cannonballs
and visitors my apology we told them a few days ago
my men are still being trained in their use
look how much money we have 53,000 Florence which was
the currency Florence yes so we are now heading back from
il vaticano roma with mario on our little horsey
horses and we're about to come back to our family villa location you can see
that we've got the brother uh not brotherhood the assassin's
logo on top and it feels very famous in the village
uh because he's kind of the back it's you
it's good to be home these places just keep getting better
yes so everyone's very happy to see it see you back thanks to you
and we also renovated this place in Assassin's Creed too
it's your sister claudia you're glad to be home
how is mother she's fine i heard you will be turning but i'm glad to see
you with my own eyes the contestant for me too
the contestant
here
you're truly dead she has a really like good but bad
voice line at a later section but it ruins it if you've not played
this game
so we are assigned three i repeat three little side quests here and it just
kind of shows you you know you can walk around you can walk around in the
game uh if you hold the trigger you will do
and look no one uh a bit of degradation there mate
need some help
did you know to say push in italian
oh also it's yours a bit of a a bit of a slag
a bit of a waman's man we bit of a slag but anybody anybody
we'll make sure he gets his whole oh that's actually scott's i can teach
to say get your whole means to pump a girl
class i could tell the moment i saw you no one in town watch who's such
bern i am sure it's on itself to be proud
what do you know of it he's this laudia thinks the world of him
but he rarely visits us know what i gather
is this the rizio auditory definite for renzi for real for real
you you the party was supposed to be a secret
well that's what happens loose lips and all that both bought man top hen
i am sure i can think of several things i'll be waiting for you when we get there
she is offering us gratitude and services to keep her sealed
she won't be sealed once i'm in the room i don't know what she's like
so we have to complete our first quest
i have something in mind oh she's touching her chest there is one condition
uh nipple stimulation you must wait until tomorrow
oh it's always tomorrow with you lassies
it's never now it's never like come on let's go behind the dumpster
always the morrow with lassies man can i trust him
the link in description has been updated just make sure in obs you have the
audio set to monitor
sure i'll totally do that anyway uh one out of three side quests okay
so you're supposed to do the flower girl first okay because she drags you
into the villa like up to the villa okay
uh fancier shag from hcw himself can i do an italian accent with the scottish
slang fancy ashay uh no i didn't i just
sounds like say fancy ashay like no no toilet time
oh mario is going to murder me i have lost his favorite horse
ah you're tipping wait i didn't hear it though i see the tip i saw the tip
i saw the tip oh hold on wait i just bet if you run ahead of the horse you can
actually get the horse first time in the tutorial section keep running keep
running keep running and then if you press spam b
oh we missed it you can get it first time in this tutorial section
i'll open up the stream elements so i can see who just
oh my god this freaking horse he always jumps around
get on the okay there we go horse speed trippers dominated check
but you can't do that world record pace ruined
wait so did you guys hear any notification of that tip
i need to go read it hold on oh my game paused oh my god such a professional
streamer by the way uh stream elements uh mm-hmm okay stream elements sign in um
we hear it you don't i did hear it oh you heard it was it loud i need to turn it down
oh no i don't have my login for stream element i can connect it to my youtube
uh management that connected to my youtube or is it no wait that doesn't sound right
no it should be connected to youtube stream elements should be connected to youtube yes
yes okay if the stream goes down it's because i'm a fanny
fill stop that is the same uh uh can i
uh right why is it showing me people subscribe to the youtube channel that's terrible well it's
good that you subscribe but it's clogging up the freaking thing right save
i see it i see tips i see snow paws as well taha get it anyway sorry thank you so much
6.9 Assassin's Creed battle hood thanks for playing this game uh why are you
thanking me this is literally my favorite game uh someone called bejinga works now okay
and anonymous for the four thank you for the tips i really appreciate it
right okay straight back into the fun we've just spend as much time in battle as your uncle
my battles have already won i see that is good news
arrivederci has arrivederci
are you squinting me right now right so you're like so the next objective is up there and you'll
be sitting yourself oh i am gonna have to really annoyingly walk up all these buildings climb
them up eh no the game is kind enough to give you these sandbags up the sandbags you go
right why can i not hear notifications i'm actually gonna miss donations if i don't have the sound
on just give me a second i'll just uh uh huh mm-hmm mm-hmm yep i know what i'm doing
advanced options okay advanced options so hear me out hear me out okay monitor
monitor monitor only monitor and output that sounds right yeah yeah that sounds right
um hopefully i'll hear it next time if someone is wait i can repeat the donation like a five head
oh i missed a donation anonymous said how's your day started i'm fucking poke champ hold on i'm
gonna test this if i can hear this are you squinting me right now i hear it okay i will
know when people are kind enough to tip thank you for the tip thank you for the 420 blaze it
how's your date i'm freaking polkers man congrats on the agency what'd you say about the agency
why doesn't not display your message i'll need to update that later i don't think i can do it right
anonymous congrats congrats on your debuts good luck to you thank you are you squinting me right
now that's 50 why are you giving me 50 that's a lot of money that's like that's i'm gonna be honest
that's a lot of money you need to be careful giving me a lot of money uh because i'll just spend it on
the girls thank you 50s a lot though please be um came to your pockets and you know save for your
future and all that the cannons the cannons okay back into the game i apologize but thank you for
the 50 thank you everyone for the tips honestly all the time in the world now all the time in the
so poor esio thinks he's retired after his escapades and assassin's creed too has ended
brotherhood's about to give him a very terrible wake up call
so we're now getting the cannon master to fix the cannons
it's
not clock it's ac oh thanks for being with me macy appreciate you i think she's asleep right
now
wait why can't i open up the game now oh i cannot be this bad please i cannot be this bad at
streaming hold on right there right right right but now i can't see myself oh you know what you
know what you know what okay okay okay i can now see the messages i can now see myself and i can
see chat so i won't miss a thing surely won't miss a thing surely surely call me surely temples
didn't call me strong enough okay i can see don't know if i miss them i can see chat i can see
assassin's crew
what makes you think i can even read that
i'll read it after the sections
that is the future i can't believe it there'd be it too can i tell you a sad story i actually
really cried like i cried squiddin me right now eh right i'll read the the random italian
this person thinks i could think i can say ciao mio caro eraro verdre uno così belle
e cosi te lantoso for se puiowni i se gnarami la tua bellissima lingua thank you for listening
to my italian well i gotta give to compliment again on your heart love the accent by the way
how many times did you play the game to know it so well um the answer is uh i actually couldn't
even count how many times i've played this game i love you know anything killing us is that breath
take a drink of war
did you saw my mother in italian okay one of my biggest pet peeves about this game
the freaking cannons so you see how the hit markers there it looks like you're gonna hit it
and the cannons are like way loud in this game they're like far too loud they're insanely loud
foul-ass breath the guy sounds like a skyrim god most video games reuse uh voice actors so you
will recognize people over and over again it's very common if you work in a video game that you
will be used for mbc's for example um are just miscellaneous characters all the time very common
skyrim is probably the biggest example of like the same seven voice actors being used over and over
again um other than sissuru and skyrim shout out to sissuru and skyrim can't remember the actual
guy's name but goodness greatly he said hi my dear it's rare to see one so beautiful and so talented
maybe you can teach me a beautiful laugh wait you can't even speak english and you like my accent
bro you're gonna be in for a shot come on my favorite oblivion line oh let me retake that
let me redo that and they left it in the game okay we have now just finished all our three
side missions we have just handled the cannons hmm suspicious i wonder why we have also been
able to ride a horse that's because in later parts of the game horse riding is very uh necessary
to explore certain locations um it's just not possible on foot it is partly you can do it but
it just takes up so much time um and we also helped the lady which established that itseo
adetori is a bit of a bit of a ladies man and he's out for ladies holes i mean we're all out
for the ladies hole at the end of the day aren't we lads hey hope this is outrageous
by zura by zura by zura
there are two major uh hubs of english voice actors the pill from the pleasure of your presence
so this is katarina sports uh she is a real person uh did occur your mercenary a very badass
personality is likely that i can give you what you see based on a real person but we will talk later
we're like katarina do fanny and because we're getting her last hair once so far
that's her mummy mummy that's marquia velly recurring character
i wish i could show you the magic she performed very good line
there the moving painting of the goddess minerva spoke
told of a terrible tragedy to befall mankind in the future
but gave hope of lost temples that will provide aid to humanity and then she called out to a
phantom desmond as if he were there who's dead beside her after her warning she vanished
amazing i cannot imagine such wonders the vault did not house the terrible weapon fear
this is good news what about this goddess this minerva did she appear human yes but her words
proved otherwise all of her kind died many years ago i wish i could show you the magic she performed
oh that was a good delivery good delivery
the script pulled off another one i got you pulled up another one
i'm surprised she remains so composed just watching the mirror on her the spaniards lives
some of the voicelines are a bit goofy you should have killed you we're sure to suffer for it i'm not
here to debate the past together we should discuss the future no i am leaving me
i do not know why you spared him but i trust your judgment
damn straight you do uncle mario here real one
that's me uncle mario
mario maria auditory that's your mummy big mummykins did you know actually that's a bit sad
maybe not we'll just continue to the next part of the sequence oh right ready everyone group
session right now everyone get it out not for this bit the bit that follows after hold on
wait for it wait for it see this is what happens when you pay for the premium pass at the violour
meet and greet booth you're presented with a bathtub and then this part is me that's you
okay that's you in the bathtub this next bit is me
all this for a hundred dollars for the premium pass yes please
coming at you my bikini welcome home reflin in my accent obviously i'll have to like really
put on that accent welcome home reflin mom is misty
do you think a con would let us have a meet a booth that would be hilarious
oh i forgot about that part of the scene oh oh like what happens in the asmr booth stays in the
asmr booth everyone's okay everyone's uh fun fact i played this game in front of my mum and she was
mortified at this scene because i was very very young uh and i remember playing it at midnight
and i had the dining room chair in front of the tv my mom let me play it on the big tv
uh and she was like what are you playing i'm like it's a sapis grade mom please i didn't make the game
one should always have the freedom to choose oh so salty so salty
so what's that probably just training exercises
yeah damn training exercises out of control
i have to find mario and rally putting the ass in the size
actually that's another side note i can't remember why my dad needed to spell
oh i was telling my dad about like some of my favorite games of all time like a couple of years
back now he was like how do you spell assassin i was like ass ass in and we both looked at each
other like that shrek meme like like burst out laughing such children honestly
i'm not i'm not gonna lie if i felt like that my ankles would be gone they would be dust
okay this is the worst part of the game that's about to come up because you can
do everything right and the game will still fail you
so mario has the apple of eden piece of eden
away
the one italian like oh my god she really likes assassins my goodness
to say helping uh oh no we lost our monies it's not about the money money money
forget about the money money money
you do not actually have to do anything the horse will automatically run for you in this sequence
so the entire town is now being absolutely destroyed and raided and i'm currently
singing that one scottish song
all the horses get back up in this video game i just for anyone who doesn't like when the horses
go down and with you with that the horses always stand back up in video in this video game no horse
ever stays down even if it's been attacked if it's been hurt lalala okay this is the part i hate
you can destroy all the cannons and all the freaking towns people won't escape and you can
fail this section i have done it consecutively all you have to do is destroy the cannons ignore
everything else but the freaking it's really hard to tell yeah see i should have hit that third one
but it's really hard to tell like with the edges of like the radius your area of effect if you will
and my goodness gravy it's frustrating
no horses were harmed in the production of this video game no they're not so
please don't worry all horses get back up the aoe area of effect it's it's so freaking hard to
tell because you could perfectly angle it and you're like i should have three but yeah and especially
the ones on the hill this oh beautiful beautiful do that again hen do it again do it again do it
again give us three oh baby right so unfortunately you can't really do much more after you've killed
this one boom baby okay next section we've got to do this bit correct because this is where you can
fail the problem with the hill is you have to like judge behind the cannons oh triple baby
let's go three for three obviously we can't do it for this one because it's not third but
we've got three for three so far
okay wait what that one survived hello
excuse me excuse me do my eyes uh so this is the problem you can't really hit those ones
now you might be saying you should hit that big brown thing i've forgotten what their legal name
is uh but the big brown thing doesn't count uh we can kill it we've done what we can so either
we'll fail or we'll win depending on what the game feels like see there's 20 villagers 10 5
we did it we didn't get a balista a siege tower i
soldiers are climbing the walls okay this is one bit i don't like about this game are you ready for
they change your weapons so they've given me a sword i've said uh let me keep my blade out because
i prefer fighting with a blade the only enemies that you're not to go against with the blade
jump down nco jeez yeah my ankles would be disintegrated if i did that um it's much easier
to fight with the blades oh my god he just curbstomped that borja guy did you see that nco
that's a war crime you can't curb stomp people that's not how it works jeez it's the old okay hold on
these enemies oh my god i just got twatted oh i'm getting twat twice sorry i'm too busy
try and be chatting and kill at the same time um no i'm missing oh no everyone gonna know i'm a
terrible gamer um the only enemies that are not effective so like these guys for fuck's sake
they freaking attack before they're supposed to you can break their stance just by spamming
it's not a problem again you for these guys that are double armored up literally take your gun out
boom up it didn't register esio he's getting a bit close mate you're gonna need to aim
that was getting a bit close for comfort
point blank esio that probably wasn't even five meters no been do we need to put glicks on him
oh this is a sad bit
no
this is an invitation my family to yours
to yours
there was a sentence that he said though that your friend this gun that your friend fashioned for
keep that in mind i can walk faster means to stop in italian
so we are now basically running on fumes adrenaline wise we've literally just been
absolutely destroyed we have three bullet wounds i think shoulder uh abdomen oh okay
just to show we've got two bullet wounds i could have sworn it used to be three but
i won't probably just wish me wish me remember being uh but yeah we've literally our liver is
currently bleeding out our kidney most like ow what happened there did you see me get turned
into that rubbish pile i was like liquid did you see that ouch i don't want to be jelly please don't
turn me into jelly hey leaf claudia lonia bam
so you'll get assigned one soldier to kill in the sequence but they all do they all are aggressive
towards you you can clean them up if you really desire but if the arrow is red that means the
ai has assigned to attack you if the arrow is yellow they'll attack oh also the guards have
assassin abilities like how are you sitting on the wall the coding in this game is a bit funny
if you upset NPCs they turn into assassins and start climbing walls and stuff
you could always break a guard's stance with a kick if you are struggling to fight them
but we do get access to long range weaponry very shortly um but yeah uh you can ignore all these
and just go straight in here no you can you have to wait until they're assigned to you okay okay
okay the game does it quite often where it won't let you in if uh someone is target locked onto you
hey come on claudia we ain't got all day jesus we're under a siege take your time hen
it's you i'm in here i will hold the back stop wait for us we thought you had to kill sir etio
not yet where does this passage lead to the north outside the walls are you surprised it exists
i might have to open my door um i must go help the troops my freaking room is getting so hot
with this computer i'm coming so we're currently inside the auditory villa we're now going down
down down down deep inside down deep inside see how do you pick them
i'm sweating um i'm sitting on my sweaty feet right now i don't know how you guys
sit in your chairs but i sit on my feet
we will play assassin's creed 2 because that is a very beautiful section in assassin's creed 2
we're essentially playing assassin's creed 2.5 it's fame brotherhood's good game
right lure lure i'm gonna take a war sip war sipping tin take a sip with me if you don't got war
you must leave this place take mother to parence get me a horse you are not coming with us
where are you riding to roma go my son destroy them but remember for whom we assassinate
the horse was a paid actor
i'm not flexible enough to sit on your feet i'll make you flexible once i've done me
sorry
we're actually speed running
just love this game a little everything about it the patience fantastic we've
completed sequence dna one battle wounds achievement unlocked
i will tell you at the end a very sad fact about that blonde girl you see on the screen right now
but only at the end right so that says in present day
congrats if your name's desmond congrats congrats if your name's shawn shawn's one with glasses
congrats i'm convinced we need to get our hands on etio's apple of edin minerva altered it somehow
when she are they tame traveling where's the autotorizo i will tell you in a second it's our
last safe but we were present day it turns out the templars are watching the border etio hid the
the poe sometime in 1507 but when i try to access that dna sequence he seems to be remembering
something else like a memory inside a memory yes exactly maybe exactly maybe i believe you
experienced something similar if i could have stagger didn't you subject 15 exhibited memory
within memory like patterns but she was pregnant the memories of prego's father and not in this
oh my god we've just been fat shamed in 2024 you guys remember when bao got that model
and she was like inflated and someone was like this is fat shaming it was like no bro that's real
34 open your eyes
legend coming out in inflation model and someone's like you're fat shaming it no more the bugger
they're gonna find us no they aren't come with me
there's a lot of cutscene stuff up ahead but i'll try and for those who don't know the game
i will very quickly summarize from the inside we're not getting in this way what's her next
move the road just moves back into the highway this is not a good place for us to be right now
do we have any tarps we need to cover up the van i really hate to stress this yeah but we are
running out of time that's Sean we'll help us that's Rebecca that's Lucy any ideas i don't know
maybe there's another way into the sanctuary hey i think i've got something
okay so we're modern day Desmond if you don't know the game we basically have a special bloodline
that commutes to the gods that created us and and we use Desmond's DNA sequence in order to go
back in the past very fictional based i absolutely love the concept when i was a child and i wanted
it to be so real i was like take me back to the battle of anaconda take me to big willy walrus
i want to see the construction
so we are like the trunk i'm sorry i don't know what the trunks are
are memories are stored in DNA yes that's the quickest way oh my god me and Lucy
oh yeah you don't have fun you'll have fun with me the night Lucy
okay
okay there we go oh that was a loading screen by the way it looked like it wasn't they were trying
to hide it what was that i don't see anything so Desmond also sees the past because his it's
basically leaking into his present so Lucy can't see any of this we can see this
they escaped through here what that's you and the villagers after the attack i can see them now
i know it's difficult but try to compartmentalize focus on the present what if i can't stop the
visions how long before i start painting symbols on the walls don't joke about that subject 16 had
the bleeding effect that he's talking about and ended up in himself but we learn more about him in
Assassin's Creed 3
well the animus he does turn man please do not refer to the animus that lets us go back into the past
is the animus
oh is it revelation
oh it's
i'll find a way around oh it's revelations you're right sorry my apologies i apologize
i would say this is a revelation do you guys remember dan bull's cover of Assassin's Creed
brotherhood revelations where i meant if you see any remind me not to make you a look out
so we are now backtracking her weight oh sorry more ghosts this is the problem there's so much
dialogue in this game at the start and we are now backtracking trying to get back inside the villa
oh no claudia that's our sister
just joined why is he wearing jeans we're in present day actually yeah could you jump
about in jeans how about you give me a boost i don't even wear jeans i don't even wear clothes
after time actually do you want to guess what clothes i'm wearing right now because it's not
what you think
we are selling tutorials so it's a bit slow but what are you going
um i just wear a bra and a hoodie that's it so my bare arms is on my game and chair right now
with my sweaty feet as well they never stop sweating neither do my hands my hands are very
sweaty right now actually but they don't sweat as much as my feet i'm sorry i don't i don't think i
don't care i'll show up about that oh my marriage oh i have marriage oopsies forgot to talk about
that i have marriage if you want to support me i'm getting key chains with girls and we're i'm
gonna make a little keychain ASMR so the thing about this cut scene you have no health so you
can literally just do that there you can't die in this cut scene in this section of the game
it's not a cut scene it's a section again you can just drop down it doesn't really matter
when did this become i wish i was rich then what would be left for you
nothing nice try ready
god well lucy's such a skinny legend honestly found a switch
oh no no don't do that that's the woody here we go
oh something's open yeah my leg hey yo
absolute brain so he shouldn't have said this line yet because oh i've never had that happen
before i got pushed out of the way by the shadow oh my god i've never had that happen before the
shadows are freaking i wonder if you can attack the shadow i've never been pushed out the way by
the shadow before see this is the thing about playing the same game over and over something
you'll happen every time and it's just fantastic anyway we're about to swim in medieval toxic waste
the game's being coded as you play
easy for you you aren't swimming in medieval toxic waste
it was lucy's idea
whoa whoa uh see when the camera angles start to shift it actually makes things like really hard
to judge it's good for the skin remember that one post where that guy was like i'll for 500
dollars let me go in your septic tank and he just hangs out in there and does the thing and it was
like oh you're i mean yeah that was quite the pose
you're going so fast the game can't keep up that was minging on his phone
i have to get wet because you're here charming oh my god it's you know this man
did you just ask a woman why she's not wet thanks that's sexual harassment honestly
water check oh i just fell water oh well it's fine
sorry it like cold water just went on my leg and i'm like ah you know what that's fine
that's actually not that big a deal
jesus it's you know that's brutal making someone fall to their death
now i'm wet i'm a cut of fish i was wet from the start
human resources why a septic tank it's just what the guy wanted it's like that japanese post
oh this is another thing there is this is a true hashtag true story um
so this wife went away on holiday for the weekend and her neighbor on friday went into her like
toilet tank like japanese toilets are different from the way it's like done so he could look up
and peep at her while she disintegrated basically um and because she went away on holiday uh that
man perished uh via um freezing to death in kaka it was like bro don't get me wrong i'm no really
any shame in anyone for what they like but to die to die i'll wait here
it's a bit extreme it's a bit extreme like oh i did the last one oh jisun messed up on that one
i'm not gonna lie oh jisun uh got it yeah thank you desmond did they scatter his ashes that's too
funny that i can't even laugh at that that's awful that's awful oh my god that was so quick what is
anyway the sequence is just teaching us the relationship that it's ill has with lucy
a desmond has with lucy jesus i have the bleeding effect myself no no before you freaking take
that out of context the bleeding effect is when desmond thingy's uh vtuber's stomach is so it must
mean they're they're just a ketchup packet no stop it with the ketchup packet allegations okay
vtubers can't beat them enough my goodness vtuber feels mildly ill oh she must be a ketchup packet
you stop that right now naughty naughty stop it it's all right i'm a mustard pat it comes out
yellow hello should i be worried do we need to get you a doctor
when the past memories and new ones melt in yes desmond has a very hard time differentiating
himself from xio because he spends so much time in the animus as xio i mean you'd do it too
you'd do it too you'd do it too all right friendly over the section
oh my god it's the back of the statue
repeat after me stat u that's how you say statue in scott's stat u no t stat u
oh i guess there is a t technically
well i'm as if you die in the animus
and you just perish
naughty i've finished
wow weapon ice gets free true
oh
that's you must have come back your way after the attack but why desmond desmond let's open that
door and eat big dizzy here's like big easy big as you are the three
do you have any fizzy juice no i may get cooler later but right now i'm i'm high i'm high is okay
i'm literally playing my favorite game of all time i'm allowed to just word vomit and do whatever
i please life is good brov brov life is good i'm happy i hope you know this experience is enjoyable
don't apologize about burps i don't burp much of war but hey can you open the damn bookcase desmond
says shon as i cut over his voiceline
yes it's ill has three things about bloody time sassan's great to sassan's great brother
to sassan's great revolutions are all it's well the story line there are numbers underneath
the numbers may send oh my god we need to play black ops in 1421
oh my head oh that's all right desmond has a boo boo
let's get the animus down there
you're gonna create an entire corporal weirdo
uh um was watching the everyone's 2.0 is uh a lurking in the shadows
i'm so happy make sure you aren't followed
what is that smell it's my clothes it was lucy's idea the smell like you swam through a sewer
it was lucy's idea it was lucy's idea wait a second guys you need to remember the there's a line
is it confliction in his voice i don't think that's the word
my name rule one suck your the king
oh the girls they're absolutely fantastic in their 2.0s absolutely adore them
um like obviously i'm happy to talk about like some behind the scenes stuff but like they were
kind of shocked that i'm like yeah just do what you want like whatever you want go for it you can
see what you want obviously as long as you don't see any nda content you can talk about the interview
with me if you want you can talk about how you found the process talk about how you found the debut
um yeah just do what you want have fun i'm here to be a booty hole right look around montoregioni
for circuiters and a little dude asked they'll re-route small amounts of electricity to the
power line underneath the villa don't ask me how they work if i understood that i wouldn't be the
the fella hiding the van i used to think he um he is he wheatley i think he might be wheatley
i'm not sure from uh portal 2 so we're now currently getting an energy supply to the animus
underneath the villa in order for upstair go the big baddies are called upstair go in this game
or templar so those are the big baddies um so basically you just need to go around the city
you can see that the patched everything up from the uh five centuries ago uh that the big old
fights were occurring i really like stacey milk i saw the reaction to fondle a bosom
admit that it was funny okay admit that it was funny or pick up 24 cards in uno right now
and anyone sitting with 24 cards in their hand are liars okay fondle a bosom was hilarious i don't
care i think someone was like it sounds like you're naming them from like that parody um uh that parody
movie uh austin powers and i'm like yeah you're supposed to have fun names who want serious names
that like no one can remember like cuttles cuttlefish okay strongy cuttles let's go uh a polar bear
okay i see i see snow paws yes she has paws and she's cold i see snow paws let's go like it's
really it's not that bad um so you're supposed to just look around with eagle vision to get a sense
of moving around um and all that jazz there's like one right next to me isn't there yet it's right
behind me uh box that was not a name carambi no carambi for like a cs go whichever perfect name
don't care carambi yes and caram sounds like ha ha ram so you can probably make a few puns
yes it's booted we're good to go yes it's booted name from money python's life of bright incontinent
above african saw you's all laughing at it and someone posted that incontinent to a screenshot
i was like oh no they've got me laughing that was like oh that was actually really funny
right we're going in the animus we're about to go back into the past to be it's your auditory
if we're still in the tutorial stage i will tell you when we get out of this tutorial stage
we've still probably got another hour in a bit sanctuary sanctuary as you may have noticed in
the van i've made some improvements to the animus and i've already seen a new vr training program
here you can show off all those flashy moves you picked up from your ancestors let me open one
in the mission ac show ac hall okay but it doesn't make sense maybe if we had like a fire and ace
like vtuber design ac no we can't like call ac we already have ac oh oh shit okay so this is
the virtual training i despise it i absolutely despise it i just cannot stand this section
it's for people who enjoy the combat or practice in it me i hate to despise it okay you see that
skinny guard he is a problem they can grab you yeah see the guards are trying to grab me and then
it breaks your streak if they grab you and it's so annoying i freaking hate the wee guards honestly
oh and i hate the lancers too i absolutely hate it i'm much better in combat yeah fuck you take it
take it the lancers have much bigger reach and are very hard to counter so when you're on a
killing streak it's much better to aim for those guys to defend your streak basically
skinny ball bad guards oh honestly lancers hate the skinny guards hate because they are agile
warriors and you have to freaking have a wee knife out in order to counter them properly
shrimp check yep posture still shrimp thank you oh we're in the tutorial for like another two hours
but the reason i'm going to praise the game is because it's hidden that you're in the tutorial
you progress through the story of the game via the tutorial like i know it sounds silly to praise
that because obviously all games work like that but i'll kind of point it out if you need to take
a break log out of the anime you can leave the machine whenever you like i'm all set to go don't
worry one last thing as you raise your synchronization by executing is that the way
press memories might even discover some repressed memories she be caught in bottom
ass and feet locked on that seat oh that's actually a really good like model
ready for like a eight hour stream ass and feet get on that suit
anyway i never expected you to see you play something i have terrible news but these
shippers normally play a video game with eye in the database now you won't find it
okay we're here present day
give me one second i'm gonna get a cola okay i'll leave that on so at least i'm not yapping
over the actual cutscenes for once in my freaking life
oh my god we're being touched by a whammy sorry i forget my hip i need to close my eyes if i walk
away so the sleep thing clicks on right but come on me come on me oh my god listen to the music
beautiful
oh gorgeous
i just got chills it's such an idiot i just love this game so much
it's just feel like so full of it like my heart feels so full i get to share this game and
just appreciate it for what it is and this game come out in 2010 and it aged beautifully i will
not tell i will not take anyone telling me this game didn't age well so we're currently injured
and going to the doctor we're about to learn about health bar so we're still injured we're
still hurt in the top left corner we have five health squares and only one left that is how
we deal with health in the game do not take that horse i don't know why they put that horse there
unironically you don't go any faster on the horse to get to the healer
trying to tip you it says internal server it's okay you don't have to give me money just hanging
out it's fine i'm not sure what the problem is but hey but don't worry you don't have to give me
money thank you for being here for a man of your age tisk tisk
someone your age cannot recover from your wound like this with medicine here is something to
dull the pain it would heal over time four out of five doctors would suggest leeches
no leeches things however i can recommend several good colleagues around the sea do you
need anything else have fun at work don't worry guys if you ever have to leave stream i am an
endurance streamer i'm not very friendly because i'm a long time streamer um i do plan on streaming
for eight hours or finishing the story mode of this game um and tomorrow we will 100% it
because i've never 100% at the game before but with your encouragement i think it's possible
i think i could 100% this game when you collect all the board your tower like the flags um
all the hidden flags that are also in the halls of narrow which i will teach you all about very
shortly so this beautiful cutscene is how we unlock sections of the map on the HUD okay they're all
hidden at the moment but we are going to be doing map update as you can see uh synchronized view
points beauty beauty beauty it jokes on you i'm listening at work oh my god those are the naughty
naughty stinky borja we don't like borja we don't take kindly to your kind around these parts borja
100% in this game in two days possible yes sir with autism anything is possible i'm so sorry
i'm so sorry i apologize um i am very passionate about what i'm passionate about and if i am like
unable to do so so ie i can just straight up like play this game the way i wanted then yes
we're also like 100% in skyrim next week achievement one i'm so sorry it must be like really weird
just randomly coming out with it i'll uh we'll refer to the strontism how about that so we're
currently tailing do you see the yellow hit marker or hit box above these this is tailing it means
do not be discovered by them they can be pushed by npcs so they can turn around and look at you
it's not um it's not the best but um it certainly works perfectly well um
it's absolutely beautiful game so we're just entailing these guards don't look backwards
unless an npc kindly bumps into them so we can get as close as we want we can like creep on the
walls cc he just turned around there if i wasn't creeping on the wall even the game's like uh you
should maintain your distance you're a bit too close but we can like creep creeping
okay and you can also blend in but i am not controlling the movement of this crowd the
crowd will go on a certain path so you can part ways but you cannot be discovered while concealed
in a crowd like this guards can walk by me i can have high notoriety and guards will ignore me as
long as i am coming 100% in the achievements in skyrim sorry i don't mean 100% in skyrim because
that is impossible as you said because of the repeating quest factors the achievements i have
100% in skyrim achievements multiple times and i would absolutely love to share the experience
with you and tell you about all the secret uh little bits i know um and yeah okay i'm also
going to mention the multiplayer in brotherhood i believe the servers are down okay oh whoa that
just came out nowhere hold on hold on we weren't even at the we were not even at the section okay we
didn't even go we were nco didn't kill civilians did that kill a human like a non-guard what is
going on oh my god sorry the sequence was not supposed to start on that staircase it's supposed
to start by this freaking did that kill him if i'm a citizen
what just happened i think i was too distracted i apologize but don't worry we can always replay
and come back for 100 percent i can't believe i just killed a citizen i never make that mistake
in this game sorry
i too have lost family to the rope
i understand how can you my libya was innocent i have lost family to the rope treachery
you called you cuddled off that's so hangy if i cut her rope
what the fuck down sorry you guys didn't see that all these options just popped up on my screen
i was like these are too many things going on right now okay so this quest do you see how
we are assigned someone with a name that is because you're actually killing multiplayer
characters that are in multiplayer i know it sounds silly and i know it sounds bizarre but
when you could play uh assassin's group brotherhood multiplayer um you got to pick between the skins
and we're literally about to kill someone who is a skin in the multiplayer mode uh 100 for this
one is just air assassination super simple and easy uh the guards do attack you but some turn
into cowards once you kill multiple guards which is a lovely paypal support doesn't open for several
hours did i break paypal are you guys trying to support me too much that we broke paypal
wait can none of the girls get donations right now uh so you can't be grabbed but as i said
the more guards you kill some of the weaker ones like the ones with just a hat will turn into
cowards which is an absolutely lovely human detail yeah see the ones with uh those like
beret type hats they turn into cowards beautiful beautiful detail i think that is gorgeous to show
human nature instead of the ai just being like constantly attack attack attack die die die
because you will i just think these are and this is 2010 development was 20 2008 2008 maybe even
as far back as 2007 um so you're not allowed to scale the rooftops because guards find you extremely
sussy but guards on the floor don'ts like this guy does not care about me right now um but like
for development that far back to like capture to even think outside the box to capture human nature
like that definitely hats off to the development team um i know it is by ubisoft and there are some
very there's a very unique ending to this tale and assassins crude brotherhood and i couldn't for
the life of me uh there's a feather up on here by the way uh you can grab sightings if you cite
something but can't grab it you can go into ego mode and then it'll automatically stick to your map
which is fantastic so if you see something but you can't grab it in the moment um but yeah
this game has also been rated in the top 100 games of all time i believe it placed around 60th
on recent 100 uh game ranking tech things but sas crude brotherhood always makes it and i 100
agree for me it is first place but i'm biased but absolutely deserved it so we have met marquia
veli this is marquia veli he was the guy um that was in the villa and that was disappointed in us
not killing the spaniard uh and he is gonna tell us what's going on in roma because we don't know
what's going on in roma we know the borja is everywhere as we can see them literally in front
of us right now so we are going to get the dirty details on what's going on in roma you would be
wise to purchase missing equipment you will not live long in roma without supplies i have my blade
and the guards have their guns good to see of the borja fortunately i can help
borja hate we hate the borja perhaps you will listen to reason i'm gonna burp is that okay
i will let you know that was me popping my lips that was the actual burp sorry sorry to mislead
you like that so you need to wait for a little second because if you go too quickly into the
blacksmith the items won't actually be available to purchase which is your literal quest so you're
buying an armor and a small weapon this small weapon is what you use against the skinny guards
because it is amazing for taming on defending yourself now you can survive that's right that's
right i debated you didn't know yeah you thought that pop was my burp
and
so for some reason even though you're right next to him
he gets really quiet in certain voicelines
i'm literally hugging him to get him to talk
money
jar of leeches
so again eagle vision to lock in that flag because we can't grab it right now but that's okay
so
okay so we're starting to learn that the borja has overtaken roma and is completely messing up for
the people and mark you avail is obviously not very happy but we have to do what the current
laid-out rules are and the yummy jar of leeches the cuttlefish eat leeches i feel like they probably
do
i'll talk after this but
water check should we not travel by horse roma is quite large as chaserates conquest in romania
continue to succeed the borja growing power they have taken desirable areas of the city for
themselves we cannot use the stables here oh they will have the borja is low now what are
you implying it's you do not play dumb with me matthew early do you have some kind of plan
i am improvising okay now to very quickly bring you up to speed the borja are forbidding us in
this section to use the stables and other areas of development also this is the most
fucking annoying thing to get a hundred percent on hold on oh get off the horse i hate when they
go on the horse oh no i've made it so much worse okay so this captain you have to grab him and put
him in that um uh oh my god that freaking citizen was in the way i didn't want to strike in case
i can't see because of the camera angle by the way this game aged really well it aged really well
i promise it aged well no right i am going to no he's on it no this couldn't have gone any worse
please i've never had this issue in this game before right just grab him grab him and push him
fuck him you can kill no right no right we're not a hundred percent in this right now i'm literally
bright red an embarrassment of this gameplay where fuck you fuck you fuck you fuck you
please get off the horses i hate when they're on the horses all right maybe i can do it hold on
oh my god i can still 100 percent it okay you need to basically drag this guy to the scaffolding
and push him in it yes whenever you kill a captain of a district always loot his body he has insane
amounts of money on his person that was terrible but we resurrected it the reason and you have to kill
the other guards first is so you are free to push that guy into the scaffolding to achieve 100 on this
borgia tower my god i have never attracted those other four guards before i've never had them jump
on freaking horses before that was terrible but we did it we got a hundred percent oh my god
i'm my face is bright red i'm like oh my god oh i forgot to burn the tower oh for goodness sake
we're okay we need to call it not the tower oh my god i'm getting so flustered oh right so we've
just reclaimed this district so you need to burn the tower to in order to symbolize to the borgia
they're no longer welcome in this area and their rules no longer apply to this current district of
roma okay wait i'm an idiot markia valley hasn't told me to burn the tower yet please pardon me
for jumping that i'm skipping ahead of the game right out my way out my way out my way out my way
the guards make peep you here but they don't actually get you okay we are now giving instructions
you are right we need to send they see oh i might need to take my hoodie off i'm sweating and embarrassed
man i was like oh my god you guys are gonna think i've never played this game before i'm like no
it's my favorite game of all time the guards outside there will peep you but they'll never
follow you inside as long as you keep moving yeah the guards will never go for you um literally
xio is exhausted he's climbed this tower three times now he's like jesus women give me a break
okay you can ignite to the borgia tower like so
oh because they all get killed okay now this is another interesting part of the
game which you can renovate districts to have an income
the controller vibration on the literally uh is crazy okay we have just renovated the
stables we now have access to horsey warseys yeah no so we will jump on a horse thank you
horse vtuber we love you he does he's supposed to talk to you through this but it bugs out so
he's not talking to us right now but basically he's like uh you can't just do what you want xio
it's dangerous roma have been here the borgia have like settled their ways the people are scared
basically too long didn't read thank you marquia valley for your input it always bugs out he should
be talking to us like right now you always use the white and gray horse here i'm gonna say something
oh here we go but can you also close them i intend to heal the sickness or treat it simple
stop sparring with me fine let us talk openly there
oh he mad at us i am inclined to disagree look at this is the center of borgia
killing one man and not change this you need to take away the source about
are you suggesting we are beating to the death yes brotherhood of the people yes yes yes yes
oh shit sorry sorry also you should always go behind the npc because that'll happen
the audio is bugging out
wait can you guys not hear the game
go get back with your stolen i will wait that he can't be torio i need to get
contact there i sound fit give me a bath
why oh input what you can turn this feature off i never fucking asked you to turn it on you twat
fuck off right
is it still crunching is it the game that's crunching or me that's crunching
oh shit i'm oh fuck it's a chase mission it's a chase mission
it's the game that's crunchy what the frick why have to be crunchy
why are you crunchy okay i'm opening up the game i'm gonna muck around with the audio
mission failed we'll get him next time
great why would you be crunchy even though i didn't change a single thing am i gonna have
to close the game and open it back up again i think i may have to
yeah this isn't gonna do anything okay okay we're closing the game closing the game
abort memory oh my god we're in the middle of a freaking yeah yeah yeah no progress is going to
be lost sure yes less naughty boy why would it be crunchy i got a notification and the thing was
like i am changing your input and i dismissed it because i never told it to do anything and i just
freaking did it i'm gonna burp who goes there by the pope identify yourself i said close game
did i not say close game would you like to would you like to close perhaps yes yes you may close
the game yes that's as perfectly fine you're allowed to uh right close that maybe i just
need to do desktop audio capture this is plausible and this is probable all right okay hold on i'll
down hold on look come on no streamer's gonna go without unhinged yes open close okay it's opening
it's opening drum roll come on you can do it buddy oh okay okay okay okay it's loading the logo
and we can't see it yeah i'm just like let me just set a calibrate the game real quick
just a few technical difficulties
also me this game stood up to the test of time clearly fucking not they don't
can you lovely jubbly peeps can you can you hear this is that crunchy no
no is that still crunchy if not you're just gonna have to hear my desktop audio instead
sounds good okay why is game not on stream stream screen
game hello game game would you like to show up please is it because i'm not is it because i'm not
in game no no no no don't be shy don't be shy come on let me warm you up let me warm you up come on
you can do it i believe in you that's right show your face come on show you show us your face
come on you can do it get it up get it up you fucking twat why the fuck is it
oh no i'm pretty sure Assassin's Creed brotherhood is like really problematic to capture in window
and i've just fucked it up because i closed it there oh thank fucking god i thought i was
gonna have to end the stream to like get it to start back up again don't ever do that to me again
oh my goodness oh shit right chase chase chase uh i used to kill this guy all the
get time and not understand why i'll go away keep keep keep keep keep keep
rip your ears is it too loud sorry the guards don't like me yet they're pushing me away don't
push me i'll push you stream with me okay okay okay okay oh thank god i was so worried
my heart feels full of relief it is so bootyful um obviously because of it's an older game you
can see the distance rendering not loud just the scream was ear piercing oh okay do apologize for
that sometimes i get a little bit excited but i'm sure you like it when a girl screams in your ear
not now shon not now shon go away get back here give me my money back
okay there we go we made it
did you liberate your money from our friend
and be a small victory they are up and time with work we'll have a few dozen more
depends on the the the subject six you mentioned we'll be broken we'll do that at the end i don't
want to do subject 16 right now where is my contact Vinicius he should have already intercepted the
letter okay follow me okay we are now raiding our horses through roma uh mark your valley is
just kind of spanked us for being like you believe in the people and esio goes yeah i believe in the
people and then the people just stole a lot of money from us but we got it back that's fine that's
the main thing but esio is starting the concept of the brotherhood of assassins where you take an
ordinary citizen who is fed up with life who is being treated badly who has just had an absolutely
awful time and you've gone hey do you want to get back at your oppressors and then they go uh cc
because obviously they're italian they wouldn't say yes they'd say see you and then the good part of
the the best part i would argue about this game starts up from there
okay so we're just following horsey horsey around
i love you excelene because i'm low IQ don't worry i'm low IQ in general but these are just
one of the games that i'm like uh i love everything about see the means of the projection
astronomy can relate to being a precious gosh steady on thankfully i was born in a good time
line but uh if you didn't know the english tried to eradicate uh scottish people many a time uh
however uh the romans built a wall called hadrian's wall because they weren't interested in going
any further into scotland they said now you guys can keep it we're not interested in invading us
that's true that's actually science
leave my thieves alone you foul beast oh that was a bit steady on it esio what was that so you're
supposed to like jump on them okay well we got countered so i'll just be up this i just kicked
i've never had these issues oh my god performance i can't get up one in three men
time me at the term the bass okay we'll find you at the bass okay we're about to do a major
tutorial part coming up but don't worry it's like a good part um so we're just gonna skedaddle halfway
through this we're currently in the coliseum uh coliseum has been wrecked for many a century now
this is very accurate to probably what it looks like i'm going one one one one in three men but
one in one coliseum how dare you i assure you my bony bony can my my pecker um it's so easy to get
to get engorged oh my god i want to be an announcer any engorgers anyone getting
engorged right now yeah yeah i bet you are okay this part if we can do it flawlessly first time
so i don't need to be embarrassed however the game crashes at this part multiple times for me so
first things first take out your wee knife know the big knife take out your wee knife okay
for this part that comes up because you're supposed to not get hit god damn you can see me
river and moon walked into that sequence there we are about to encounter a second enemy not
the border romuli let's see if i can do this without messing up okay pause you have to reselect
your small knife because the game always right if i don't get hit i am blessed by the gods because
you're supposed to do the sequence without getting hit i hate when they attack that blinking means
they're attacking and you can't if they have the red hit marker above their head you can't
tell if they're about to okay we got we got the ten in a row serial killer achievement
oh we did it hundred percent of that oh that bit always stresses me at my heart rate
okay this is a tutorial sequence this is called the layers of romulus
goya or romuli if you you want to get take his baking but romulus
wow i swear she killed them all with one knife so this is timed okay we're on a timer
and you will watch me pass up flags and as well as pass up treasure boxes because we will have to
come back in a hundred percent this section because in order to get the hundred percent
and time love is what this one is so we're just gonna speed on by we're gonna do a little speed
gonzalez i am not going to read chat for eight minutes it takes me about seven minutes to do
the sequence the timer is eight minutes i apologize chat i can see you rating my burp in the corner
of my eye you must always do the levers in this order in order to maximize your time
um it is possible that you fall in a sequence and you'll lose time um but normally i finish
roughly 40 seconds to one minute early um unfortunately this game's a bit funnery i've
just wasted a bit of time doing that which is a shame but hey ho it's what happens
uh but yes obviously you can tell the music's a bit different the i don't know how compose the music
or who is commissioned to compose the music very very good okay i can read you for like one second
she hates us no i'm done i need to do the time sequence i finish early oh i finish early all
right you want to tell me you can tell you how early i finish i think i've said this before but um
my record is like one minute and like 54 seconds roughly and the only reason i know why is because
that's how long the preview was for the video it was a free preview i'm just gonna admit it sorry but
if you guys are like i'm so nervous to talk to her in chat i am absolutely not destined
uh to be professional or whatever but yeah that's actually true story i could probably find the
video and share it um if you really wanted to see how good that preview was um we're under a timer so
we are just gonna kind of right okay you need to look for the open gate and i get it wrong all
the time but open gate and then take a no oh my god i get it wrong all the time do you know how
many times i've freaking played this game and i do that every single time you'd think i'd learn
honestly uh one day i'll learn but i have a fun factoid that i will tell you later once we get
to that part of the thingy but uh this will not be the only time we are playing Assassin's Creed
on this channel a Assassin's Creed brotherhood on this channel in particular um because i um have
very much tism this game into submission and i don't know should i just ruin it you know what if
you're here right now i think i'm allowed to ruin it so my birthday is the 10th of october
um oh you must always grab this light the game will pretend like you can do it so october 10th is
my donathan and you'll never guess what date uh gets mentioned in this video game october 10th
so we're playing it on my donathan um and i get to nerd about the game all over again and i'm already
beaming with happiness just thinking about it i was like oh no no no no i'm going to subject you
this twice you will you will watch me play this game twice and be so happy about it
um we're getting close to the main hall the main hall is where the last major part of the
sequence comes in i'm glad the game didn't crash actually earlier because i've not really had i
don't really experience any crashing after the wolf section once you've killed all the romuli guys
then uh not once have i had the game crash on multiple playthroughs um this game was literally
made for me for real for real like actually though like i mean how did they know like oh my god this
is work um for safety i just follow this i think you maybe can jump off as a fire but uh i'm not
risking the run i do not want to play this like section again it's not boring but hmm
i'm trying to choose my words carefully as if the dev team are sitting here watching they're not
um obviously every game section you have a preference for me being tamed to claim about
isn't but i understand that they do have to introduce some sort of element like
not to panic the player but if you were just to willfully glide through these areas then it might
be quite boresome any boresoms there's a flag to the left we will not be collecting it there's
also a treasure box up ahead again we're not going to be collecting it we are trying to get
our eight-minute timer we have entered a cutscene and we will also have a foot set there this is
the grand hall this is the last section and it's a nightmare if you mess up on it but uh i've done
it quite a lot so the CEO of Ubisoft sitting in here like you're doing what to my game um
um i always mess this bit up as well you need to look for this one in order to get inside
this section um now Assassin's Creed was made long before the yellow paint so they use candle
light and fixtures i'll show you one section that really highlights the old candle fixtures
and we're about to break this so don't be shocked it's quite loud at the breaking
yeah so the game will help you in case you mess up because they have been
they know they've made it awkward so you saw that those treasure boxes you see that flag there
again we're just gonna ignore it we're here for the speed run and we're not i actually don't know
what the speed run of this game would be i assume it's probably like under three hours the first
time i played this it took me so long to figure out where i had to go you have to go on the chair
literally the chair and then this little pathetic beam do you know how long it took me to find this
beam as a child like i started asking my mum for help because my mum plays Tomb Raider and she was
like then you look at me straw day and i'm like mum you're smiling like i'm a child you can you
must be able to see uh you must also grab a lot um to to like save yourself see this doesn't look
like you should be able to grab it but if you hold b you can get it sorry i play xbox controller uh
i don't know what it is for like ps uh four is it triangle no triangles why um
but yeah
we're almost there we're doing good for time we've not actually made any mistakes yet like
such as falling off falling off is the oh man is she fell off okay okay dude you're done
um it's the biggest mistake you can make in these time sequences uh but don't worry the game does
try to resurrect you so this is the freaking jump that i've it's freaking humongous and it's you
know you cannot make that in real life but we are perfect for times um and when you pick up
the objective the timer stops so you could in theory go back and get all the stuff you missed
however i am much more happier to continue on with the campaign but this is a tutorial section
that's part of the main quest line um for the layer of Romulus which there are six total
and it unlocks you special armor uh i personally don't actually go right we're gonna pick it up
we're gonna pick it up so we're picking it up now so the timer has now officially stopped we are no
longer under the eight minute timer so i leave my family's armor in here one of the finest sets
ever made may you who finds it receive strength and battle change of handwriting we have taken it
and set it back behind the iron door six keys unlock it spread amongst our brothers it shall
be said to come from your Romulus and they will worship it and we have a picture of the armor
that we may unlock at a later time again i don't normally unlock it through my like first playthrough
it's not necessary it's a bit time consuming as well it's probably like an extra hour so the
timer is paused if i pause the game time remaining 133 so yeah we can pick up all these treasure
boxes because we're gonna need it you get florins in this game and the campaign actually requires
you to have 3,500 florins at one section um and we just want to make sure we go above and beyond
because we cannot invest in like properties for example that part comes very soon um
how kind of them to write in clear uh yeah detail for us to read their uh evil plans basically
but there we go ancient roman tomowers would you like to taste my ancient roman tomato
that tomato at golden boy achievement unlock so we've done one that's one layer of Romulus
i'm gonna head off thank you for hanging please don't worry i believe shibi is coming up in an hour
no in 10 minutes who's coming up next
i'm going to take a drink i believe the gorgeous are supporting them is that where the ketchup
no you're done you're done bam you're not bad and nine minutes yes okay when shibi goes live
please do tell me i will always recommend you guys go watch my gen mates another encryption this one
was supposed to be ledger because they are transmitting them because i'm an endurance streamer i'd
rather you support them we have nothing sometimes logic is not the only way to are you also an older
yes you said we had allies in the city bring me to them okay this is a beautiful quest
it's a beautiful quest and it has include revelation yes you play a much older etio i
think you're like 70 years old technically and you're like jumping about paragliding and stuff and
it's like really um they really stretch the old dates to make sure they could get them in this
um see you tonight when mercy rates into you honestly though gilf etio
brotherhood is etio and his prime for you for it he's like 42 or 41 i believe in this game
bit of an old man but hey
okay we're about to unlock the next sequence it's so good
so the map of roma is massive but there's guards everywhere so he's telling us if you use the
aqueducts you can move about real quick so we are going to use the aqueduct right now to get to
island tebarina and this is where the sassans are based on on the map in roma
when mercs aired in stream stroneys just finished the intro yapping of the story
honestly oh my god azerid it's so well on her 2.0 she's fantastic with all her yapping
i think someone said yep for corn and i was like well that's pretty smart i like that
i've heard a great deal about him from my cousin so he's not really in this at all
fabio i feel like he might have been dlc content or something he has two seats in this game
and yeah i don't know what i'd rather confuse i hope we will be free
she will occurs i wonder why i picked a zura
what are you also unaware that the borja have captured the apple have eaten
oh i do have lost the apple
so you do not know what goes on with our enemies do we at least have an underground here to work
with no underground network found our mercenaries are ensnared in elusiva la volpe doesn't even talk
to me we have girls working for us in a brothel frequented by cardinals oh my god is she be you're
in my game but the madame there is okay no not that rather attend parties than further of course
what about the city's thieves do they have a deal see but they refuse to talk to us i do not know why
what are you going to do to make some friends make some friends ah such a good line
because we're about to make three different allies of different districts we're about to
make friends with the thieves we're about to make friends with the holes we're about to make friends
with the mercenaries let's go it's a very good very good we also unlock notoriety in this as well
um and we also unlock having little uh the achievement unlocked from in ruins
make friends with the holes to the window the fighter the lover and the thief to the sweat
drop off my boss oh ski ski mother you want a scottish cover of that song
right we are going to do the eagle point right now just so we can kind of see what's going on around
island tibirina please do right so we are going to purposely do the thieves last the reason for
the thieves last is because it introduces notoriety so guards are going to start harassing us a bit
more um heralds are going to start talking about the devious acts that xio has committed and we're
also going to have witnesses that have falsified their testimonies you didn't falsify your testimony
to me we've also been introduced to the bank um where we can get money for investing in the city
every 20 minutes we will get our little 20 or cut from investing in these places um
and we have withdrawn four to eight florins we are rich we're rich we're rich any you played that game
have you heard about that game that that one game about the the guys that dig in the mines
right uh we're going to go to sorry i didn't want to learn the lore of the bridge sorry bridge
not interested we're going to go to the holes first because there's holes in the lion
um and do this quest line this is the campaign quest that requires florins in order to progress
however you can get a very i think you get roughly 2000 florins for doing this quest
if you loot the bodies of the what the heck this place is bourgeois should we just destroy rest
that we're just gonna go kill the captain i hope he's not a coward because cowards run
oh he's not a coward okay we're gonna excuse me excuse me have you heard about this have you seen
about this please don't shoot me please don't shoot me i don't have much i don't have much
healing vials on me right stop shooting me at least fight me like a man come in my face and say
what are you you just completely dodged that right we're gonna heal and we're gonna loot this guy
we're gonna unlock this area because see how the the map is red that's because the bourgeois
is uh joined by this guy okay this looks bad with how much red is on screen i will get hit
there's absolutely no doubt in my head we're gonna get hit but it's fine we're gonna deal with it
we get the big guys first because these you want to kill the big guys in sequence okay no we just
attracted the attention of that guard over there which is such a shame no we attracted more attention
okay the camera angle gets really bad under here oh no we attracted more guards not again it's
happening again i can't see i can't see stop it stop it no more no more okay we're fine we're safe
no not the horse leave me alone i hate when they go on the horses okay okay
aerosacinate the horse guy okay we did it we did it okay smooth move smooth move no get off the
horse get off the horses please you're getting you're getting bulleted boom that's right get off
okay okay okay and then we're gonna stab them okay yeah the horse is beating them up gang violence
gang violence yeah i'm horse beat them up yeah horsey yeah okay we're getting a horse feature bar
let's go come on horsey beat them up horse beat them up that's right trap alone okay we're just
gonna kick them today okay i was remembered to let the body of the guards i was amazing i've never
had the horse help me before oh it's fantastic oh in the midst of good uh there might be an archer
on the other side but it's not a big deal at this point because we have got the thing uh right how
do i get up here um we are going to unlock what's called a leaping glove um which means we can do
very very big jumps uh unfortunately we can't do it at this section of the tower so we're gonna have
to drop down and reclaim it a different area we unlock that in sequence four i think at the end
of sequence four i can't remember um but it means we can jump things uh very easily and it makes
claiming much faster because right now it's a wee bit slow but it's fine um time to work please
enjoy your work thank you for hanging out i'll appreciate you i believe sheebie is going live
right now she be caught in boom if anyone would like to uh depart deeply depart it i'm sure that's
the song i am the one the only one don't need a gun to get respect up off the street my enemies your
enemies we wet them up like a canteen uh right she be sorry i'm getting very distracted she be caught
in boom is going live i am going to get uh maybe any lurking mods could post her stream link if you
guys can post links yes she be gone live yeah uh management can you post she be's link please do not
be afraid to join she be stream uh i'm probably gonna be online for like the next eight hours so uh
i can keep you company uh after that please do support my uh lovely gen mate she's fantastic
she's incredibly witty uh witty on that thief give me your money uh oh
that's really embarrassing SEO he just i just grabbed over the barrel and rolled over okay we're
not even it's okay we don't need the money it's fine it's fine it's fine okay yes please feel free
to check out sheepsters uh i'm just doing brotherhood for the rest of the day so have fun enjoyer and uh
uh oh this is the dead end i always forget the section uh normally recruitment's actually
spawning those sections and they're so annoying to try and get them do a barrel roll literally
yes oh i'm getting i'm getting shanked oh yeah oh yeah i'm getting picked up by thieves right this
this isn't a part of the lame ill for these skinny agile guys you must take out your small
weapon drapes swords as well work but um yes you had so you have to wait until they attack you
basically because they're so agile it's such a and then you can do that but
oh my god oh i don't want the guards to see me with this body we're just gonna go straight into
the memory to win the guards to make the bodies on me it was fun hanging yes have fun with sheepsters
bye bye thanks for hanging do you know where she is
multi-stream drift that means help in attack oh my god she got her look at her nose she got
a nose job look at that peak on that nose that's beautiful i will get her back
beautiful beautiful oh i really need to pee not gonna lie can i need to pee um maybe after
i finish this act we can go pee if you see top left it says like i've got 5 000 florans but i
need 2.5 it must be 3k for the banker uh sequence but that's not yet the banker comes later um
banker is a later act we are currently doing the lover the thief and the fighter
okay now that i've noticed i need to pee i really need to pee um uh brain psychology have you heard
of this uh do you want to maybe not i'm a bit rude we are just gonna run normally you can just
take a horse over this section but i find they've spawned a wee bit too much people to like walk
around and the horse really struggles to go in between like the streets especially if there's
narrow sections whereas etio can just straight up jump over uh so we will be just doing that
self-fulfilling prophecy i need to pee oh my god weapons if we all pee together at the same time
will we like affect the water like flush system why did you take out the sword etio i
he just poked him in that eye etio that was that was a lot oh
whoopsies i actually didn't mean to do that i literally just smacked my mouth i didn't mean
to kill him i'm sorry you're just trying to get your paycheck for your wife and kids and i've just
like literally made made her a widow oh don't really feel good about that one so this is a
borger zone it's actually really annoying do we do the borger zone before we do this
no we won't i can't be arsed we'll come back to this zone it's a lot easier when you have recruits
have you come for the whore are you here for the whore close enough are you dancing to me
it's what happens at football halftime oh i heard that hey let oh my god i don't remember this part
right again no way did you see the four things behind me soldiers are about to board this boat as
well okay you must loot the bodies oh i forgot to loot the body oh that's nice oh why are the freaking
now
energy pro okay so we're gonna look the bodies of the thieves because they normally have unique
items like elf and ivory 200 coins i thought it was a bit more than that uh yeah vlad then
paler coins um these items can be traded at shops for special items who goes there identify yourself
um and after completing this quest we unlock courtesans which can distract guards um they are
very vital to a later campy a later sequence uh actually the banker sequence which i previously
mentioned is when they are vital and a part of the gameplay you can also get favors done by them i
don't mean like that because they're courtesans i mean like so the base price to hire a group is 150
florans but if you wow them uh you can get a discount rate of 75 florans i've made that sound so
weird i know but it's the gameplay um the thieves if you upgrade them and impress them the thieves
will pick pocket naturally as you walk through clouds but it's a little bit more it's not awkward
to get the thieves favor they just have a few more unique um a few more unique things you have to do
i will explain it when we once we unlock it we're about to unlock it right now and it'll make more
sense um but we're basically making generic allies and soon we will make brotherhood allies which are
assassin allies and they will help your gameplay if you feel like you are a weak gamer or you're just
not there with it with timing and like things if the games are going too fast you're i can't keep up
this is the kind of game for you once you know what you're doing and get used to the controls
because once you unlock assassin recruits your life is so much easier from there it's it's bliss
it's a dream it's one of those games where not everything has to be on you in order to progress
and that these are my kind of games okay i don't want to feel stressed out uh if i don't hit that
you can quickly loot this little box that's on the balcony here uh 75 for a whole group of them
damn no wonder strongy only was 100 for the ace of wire but could you imagine if a con would let us
do that though i think we'd get kicked out i'm not gonna lie not that i'm insinuating anything
would occur in the booth but i feel like i do not know things may go hand quickly uh
oh is there sister and her mom they're in roma now
you cannot close i need your help
he he good morning good good morning good afternoon and good evening oh yes good morning
good afternoon no good morning good evening good afternoon there we go that's
so claudia is currently she be gone bum because she's about to run a grotella the blooming rose
why do these ladies have horns that was the style back and then they did their research these are
the hairstyles uh at the time good morning good evening and good night did i say the wrong way
sorry i'm a wee bit slow so we are now about to renovate this lovely location
and our sister claudia is going to run it and we now have favor with the courtesans
uh the rose that infuriate the blooming rose or something like that um there's a flag at the
top you can actually see it shimmering right now very slightly um but we're about to go insane
gentle called the blooming rose honestly though there are cons in Glasgow that would let you do xd
we were talking about like actually coming to physical cons
the most popular brothel in roma rose in fjord well invested here i keep a list of the skills
taught to my girls you're not gonna need them much think you could do better
no problem that's you the board job make it difficult for claudia's girls there are several
things you could do that would aid them i will keep that you can do side quest for the brotella
with your mum or whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa no no she assigns you quest
you do not do a quest with your mum in the game okay
apologies right okay so as i was talking about you can kind of level them up you can be given
assignments so right now it costs 150 florins to highlight uh to hire a group of girls um
send 10 guards distracted hide bodies um poison uh assassinate from blind spots
assassinate from behind smoke bomb we've not unlocked smoke bomb yet that comes later
but you can do these and gain favour with the factions and it makes your gameplay a lot easier
um right next we are going to actually factually do the mercenaries which is this one i'm just
highlighting it on the map so i don't get confused yes it is very far away um however
well we can just run there i think i can't take a horse and i cannot take the aqueduct because
as soon as you summon the horse you basically get walled off by the layout of the map which is fine
because we're literally in an area where people are supposed to be living and thriving and doing
things so yeah horses aren't really supposed to just roll all the way through though this is a lost
memory of uh the girl that got away but we're not gonna do it right now we're gonna do it at the
end i do apologize if you're really interested in the story uh what's her name chris christina
is her name um but that sad part comes in later uh it is a very unfavourable and sad memory so i
like leaving it to the end i'd rather just focus on the happy times only 500 more meters to go
christina i knew it was christina yeah this game as much as i'll meme about the render distance
like as soon as you get closer to someone i've just added so much time going this way whatever um
i'm like i'm trying to find the main freaking road but i can't find it it's really annoying
okay i found the main road and i'm about to go off it yippee oh i didn't mean to do that
swap to my sword oh this entire zone's red and i'm not strong enough to kill him we are
did we just run through the area to save us time to be honest
no no i'm not stopping you can't make me go away you stink stinky stinky guard
we'll come back once we unlock recruits um i can't get over your accent thanks respond in with it uh
if you'd like to visit Glasgow please do please support our economy because it's in absolute shambles
in the UK um maybe i should do that maybe i should like plan a trip if you ever came to
scotland and i'll be like you should go here and you should go here because i've been here and i've
been there um that'd be cute um the order is an acquired taste oh yeah stinky uh oh stinky
okay these are the french what do we think of the french what do we think of the french
we think they're fish they smell sorry there's like a football chant that's like what do we
think of the french i can't remember it but it's like what do we think of the french what do we
think of the french uh Glasgow's nice while you visited glad you didn't get stabbed the one of
the highest rate places to get stabbed however rate is one of the friendliest as well in europe
all of europe i don't know i don't know what it is what it is okay we made it we made it
we are about to meet Bartolomeo the owner i guess of the mercenary guild
come in come in i'll kill you if you don't
water check Bartolomeo you have to meet my wife Bianca oh no fantasy yeah Bianca's
his sword sorry his sword of his name is Bianca did you check behind the table okay that's a
reference to assassin's creed one just so you know
fantasy day ah don't mind if i do on chante
i still haven't harassed emi with my french uh scottish french accent
i should force her to make an ASMR french collab with me but i like purposely put my accent on
and she's just cringing in the corner don't forget to stretch yes uh i will need to educate you guys
on why we need to stretch our legs to make sure we don't have a bit of veins
our position is weak
if you can defeat them we can concentrate our forces on the french round
so i will educate you right now my lovely jubblies
did you know overwhelmingly the people that suffer from hemorrhoids which is a failure of a vein
in your booty hole is office workers because they sit down for long periods of time so i always
recommend stretching often or standing up we are all about to go for a pee break and i recommend
you all get up with me um sorry that i never explained that mission there if you kill only
the captain you get a hundred percent super simple easy and you can also pick up a flag on the way
uh so yes uh we desire to not have any issues with our booty holes so i will recommend we stretch
roughly every two hours um i've no idea how long i've been streaming for but we should probably
dozen um the guards will not harass you at this area it's super easy and you can pick up this
uh little treasure box it's phil yes um uh it's quite interesting like the knee uh this sounds
absolutely bizarre but the nature of hemorrhoids is quite interesting because it's literally just
what side am i supposed to climb up i can't get up there um it's literally just a vein in your
booty hole that's you know failed and there's nothing really more to it it's just like adios
i'm out and then that's what hemorrhoid is and you just get a cream and you know put it on your
butt and then it goes away it's really bizarre or if you're someone like it's a really a shame
i've like heard stories like people who suffer uh you need to like get on operation on your butt
but um yeah i don't know i just sorry i'm just vomiting about like biology and diagnosis and
stuff so yeah i am not expecting these topics a conversation and so i do apologize do we go left
or right here i actually i think yeah we were supposed to go left okay
the butthole though yes you you will have the healthiest booty hole uh enjoying my streams
because we will have healthy butts together uh okay first synchronize the viewpoint and then
ignite the board your tower do not ignite the board your tower first because the viewpoint
will not register and you will have to claim the tower all over again once you have done a tower
you never have to go back up it there is no uh treasure chest added on top of the tower there
are no flags added on top of the tower um yes i don't worry i love every second of your conversation
yeah i do like my conversational topic uh the game will always give you a way up fast if
they've kind of put you in a thingy because they literally leave you in the water after that
sequence and i was like okay then i guess we will call a horse very quickly or we'll steal a horse
but a really strange developmental fact is um depending on the horse's color depends on its
speed in the game the lighter and whiter the horses the slower it is and then obviously it goes up to
all the way to a black horse and a black horse is the fastest horse you can get in the game
i don't know why the developers did it like that um but i noticed it as soon as i like started
playing the game i was like huh why did they do this it seems like such a random thing um
but we're on a dark brown horse which is the second fastest so we got here lickety split
but if you can somehow memorize the speed of that horse when we get on a white one uh yeah
it'll be so slow in comparison now that the pope's dogs have fled we're talking about horses
still right yeah it's great play the game i will show you literally i don't know why the devs
don't know well when you approve the fact that's a true fact i don't that's group of things
oh yeah my all account got restricted and i had to pass like a 10 sec like 10 captures and i can't
be bothered doing it so my account's just restricted right now i'm so freaking lazy it like makes me do
like these 10 things over and over and i failed it the first time and i'm like go and stop playing
like you know full well i'm a human all i did was retweet someone artwork of me and then it
blocked my account again i've done it like three times now i keep getting it like horses are like
cars red car go first as you can see this board shows the ranks of our top warrior again uh same
thing as before if we improve the mercenaries they get cheaper i don't know if they get more effective
cannot prove that i don't know if they get more aggressive and successful you also have fun
now if you'll excuse me a bit silly in it yes it's silly brb you got walk home please do not get
snatched on your way home where is bartholomeo at the fight downstairs he has such an aggressive
view of the world the red ones go faster oh we're unlocking assassin mission contracts as well
you get some florns on the side super easy super quick if you unlock your assassin signals
and do these really fast not a problem we will do a pee break in about like five minutes time
okay now we are going to be able to utilize the aqueduct in order to get a lot closer because
if you see the meters it says we're 1000 meters away we go to the island tabirina that's the
closest we have unlocked to the thieves at the moment it wasn't kind of the market
is that that may be true i actually don't know if they get more plentiful the like higher you
under your the higher like tier you are with them
jeez it's almost just killed myself from that board there goodness all right they came out
there we are we do have to run for this but again unless i take this guy's horse you don't want
mine now yonkers thank you very much please okay out my way so this is the problem if the if you
gallop through crowds the horse will fall over but if you just sprint through crowds the horse
won't fall over um literally we commit grand theft horse say apologies to that guy he probably
spent thousands of florns on the horse and i've just ran away with it and you get to keep the horse
i've still not unlocked targets so we're not going to do that we're just going to swim
across the water really quick we the pirate ship always stays after you have done that i don't know
why but the asset does get reused in a Leonardo mission so it's not like a massive waste so we
are now currently trying to run out of range of the horse that's across the water because if we
call on it it's going to try and okay there we go we're out of range so we can spawn in the horse
at any point but uh it will try to come over from the other side of the water and it can't
so you need to go out of range to despawn it and then you can respawn it on the other side
fucking hell this horse is zooming my god what kind of hay did we give it
it's so fat why are we going so fat i need to help it oh my god that was dangerous that was
dangerous like didn't even got a helmet on he's not even got we crashed pads on
this is Lavalpe the owner of the tea skill horse doping honestly
i know the answer you always do you want to put my spies to work then go in aiding
Machiavelli no thank you the horse really gotta go fast should have made it blue like
panic bang bang a wee baggie to the horse we baggie is slang for
yeah i think you can you can get the rest from there he is an assassin not a traitor
i am not convinced a what a wee baggie means
care to accompany me so Lavalpe thinks that Machiavelli is a traitor to the assassin's guild
which is the reason why Lavalpe refuses to communicate with Machiavelli uh can i get a
horse please because this is going to take a while to get to the location we need to get
hello let's go right let's get out of the way of the humans because the humans are in the way
um after this we gain notoriety unfortunately which means there are gonna be
posters put up about us and they kind of pop up on the map a bit too
a bit too much and they're always like above
money oh yeah we're at six thousand that's not honestly that's not bad
um we are gonna try and get a crossbow bolt you can unlock a crossbow bolt just like the archers
but you need to pay for it and i think it's 13 000 florins and if you decide to invest in buildings
like boot i keep saying butchers like the blacksmith for example and it does like
it adds up over time but it kind of is a bit difficult it's better to like save your money
for the quest because you can easily defeat the section after oh you like my twitter picture yeah
yeah i totally made it myself i did not make it i didn't make it at all i yanked it
okay okay this pay attention look at his body and look at him holding his arm please make note of
this as his i know it sounds crazy but i'm gonna talk about reusing assets and how genius it is
in video game development okay so he is hunched over and he's holding his arm please keep this in
your mind okay let's see if i can shoot everyone right you first right you next right you next okay
you know how about you okay oh oh hey let's go baby do you guys see the behind of the scenes
and lord of the rings where gimley's like right you first right you next you'll come to me i'll
beat you up right you next right you next that's basically what we just did okay now this section
is actually super easy it was really hard at first we might get caught because i'm he gets lost so
quickly but basically you have to hide here and then we're gonna wait for a group to walk up and
then they will see that group there that's coming towards us we hide in that group and then that's
it we've done this section of the game but please make a note of his body how he's holding his arm
and he's kind of hunched over because i'm gonna show you a reused asset you might not know about
wait why why is that group highlighted hold on a minute am i supposed to be with the other there's
too many groups please please okay you okay i hate this bit because the tree gets in the way
yes you heard me right the tree gets in the way and breaks up the group often but we're just gonna
blend in don't look at us guards we're just citizens i'm a monk amen amen i don't know what monks say
and then tada oh excuse me you are right there and he's like that could have desynchronized
because he got caught on those people i'm not even kidding i'm not kidding
analizing asset analizing well this asset be reused later yes it will
you know how to disappear
if you flora you know how to disappear heck yeah
okay we are gonna take a pee break right after we've done this bit because i need to pee
and i'm gonna get more water because i'm out of water already so these are witnesses we lose 75
percent notoriety if we do that and we are also going to complete a thieves challenge
which is drum roll please is to pick pocket 500 florins and a really quick way to do it is by this
you pick bribe him 500 and then yuck easy come easy go baby
and then oh i still have notoriety um that's not supposed to happen it's supposed to disappear at
this point excuse me whilst i kill this other witness oh no there's guards you know what i can
deal with the guards yuck leave me alone i'm a good citizen i promise i'm just a scary scary
monk you've got the wrong man everyone else for his hoodies okay it's not just me oh i'm like
running into more enemies oh wait wait wait hold on hold the phone hold pause pause pause
pause pause pause we did it we did it we snuck on him oh my god we snuck up on him oh my god it's
normally so hard to do talk about opportunistic killing my goodness okay we've just secured
like a third borja tower oh my goodness i can't believe the timing just happened
oh that was perfect timing i could not have asked for better oh my god i could not have asked for
better is he still trying to oh he just drowned okay oh that was amazing i'm so happy with that
okay we're gonna burn this tower there are a few archers on the roof but uh they're not too much
of a bother all right you can just kind of you know unfortunately you do have this one's a bit
more awkward you have to like you have to like kill him and then you have to go up there and kill
this guy too and it's a bit annoying to navigate whoopsie oh wow i made that jump there's a guard
down there but you don't have to kill him if you don't get down nope i will take your get down get
down oh my god you know that song that japanese one you heard of this you heard of that thing
oh maybe if we get 3d models we can all do that trend get down uh right we need to find the
synchronization point for the map boom synchronization yeah i used to watch a lot of hadsuni miko mmds
like dance and stuff and that was the first of her exposure the hadsuni miki pretty much i got
so i have another sippington of cola okay
oh my ankle just cracked i don't know if you heard that if i got picked up in the make my
ankle just cracked ew because i'm sitting on my 15th i'm wiggling my toes right now that's right
what you're gonna do you're gonna you're gonna try and stop me exactly you can't i'm just a little
toe wiggler okay uh we'll get a horse we'll complete this next but i think we have to defend
the thieves guild and upgrade it and then that is i was done with dna sequence three question mark
there are nine dna sequences in this game and they're all perfectly leveled out but we are getting
very close to being out of the tutorial section very very close i believe after act five we are
officially out tutorial andy's own what the night of this has been a toe wiggling street
listen to me i know what we saw but you have nothing to fear from marquirelli what was the
streaming page you watched mmds from i just youtube like hadsuni miki dancing and like
tato um who else did i like what are the thieves ah what's the yellow one called
goodness me i've forgotten her name i would like to know it not lin and brin to make sure the
board just stay away perhaps it could look like i forgot the yellow no not kagaman i like that idea
tato hadsuni and the yellow one
okay renovating the diesel oh sorry i just called on the horse by accident sorry horsey please don't
come um my name is neuro neuro i think her name is neuro no it's not a boy right type in hadsuni
miki o teto teto and it's like beep beep beep and it goes
not gumi uh gumi never really appealed to me sorry
yellow miku with a one-point help basically uh i like
but we also have gambling it is a great
gamble but we gamble all the money before i go for a pee just for the heck of it
you're here it looks like watermelon melon candy watermelon sugar
i actually quite like it um because emi's ginger she's our yinya if you're scouts she's a yinya
so i didn't like want to have like orange orange so i'm very vibrant in my clothes
okay we're just gonna gamble the money and then we'll go for a pee
okay what i play with me friend yeah but what i do though i actually i've never played this game
oh god what i do
first rule rule the through the seven seven eleven suck a dick or a ball sack
it wins the game without payroll of what
i'm all in max wager have absolutely no clue let's go
did i win
did i lose that all
oh
did i win
oh no i'm just gonna have to play more assassin's creed with you guys then
you oh no oh well okay is this the end of the sequence no the okay we're gonna
unlock the place roma is doomed literally can't play landlord simulator in assassin's creed brotherhood
i am doomed the house always wins do not gamble did i tell you that one time i got offered a lot
of money to do a gamble ad true story uh it was one of the biggest sponsorship offers i've ever
received and i saw they offered the money first like in the email they were like this is how much
will pay you and and i was like oh my god i've never never been paid that much money before
and then it was a gamble ad and i'm like oh that's that is why uh so yeah how much money uh four
thousand us dollars for a one minute advertising segment of a gamble advert a site biggest offer
i've ever had uh which was pretty insane so we're just going to finish the sequence and then we're
all going to be yes but will it pay for all the fallout yeah literally uh i was i'm like obviously
some people are our shop we must talk yes you got it from a guard good guess from one of my contacts
we now have the names of several templar agents cesare has recruited to terrorize roma how do i
find them i can give you a general location i suggest looking for signs of distress nearby
this isn't the end of the sequence my contact i'm gonna wait myself i'm not gonna lie i've had
like three glasses now okay i think i just need to hire two more recruits and then we can all go
be claudia bartholomeo and bursty i have no idea how you do i can do it i can do it i can do it
i can do virtue
okay this is the claudia thing he must pay for mario's death
that the apple has been secreted to someone for a study i am working on determining his
idea i'll pee right now don't think i won taterina will be moved to the prison within the castello
next week i'm gonna do i'm gonna pee then i'm not gonna be so the castello it is roma will heal
quickly with cesarean rodrigo god only if the opportunity to sustain the mario's will i take
do not repeat your mistake you must kill them now i'm with machiavelli etio
we should not wait bartholomeo is right they must pay for mario's death
they must pay for mario's death i just love the way she says it
it absolutely does not come across like that but my brain let me pay for mario's death
okay it's this act almost done yes we're gonna fix aqueducts in roma as well
the briefings are right here
can i say something really bad i thought about being a donathan reward a little
apple juice or homemade slime
i don't know if that's terrible or not but like i thought it would be funny if it was like you
can have apple juice or homemade slime what would you like from this the cuttlefish
um because and it would be extra funny because i actually have really smelly apple juice
so someone can inhale it and be like
okay we did it fixer upper act four is when we get the brotherhood together officially
i'm gonna let the game run in the background because it'll actually generate us income a
den of thieves i have apps i can't even remember what's in there
oh no is this when we go to the castello i think this is a castello mission right i'm gonna let
the game run in the background because it'll generate me some money in the background please
everyone get yourself new drinks if you need water or fizzy juice or whatever you may drink at the
moment um please get up and stretch i'm with your peep i will be roughly three minutes i'm gonna
maybe get a snack i actually boil this i boiled some eggs in preparation of the stream so i can
grab a boiled egg and eat it as a snack because i don't have time to like make food for so i have
boiled eggs okay right i'm gonna let the game run in the background but i'll meet my mic and all that
jazz i'll open it like i'll open the game back up so it's not just like pause pause but i go pee
oh
Caritas
Una moneta
Messere per mangiare
Fate la carita
Caritas
Messere per mangiare
Di drago o fame
Caritas
Una moneta
Fate la carita
Caritas
Messere per mangiare
Fate la carita
Di drago o fame
Una moneta
Caritas
Di drago o fame
Messere per mangiare
Caritas
Di drago o fame
I keep wanting to call it the Butchers, the blacksmith.
Did you guys pee and get water and stretch your legs instead?
I don't even drink energy drinks.
I'm eating meat and trying to play at the same time.
My mouth is stuffed full of meat.
Beecherbers when they're trying to do the most clippiest bait clip I've ever heard.
My mouth is so full of meat.
We got it. We know what game you're playing. It's fine.
I'm finishing it.
Sorry for the people that don't like mouth sounds. I apologize.
I actually can't remember what happens in this sequence.
My brain is blanking.
Well, it looks like I should have taken the aqueduct.
We're going into the castello.
We're about to go see Catherine of Forley.
Catherine of Forley.
She's currently stuck in a jail. She's got the jail.
The police in Scotland have got polis.
Actually, that's how you say it in Gaelic as well.
You say polis.
What are you eating?
I said a stick of meat.
It's like a pepper-rami.
But it's called a twizzle stick or something.
Oh, shit, I don't want to get in trouble.
Oh, I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Excuse me.
Come through.
That's what I didn't want to happen.
Because I'm literally just trying to get into a memory right now.
Excuse me. Pardon me. Didn't mean anything.
Well, you could've ignored me, but no, no, oh, are they still looking for me?
So that indicator means they're still looking, but they've not been coded to come down the
stairs or something?
Cause, yeah, they should've came down there, but they didn't.
Well I ain't complaining, I've never gotten in trouble, hee hee.
BOO!
Yeah, now, do you see that flashbang?
How does Haggis taste?
I actually really like it.
SHE HORROR FORLY!
I drinking lots of water to stop the neon.
What's Haggis?
Haggis is a meat dish.
I'll be free, your time will come, I swear it!
Keep your eyes on her eyes.
You're going to torture her.
You are here for Cesare and Rodrigo.
Girl spent in fire.
If we help her now while she is weak.
Haggis is a meat dish, a native national...
Let's kill Cesare and Rodrigo first.
It's not our national dish, I don't think.
Who goes there?
By the Pope.
I ate and I had a bit of water, so that didn't work.
It is, I believe, sheep liver and sheep lung mashed up.
And it's quite peppery, quite a peppery dish.
It's really nice.
You might have heard the phrase, neeps and tatis.
That means potatoes and turnip.
And it's just like a nice mash together.
It's really nice, I like it.
Okay, so this one's like, don't get caught, but I couldn't get...
What will they do?
Don't get detected later?
Because I actually don't even know how to do it.
So we're going to do it for the first time together.
I've never done this section without being caught.
I assume maybe if I had a crossbow and it can kill from afar and resupply.
Isn't Haggis a wee rodent?
Oh, aye, it's a wee animal.
Haggis is mainly pork, is it?
I don't think it's easily accessible, like, outside of the United Kingdom.
It is referred to as blood pudding.
Oh, no, that's black.
Black pudding is different.
For breakfast, we do like, it's a discus.
So on the way, a discus of, it's called black pudding,
but Americans refer to it as blood pudding.
But it is made of blood, so I do understand why they call it that.
It's just we call it, it just sounds a bit barbaric.
But at the same time, it's like, well, we are eating, you know what I mean?
No one cares.
Greetings, greetings.
You really say greens?
Alright, let's kill him from above.
Thank you very much.
We are going to have to come back on this.
Haggis is a savoury pudding containing sheeps,
sheeps pluck, minced with chopped onion, oatmeal, the spices and salt mixed with stock
and cooked with traditional, da da da da da.
I don't know how I could do that in the corner of my eye, but here you go.
I actually played this game so many times, I'm like completely sequenced out the wazoo.
But yeah, I'm a bit confused how you're supposed to do this section
without being caught without a crossbow.
I think we'll get access to the crossbow when we replay the memory.
Oh no, go away. See that's the thing.
Oh my god, no, no, no.
By the skin of our teeth, did that man not shoot?
Oh my gosh.
By the skill, by the skin of our teeth, by our gamer skills as well.
Yes, I give it to my gamer skills.
Oh my gosh.
Must have been the wind, literally.
Their brother and sister, by the way.
How it left so shut.
I'd rather like it open myself.
Have you talked to the Pope about the funds requested by my banker?
He is away from the Castello.
I do need some convincing when he returns.
That shouldn't be a problem.
Should it?
I wish that was me for real, for real.
Only it gets quite lonely here.
You and I spend so little time together.
Busy as you are with your other conquests.
Once I have secured the throne of Italia,
you are going to be my queen and your loneliness.
We'll be a thing of the past.
Ashight, baby.
Oh!
A bit of hair yonking.
We need to tag this up.
We need to tag this stream up to high heaven.
We've got hair yonking, we've got kissing, we've got bin best.
A lot of things going on.
I'm not to go up, I think I'm to swing to the side.
Yeah, surely.
Imagine if I went the wrong way.
Right now.
Hold B and then you just grab onto everything.
You can go down and speak things of it.
And what was it?
His ball was like one black thing shriveled up or something like that.
That Spaniard guy.
The Spanish were wild then.
To even get to that stage.
Not going to lie, not going to lie.
Who goes there?
Identify yourself.
What do we need to go up?
Square Sausage.
I miss square sausage.
If you didn't know, in Chicky Scotland for breakfast you do square sausage
and it's literally a square of sausage meat.
I wish it.
And I have it on a rolled way onion.
Didn't you just have his private...
I can't remember.
Whammin' on whammin' violence.
It can be.
You can put tomato sauce on it.
It's like tomato sauce, fried onion in square sausage on a roll.
Simple.
Simple, bruv.
Can I get more simple on that?
Right on the hip as well.
Excuse me.
Sorry, that actually really hurt.
I need a safe word.
That actually really hurt.
Please don't do that again.
Right, I'm pretty sure for this sequence if you time it right
you can be like not detected by the guards somehow.
Yeah, like literally he doesn't...
Yeah, so at least we know that for when we do play the 100% not detection segment.
And then there should be a guard to our left.
Well, we don't need to not be detected right now so it's fine.
The safe word is more...
What do you think is still it?
Should be in the safe word for a sheepskater.
Can you reach this water jug for me?
Okay, kill that guard first and then kill him.
And then that'll be how we won't get detected.
Surely.
Yay!
Castello crashing.
Paying a visit to the tailor.
Brown sauce and I'm not brown sauce fan sauce.
A bit of Harry Potter sauce with HP sauce.
It's tomato sauce or ketchup?
I'm gonna say something really dumb.
I don't know the difference between tomato ketchup and tomato sauce and tomato ketchup.
Ain't they the same? Aren't they the same?
Aren't they the same?
Phil Sinkfield, yes, we will be coming back to Fully Sink later thing right now.
Oh my god, that poor guy.
I didn't even know he was in here. I thought she was the only one here.
Brand? One has sugar, one doesn't.
I guess tomato sauce is probably what I like then.
This section can be a little bit finicky.
I love you so.
I want to sing it from the heavens.
Please, you must whisper it only to yourself.
If Cesare found out who knows what he would do.
These hoes ain't loyal.
He killed my husband.
Oh.
For real, for real.
I'm late for rehearsal. Farewell, my love.
No, ketchup has way more sugar than other ingredients.
Oh my god, not kidding.
She got a point. Ketchup has a ton of sugar.
Okay, whatever the sugary one was, I like it.
Brain says yum.
We shall see how it feels when the shoe is on the other foot.
Oh.
She's playing.
She said, guess what?
I'm not the only one that's going cheating around here.
He loves me.
Oh, she's like actually animating the flower and stuff.
Hello.
Imagine counting flowers and someone just goes,
wow.
Oh my god, I think I would have a heart attack.
I would have enjoyed this.
Guards.
Jump on you and say hello.
That's what happens in the ASMR booth.
What happens in the booth stays in the booth.
I see that premium pass around your neck.
I'm jumping on you.
Thanks for supporting me.
I just have to wait for these guys to attack
because they are such a nightmare.
Literally, it's just so much faster to let them attack
and then...
Right.
Oh, I think I just net.
The jump scare.
Foxy jump scare.
Princesses from Kessels now.
Ora, ora, ora.
Right, so this is really awkward.
If Lucretia gets away, like back to that starting station,
she will spawn out of bounds
and there's absolutely nothing you can do about it
and you have to restart this section again.
It's so annoying.
Thankfully, the last few times I've played this game,
it's not happened, but when it does happen, it's so annoying.
Oh my god, it's so annoying, Lucretia.
If you can get...
Excuse me, I wasn't even putting her down
and you just whapped me with that frickin' weapon.
Stop it!
You're upsetting me!
Don't upset me!
Oh my god, please do not do a finishing move
if she gets away because I was busy doing a finishing move
to look really good.
The passing was, your hand was finished
and their memory's erased.
Oh no, the tombstone's erased.
See, she does that.
See, if she jumps out, you have to go grab her.
However, if the people are attacking you,
then she'll wait on the side patiently for you to kill them.
Oh my god, is she actually getting away?
I'm getting nervous.
Stop it, Lucretia!
Hen, Hen, calm down, let me just kidnap you.
I mean, come on, come on, let me just kidnap you, okay?
Let me just kidnap you.
Shhh!
You like it really, come on.
Your man's not gaining any attention
and look at me, I'm picking you up, I'm throwing you a boot.
This is exactly what you're wanting, Hen.
Lucretia, didn't you fight that?
Didn't you actually fight that?
Okay, shhh, that's right, that's right, just accept it.
Shhh, this is so weird, I'm sorry.
My words are wasted.
Hippocrita!
No!
No, come on.
Okay, we did it.
Hippocrita!
Just kidnap me, Strony.
Crank sale, those are some big words.
You're not supposed to say that stuff.
Pip sweat detected.
Strony be taking tips from Mercy.
That's enough out of you.
He's smart, I can't read him.
Okay.
Do not be detected.
Again, another do not be detected.
But there's two guards literally dead ahead.
How am I not to be detected by them
when we play this for people?
Did they come in here?
No, this cannot be.
Did they actually come in here?
Okay, one gets his...
No, okay.
How am I supposed to deal with two of them at once
when we do it for real?
Eh, you better calm down, hen.
I'm rescuing you, Christina.
Then you get on at me about taking so long.
What are you doing?
Catarina.
I can't wait to hear your ASMR streams.
Oh, it's just absolute word vomit, I promise you.
Absolutely nothing makes sense.
My accent gets a little off the wee bit when I whisper,
but it's not really a big deal.
Like, I can make it...
I can enhance.
All about that?
Yes, yes, yes.
I know.
You gave me your hole, so I'd protect you.
It's... oh.
Hello.
Bye-bye.
I do be a really skilled assassin, honestly.
Ready?
Where?
He's just like me for real, for real.
He literally went...
Where actually is the auditorium?
Confirmed.
Never do that to me again.
Man, they didn't even let her put on her dress and stuff.
It's all torn at the bottom.
Oh, also, you can walk on barrels.
If you wanted to know that,
you can like jump up on barrels while carrying people.
It's just like a silly little goofy thing, but I like it.
Okay.
We pop you down there, pet the eagle,
and then we just give a wee stabby stabby the eagle,
all for you, mate.
And we just pick up the lady again.
And then basically...
If you pop her down in the middle,
I think you can access both gates without losing distance.
It will warn you against distance if you get too far away from her,
but...
No, I was gonna walk away.
I was gonna walk away and you forfeited your life.
How could you be such a silly...
I think we actually might have to move her over.
Whoa, did you guys see what I just saw?
Oh, leave me alone.
No, no, you don't see me.
I'm just going up the stairs.
I'm just a tourist.
I'm a visor, okay?
I'm a visor of the...
I thought I was gonna desync there.
I got scared.
I saw her panties.
Shhh.
And I didn't even have to pay anything.
I saw them for free.
Shhh.
Wait, can that guy see me again?
Oh!
I think we're gonna have to do the old ear assassination.
Excuse me, sir.
I just moved over to do an ear assassination.
Thank you.
The audio is strange again.
It better not be.
Why?
Literally nothing has changed.
I'm gonna tab in and out of the game multiple times.
Okay, so it's gonna pause and then open back up
and pause and open back up.
There's a static noise.
Sound like a static review.
If I have to close the game again,
I will.
A desync warning.
Like, it sounds perfectly fine for me.
Still there?
Shhh.
Do I have to play this whole section again if I quit right now?
It's still buzzing.
Do you know what buzzing means in Scots?
It means you're really having to play it now.
A feature where I know you can just restart the audio capture?
I mean, wait.
Hold on, controversial move, I know.
How does that sound?
Does that sound normal?
I am now capturing my desktop audio instead of the game.
Okay, I can now, you're literally gonna hear
if one of the girls DM me on Discord, that's the only thing.
Okay, let's get across the bridge.
Risky, I know you're all gonna know that.
I've arranged another ASMR collab.
Like, literally 30 minutes before the stream started.
I burst into someone's DMs on Twitter.
And I was like, hey girl, do you wanna add me?
And then I was talking through my ASMR collab.
And I've already planned it.
It's not a big ASMR, it goes on her channel and all that jazz, but yeah.
Okay, we have a timer, we basically just have to survive.
So this is where you can get the serial killer achievement again,
but it gets a bit iffy.
It's not the best, I will mess up.
And where the enemies go away, citizen, I don't wanna kill anymore.
I'm gonna try and kill the wee guys first,
because they grab me like that and ruin my streak.
Okay, sorry, I'm focusing.
See when they grab you, it takes you out of your kill streak advantage.
And there's Lancers as well, I can see that Lancer.
I'm gonna try and take him out in the kill streak.
Okay.
I'm trying to get the Lancer and it keeps all into the other guys.
Come on.
Wee guy next.
Armor guy next, I guess.
He's probably the best, but okay, I can't break his armor.
So I'm just gonna go for the wee guy.
Okay.
We're getting there, we're getting there, 30 more seconds.
Do not grab me.
I hate when they grab me.
Oh no, no, no, not the horse.
Not the horse, not the horse.
I said I'm hiding from the horse, get me in the hay bale.
I'm scared of the horses.
I actually don't know how to take down horse guys.
Ouch.
Yeah, this is why I don't like the horse guy.
We got seven seconds, we just need to not get hit.
Because we can run away in two seconds.
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
Wee.
Oh my god.
Okay, so in this sequence, you just need to get out a range of the yellow on the map.
If you come on the roof, you can basically run along it as much as you need.
Or if you don't like rooftop scaling, there is boats down to the left where you can get out a range.
Down, down, down.
Bruh, bruh, get off.
My roof, no.
And then if we disappear in the water maybe, I think we can hide in the water.
You can like literally hide in the water.
I'm a call fish, let's go.
Can they see me?
Physically, yes they can see me, but game development wise?
No, they can't, so I enjoyed that.
Do that again, more game please.
Okay, we're gonna kill this guy.
Sorry, I'm sorry mate, your time is up.
Oh, I forget.
Okay, if you scare away, you won't be able to...
Right, we're gonna go for this poster just because I don't want guards to attack you on site.
If you are the highest notoriety, they will attack you.
Oh, the poster is down here, I have been fooled.
The egg is on my face.
We need to now go back to the island hideout because Caterina's forces are there.
And then we can unlock assassin recruits and then we're really gonna get into the meat of the game and I love it.
And everything is so cool, everything's so awesome.
We're just gonna, alright, here we go, yank.
He said enough, I yanked him off for heart, enough.
Enough.
Is it enough?
Don't you not want to give more?
Okay, this is the only problem when navigating with a horse.
You have to, you're like stuck to using whatever roads you've passed out and it gets really...
Why would you bother just going down to it, folks?
If you come on the roof, should you...
I never even said that, that was you that said that.
Normally I'm the one coming out with the outrageous...
I just whistled for the horse whilst purchasing the bank.
Hey, horse, can you come out here?
Thanks, appreciate it.
Like, oh, okay.
Oh, we made 1.5 Florence.
That's pretty good.
I don't think we're gonna get the crossbow before the section that I'm hoping to get it by.
I don't know why we lost all our money.
Don't know how it happened.
Something, something don't gamble at home, people.
But may have lost all our money in that.
Right, where is the bridge?
The bridge is over here, okay.
Gotta stay on them peasants.
Horse is the first customer of the store, for real, for real.
Munching on that hay.
Okay, we have made it to the island.
Never gamble with your own money, gamble with someone else's, that's terrible.
Don't gamble at all.
Save that mule.
I could not find him.
Get yourself a wee fizzy juice from the corner shop.
Maybe a wee bakery, a wee scone.
To treat those things.
The bank is in the room.
Okay.
Wow.
It's normally outcast.
Very odd indeed.
What a waste.
So the Volpe thinks that Marquee Valley tipped off Cesare to leave the castle.
So we're all suspicious.
Cesare commands a massive army in Romania.
You would never reach it.
I say we work here.
Loma.
They rode the Borja's influence while restoring our own.
And in fact,
I'm gonna start right now.
Yes.
We're doing it.
We're about to get the brotherhood.
Come on, reflings.
I want to turn you guys into assassins.
I want to turn you to deadly weapons.
The Borja robbed everything from the people to maintain power.
What do you intend to do?
You will recruit him to our cause.
You cannot be serious.
To win this war, Marquee Valley.
We need loyal soldiers.
Come on, reflings.
You'd let me draft you, right?
All right, let's get drafted.
I'm gonna be the combat medic on the battlefield.
Okay, I'm healing you guys on the battlefield.
With my...
Oh, my God.
The cutscene took so long that...
Wait!
Whoa, I've never seen this happen before.
To recruit spawned and the cutscene took so long,
they both died in the instants.
Oh, my God.
All right, she's still alive.
Let's save her.
Oh, my God.
It's Shrek and...
No, no, no, no, we've just attracted more guards.
This is terrible.
She has incredibly low health.
Oh, goodness me.
Oh, goodness gravy.
Please don't perish.
I hope she doesn't perish,
cause we're actually gonna have to...
Okay, she didn't perish, thank goodness.
Already sold my life.
One!
What did you sell your life to?
Sin?
It's a lady assassin.
You'll never guess what I do to the lady assassin.
Okay, I'm gonna open up the map
and the map will tell us where the next recruit is.
So we can go recruit this person.
And now we are about to unlock assassin recruit signals,
which means in the middle of a fight
we can literally ask the game to help us.
And there's also a really fun minigame
where you can level them up
and make them even stronger to the point
where they can fight incredibly strong enemies.
And it is so satisfying watching their health bars go up.
Oh, look, I have it already, actually.
I'm gonna use it for this citizen.
If I can get to them in time before they perish.
Here we go.
Oh, it's another lady.
Oh my God, we're like doing all ladies in this assassin group.
Oops, my bad.
You can't really...
Oh, okay.
Hold on, let me go.
Let me get up.
Okay, we're...
Oh my gosh.
Assassin's Creed Brotherhood.
More like the sisterhood.
Am I right?
Ha ha.
Hopefully we can get a few guys in here.
We need to repopulate Roma.
You know what I'm saying?
Yum yum yum yum.
Let's unlock the doctors
because we can get more money in general.
Strong door calls for aid.
Me on Christmas like.
Okay.
So...
Lead...
What did he say?
I don't think I've ever heard that.
I've got a new lead based cure for syphilis.
I didn't know that was in the game.
That's outrageous.
Right, we're gonna go pick up this other assassin recruit
because they're like 100 meters away.
That's absolutely hilarious.
And we're also gonna send one of our assassin recruits away on a mission
which is how you level up the assassins
and you get a stupendous amount of money for it.
So I get 650 florins for 6 minutes I send this person away for.
So this is your biggest money maker
sending your assassin recruits away.
So we might be able to get the crossbow ball
if I dilly dally and do a few save quest things.
Or we can just rush through.
It's not really rushing because
it's just playing the campaign but yeah.
I'll have to say nothing is true.
Everything is permitted for real.
I'm training my reeflings to become weapons of destruction.
Where's the citizen?
Oh, they're already fighting.
Oh, the citizen might die.
Oh, why is this building so tall?
Oh, can I get them?
Can I save you?
I'm coming, I'm coming.
I'm helping, I'm helping.
Okay, we got it, we got it, we got it.
Okay, good.
Oh no, there's more guards that have come in.
Oh, I don't know how low his HP is.
The recruits are so bad at the game as well.
Oh, I'm so bad at the game.
Oh, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on.
Oh, come on, you can do it.
Okay.
Oh, we did it.
I instantly you want to pick up the recruit
because it gets rid of any guards that are nearby.
Mere gracia, Amiko.
Weapons of destruction.
Achievements, brotherhood.
If we had gamer score, we'd probably have like 200 venerals.
Oh, these are the Borja zones that we've liberated.
We've done three places, so we're allowed to have three recruits.
We've done four places, excuse me, so we're allowed to have four recruits.
I literally just remembered.
We can go to the main quest, which is down here.
There's actually someone we can recruit over here.
Nah, we'll go to the main quest and we'll pick up recruits on the way.
We've got a fill bar of recruits.
Unfortunately, they're very weak, so it's not very good.
I'm chasing after you, my recruit.
It's not very good to send them to battle
without kind of leveling them up first
because your recruits can perish in a fight, unironically.
Yeah, your assassins can die, it's very dangerous.
Across the bridges are our first mission.
These missions are all based around calling your assassin recruits in,
but the bar does take exactly 60 seconds to refresh
from when they disappear, not from when you call them in,
from when they disappear off the map.
And some of the missions, they take a hot second.
It's good to get multiple bars of assassin recruits,
so the more Borgia towers you destroy, the more recruits you're allowed,
and you've got a maximum of three bars, so six Borgia towers.
Where the heck am I going?
Oh, this one, I remember.
Hello, sorry to swing in about that over this very sad scene.
Mafato!
This is another multiplayer character that we kill.
We must follow the whores,
so they will point to where we need to go,
but I have played this game many a time now,
so you can just keep running in general.
Running, running, running, running, running, running, running, running, running.
Yeah, we do have our recruits ready to assassinate this guy,
and we should get a tidy sum of money for doing so.
I've actually never tried to break this sequence
and go outside of what the girls point you to.
I've called my recruit.
I don't know where she is.
She's taking her sweet time, right?
There you go.
Get him!
And then with 100% of that,
I'm going to shower.
Hold on, let me pause the stream for you.
I'm teasing.
Enjoy your shower.
Don't forget to do your belly button and behind your ears.
A lot of people forget.
And make sure you soap all over,
even on your booty hole.
Soap cleans itself due to the nature of it.
Not that you're expecting a visitor anytime soon, are you?
Do you get a lot of money if you loot?
No, you don't get anything if you loot the multiplayer.
Ooh, new recruit, let's get it.
No, they're fighting.
Stop fighting before I even get there.
My goodness.
Stop it!
I'm coming to hell.
Give me a second.
Let me cook.
Oh, my God.
I've just invited even more guards to come over.
Oh, please don't.
I don't know how damaged they is.
Please don't do a cutscene.
There's too many enemies around right now for this.
Oh, oops.
I am actually going to pick up these bodies
and put them in the hay bale
because if you put five in a hay bale,
you do a cortisol challenge.
I'm just going to do this now,
so I'm not going to talk to them.
I'm literally going to save his life
and then just be like, excuse me,
I'm just trying to hide the evidence
of what we've just committed together.
Mother Mary.
No, not the sword.
The body.
No, the body.
Thank you.
No requiesce de parti.
One more body should do it.
No, not the weapon.
The body.
Taking out the trash.
Okay, there we go.
You know what always bothered me?
When you kill some evil bloke
and then Exo is cradling like a babysitter recipe,
he has...
Whoa, what was that?
Was that scaffolding in that cutscene?
The camera is so good in this game.
Like it's so good.
Do you guys remember the asset repeating?
I'm going to show you an asset that was repeated.
It's right in this next quest.
So remember how he was holding his arm
and he was injured?
Well, guess what?
This is where they reused the asset.
On this little crying kid.
Don't worry.
There's not a random kid crying in your headset.
It's part of the game.
This is a shrunken down version
of that guy that got injured.
Not at this stage,
but it's the same clothes and all that.
And when he walks away, you can see it.
Okay, so stare at him.
We know you use reused assets.
You be soft, we know.
This is the next one.
Sleepy.
You are scary,
but you look very brave.
Right, now watch him walk away.
You think you can distract me, video game?
I'm on to your secrets.
You might as well have me on the dev team.
Look at this walk!
He's injured!
I can see it!
You can't hide that from me.
I've played this game far too many times.
That's just the injured thief.
Asset reused.
You can't get away from me.
Honestly,
I wonder if there is behind the scenes development
of Brotherhood,
because I actually haven't consumed any of that.
And if there is,
I know what I'm doing the moment I go to bed.
Among other things after looking at Marshmallow,
hehehehehe.
Okay, we do have two assassin signals,
which is really good,
but I should probably send the recruits away
just to get stronger,
but not right now,
because we're in the middle of a secret.
I'm just going to start upgrading stuff
as I find them.
Yeah.
Injured thief number 312.
Okay, camera angle, please.
Ow!
I just bumped into those guards.
They literally could have reprimanded me for doing that,
but I guess not.
Right, we have two assassin signals,
which is good.
Actually, I'm going to send them a fight
to get some experience,
because I need to get them strong.
So, we're just going to watch them do their thing.
Hopefully they'll hurry up and get some XP.
Yep.
Take your time.
There you go.
They get XP every time you call them
into a battle or send them in missions.
It's not a problem.
There we go.
And they've respawned,
so it's all good.
We will keep another signal
to do this mission, though,
because to get 100%,
you have to send your signal
to kill the person.
Again, another multiplayer character,
which is why they're so designed.
I can't really remember.
He looks behind you
on the bridge a lot,
and I like to write on corners.
It's quite funny, actually.
You don't ever use the recruits.
Are you joking?
That's the best part about this game.
If you suck at video gaming,
you can literally just call in the recruits
to do everything for you.
He should start running in a second.
No, around the corner he runs,
because we're to go over there.
He's like,
yes, there's absolutely no one on this bridge
that looks threatening to me whatsoever.
Me just standing,
not even hiding in the crowd or anything,
and stops...
Oh, see, he's bumping into NPCs.
That's the biggest thing about tailing.
If that NPC bumps them,
they can turn around
and look you right in the eyes,
and you're like,
oops, you're not really supposed to do that.
He literally has a knife out,
and we're gonna...
I think he looks back here,
and then, yeah,
I remembered.
He looks back here,
and then he looks back as after he does a sprint
on top of the stairs, okay?
You're getting all the strats,
so he doesn't look back anymore
unless he gets bumped,
which he shouldn't.
No, he didn't.
He didn't. That's good.
And then he's about to break out in a sprint.
Hey, that's right.
And then you follow him,
and then the game wants you to...
I don't think he should have turned around at that point.
No, he shouldn't have.
I don't know why he did.
He's not coded to turn around at that section.
He's coded to turn around,
like, at the top of these stairs.
Unless the sequence broke.
Okay, the sequence broke
because he's supposed to do it
at the top of those stairs.
My goodness.
I thought we were about to desync there.
Not a game.
You gave me a heart attack.
We must ensure that the kidnappings continue.
No, there will be no kidnapping.
Hee hee hee.
Requiescati bacce.
And look at his hook arm.
Yawing, using that for a design.
I've got two sets of recruits.
Can they hurt these guys without dying?
I want them to get XP for fighting.
Can they do it without Persian?
I think they can, but no one leveled up.
Not one person leveled up doing that.
Nah, you're done.
You're naughty.
Users supposed to level up.
Did I get into the multiplayer?
No, I didn't actually.
I can't quite remember.
I think it was like you hide among the...
Oh, someone did level up.
We'll give her a weapon.
Look, we've got so many assassins.
I'm going to send them on...
Missions.
Sorry if this looks like chaotic mess on the screen right now.
It's just I've done it so many times.
You need to look for difficulty level 1 missions
and then send the recruit on it
and it will automatically make them level 2
so they can at least have a bit more of a fight into them.
The pigeons' eyes.
They're a bit...
Look, the game's from 2010.
Okay, it's an older game.
I'm not going to steal a horse.
That's not nice.
Committing Grand Horse Aul.
But we'll do this.
Have you played Unity?
I haven't.
I played Assassin's Creed,
Ezio's storyline,
and then I played 3
and I didn't really enjoy it so much.
And then I played Black Flag,
but I suck at it
because they changed the controls
and I'm absolutely awful at it
and I've never actually successfully completed it.
I have no idea where I'm supposed to go.
I think I'm going to go into the Tiberina Island.
I'll just use that bridge there.
That looks right.
You enjoyed your night?
I know Odyssey came out.
I never played that.
Like, the newer Assassin's Creed
I'm absolutely not familiar with at all.
I do apologize.
I mean, maybe we can play it
for the first time together.
I think Odyssey got a really good reputation.
I know there's that Japanese.
Where the heck am I trying to go?
Sorry, I'm getting so distracted.
Talking and playing at the same time.
I'm sorry.
Guess who we're about to meet?
Are you ready?
It's you.
Who are we about to meet?
Leonardo da Vinci himself.
Hello, Leonardo.
Long time no see, buddy.
So, remember when Chesery said
the gun was crafted by a friend of mine?
It was crafted by Leonardo.
Because he's my friend.
Oh, congrats if your name's Leonardo.
He wanted to chop that thing off.
I don't get any of the modern ACs.
They don't have charm.
Yeah, the apple.
I gave the apple to Mario.
I am sorry.
Don't say that.
What's 100% thing for the tank mission?
You're making me scared now.
Is it hard?
I thought this game was pretty gamer friendly.
You're making me now.
I'm starting to break out in a sweat.
We ain't even played the tank mission yet.
Oh no, what is it?
Stop!
Is it bad?
360 hours for this dream?
I'm sweating.
Leonardo, he's drawing, he's doing his thing.
Did you know Leonardo da Vinci liked Willy?
That's a true fact.
You're getting educated with me.
The tank mission?
Oh, you're making me nervous.
I'm getting scared.
Is the tank mission where you have to claim all the towers and stuff?
I like to get the thing.
Okay, we have a long double blade.
We can now do double assassinations,
which is one of...
That was me slapping my leg before anyone claims that it was a fart.
I already know what I'm doing.
Fart and don't ever...
We're just unlocking new weaponry.
The next thing we're going to unlock is a leap glove,
which is fantastic to make jump-claiming about much easier.
I just remembered the tank mission.
I'm getting fucking nervous.
We're making me scared for when we do it.
I was going to leave the missions all to the end,
so we're doing story mode,
and then all the side quests stuff tomorrow,
and then 100% sync.
I don't know where we're heading next.
Oh, okay.
800 meters!
That's so far away.
I don't know if we can take an aqueduct.
We can take an aqueduct to...
Where the heck are the aqueducts?
Okay, behind me.
We can take an aqueduct to the mercenaries,
and then we'll just have to horse on the rest.
I'm getting nervous in case I can't 100% it.
It's literally in the title of tomorrow's stream.
I'm getting nervous.
I'm getting shaky.
Okay, I'm getting nervous.
Where am I trying to?
I'm trying to teleport.
Okay, first I need to go inside the guild,
and then I need to go to the mercenaries on the map,
and then we're going to do the first of the Leonardo missions.
Where's the heck?
Oh, there.
I'm literally right here.
Here, right here.
Yes, we'll do the Leonardo...
First Leonardo mission.
I will do the others at the end,
because I think it takes far too long to do them,
in my humble opinion,
although I can't remember them.
The layer of Romulus are like,
pretty good for climbing,
for those interested in climbing.
Where's my horse?
My horse.
Come here.
You're teasing me.
Okay, right.
We will very quickly skedaddle over to this area.
We actually still haven't unlocked the full map yet.
You don't unlock the full map until sequence 7, I think.
Act 7.
So we might hit a boundary wall.
I'm not sure if I'm going the right way.
There's multiple ways you can make your way to the location,
but I think I've done it right.
Yes, the boundary wall right there.
So we are doing it right in quotation marks.
Is it up or down?
Why are you sitting on the horse like that?
What is it?
Explain yourself.
Okay, we did it.
We did it.
We're here.
I think we just have a really basic mayor scenario,
and then we will do the first Leonardo mission,
which I hate,
because we've actually not got the crossbow bolt,
which is much easier if you have the fricking crossbow bolt,
but it's fine.
The mercenary should spawn in right in front of us.
3, 2, 1, A.
That's right.
You yikers.
Come with me.
You're going to beat these people up for me.
Thank you.
And just tell them to fight like that.
And that is how you utilize the mercenary.
Sorry, I'm itching my eyeball.
I have a real eyelash again.
And then basically, they just do all the work.
I can call my assassins and...
You know what?
I'll do it for the XP there.
Oh!
I just unlocked an assassin from everything.
I'll take it.
No, I'm kind of through with that.
Ooh.
Okay, done.
Okay, we now are going on a mission
in a different location.
Map retrieve from the overseer.
I cannot read that fast,
but thank you, game, for having faith in me
that I can read that fast.
But the truth of the matter is, I can't.
Don't do that.
Don't let that happen again.
Have a little drink of water, game.
Game, game.
My voice is dying.
I don't know if you can tell how messed up my voice is
or if it just kind of sounds like my normal voice at this part.
I'll go with the machine gun.
So, this 100% is don't kill anyone.
I have never done that before.
I always kill people.
And it's like, really, it's so much easier
if you have the crossbow bolt,
because, like, for goodness' sake, it...
Because the crossbow bolt doesn't give your location away,
but the bullets of the gun do, it's pretty bad.
I'm actually not wanting to move.
Yeah, that's why, because they turn around.
I'm gonna yank him.
I'm actually wanting to go back and kill that guy
if I'm being honest.
Maybe don't have to, question mark.
There is a rotating guard ahead, which I don't like.
Oh, he's coming!
Are you joking me?
I've just missed him.
Oh, just missed him.
We need to shoot him in order to get where we need to go.
There's two bullets.
Whenever there's a pigeon ledge, that means you can do a leap of faith.
Your enthusiasm of the game is cute.
It's just such a good game.
So, as long as he doesn't turn around.
If you run, it'll notify the guard of you.
So, don't run when you do these kind of things.
Or else the guards, the AI is basically going to be like,
I have found you.
And then you're like, please don't do that.
I would like to be uncalled,
because I don't want to redo this entire sequence all over again.
Okay, this is a bit of an issue.
There's a guard that rotates around the century of the wall,
and that one up there, I need to shoot both of them, basically.
But I need to wait until the other one rotates away.
Why don't you just hypnotize the guard?
For real!
But they can't see me from this distance.
I'm potent, I'm not that potent.
Right, so we can do that, at least.
And then, maybe...
Wait, there's a guy there.
Oh, I don't like that.
Uh...
Sorry, this part, you can fuck up so easily.
Okay, we didn't fuck up.
Burn it, and then we get this checkpoint.
Okay.
Ta-da!
We have achieved the checkpoint, we no longer have to sneak around.
We can just do our thing.
Pew!
I don't ever want to do that again.
She says, as she has to do it again.
You can just drop down, doesn't cause any damage to you.
But the music creators for the speed-up song,
like that is so terrifying.
It strikes blood into the hearts.
It strikes fear into the hearts, not blood into the hearts.
I mean, that's what hearts do, they pump blood around and stuff.
Get all oxygenated again.
Okay, this is the part I freaking hate.
Because I don't know how to, like, not get it to lock on.
You can literally go side to side and evade.
And you will still get... Why are there people there?
Like, I'm evading, but I'm probably going to get hit.
I don't know how to not get hit.
I played this so many times.
Although I did evade all of those,
so maybe my swirling is doing much better.
Evasive maneuvers, evasive maneuvers!
Ah, see, I don't get it!
I'm literally going side to side.
I wonder if it's a distance thing as well.
Like, if I get too close, the game's like,
you're not allowed to get that close,
and it's like, oh, sorry, you didn't really explain.
Like, pardon my French,
but je n'ai c'est quoi, on what's going on me.
Okay, let's go. Next sequence.
This is actually pretty badass.
I can't seem to have to admit.
Stabbed-in throw SFX.
We will use the tactical camera,
because it's literally, like, if you're down here,
it's like so close.
And you can use the map to see who's coming up,
so I can see there's one on the right,
and then we're going to swing back left,
and then we're going to swing back right.
You don't need to worry about the archers at all
in this part of the mission.
They don't hurt you.
I've never been hurt,
but you can see left side again on the red dot map,
which I'm covering up! Lovely!
I just realised I'm covering up the entirety of the map,
so you can't see any of that that I've just been commentating on.
I do apologise.
Again, the horses always get up.
Please don't worry. The horsey-worsies are fine.
You can pre-fire when the red markers spawn in.
You can get to it.
And you can, like, hit them before the markers actually show up,
because that's really loud.
Hopefully that's not too loud for you guys.
The horses are fine. Please don't worry.
All horses get back up in the game.
If they aim a bit too close, they're going to get me.
Am I going to get away with that?
Shoot them down!
That wasn't bad either.
Oh, back up on the horse!
You better stop!
This is, like, Snape or Simulator, honestly.
Oops!
Oh no, I'm going to get shot. I messed up.
Hello?
They're out the road!
I actually wanted to perish there.
He said I like feeling pain.
Sorry, I'm, like, really focusing.
I don't have the best aim on analogue.
So, I'll try it.
But yeah, this is the first mission.
It's the easiest out of them all.
This is still tutorial section stuff,
because the Leonardo missions are main game.
So, this is technical tutorial.
We still go in there.
I'm trying to remember the axe.
Maybe axe, which is the order.
Oh, can I hit the barrel?
Yeah, I can hit the barrel.
How many are there?
Okay, we've almost done the sequence,
and then we're back into the main game.
I might get another Kola, actually.
My voice is feeling it.
I don't know how to extend the stamina of my voice.
I'm not really sure.
Other than, like, be quiet five heads.
But, like, I want to stream.
I want to have a good time.
Like, I have so much lost time to make up for.
Like, you have no idea.
I saw you spawn in. I saw that.
I saw you spawn in.
Hydration and practice.
I've been using my voice for years now.
Just speak smaller words.
Okay.
Work is a call center agent.
Water helps.
Oh, actually.
Hopefully none of the girls are in here.
I want to do a short with them.
Apparently, girls can't make good weapon sounds.
Like, I'll make the sound of a gun.
So I'm going to ask all the girls to record an audio of them making sound of a gun.
And then I'm going to put it in a short.
It's just like a goofy, funny-ha-ha thing.
It's nothing serious.
I'm going to take a few yards from the location of where I'm supposed to go.
Are you kidding me?
So I was going to do a shotgun and see if they come up with, like, pistols.
Or maybe an AK.
We've got quite a few levels up.
We've got level three, which is fantastic.
We're starting to get a bit more serious with the recruits.
They're starting to get a bit more, like, they can survive.
I'm actually going to send them on a bigger mission.
I'm going to take the level three to go level up someone.
Can I send them on level twos?
I'll send them on level twos. It's very unlikely they're going to fail.
But the level two missions are quite long.
Wonder who's going to be the best.
I'm going with the classic shotgun, like, the ch-ch-ch-loser there.
But I'll be very interested to see what the girls come up with.
I'm trying to go brrrrr.
Wow, okay, I guess I will go back to the mercenaries to use the aqueduct there.
Oh, there's an aqueduct there as well.
Is that closer? I think so.
You can roll your R's if you're Scottish.
I know some languages, like, don't roll their R's.
I was going to say something and my brain completely blanked.
I'm now going to pretend otherwise.
Oh, I'm out of bounds. Hard and moir.
Can I still get to this aqueduct?
Not aqueduct, the...
It's not cistern. What is it?
Is it a cistern? Cistern access?
Oh my god, new name for Niji fans just dropped cisterns.
That's awful. I'm sorry, I shouldn't have said that out loud.
That's the dumbest thing I've said all day.
My views do not reflect that, Alveolar.
My views are my own. I do not reflect the company.
Thank you. I'm just playing Assassin's Creed, please, the middle.
What does your 11 kill streak sound like?
I don't know how to make sounds of knives or weaponry.
Watch whoever you enjoy.
Someone sent me a marshmallow and it was a link to someone from an agency.
I'm not going to name the agency.
They were like, please save her.
And I was like...
What do you want me to do?
They're locked into a contract.
We have a non-compete at VLR.
You can literally jump straight into a VTuber agency once your time's up here, if you're finished.
But what do you want me to do?
Seriously, you want me to message the company and be like, hey, can I buy her out?
Thank you for your faith in me, but what am I supposed to do?
I mean, sure, I would if I could, but...
I want everyone to be happy and having a good time while they're streaming, but...
I can't help everyone.
Set them free?
No, that sounds so bad, because it's like...
It sounds like buying like...
Hederation check.
I'm going to do a burp.
Buy the company, my goodness.
No chance.
VTuber Moses?
That is the funniest thing I think I've been called in a long time.
VTuber Moses, set them free.
That's hilarious.
Hijack the company.
Let companies cook. You'll see eventually.
Let my people go.
Once Cesare arrives, you will never get to him.
I intend to kill the French general.
Okay, we're getting assigned our next act.
The Frenchies.
Desolé if you're a French fry.
It's not in personal, mate. Not in personal.
You know, viva la France and all that.
And c'est la vie, and what other words do you say in French?
I will have my thieves as I retain his location.
I have no recruits to send on a mission, because I've already sent them on the mission.
Where are you going?
I am not used to anyone without follow-up.
I am Swiss, I totally support any French propaganda.
That's awful.
Oh, I said it wrong.
Oh no!
Oh no, I think I'm going to have to go back to scuff tracking.
My iPhone is at 20%.
Scuff tracking, here we go.
Unless I can get it to balance with the charger in...
Oh my god, you're hearing everything connect.
Okay, can I get it to balance?
We're getting a bit horizontal.
Right, this is dangerous.
I'm going to put you in front of my glass.
And I'm going to wedge you in between my keyboard.
Okay, this isn't working.
I'm going to wedge you in between...
My tea cup.
Let me just...
Oh, pardon me.
Okay.
Uh-huh.
Oh yeah?
Okay, yeah?
Are you still tracking?
Hello?
Yes!
I get it.
Okay, what actor are we on?
The banker or the French one?
I think we're in the French one.
What broke?
I didn't break anything.
If I ain't broke, don't fix it.
Right, we're going to see how much...
We're going to see how much it costs to buy the crossbow.
$12,800.
I don't have that.
I'll look away for a second.
I'm going to be wedged in between a body part.
How dare you insinuate?
Right, what mission are we doing?
Memory Star up here?
Is it the banker that we're on?
I kind of think we may be on the banker mission,
but I can't really remember.
And my wife had a baby?
It's Tony Tern Golem.
I want to try and do that,
but I think I would destroy my voice in like 20 minutes.
We hate it.
It's ink in the back of my throat.
It's your ink in the back of my throat.
We're going to rebuild.
We built this city.
We built this city on Florence.
Because that is the currency.
Actually, I need to do that audio.
Keep forgetting.
Post it.
I need to make it.
I think I can probably do it after this stream.
It's a free audio.
It's just on the ult.
I'm golem posing whilst gaming.
I mean, if you want to get technical.
Should that be a donors on reward?
It's just a picture.
Obviously I'd edit my face out and all that.
It's just a picture of me like bucking a snake.
Because that's a normally game on my chair in the golem pose.
And everyone's like, what is this?
And I was like, it just means what I'm doing.
Something the adventurer is.
They're like, what is this pale creature?
Oh wait, it clearly is golem.
No questions asked.
Oh my, yes please.
Excuse me, I'm on the mission.
M.E.'s eyes are currently rolling out of her skull right now.
How much?
Oh, I forgot to put what she was saying.
Yeah, I decided on...
Strongly clips and strongly...
R just to be strong R and strong clips.
Because I couldn't think of anything else.
Although someone sent a really good suggestion on Marshmallow.
I might change it.
I mean, we're super early days.
Like, I can literally change it.
I have something else.
Hey hey, Pipi!
Excuse me, I'm on a mission.
Where?
A mission?
Oh Lolo?
Okay, this is the banker.
This is the banker act.
Sorry.
I can't sing and do the golem voice.
My only wish?
I sound like Marsh from Homey.
Oh, I can't sing in the golem voice.
My only wish to catch a fish so juicy and sweet.
Homey!
That's terrible.
That's awful.
I think Emi is Kubeko.
She is, how you say, a tabernac.
And, yeah.
She doesn't count.
She doesn't count as a true Frenchie.
A true French fry.
French fries are European Frenchies.
The Swiss are the Swiss.
And the Kubekois.
The Kubek.
Kubek.
Homey is the silo stuff.
Honestly, her Kubekois is something I've heard before.
She says she's not very confident.
But as long as she can form sentences,
the best I can say is like,
Je vais, je vais, tu vas, il va, elle va.
Nous allons, nous allons, il va et elle va.
I can say, I would like, je voudrais,
I can say, I, which is, j'arrive.
I can say, I don't think I know any more
doing words in French, any more verbs.
All the French fries are like,
Okay, here we go.
I'm back.
What did I miss?
We're memeing on the French, like everyone else.
Voulez-vous coucher avec moi?
Oh my God, my voice cracked.
Did you hear that?
Took years of French.
I think I can say the colors in French.
Rouge, rose,
orange,
green,
jolie,
noir, blanc,
marron,
what a French.
Do you money too, do I?
I'm looking for chésarés bankers.
Palais-vous francais?
Oui, oui, avec les poissons,
dans les sacs.
Ouais, what did you just make me say?
I can like kind of half read French.
I have no idea what I'm saying,
but I can kind of read it,
like with the letters and stuff.
The French aren't real,
it's a lie made up by the English.
Je suis monté, pardon.
All right, this way.
You're going to have to protect me, though.
The guards aren't being very friendly.
You're going to have to protect me.
Hello, gentlemen.
May I please double assassinate you?
No, double assassinate.
Oh, don't be detected!
Don't be detected with the mission,
and the first thing I do is go up
and kill some guys.
I'm not very smart, am I?
Oh well.
A little oversight, but...
It's fine.
Morning!
Good morning!
Good evening!
I really don't want to send my assassins
on, like, the Lancers,
but as long as they kill the right guy first,
it should be fine.
Right, sorry, the senator's currently complaining
about his money issues
and how he hates the Vorgia.
I'm talking right over it.
Oops!
Well, thank goodness they called,
came in and in.
Uh, hello?
Whoa!
Yeah, see this?
The citizens become assassins,
they get scared.
Why do you not do double blade?
I have a double blade.
I'm pretty sure there's, like,
stuff to do double blade stuff as well.
Uh, really appreciate it.
A few different skills to do here.
We should probably get rid of some of our noray.
This is where we start now.
We're doing 100% tomorrow.
We're just doing campaign mode right now.
Wouldn't be good time zone be easier.
Aha!
Good time zone, everyone!
That's awful.
Uh, we may be able to get a gun.
Yes!
No!
I was gonna sneak by them.
I like how he's continuing to talk
whilst being beaten up by a sword.
Are they not attacking him?
Assassin recruits, are you so for real right now?
Can you attack him?
What's going on?
Oh my god.
Oh, they've attracted more it guards.
What?
And now someone's grabbing the guard?
Hello?
Right, no.
This isn't my problem.
Sorry.
I don't know what is going on over there, but...
Uh, I don't think they will attack us.
We're so far away.
Okay, so the assassins are dealing with them.
That was, I think the AI was like,
no idea who to target first,
so it was just going for like everyone.
As a Spanish speaker, it should not be that bad.
I can understand quite a lot of Spanish.
That's the best I got for Spanish.
Sorry, but man's not got any Spanish.
I'm trying to think about this one.
Puta matvee!
Oh wait, no, I did wrong.
That's my Espanol.
We're going...
Guards, guards, guards.
No, a horse.
Anything but a horse.
I'm sorry, but you're getting targeted first.
I don't want any horse problems.
Oh, the senator's under attack?
No, they should be attacking me.
How much health has he got?
Oh no, he's still like not even lost the square health.
Oh no, oh no, oh no.
Assassins help now.
Okay, we're good, we're good, we're good.
And someone got promoted.
Smells like promotion, boys.
Can I...
I don't think I can sneak past these guys, so...
We're just going to go for it, we're just going to send it.
My assassin recruits just take too long to come back and...
I'm dumb, so...
Time to get some sleep, please rest well.
Sleep well, sweet dreams.
Do you know other Italian words?
No.
Only like Spingy for push, Ayuto for help.
Katsuo, to swear.
It's Emmy at piano.
Aw, it's Emmy at piano?
She tickled on them ivories.
Thank goodness I have ivory skin,
because my goodness, I'm in for a good time.
They're attacking me, anyways.
I've not played this game, I've played the game in Dutch once.
Just so to say follow me in Dutch, you say volg, mate.
But, yeah, not really.
It's just subtitles and stuff.
I knew it.
Why in Dutch?
I wanted to learn Dutch at one point, but I gave up.
I only know Scots in English.
Family.
Yeah, Dutch is one of the easiest languages to learn.
If you're English speaking,
it only takes apparently like 40 hours to like get the basics to...
in all that jazz, so...
20 Florence, that was it.
In that chest.
It is a very goofy language,
but it's so easy to speak and learn.
So, if you're ever bored and you're like,
I want to do something,
just learn some Dutch, learn the animals.
The animals are quite funny,
because you can see how literal it is with animals.
So, Tartel is shieldpoden,
which literally shielded,
and then padded.
Shieldpoden.
It seems you are ready to die like a gentleman.
I've got to learn German since my sister moved there.
Hello, Lloyd, how are you?
Are you good?
Is the grass road?
No, the grass is groin.
There's some German for you.
Right, if we don't touch the floor, we get 100%,
but it's a bit finicky, honestly.
So, it's not a big deal if we touch the floor.
Yeah, the grass is groin, yeah.
Dine and murder is a lovely lady, yeah.
Sorry, I'm like completely goofing off right now.
I'm not even explaining the game anymore.
I'm just having a good time.
Most English people have difficulty with the ch.
I assume that's what you wanted me to say.
Yeah, in Scots to say a lock, which is a lake,
you say a loch, loch.
And then we also roll our r's.
It's not girl, it's girl, girl.
So, Scots kind of naturally have a buff for other languages,
which is pretty handy when you're trying to impress someone.
I think to say, all day every day in...
All day, took one Taiwan, all day every day in Vietnamese.
Nah, I don't think that's right.
Please perish.
Give me a clap, Papo.
I'm gonna clap them.
Sorry.
Yeah, this is just a classic tailing mission.
You're not to be out of their POV for 25 seconds.
We are tailing the banker.
He currently has our Jussie Jussie money,
which we do get back at the end of this mission.
I thought it's he was about to jump on the floor there,
and I was about to inhale a big inhale.
Khef me in clap, Papo.
Me spank me daddy.
Oh!
Khef me in clap, Papo.
There you go.
To the one Dutch person listening in right now,
he's having the time of his life.
He is absolutely on it.
He's like, I'll see your belief.
Oh, no, that's please.
How do you say mercy?
How do you say thank you?
Thank you, Bill.
He's like, oh, thank you, Bill.
Strawberry.
Thank you, Bill.
And his reactant.
It's me.
That's it.
I know like the other stuff, like Iquil.
It's like I won, like Iquiline.
Iquiline.
Go, go, go, go.
If you are a human, you say Iquiline.
If you are en vrou, Iquil.
Is he gonna get me in trouble?
I don't.
I think I can like kill this guy from the box.
What's inside the box?
Nothing.
I'm stuck.
Please get out.
Okay.
That was funny and unique.
Please don't do that again.
I always forget how to navigate this part.
Are you a fish?
I'm a cuttlefish.
I'm a little piece of paper.
Because I do hypnosis.
But I've yet to actually make a hypnosis.
Well, I have a hypnosis audio coming out.
But like an actual free to view one, like ASMR stuff.
Oh, can I need to get on that?
We go cold again, but it sounds terrible.
I'm kind of glad because I literally have so much ASMR stuff I need to edit.
And basically I need to wake up and then work before stream.
Because after stream, I can't do anything.
I don't want to kill this.
Someone's up there.
I really don't want to kill because if you put the bodies on the floor,
sometimes the bodies desync this.
Please stop.
Are you kidding me?
This thing was don't be detected.
I messed that up.
My goodness.
No, don't fall.
Okay.
It's fine.
The senator's right there.
The banker's over there.
Well, failed anyway.
It doesn't matter if I touch the floor.
Oh.
You brought the money.
Well, well.
Yeah.
The banker has a special evening plan.
I'm either on Twitter or on YouTube, but I've got three ASMR videos.
I need to come out and be like, thanks for 3,000 subscribers.
Subscribblers.
I better not lose sight of that.
Yeah.
Basically YouTube, like my stats say that I've been like subscribed to like over 5,000 subscribers.
But obviously, like, because we've been getting cold, it like keeps going down again.
And it's like, oh, okay.
I guess.
But, oh no, I can't leave.
Oh, I don't have to leave.
How do I get up here?
What are you thinking?
Where's the law?
Oh.
How do I get up here?
Yeah.
Oh.
Well, Vila only stream on YouTube.
There'll be Twitch streams.
Um, not really interested in Twitch because of the arbitrary, like, you're fine, but you're
not fine.
And yeah.
Whereas like YouTube, at least it's kind of like there's definitely an open status
quo with YouTube.
And that's much easier to, like, freaking sick.
Ezio.
Darling.
Hen.
You're stressing me out.
Get up.
Get it up.
Don't be nervous.
One in three men.
Get it up.
What do you mean?
I'm putting more pressure on you to perform.
Get it up.
Maybe that would be a really funny audio.
Like, I'm absolutely desperate and I'm like, get up, get up, get up.
But I'm feeling that'd be really, maybe for a meme audio.
I can do that.
I don't think that'd be a really funny audio.
I get, like, really aggressive, like, come on.
I've never been all on some before.
A lot of people have been.
Yeah.
The culling stops once, like, more content comes up.
So once I finish the stream, YouTube is going to have to admit to itself that I have 8,000
hours.
No.
I have eight hours in Assassin's Creed and, yeah, people were, like, actually interacting
and stuff on stream.
So, yeah, YouTube.
Strongly won.
YouTube zero.
And the girls have been absolutely fantastic about the culling as well.
Like, they have been, I asked them.
Like, I do not expect the girls to stream every single day.
I've told them countless times.
The only reason I can do it is because I have Rotism, your honour.
But I did ask them, like, hey, for the first week, you're most likely going to have the
most views.
Like, you'll kind of, like, the debuff, no, buff from debut.
And, like, all of them were like, yeah, I'll give it my all.
Like, I'll stream as much as I can in the first week.
So freaking thankful and grateful.
And, like, I really think it will, like, completely help with the culling and all that jazz.
So this mission is bizarre.
You basically have to guess the path of where you need to go.
And, of course, I haven't unlocked the map.
So I've freaking done it wrong already.
Is it this way?
But you're also timed as well.
And I don't think I can remember off the top of my head.
I think I have to go up these stairs.
No, right, I'm going the wrong way.
So they get, like, suspicious of you if you go the wrong way.
And it's like, I'm sorry.
Oh, I know, like, the general idea, but I don't know the right way, 100%.
I don't even remember going past these portals, honestly.
I think we go right of the church.
And there's, like, upstairs, right of the church.
My brain is telling me.
Goodness.
Yes, and then take a left under here, and then the bridge that's up ahead.
Okay, I think we've already nailed it.
That is literally how much I've put to scoop.
The noise keeps putting me off, but, like, I know where I'm going.
Okay, geez.
Literally, this is the correct way.
And the game's like, I was suspicious.
No, this is the correct way, and I know it is.
I've played it enough to know this is the right way.
This is the way.
Anyone watch Mandalorian?
Grogo's adorable.
Grogo.
See, there we go.
We did it.
And yeah, that's all we have to do.
And we have completed this section.
None, none, more than an angry scorn.
Oh, yeah.
PayPal.
I don't know what's going on with the PayPal for the business,
because we literally submitted.
It has been established for months.
Like, all the stuff we've established for months.
I think, unironically, you guys were supporting, like, A.C.
and me so much that PayPal's like, this is suspicious.
And then the PayPal's now blocked.
So thank you for all the support you've shown the girls already.
You literally got the account suspended.
You've literally, like, so much support you've suspended
being able to support the girls' monetary,
which is hilarious if you think of it.
Okay, we're just tailing the guards.
This is the course on mission I was talking about,
which is necessary to have them.
And if you avoid the guards as much as possible
to hold on to the group for as long as possible
because you have two sets of girls
that will go out to distract guards.
But if you get too close to guards and you didn't want to distract,
they essentially get wasted.
And it's about me literally suffering from success.
I think management managed to pay everyone
for the watch-alongs in time before that happened.
But I hope so, because there was a lot of money.
I think, like, the total for sponsors...
No! We lost a group to that.
To the PayPal.
I think the total of, like, sponsorships was, like...
I don't mind talking about this,
was, like, roughly in the 5,000 US dollars mark
for everyone, like, compiled.
The original budget was, like, 20,000,
but hardly anyone was replying to the agency.
So shout out to Umi Plus and shout out to VNU Agency.
Don't be surprised if you see us collaborating with them.
They were fantastic and lovely
and actually gave us the time of day.
Um...
Yeah.
So don't be surprised if you see us working with those girls
because their agency was kind enough to give us the time of day,
whereas pretty much everyone else ignored us, so...
Yeah.
Happy it went well.
Yes, the watch-alongs were a complete success.
Special thank you to everyone who did them and all of that jazz.
I'm currently listening to flirting in my ear
because I just heard her say,
Priest of Confession or something like that.
Oh, my God.
What happens if we had a nun design, okay?
But then she had, like, a real design under it,
but we promote her as, like, a genuine,
like, completely covered up nun.
And, like, the promo artwork is at her voice lines
or, like, super conservative and everything.
And then, on debut, she reveals her real design.
That'd be so cool.
I'm allowed to say this stuff out loud
because I don't control the design,
so I'm allowed to say this stuff.
Um...
I've got none to do with it.
Uh...
I love having no more responsibilities.
There's not gonna be a Fond de la Buse
because I don't have that responsibility anymore.
Yay!
But admit it, you love Fond de la Buse.
I'm allowed to do it.
Seeing you all to come alive was so fun.
Did you, like, see in the behind the scenes
of how we all looked?
I am very interested in getting a Celtic design.
Uh, I'm gonna say something controversial, Karen.
I actually don't, like, have Mbuba on Vichubama Do.
And not my thing.
And, like, the cleavage and all that.
No, not my thing.
No, he got yo-inged by two of the freaking girls.
Are you so dumb?
Why would you do that?
Grrr.
V's sucking my fame age is like,
bruv, it was rough.
It was rough.
Development was rough.
I'm very happy.
I never have to develop anything ever again.
Like, it's completely off-handed.
I no longer have to do anything.
And it's so, it's such a good feeling.
Right, we're just gonna hire these courtesans
to make sure all is good.
But I think we're, like, pretty safe.
Make yourself flat.
Honestly, I might.
Um, in an alternative costume or something.
Design.
Alternative outfit, that's what you say.
Target is on the move.
I repeat, tango is on the move.
Alpha.
Bravo.
Charlie.
Delta.
Echo.
Foxtrot.
Gamma.
Indigo.
I don't know if that's alphabet.
Right, right, right.
Girls, girls, put your arm down.
Put your arm down.
Into the hay bale of we go.
The hay bale of shame.
But big plus for you.
Behind the scenes and the info.
What better way to celebrate my victims
than to join in the brotherhood?
Yeah, like, I'm really, not really bothered for secrets.
It's like, how do you do this?
Well, put a lot of money behind it.
Okay, how do you do that?
If you ever want to start a VTuber agency,
I'm gonna say this to you,
and this is the best advice you will ever get.
Whatever you think it's gonna cost,
double it,
and then give it some more.
Whatever time you think it's gonna take,
double it,
and give it some more.
I had a lot of issues with, um,
like, artists going past, like, deadlines.
So, everything slid back into me,
and it was horrific for me,
which is why I don't have a lot of things done.
Like, my ASMR audios are recorded,
but they aren't edited for you that go on YouTube.
And it's a shame because I wanted to have that all done,
but, you know, things happened and stuff happens,
and...
But everything's been fantastic.
Like, the reception the girls received,
like, I'm just so glad people are, like, loving on them
and just so happy with them.
Like, um,
it was, like, not easy to have...
I'm about to get caught,
because I'm freaking sitting on a wall.
It was, like, not easy to, like,
assign people a pre-made model.
Like, I saw some people, like, ask,
like, why don't they just create the models themselves
that they like?
And it's like, you have...
I understand that Idol End do that.
You have no idea how freaking hard it is
to coordinate, like, X amount of modellers
to come together, to come make a concept,
come to this, come to that.
I am not doing that approach.
Please do not think the other is going to end up doing that approach.
However, the girls are more than welcome to...
Hello? Hello? No, we missed a...
We missed the opportunity to assassinate them.
Bruh.
Come back here right now. My goodness.
Come back here.
Oh, right. Well, just do it later.
Oh, but just...
Are you supposed to walk right in front of us?
I think the court is on its path and maybe mess them up.
Bruh, get right back here.
But yeah, I am more than happy for the girls
to tell me what they want for alternative outfits and stuff.
That's not a problem at all.
But to do a debut that has input from the start,
that's like being signed on in development
is like six months in the making.
No one wants to be hanging about six months
waiting for their new job to start.
Yano?
Oh, Meru. Hi, Meru.
How are you doing?
He has a game.
Amy's gone live.
Okay. Amy...
Oh, whoops, I was in pain and tension.
Hold on, I'm getting walloped by a frickin' lance.
Oh, no, the hay bale!
Oh, my ankles!
The hay bale! I missed...
Oh, that's more guards!
I'm just... I'm hiding in the corner.
There's so many guards around me.
Oh, my God! How did they all follow me here?
All right, I'm calling in the assassins.
You're stuck.
Oh, my God.
There is so many.
Rip the ankles, I know.
Funny you come in here, Meru.
I was just talking about your agency.
I was seeing how Yumi Plus
is one of the very few agencies
that responded to the watch-along offers
that VLR made.
Suspicious shout-out to Yumi Plus.
We love Yumi Plus out here.
They found us in two seconds.
Literally, I was pinned against that wall.
I was like, please don't find me, please don't find me, please don't find me.
Oh, what? Yeah.
Hardly.
We were talking about the watch-along sponsors for VLR's debut.
And your agency and VNU
were the only two agencies
that were kind enough to respond to us.
Where are Claudia and Maria?
We just talked with the money.
They followed us all.
So, we're trying to go to Amy's room.
I have good news for you.
I promote you to go to Amy's room.
So, if any mods you get,
one speaking permission,
Amy's stream link.
That's your only time you're allowed to talk.
Whoa, what's going on with the code in there?
I don't think I've seen that before.
All those numbers?
No more talking mods.
Silence!
Thank you.
Please enjoy watching AmyBizu.
I recommend you watch any of my gen-mates when they go live
because I myself am an endurance streamer.
And I will be here for many, many an hour.
I will be trying to finish the campaign mode of this game.
So, please do not feel any type of way
if you go to watch any of my gen-mates.
I absolutely appreciate it and love it.
Please always consider liking and scrub-scraping
to their channels.
I would love to see them get ahead of me sub-wise
because the girls are fantastic
and they have so much potential that I see in them.
And I just want them to...
I did not want to take your horse.
Please get back on your horse and leave me alone.
I apologize.
Oh, we're still short of the crossbow.
Maybe we can make enough money if we send the recruits.
What kind of need the crossbow for this mission that's coming up?
If you do not have the crossbow, it is a heck on Earth.
It's not a fun thing.
Mercy's laugh is so good.
You're running the content. You didn't say content too?
Yeah, tomorrow we do all the side content.
Today we do campaign mode and go back to 100% stuff.
Yeah, see, look at that money.
A thousand florins, thousand, thousand...
Oh, that's also another Scottish slang for you.
Sometimes you can drop the T-H and make it an E.
So the number fair T becomes the number fair T.
I don't know if you can even hear the difference, but yeah, with an F.
Very.
Whoa, we have 15,000? That's like so much money.
I didn't expect that much, actually.
I'm going to send the assassins on another contract just to get them more XP.
Because obviously the higher they are, the more likely they are not to fall in battle.
I really don't want anyone to fall in battle.
We should get a level up if they come back soon enough.
Right.
Someone say gambling time?
Wait, why is Amy doing it on her stream for you to say gambling time?
Is she being a naughty?
Oh, there's a thief down there.
Oh, I did gamble with all the money.
No, we're not gambling with the florins.
I need it for the crossbow ball.
And then we're going to go and travel to the barracks.
Come, will be cheap.
Crossbow ball.
Best in slot, which is BIS.
Best in slot or biz for short.
Any biz.
She's doing ASMR.
Oh, that's why she DM'd me asking about that.
Okay, yeah.
It makes sense now.
You may enjoy Amy's ASMR.
For no particular reason.
We gamble.
It's supposed to be ASMR.
Yeah, I never should.
I liked it, like ASMR.
I should DM and she's like, am I allowed to do ear licking?
I'm like, you know what?
Just go for it.
I said, I told her, don't breathe while you do the licking.
What does she mean by this?
I'm not that does not surprise me.
The French puttane have us under pressure.
Tell me about their gender.
Hydration check.
Chairs are a persuaded King Nui to lend him an entire army.
But don't let go.
Gamba to impress or discuss the course.
I don't have time before I have Valois by the throat.
We have them in a retreat.
They seem to be getting closer.
The situation...
What does that mean?
Ear licking.
Benny, so maybe I could use a little help.
Yeah.
Don't take any damage.
Close it.
Oh, I should have bought smoke bombs.
This is bizarre.
They spawned in so many enemies.
I get it's supposed to be that you're overrun, but...
My goodness.
Hold on.
You can disengage from fights by just running away and jumping.
For some reason, jumping makes the AI cry.
The AI will not swing for you if you jump.
The other entrance.
Wait a minute.
That has a double meaning.
No, no, refling the other entrance.
The other one.
Okay.
Now we destroy all of the baddies.
Oh, I do love going on a kill street because it's really satisfying.
Is that everyone?
The Baron de Rova, signals from the field.
Oh, bonjour.
You can come closer and say that.
Soon, all of...
Italy, I will be speaking to.
Very sensibilities.
It's so nice of them to wait one by one to attack you.
I know they have such good manners, honestly.
Mommy, want to explore that?
I read the funniest thing ever.
And if you know, you know.
It was like, what happens if they take my boy cherry?
And it was like, story will leave you thinking it's...
I was cackling, reading that.
I was like...
I wish you a lot of fun playing Brotherhood.
Going to watch the stream later in the day.
Until all of you have fun watching.
Good night, rest well, sweet dreams.
Thanks for hanging in.
Okay, right.
Look at the speed of this horse.
These horses are so much slower.
What did you mean by that?
Development team of Brotherhood.
By making the white horse the slowest and the black horse the fastest.
What did you mean by that?
Do you want to elaborate?
No?
Okay.
Something rather odd.
Rather odd about that.
But then again, it could just be coincidence.
But then, is it coincidence if you go up to like...
The tan horse is faster than the brown horse is faster than the black ones the fastest.
Should we be offended by a game that was made 14 years ago?
So deep!
It reaches out in the mountains!
Don't let the game journalists hear me.
Oh no!
It's candle to be...
I miss when they can gallop.
You can still gallop.
You have to hold A.
But the problem with galloping is if there's people in the way your horse will fall over.
Canceled on first game stream.
Wait, why would I get cancelled if I point out what the development did?
Why am I getting...
Hold on a minute.
No, no, no.
You can't cancel me.
My views do not reflect to be a lawyer agency!
I just screamed that.
Right, this is my only gripe.
This is my only gripe with this mission.
You get left at the gate here only...
I repeat, you get left at the gate here only to have to horse your way back to the villa
when the last mission just got you from the barracks to there.
So you've literally just gone back to like what you just did.
That's my only gripe.
That's right with that.
On the end.
Oh, I should do.
It is smart.
Like just me going for like 30 minutes ear to ear.
What was that noise?
Was that a door?
I sounded like...
Once inside, your men can overpower the camp's patrols, correct?
Yes, but...
Especially if the patrols are taken completely by surprise.
Yes.
My ankle, I'm sitting on it.
Funny, I can't believe it.
We are going to walk, right?
That person grunting?
Literally, man.
Cody, you're truly a man after my order.
I'm going to burp, I'm so sorry.
Oh, that was a...
Maybe burp.
My troops will gather it from the day.
Should have been a frog V to burp.
That would have been very good.
Oh, could have been a hypofrog, honestly.
Do you ever sit normally?
I honestly cannot sit in a normal chair.
Maybe I should do a foot cam, like a thigh cam stream.
And it's just me showing you how badly I sit, like the entire time.
I thought a foot cam stream during a horror game would be funny
because you can watch me shake my ankles.
And I also have a thing where I press my toes into the ground.
Like, I literally have like little indents on my toes
from where I press them into the ground
because of the way my, like, toes like, form over on it.
I know it sounds really silly, but, you know...
Sometimes you don't pick the rotism.
And the rotism picks you.
Um...
And we've got three so far.
That would actually be funny.
Okay, I'm down for it.
Wait, okay, my guy's already gone.
How about five cents on you?
I don't want to get caught because we can easily 100% this.
But the assassin recruits take so long.
Okay, thankfully they got caught in the...
Whoa, we're getting action shots, like the horse...
What? Okay.
Let them get up.
Look, look, they're a new recruit.
Let them get up, let them get up.
Is the other assassin gonna try and help or...?
No.
He's just letting them get absolutely lanced.
Right, I'll help him out.
Oh, she's losing health, I don't like that.
There, right, go kill the other guy now.
No, I got these...
I got discovered because of that.
Okay, whoa, we need to help.
We need to help, they're too strong.
This guy's too strong.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, not the horse, not the horse, not the horse.
And the boss, and the boss, get him in the boss, hit him in the boss.
Hit him in the boss, like, don't speak to...
Okay, okay, okay, okay, horse, it's fine, it's fine.
I don't know how to go against the horse.
Please leave me alone.
I don't know how to deal with horses.
Okay, there we go.
Okay, we're dealing with a crossbow ball.
Jeez.
Rank 10 assassins are so good, honestly.
We are very slowly leveling them up.
I'm wanting to try and pick a fight.
Can I pick a fight?
Ooh, feather.
Look how daintily I jumped over that, that was beautiful.
Oh, are you stuck?
Are you okay?
Have you heard about this?
Have you heard about this jump?
Hey, there we go.
Right, we're going to upset these guys.
Oh, okay, never mind, okay.
Wait, that's a barrier?
That's a barrier.
Can you jump over them?
Whoa, I've never seen that before.
Right, okay, we're going to upset these guards on purpose.
So we can...
Ouch!
I didn't expect that, jeez.
Oh my goodness.
I just got double whammy right off the bat.
Oh my...
Right, okay.
I need to take the big guy.
Thank you, big guy, for perishing.
Can't handle you.
Okay, how about that?
Yeah, big...
Oh, we need one more.
Right, who's going to perish?
You are going to perish.
Oh, see the horses are getting stuck here.
I don't know where I'm supposed to go now.
Oh, I'm good.
I predict a riot.
Ooh, do you not want to go down there
because it's such a nightmare getting out there.
How many steps is that?
I don't even think I've done a double kill yet.
I'm probably going to have to wait till the air stops.
I'm going to have to go back to the barracks.
I'm riding a horse and I'm going to go back to the barracks.
Oh, I'll most likely do a full playthrough
of Esu's storyline.
Where am I going?
Have you seen this?
Okay, wait, I'm just being deaf.
Ooh, right, we're going to do this Borgia Tower.
That's a lot of guards.
Are we going to hit by Border Patrol?
We're going to get you.
And then we're going to just sneak up here and kill you.
Okay, I'll take that.
Do you guys need help?
I'll give you a second recruitment beam
and let you guys fight it out.
And I'm going to climb up here and do this.
Do we skip up here?
I cannot play Assassin's Creed 1.
I absolutely suck at it.
I am so sorry.
I cannot do it.
I've tried Beyond Belief.
I ended up watching someone else play it
just so I know the storyline.
Beyond Belief, I'm absolutely trash.
I probably...
No, I'm doing variety,
but what I'll probably do running up to October 10
is I'll play Assassin's Creed 2 before it,
then October 10, play Brotherhood again,
and then after play Revelations,
and then we'll get the full Ezio story.
Sometimes it doesn't engage in combat mode,
and then the enemies get a free hit on you
because there's nothing you can do.
I don't know why it does it.
I mean, I don't know why it does it,
because stuff and things, but...
We're level 4.
We're getting a little bit decent.
It's not the best.
We're really not that strong.
Plumping it all into armor
because I get so nervous for them.
I don't want to do a level 4.
Maybe a 3?
Send 2 on a level 3
and split the XP, which is like 100 each.
Yeah.
Oh, a second one?
Okay, we'll do that.
Okay, that's some all sent to get...
Oh, my tummy rumbled.
My tummy rumbled.
Make me to get some...
Oh, my tummy rumbled again.
I don't know if I was getting picked up in the mic,
but yeah, I think I'm getting a bit peckish
for, like, actual things.
You know, sometimes a meat stick doesn't do it.
Sometimes you need more.
That...
There's so many jokes I can make,
but they're too easy.
I'm just going to leave it.
Actually, I'm going to buy smoke bomb pouch if I can.
It's 9000 Florence!
Who has 9000 Florence?
Unreal.
Unreal Engine.
Who has 9000 Florence?
Not me.
Yeah, two me say.
You know what they say?
None in the pink.
All in the stink.
Oh, 9000!
Okay, we're going to get a smoke bomb.
Excuse-moi, excuse-moi.
J'ai vu du smoke bomb de pouch.
Pouch de smoke bomb?
Smoke bomb de pouch?
No, not the knife belt.
Okay, we have smoke bombs, almost.
We, a viewer, are not serving the talents.
Okay.
I can't believe...
I actually don't get enough of a cut or a split
that I can't even afford to...
Oh, there's an assassin recruit down here.
Yes, I will help you!
No, let me help you!
Oh, it's a lady.
Oh, my lady.
We actually need to smoke bomb
because we need to kill people in a smoke bomb.
For, uh, why...
What?
Why do they just get aggressive on us?
Sometimes you need a group of meat sticks.
A smart booth.
Who said that?
Maud just put them on a warning.
Whoever insinuates that the A smart booth
is going to be utilized for anything but tingling.
Put them on a warning.
Don't.
Teasing.
I'm teasing.
I actually think I might need to get...
I, like, I never noticed that I'm, like, hungry or need to pee,
and then as soon as I notice it, I'm like,
ah, I'm perishing, I'm perishing.
Maud's failed this man's tax return.
Oh, my God, I cannot wait to...
I have a funny short coming out about, like,
what you can get taxed back in a VTuber agency.
Uh, you know my doughnuts on rewards?
One of them's going to be a length chart.
I get to submit that for tax back
because it's what I needed to do
in order to operate.
Like, it's crazy what you can get in tax back.
Like, obviously it doesn't mean I get the full price of it back in taxes.
No, it just means, like, the...
It's like, okay, you can get a few, like, $2 back on your tax return.
It's like, I think.
Thanks, appreciate it.
But, like, yeah, you can get tax back on models,
get tax back on equipment, get tax back on internet,
get tax back on, uh, rent as well.
I get tax back on paying your tax, the stream.
Oh, I don't even want to think about taxes, honestly.
Although it was pretty, pretty...
It reduces what you owe.
Yes, it doesn't mean I'm going to, like, get the full thing back.
Sorry, sometimes when people talk about tax back,
it sounds like they mean you get the full thing back,
which is not the case at all.
Everything is a business, right, of, like,
if you can justify it 100%, like,
because I can, like, imagine a vealer got audited
and I have to go, like, oh, yeah, you know,
this special artwork, um, that was part of the business
because we're an entertainment business.
It would be hilarious.
ASMR Girl IRS agent interrogates you.
Wait, what am I doing?
Oh, right in the balls, right?
Oh!
Wait, why did...
Did I just break?
Oh, my God.
I'm sorry, I really just...
Like, the Lance men.
Small poles only, please, my goodness.
They're so hard to defeat.
The company has an account and does everything legally.
It's by Otonus.
Okay, dude.
Management.
Actually, there's an account and that's true.
Small poles only, so ogre.
Wait until he'll tell you about my doctor's visit.
That's for a later stream.
You tell it in, like, raw 4K detail about, like, what occurs.
Right, what am I supposed to do?
Follow Bartolomeo and his mercenaries.
Okay.
Okay, he's about to activate this next thing.
I am now to perish the guards of my own death gold.
So this guy can go first.
And then I can do you.
And then, last but not least, I can do you.
No.
Don't be silly, Ezio.
Aim on the guard, my goodness.
By the way, this came...
What?
Hello?
I got desynchronized, but I did what you asked.
I did everything right and I still lost.
Wait, this isn't the original checkpoint.
We still...
Wait, we hit the checkpoint and it let us go through.
Okay, okay, okay, I'll take it.
Okay, next guard checkpoint.
There's one to our left.
I might go kill him the new.
Good day to you.
Please stop walking.
Thank you.
Okay, there's a second guard there.
I really want to get...
I need them to split up.
Focus, focus.
Focus, there's a pizza on your focus.
I was too in range.
If I can time this right, I'm not going to desync.
I did it.
Did you see that, though?
The AI looked at me.
Oh, my goodness, right?
What way are you going, Bartolomeo?
You're going this way.
That was the way.
I'm French.
Freeacak...
Don't make me sleep!
I am a French.
I am a Frenchman.
I am not Italian or an assassin.
Ooh, I don't know how...
But we did get desync to do that.
We made it which is a funny thing.
I have a guard right here.
I don't remember this part.
All right, you perish. I've got two guards next to each other. I don't like...
Oh, he's coming this way! Oh, there's a dead body!
Oh, okay. It's fine.
Oh, no, he's gone for the dead body!
I didn't think that through. That was very lucky that we didn't desync all there.
Phew, we did it. The hard part's over. Now it's for the easy part.
Where we just walk up to this gate.
And then we get to learn how French people say Italian dog, which is chien du talien!
Are you gonna have any European-friendly streams?
Like, you mean start an earlier than the time I stream right now?
This is probably going to be my stream start time until...
Daylight savings kicks in for some places.
Which part of France are you from?
Montréal!
Open the gate!
It's E-friendly. It started at 8 p.m.
It's a bit late if you're, like, German ahead one, or...
Is this a European-unfriendly stream? Like, do we not like them?
No, we do. It's just time zones. Like, it's 4 a.m. when I start streaming.
So, I'm doing my best.
But I'm an endurance streamer, so I do hit a lot of time zones.
And it's unlikely, like, reeflings have, like, 8 hours to set, like, through an entire stream.
Like, maybe if you work from home, or you're listening at work,
but it's a bit dangerous listening at work, because sometimes I tease a lot.
Like, especially in ASMR streams, I tease quite a lot.
This is me just having a really good time.
So, I'm pretty tame right now, from Brotherhood.
Repsleepska. Yeah.
If you live in Turkaya...
Arkadijim! Arkadijim!
Means friend.
And... Turkay.
I think.
Enough of your crap.
Release my wife.
Such entitlement from a man born with nothing to his name.
Mine is worth its currency.
I work from home, and your endurance streams probably end when your work starts.
So, I'm definitely gonna be...
How can you focus on working, listening at the same time, though?
Unless it's, like, background noise. That's different.
Arkadijim! I learned that from Assassin's Creed Revelations, because it's set in Turkey.
Never learn.
These guys are, like, the hardest enemies you can kinda get.
But if you just jump at them, you can get away with it.
Well, you just gotta break their stance, and just lick that down.
And back to me.
The trick is, I don't really work.
So, this cutscene is a glitch that was never patched out.
This is a full edited cutscene, where he, like, go get my wife.
It never loads. It will never load in time.
I have no idea what it looks like.
Well, I assume it looks like him, um, screaming at you, and then he gets his sword and goes offscreen.
It will never load. It doesn't matter what you do. It never loads.
Unless, like, maybe someone went into the game data, and, like, I went into free camera, possibly.
Um...
Then you could definitely do it.
I said small poles only!
We don't want them being p-
No! You've ruined my speed!
Okay. We did it, though. It's fine.
Can I open the gate, please?
Become anonymous to open the gate?
There's no one attacking me!
Right, that's what I thought. I was gonna say, there's literally no one attacking me.
You underwaste my lack of shame. I've listened to some pretty sick stuff at work before.
Honestly, whatever helps pass the time, like, I'm sorry, but work can be so mundane.
Like, the best work days are the times where you're super busy, because you blink, and it's the end of the day,
but you are shattered. That's the only problem. Like, you're absolutely exhausted, and it's really...
So, you're actually on a timer in this section, and I only have six crossbow bolts, which I do not like at all right now.
You can. I might mess up the sequence. I do it quite a lot.
Don't look back. Don't look back. Don't look back!
Okay, we did it. We did it. We did it. We did it.
You need to air assassinate him for 100%.
All done.
You have no clue how many hours I need to kill in the day.
Damn, straight respect is earned and not purchased.
Hmm, hmm.
Oh, you should probably go to sleep if you need to be up in six hours.
It's healthy to get eight hours of sleep.
Digi, no. Men need eight hours of sleep, where women typically need ten hours of sleep.
But yeah, definitely don't risk your health.
Sir Shameless, they call me.
I'll be honest, all your girls make my work day go by real quick.
It's lovely. Oh, there's some reason to hear.
AP Gal confirmed Lord.
Oh my god, VTuber streamer parody of that song. Let's go.
Okay, then you can collect both of these chests if you're fast enough,
whilst it's telling you this act is over.
I swear they purposely did this because no other act takes so long to complete the sequence six,
like the ending bit to tell you it's over.
I decided a long time to destroy my sleep schedule.
That's so legal.
Forget Paris.
Worth it feels good.
Sleep. What is that? I don't need to sleep.
Oh, she caught me.
If I can remember this sequence, we may have to...
Oh, that reminds me, there's actually a thieves challenge,
which is to dive 200 meters, which you can do off the top of this building.
So we might as well do it now because we're pretty high up.
Ready, steady.
There we go. That's a thieves challenge done right there. Dive complete.
Oh, I've got a hiring discount on the thieves. Fantastic.
I... well, enjoy that.
I need to level them up a bit more before they pickpocket,
but we're getting close to the point where we don't...
like Moolah, like that. Where'd any go on the map?
Where are we? What's our heading?
Okay, we've liberated that Borgia zone, which is fantastic.
Where's the mission? Is it south?
The mission's in the thieves guild,
which doesn't have a Borgia place on the way,
but we'll start to try and get all the Borgia towers.
I'm just going to use the old teleport feature.
Yeah, yeah.
And we'll send the assassin recruits on the way to get leveled up a bit more.
Watching your streams of high level...
Can you stop that?
Try and make me blush?
Like, I'll literally just meme in my butt off playing a really good game.
Okay, we've got level 5, so we're starting to get a bit...
I'm going to put it in weapons now just so they have a few more things.
We need to destroy a tower in order to get our third signal.
Can I send you guys?
I'm going to send everyone for the purpose of levelling up that level 1.
Like, to get them really levelled up from the start.
So if they do end up in a fight, it's not a problem.
Is it working? Yes.
Have you been killing people with your horse?
Maybe they do.
No.
They're not buying it.
You buy the horse out there.
He looks like the...
Oh no, the words aren't working on my head.
Please don't shoot me and my friend.
He looks up and he remembers.
Ooh, I love birds.
Not at the bird and people die everywhere.
People die, die, die, die, die, die, die.
I don't know the words, but like, I know the tune and everything.
Mmm.
Strongly means the most important meal of the day.
We're going to not grab that thief because he's already claimed the wall.
I never chase thieves.
If they go up the wall, I cannot be bothered.
I absolutely cannot be bothered.
That's probably the only thing in this game that I'm just like, it doesn't matter.
It's just like if you wanted to poke at the money and whatever item is on their persons.
What am I doing? What?
What, do you want to do?
You guys want to do kegels together?
Are you ready? Hold for three seconds.
One, two, three, release.
You know what, you know what I learned about guys?
I learned this a while ago.
If a guy wants to jumpstart his Eiffel Tower,
he has to close his end, which is crazy.
A little, a little twitch the, what, twitch it?
Just so you can, well, twitch it, I guess, yeah.
Which is crazy lore for guys.
Absolutely crazy lore.
Well, I don't know if I was too generic with that.
In order to achieve sword art.
Oh, and also when you go with the toilet, you're perlittle.
I've sent my men out to find him.
What do we call them?
You're perlittle.
I don't know, double eyeballs can touch the toilet and it's super cold and uncomfortable.
I only learned that super recently because I saw a meme about it.
And I was like, wait, what?
You're perlittle guys.
They're going to retract and save you.
They get too cold.
They're going to go straight back up to your belly button.
No.
Kill all the attackers.
Sure, sure, sure.
Wait, why are we in this?
Oh, it's a fight.
It's a fight.
And I just sent all my assassins away.
Wrong guy.
You're hurting the wrong guy, Steve.
Right, where are the enemies?
Got an enemy, enemy, enemy, enemy, enemy.
Enemy, enemy, enemy, enemy.
Enema, give them an enema.
Do not give them an enema.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Whoa.
That was so cool.
That attack to double splash over.
I really enjoyed that.
Ah, go away.
They scare me.
That's a nice, oh, I do have three names.
Bad boy, bad boy, bad boy, bad boy, bad boy.
Bad boy.
Oh, I missed.
Okay, let's get this big guard.
Oh, wait, I thought I killed him.
I wasn't paying attention, I'm sorry.
I think I'm going to have to get food and refuel in a second
because I'm starting to get a little bit delirious.
I'm going to get some egg and I think I'll go ravioli.
Maybe a wee bit longer, maybe a three.
Three whole minutes away from stream.
I cannot believe it.
Absolutely unprofessional, unacceptable.
Oh, damn it, sorry.
Everybody wants to be in the Assassin's Creed.
Brotherhood is really, people quite work with the timing of the song.
She hates us now.
How long?
How many hours?
Five hours?
Oh, it's been five hours already.
I've been gushing about this game.
You know what, reflings?
Life's good.
Full stop, life is good.
Got doing my thing.
We having a good time mimin' along.
I'm rambling away about any old shite that passes my brain.
Life is good.
We're about to go get some juice.
I think I'll make a tea.
Yeah, I'll make a tea.
You'll get some food, maybe some snacky too.
I don't think I need to pee.
No, no pee yet.
Actually, I should probably gallop, so I'm not that far behind him,
because he is like so far ahead of me.
Oh, no!
My thieves has perished.
But thieves are ours.
Yonkers, you're mine now.
They are, they are...
Oh, I don't really want to kick them to death.
Like, make it quick.
See, oh, don't make them suffer, my goodness.
It's a bit morbid.
See, oh, when you do that, I've done that.
I think I'd rather like make it quick and painless,
not like drag it out.
Oh, he got the horse!
How did he do that?
I don't know how he did that, but do it again.
It looked like he did it with some...
Well, it's 1AM, so I'll take my leave.
Please, rest well.
Anyone who does have to rest or to sleepy bye-bye, please don't worry.
Odds are.
I'm actually still going to be streaming by the time you wake up.
I said it.
Yeah, it's true.
It's true.
I might finish the campaign and I might want to do some more.
The accusations are true.
So don't worry if you have to go to bed.
Might see you when you wake up.
So sweet dreams.
See you in the morning.
Jump off wall.
Get kicked into wall.
The accusations are true.
I'm addicted.
But not as much as I'm addicted to you.
You guys might have the nicotine patch on your head,
but the truth is under these bangs or fringe,
I've got a nicotine patch too,
and it's covering my entire forehead.
I wish I didn't send my sassons on that mission.
Whoa.
Okay, there we go.
This is the Roman bath house.
This is based on reveal, please.
They are public bath houses.
Okay, there's a lot going on.
Hold on, there's a lot going on.
Hold on.
Oh, big armor guy.
Big armor guy.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Parish.
My notoriety is going up.
I like how he just swings that air.
Whoa.
Okay, can we get him while he's on the floor?
Get him on the floor.
Ow.
Lavolpi.
Old man.
OG sand.
Put your Glex on.
Put your Glex on, OG sand.
It's me.
And he is performing in a play in Stanova.
He played in the first Stanova.
That was definitely a VA they had used a lot.
And they were like, please just use any other voice.
It's going to be so obvious it's you.
So he had to go stale and play tonight.
Or a visa game.
I don't have nicotine.
I have BLR.
That's so good.
Sleep is for the weak.
I don't know.
Sleep is very healthy.
And apparently, if you don't sleep regularly,
then it's bad for your longevity.
And you might expire.
I don't really want you to expire in all honesty.
I'm going to tell you the truth, chief.
I'd rather you didn't expire.
So, please don't.
We're getting some strawny time, though.
You're getting strawny time for a very long time every day.
You could be sick of me.
Yeah.
Oh, the music's so good.
There's also a feather on top of the Colosseum,
but we can get that at a later time.
We expire.
Survive for a moment.
Not only am I putting you at war,
I'm now expiring you manually.
You have been expired.
Wait, where did he go?
Oh, I literally glanced away
and he was perfectly hidden behind Ezio.
And I was like, oh, where is he?
All right.
Enemies, enemies, enemies, enemies.
Give them an animal.
Give the enemies an animal for how much?
What the fuck, you know?
I'm about, I don't know.
I'm definitely needing a quick,
a quick five minute break for you guys.
We'll just, I'll maybe read some Marshmallows,
I'm gonna take five minute break,
and I'll eat and restore my hydration levels and stuff.
Getting a wee bit delirious.
Just a wee bit.
Why is there so many guards this time?
I don't really recall this game,
like this part having so many guards.
Oh, there's a guy on the edge over there.
Are we all going?
Okay, he's stuck.
There, okay, there we go.
All good, all good in the hood.
She's got enemies on the brain, Freudian slump.
And I'm gonna give them, sorry,
I stuck on my head, it's like a really dumb meme.
Can I summon Leonardo?
I can.
So on these benches,
is where you can buy more of Leonardo's inventions?
Is there a thing up there?
No, it's on the other side.
Leave me alone.
What did you ask the scrawny animal marriage when?
Why are you expecting me to come in the middle of the night?
Do you think I won?
I drank a good stretch, yeah.
Right, we'll finish this sequence
because I think this is a quick sequence.
I think we're already like pretty much getting through it.
We're about to claim the costumes off of enemies.
Do you think my assassin recruits had finished the mission?
So, Lavalpe is now convinced Marquio Valley is a thief.
It is a traitor
because the events are synchronized
and not too much.
Cesare leaves the castle
when he could have got tipped off.
Marquio Valley uses guards
to tell him secrets of the Borgia
and Lavalpe finds it just far too suspicious
and he's basically telling us
if you do not put an end to Lavalpe,
to Marquio Valley, I'll do it myself.
Which is scary biscuits and scary beans.
I'll leave the toes out of the blanket for you.
Oh my God, did you hear my voice there?
For you.
Would you still love me if I sounded like you?
I'm wrecking and decking.
We're on sequence six.
Act six and there's nine acts together.
Yes, I right you would.
I am still your servant and ally.
Which was an accident.
Are you demanding that I discount your actions
and rely on friendship?
I am asking, not demanding,
to unite Italia,
I must have every institute
and if the church does not fall in love,
I will eliminate it entirely.
You know that I really work for you,
not the folk.
I can't believe it.
You said I'm getting rid of Catholicism.
There's only one way I can know that unconditionally now.
You intend to kill me.
You're most loyal friend.
I have friends that try to tell me that Assassin's Creed.
Are you letting me go?
This Assassin's Creed Brotherhood isn't a good game.
You will not regret it.
There's so many cool mechanics in Brotherhood,
wish they didn't steal the DLC though.
God, give me the costumes for the play.
It's a shame DLC was really the hype.
No one else shall have her.
Make doubly sure it's done correctly.
He said no one else is allowed to look at it.
I obey?
Ooh, that's what we should say to Sheebie.
We obey.
We obey Sheebie please.
Okay, now this horse constantly gets turned around
so you really can't be too close to him at all.
We obey Sheebie.
We obey.
We do not question.
Just taking our time with this guy
because he's so...
He spins around so easily
and you can desync so quick.
Taking our time.
Easy.
Use it.
Ooh.
This might be the longest hailing mission
they've actually put in the game.
Ahhhh.
This entire act is just tailing missions.
It's like, tail this person.
Now don't get me wrong.
I'm not one of those people that complain about the gameplay.
Like, if I complained about gameplay,
I would rather suggest something else
that's supposed to happen.
But if you consider all the different types of mechanics
or subjects that put in the game,
for example, like the lair of Romulis
or Leonardo's missions,
these are completely alternative.
If you're gonna be like,
oh, I don't really enjoy tailing missions.
I completely understand that.
I'm not dogging on your comment, by the way.
I'm just discussing it from...
If you ever wanted to kind of review it.
Oh, by the way, these guards.
Useless.
Absolutely useless.
You can just walk straight in.
I think you can also walk past these two
if you get into that hay bale.
They just forget you exist.
They think you're a fart.
Oh, whoopsies, whoopsies.
Whoopsies, I wasn't paying attention.
Whoopsies.
So it doesn't matter if the guards spot me.
It's not a problem.
Although, if I run, it does fulfill the...
Can you go in the hay bale?
Jeez, my goodness, gravy.
It's evil.
Are you okay?
Well, nerve is nilly, honestly.
You can...
If they stop looking at me...
Yeah, okay, yeah.
You hardly have to kill anyone in these kind of things.
The game is so forgiving.
That's why I absolutely adore about Assassin's Creed Brotherhood.
It is so forgiving.
Now, don't get me wrong.
You'll still get a few things where they're like,
that shouldn't have got me, but yeah.
It's so forgiving.
So if you hide in the hay bale,
wait for this guy to come up,
and then send him a...
Oh, he doesn't come up.
Well, wait for the guy to go away,
and then...
Yep, there you go.
It's so quick.
So, he gets on a horse.
You're actually supposed to go over here
to get on a horse,
to continue to follow him.
But it's not really obvious.
Like, most people would just chase on foot,
which is completely doable.
But for some reason, they put the horses...
A wee bit to the left, and...
Yeah.
It's a bit harder to recognise.
But yeah, definitely this game,
if you've never played Assassin's Creed before,
I would actually...
You'd miss out on the plot of two,
which is the start of Itzu's story,
but mechanic and forgiveness-wise.
If you're not really a strong gamer,
Brotherhood definitely is one for you.
Um...
Ah, my tummy's wobbling if you heard that.
You probably can't over-the-game play, actually.
Yeah.
The fact that you're passionate about the game,
it's just...
You latch onto something,
you can play a game,
and you have absolutely no idea what to expect,
and then you just adore it.
Like, a binding of Isaac is another game.
I didn't know what to expect,
and, like, the first time I played it,
I think I played it for, like, five hours,
and can't...
He did the turnaround thing he's now supposed to do,
and now he's chasing me!
Leave me alone!
Oh, my God.
That was...
That was gonna desync so hard,
all because he freakin' turned around!
I knew you were gonna do that.
I warned you guys.
He always turns around in this tail-in mission.
He gets caught on NPCs,
and spins around.
It scares me every time.
I never expect that...
He was chasing me, though.
I don't normally expect them to, like,
turn around and chase,
but I guess if you're close enough, they will.
I'm also gonna visit your mum.
Um...
Have a nice visit.
Sorry.
I was gonna say something really mean,
but I refrained.
I was gonna say,
I saw her earlier this day.
Oh, he's done it again!
No way!
I'm gonna chat!
Don't do that again.
Don't do that again!
You're giving me a heart attack.
Goodness me.
A stronghold's off to visit his mum.
Doing your mom!
Doing, doing your mom!
You know he's strictly doing your mom.
Um...
So...
Oh!
Please don't attack me.
Incredible.
Let the recruits deal with it.
Oh, this isn't the right way!
This isn't the way to victory!
To victory!
This ain't the way to victory!
My assassins are now...
Uh, fighting it out.
I hope they're leveled up enough to deal with them.
To deal with them, to deal with them.
Because I don't have any more recruits!
Oh, no!
I needed recruits to 100% this mission.
Can I just stand about and wait for them to reappear?
Because I am patient enough to do that.
Um...
Destruction, destruction!
Oh, I wanna play GTA 4 actually.
An eco.
Want to go bowling?
Oh, they didn't come there.
One more minute.
Oh look, they've lost the health bar.
See, that's why I always put it into health.
Because they can make as many mistakes as they need to.
Wait, why am I getting yellowed?
Why am I getting yellowed when my assassin recruits are going ham?
Am I not going to be detected? I bloody hope not.
Right, that's fine. I can be detected.
Who is shooting?
What is going on over there?
Do you not need to reload?
Hello?
They just despawned.
Okay, well, as long as they're not dead, I guess.
Jeez.
No, you did not name your...
No, you didn't...
Bro, someone in chat has named themselves Fondle of Buzum.
Frickin...
No, I can't see it anymore.
Did Mods time you ever for that?
That's hilarious.
You don't need to tell that.
I read that. It was like Fondle of Buzum, Gen Zero B sucky.
I don't see it anymore.
Mods timed out, it was funny.
Unless you were spamming, then get bonked.
But that was kind of funny, I have to admit.
I almost ran out of time there.
I'm too busy reading chat.
I literally sounded like a monkey there.
I'm not even pretending.
I almost ran out of time.
Do not turn around again, I'm going to be so upset.
I don't think he does it too much in the sequence part.
It's the ghost of Christmas pass, Frickin yeah.
Yeah.
My voice literally can't right now.
Oh, he's getting really far ahead actually, hold on.
Sorry, I'm just really enjoying reading chat with you.
I apologize.
Because I remember that people enjoy when they get their stuff read out.
I never did my high sing.
Could I do the high sing?
So, sometimes when I started upstream,
I would actually read everyone's name out
just to try and be super thankful.
Maybe for the ASMR stream we could try it.
Because I understand people want to hear their name be said by me.
Because it's nice to be acknowledged.
Let's not pretend it's not nice to have streamer reply directly type thing.
Or like generally discuss it.
So maybe in the ASMR stream, like as a one off,
I will try my best to like say hi to everyone.
You there.
That's a lot of enemies.
I got enemies.
I'm calling in my recruits.
Okay, let's get to the fight.
Take this.
And this.
And that.
Okay.
I actually...
I'm gonna heal up and try and pick up a medicine vial.
Real names or username?
I would not say your real names.
I would never encourage anyone to use their real name.
On the internet, I name yourself something funny.
Or after like a video game for example.
Oh, there's no way I'm getting...
Is he gonna leave me alone or doesn't he hurt him?
I'm gonna hurt you if you come any closer.
It's you! You're aimbot!
Your armor is not that good, sir.
I know for a fact your armor is not that good.
Give me my crossbow bolt back right now.
I know you have some on your persons.
Not the knife.
It's not a knife.
That's a sword.
Yeah, exactly. Give me my crossbow bolt back.
That's exactly what I thought.
You're not that guy. Trust me, you're not that guy pal.
I started doing a marathon.
Imagine if you did Arkham Knight.
Oh, I did play Batman.
I'm gonna play the Batman.
Please don't stop and look at me.
Please don't stop.
The assassin should kill that third guy.
What is going on?
It's so loud when you guys kill people.
Okay, now the whole of Roma knows
that you're shooting guns over there.
Stranny's not your enemy.
Oh my god, it's Fond de la Buzum.
Are you gonna role play Azura?
In chat?
Damn, I hope to see it as long as I play.
It's very long.
More like can.
It's a little arm cannon.
I guess you could go through the live-shot participant tab.
Wait, I can see a list of everyone watching?
No, that's only on Twitch.
Maybe at the start of this ASMR.
As of one off, because it's just not plausible to keep up.
But just as a thank you for showing up,
still being here, still meaming around.
I haven't played Assassin's Creed,
but it seems similar to Arkham Knight.
I wouldn't entirely disagree.
Very agile, very agility-based.
Definitely, you know, hunting around.
This 100% is just don't kill anyone.
If you scoot your bot all the way along the Colosseum,
absolutely no issues.
You shouldn't run into any guards.
If you do, you can literally just hang off the ledge.
I wish I had the climbing glove, though.
That Leonardo bench would have came in clutch for this part of the section.
But unfortunately...
I don't have that.
Where am I supposed to go?
So the watchpoint is all the way...
Oh my god, that stance...
It actually looks pretty funny.
We're gonna go for this...
Whoa, I didn't even realize that guard could see me.
What? How could he even see me?
We'll go for the viewpoint,
and then we will continue with this mission.
This act is getting very close to being finished.
And then we will have a five-minute break.
I will read any marshmallows.
So if you want to ask any questions, you're more than can.
I did miss some during the 2.0 and the exposing Bielor.
Not that it wasn't good enough,
but maybe it wasn't on-subject,
or didn't quite necessarily relate to me for the 2.0.
So I just sent it.
So don't worry, I might give that a good week.
But you're welcome to ask any questions,
and then we will rehydrate.
I'm getting a T.
My voice is perishing.
Right, where am I supposed to go?
Over there?
There is a feather on top of the Colosseum,
but I'm actually happy to just climb up again.
Okay, that's where we're supposed to go.
Couldn't see it because of the render distance,
but that's okay, because this is an older game.
If you look at the three dots where it has time stamps
and reactions and option to pop out chat,
I think it's just chatters that have typed in chat.
I didn't know that.
I was just going to get you all to be like,
hi, and then start reading your name,
ear to ear.
Senior.
I've been waiting away for the last hour.
No, you haven't missed a thing.
I'm giving away.
We are on sequence six,
which is...
My god!
Why has thou forsaken me?
Right, heading out.
Thank you for hanging.
Again, anyone who is watching,
you've done so far.
You've done well so far.
It's five and a half hours.
I don't expect you to be here for the film.
Please rest when you can.
And also,
M.E. is streaming ASMR live.
If you'd like to check that out,
M.E.Bizu, she's linked below in my description.
Thank you so much.
No more.
So please don't be afraid to check out her ASMRs.
We are about to finish up the sequence.
We just need to eliminate these three guards that come up
and then deal with the poison sequence.
And then I believe
that the sequence is over.
We are getting very close to finishing the campaign.
Very, very close.
Just run all the way around the Colosseum at this section
until you get up to the hay bale.
There is a treasure chest.
I always ignore it.
We can always come back for it later.
There you go.
You can instantly assassinate the hay bale.
Oh, it's four targets.
Excuse me, such a fakey gamer.
Again, crossbow bolts are completely silent.
They will not allure anyone
to what has happened in the area,
which is very nice.
Unfortunately, I'm running rather low on crossbow bolts.
We are going to wait for this last guy
to come out on his own
because if you actually go in there,
there is a high chance of him
just straight up turning around and looking at you.
And then you have to replay this little section again.
Don't recommend it up to you,
but he will notice the body
and then you get the perfect kill.
I'm going to look at his body
just because again, we are a bit low on crossbow bolts.
But that's okay.
And then you just need to jump down
on this little...
How do you call it?
Hanging.
Okay.
Or just don't touch any of it
and land on your ankles.
Perfectly fine.
Don't need them.
Just completely ignore everything.
My goodness.
You saw me reach my armor.
Just fall to the floor.
Literally splat.
You may notice that our health bar is increasing
even though I'm not buying any new armor or anything.
That's because after every act,
you unlock a new health bar.
So it's not necessary to use your florins on armor,
but if you definitely are new to the Assassin's Creed,
it helps out so much.
It's fantastic.
And please utilize the tailor's shops
because tailor's shops have pouches
that increase how much medicine you can hold,
how much throwing knives,
how many crossbow bolts, for example.
I cannot recommend this game enough.
Seriously, it's about eight hours total for campaign.
If you just ignore everything,
if you want to have a good time and explore,
you could easily pump maybe 16 hours.
It's good. Good game.
Heavily good game.
My knees could never do that.
No, I don't think anyone's knees
could accomplish such a feat.
Although, I could have sworn I saw some videos
of, like, you know, in Portal 2,
like the apparatus that's on the legs
to stop any fall damage from occurring.
I'm sure someone was, like, developing that tech
at one point, like, maybe for Super Soldier,
really stuff, but, yeah.
Are you on Steam?
Yeah, I'm playing Steam right now.
I was gonna try and do...
do an Xbox Game Pass,
but it's not currently on it right now,
so we don't get the gamer score.
Poison Stinky.
Can anyone look up if Cuttlefish have poison?
I don't know my lore.
Maybe my poison can...
Oh, well, I do ink, but is ink poisonous?
No, it's a deterrent,
because I can be preyed upon.
So ink is the Hayden.
I can bay.
Yeah, I can.
You know, I see my teeth, and...
I wish I had aim like that, that's cool.
Actually, that's a really, uh...
I would...
No.
Maybe.
Do you think we could set up axe throwing
at a VTuber convention?
I feel like that would be so fun.
A lot of people, like, can hit the spot or not.
I feel like it's so specific.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, Jesus!
Pick them up, pick them up!
Quite literally, Jesus.
Oh, his health is going down because of the poison.
I've never noticed that before.
Other way.
Okay.
Sorry, assassin recruits.
I'm gonna need you to, like, hurry up
and perish these people.
Like, right now, Pietro, is...
Oh!
That's a reefling after I'm done with him
in the ASMR booth.
Ah...
Mmm.
If you team up with a company that does axe throwing...
Me next, me next!
This is me giving you cola
to make you feel better.
Give me the keys.
The castello.
Oh!
Did I tell you that
after Dave...
Oh!
It's the real traitor!
It's not Marcia Valley at all!
It's you!
Random thief from cutscene.
Oh, no!
No!
No, no!
No, no, no!
Horse!
Please!
Oh, I'm getting chased by a horse right now.
I don't know, I think if I fail this section...
If you jump, you can jump past the guards
and the AI no longer targets you, I don't know why.
But there's a horse after me
and I'm scared!
I can hear the horse go in me!
Please!
Please leave me alone.
Leave me alone! Leave me alone!
Okay, I think I'm safe from the horse, silly.
Come here! Come hither! Come hither!
Ugh, move on.
Oh, that was...
That's awful.
I was right. I have to stop Levopi before he gets to Machiavelli.
Ah, Levopi's about to kill Machiavelli! Where'd I go?
Okay, the green on the map.
Do I need a horse? I can't remember the section very well.
Ba-bang. Ba-bang.
I think I can run.
If we do not stop Levopi, he literally kills Machiavelli.
Now, to 100% this, you're not to swim.
No! Don't pick...
Oh, for fuck's sake, take the horse then! Jesus!
God... Goodness, Gravy.
Oh my god, I'm taking the long way around!
Ahhhh!
Panic! Panic! Panic! Panic! Panic!
What are you doing in Seal?
Why would you randomly grab that Permanent's horse?
Climb the wall!
It hit Seal! Please, that's a tamed mission.
They stressed me out so much!
Please, I just want 100% this, so I never have to do it again.
Please, please, please!
Oh, why would you randomly take that Permanent's horse?
I get too stressed out on tamed missions. I hate them.
Here, take this letter.
Luton.
My god, this is good news.
More than you know.
I am once again in your death, Ezio.
What death is there amongst friends?
Trust one another.
Yes.
Thank you for relaying the message tonight.
I'm literally yoinked that Permanent's horse.
Calm, Nicolò.
Okay.
Love all pain and mark your will.
I heard Nicolò's impassioned play took an unexpected turn this week.
Now trust each other.
Yippee!
It seems Jezu Cristo was resurrected three days early.
Ta-da!
Checkpoint reached. That's not the end?
Oh, it is the end of the act.
We're just being teased.
Crazy Man's Steel's horse jumps off and runs up wall fight.
Literally, if you hit, like, a graphic thing like this at an angle,
Ezio refuses to climb the wall
and it gives me a heart attack every time.
Like, Ezio, please.
Look, our thieves are in the...
Our recruits are in the background.
Look, it's you in the background!
It's you in the car scene!
Well, they're not right now. I can't see them, but...
It is pain.
Claudia's gonna become an assassin.
We work in the dark to serve the light.
Yeah, absolutely cannot say any of those words.
Do not ask me to recite that.
I can say that part.
We're in our training. Oh, my God, look who you are! Reflinges!
There's so many of you.
Look, Reflinges is my sister.
I'm reciting it right now.
Oh, my God, they're gonna hold hands.
Yay!
She's an assassin.
If you get an assassin, you have to be branded on your
wedding ringer...
wedding finger.
Where the ring goes.
Is your sister single?
Hi, Claudia.
You and I have not seen eye-to-eye on many issues.
Just letting out.
But you are exactly what the order means.
We cannot promote it.
You have led the charge against the Templars
and rebuilt this brotherhood.
Now, we must put Ezio when he be locked up.
Refling!
Oh, my God, is Reflinges crowning me as their Ushides?
Ezio, Auditore, Daffy Vence.
You will now be known as Il Mentore,
the guardian of our order and our cities.
No, I can't be Kama Ushii.
I don't mean Ushii, but Kama Ushii is impossible to live up to.
That's not possible.
Remember, nothing is true.
It's true.
Everything is permanent.
Where other men are limited by morality and law.
Remember, everything is permitted.
It's Ezio before or after.
He is after.
Altair is like...
I don't even know what century Altair is.
Why this sudden change of heart?
I'm a cameo assassin.
I was the one who brought you to Roma
and the one who caused the explosion as you fled the Castello.
What?
The mercenaries who protected you at Il Colosseo were mine as well.
You just did not know it.
Maestro Mattiaveli, Cesare has returned to Roma alone.
He rides for the Castel Sant'Angelo.
Thank you.
Well...
The decision is yours, not mine.
Niccolo, you better not stop telling me what you think.
Why else would I seek the opinion of my most trusted advisor?
Go kill them, Mentore.
Finish what you start.
Good advice.
I can write a book about you one day.
If you do, it will be short.
You've been my OSHA since day one, just accept it.
I don't get it, like how?
How?
You tell me you've consumed all of these content creators
and you're like...
Yeah.
That one.
Out of them all.
Okay.
We have finished Sequence Seven.
There are two more sequences and then we've done the campaign.
It's actually finishing a lot earlier than I thought.
I've still got a couple of more hours in me, okay?
When it clicks, it clicks.
You don't pick the OSHA.
The OSHA does pick you.
When you know, you know.
Wait, the game is really that short.
If you ignore everything and do campaign only,
like, send it on the campaign, then...
On it, right?
Pretty.
You can wrap up.
Real quick.
I am going to destroy another tower
because I want to unlock this third signal
and then we will...
Actually, you know what?
I'm going to send my assassins on a mission.
I'm going to pee and make a cup of tea and get some food.
And we can just take a little five minutes to ourselves.
A little tea break.
I'll send some of the wee...
Oh, that's like everyone for that one mission.
No ideal, but it's fine.
Can you 100% not?
You can, so that will be a level up.
Okay.
Right, everyone.
I don't want to be too close to the pigeons
because they literally go...
in your ear, so hopefully that's not too bad
for ambience.
Everyone, please do consider standing up
and getting your wee legs and blood flow going
or wiggle your toes.
If you're that lazy, stretch your feet
and pull them back and forth
so your muscles and your calves
like come back and forth.
Go for a pee, get some water, some snacks,
some juicy juice, hypotenuse,
and I will be back in roughly three minutes.
I'm gonna try and heat up ravioli like fast as anything.
So I will be a moment.
If you would like to watch Emmy while she does ASMR live,
her link is in my description.
You can do that right now, okay?
I will do the old pretending to sleep
and then I'll open up the game again, okay?
So don't worry.
Don't worry about it.
Eesh.
It caused my eyes.
Oh.
I had no idea I left eights.
He was sitting like that.
That was crazy.
I was like, oh, we already had a recruits come back as well.
Okay.
I've got me, I've got all my food.
I have a bowl and it has race pea snacks.
It has two stick meat and one, eight and two egg.
I'm just gonna send this assassin away
to get like even more stronger.
Because we're cained again to that heart.
Jesus.
Is there any level three?
This is my goodness.
That took a while to find.
Oh, she went, oh, how long are they?
Yeah.
I'm like absolutely feasting.
I've got fruit juice with me.
I've got a bottle of water.
I've got a cup of tea with honey in it.
Like, oh, oh, not again.
I say, oh, would you stop doing that?
You're embarrassing me.
We're driving this controller.
So I'm gonna like munch and play,
but I didn't bring any napkins.
So I might have to suck the egg out of the bowl,
which sounds bizarre, but can you say the second drink again?
The fruit juice?
It's like, it's got mango in it.
It's like super healthy juice.
And a cup of tea.
Wait, you can't, what?
What, a bottle of water?
Oh, a bottle of water.
I didn't say it like the British say it, well,
I consider the British, the English,
and the memes like kind of about the English say
the bottle of water.
I'm like, oh, I don't know what I'm saying.
I don't know if I need to slurp this egg
because I really can't be bothered getting,
where am I supposed to be going?
How far away is this location?
Oh, it's the castle, right?
I'm gonna try, I'm gonna get rid of this.
Oh, it says he's a coward though.
It's really annoying trying to get cowards
because they actually run away.
Actually, give me one second.
My room is on fire because of this PC.
Literally getting baked.
Oh, I've been robbed!
I've looked away for five seconds and I've been robbed!
Oh, right, I didn't need the money that much.
It's fine, it's fine, great.
Let me put my headset on.
That actually can't hear the gear right now.
Did he just run up to me and like rob me?
Not seeing my room's hope,
but too hope it's just came in through a ring
and honestly, I'm sweltering.
I don't know if that's the Scottish word, sweltering.
Do you see that?
I'm sweltering.
Sweating my beets off.
Although I feel like sweating my beets off
probably comes from like, is it Mardi Gras?
Like that party that Americans have
where you unveil yourself and you get beets as a reward.
Like I think that's where that saying might've came from
because that just makes sense.
Like, oh, I'm sweating my beets off
because I'm like showing the goods so much and so often.
Right, where on earth has this got this captain?
I really don't want to mess it up
because if you mess it up and he runs away in time,
you have to wait until the following day.
Oh, I think I know who this one is.
I think he, oh, oh, oh, hold on, hold on, hold on.
No, see, oh, you know the guy that can see you right now?
I could actually, wait, I can't lock onto him,
but he can lock onto me.
See you stinky AI, perish.
Oh, beets of sweat that come off your head.
Ooh, you know what?
Yeah, I know that you said that, that makes more sense.
Yeah, probably not Mardi Gras really is.
Okay, I'll pay it, I'm safe.
Where's, yes, I knew it was this one.
Do we assassinate him from above, is my question?
I don't know.
I normally have three signals at this point,
which means I can do a raining down effect.
Did he really say where did I go?
Gryff.
Right, if I can air assassinate him,
this isn't a problem.
If I can lock onto him, I am very tall
up to lock onto him though.
No, wait, no, wait, lock onto him.
Yeah, uh-huh.
No, yes, yes, yes, oh, that was so good.
Oh, and none of the guards want to defend, that's hilarious.
All the guards are like, that man just came out of the sky.
We are not, we are retreating right now.
Does your room have poor ventilation?
That's horrendous ventilation.
Unfortunately, I'm renting,
so I have like absolutely no input
or like anything I could really do about it.
Rip in pepperoni.
He craves the drop, true.
Okay, I shouldn't get too distracted
because my tea's gonna get too cold
and my fruit juice is gonna get too warm.
I am going to ignite the,
gotta light this place up and then we're gone, oh.
You're edging me and not the good kind.
Are the windows open?
No, the window's freaking broken.
Um, like the landlord is being really nice to me
and he's like left me alone.
It's not like one of them annoying landlords
that are like trying to like trail through your place
all the time, but obviously whenever you visit somewhere
to rent and you like inspect it,
you don't actually know what's wrong with the place
until you move in and like they're obviously,
I discovered like windows are broken,
the hot and like cold, I don't know what the word is,
is not like ideal.
Are you guys okay if I hide in this hay bale?
We'll start drink my, oh, I forgot to shake my fruit juice.
Whoops, that's like real one of having fruit juice.
Um, I might just drink it real quick.
I apologize.
Oh, that shit's so good.
Yum, yum, yum, yum, yum.
It's apple, banana, lychee, mango, just smoothie.
So I'm getting all my fruit in one drink
because I don't really eat fruit that often.
I like waste fruit, so I feel bad.
Oh my God, it's mimosa, mimosa spotted.
Uh-huh.
Guys, you'll never guess who I arranged
an ASMR collab with this morning.
They've just showed up in chat.
It's very likely.
That'll be my first official collab with a VTuber.
Got Dimp on the list.
I'm hunting down everyone with radios.
I'm serious about that goal.
I'm arranging them all, we'll make it nice and easy.
Gonna be doing my best, so hopefully you guys eat good
and you can sleep to my soothing Scottish accent.
That's right, wee laddie.
Time to go to sleep.
Are you tingling?
Tingle, tingle, tingle.
Oh my God, she must be so cool to be able to collab with you.
Ha ha ha ha.
I should actually do like four Scots accent
on an ASMR, that would be hilarious.
I've almost finished my Juicy Just hypotenuse.
What should I eat first?
Should I eat an egg?
I think so.
I don't really like the idea of eggs sitting out too long.
Oh, what the fuck?
To say something was delicious in Scots,
you say it was braw, and that was braw.
That drink was delicious.
You keep mocking your accent.
Oh, I don't think people find the Scottish accent hot.
I would say like hot accents,
like unironically like French Italian
or normally like rated quite highly.
I have taken a bite of a meat stick.
I apologize for anyone who doesn't like eating.
I need to eat.
I want you to read Go The Eft Sleep and Your Accent.
That'd be good.
Is Valley Girl strongy real?
Hi, guys.
I'm so totally excited to be here.
Yeah, I'm Valley Girl, I laugh at everything.
Yeah, that's the best you can.
Yeah, you like that?
Is that what you want?
I'm scared.
I want to perish.
Valley Girl's strongy, say in it, brav.
Can you do a Scottish Valley Girl?
No, I don't think so.
I didn't think so.
No, my brain is like unable to compute what I need to do
in order to keep the accent, but make it different.
Brain kind of it.
You're not hypnotizing us Scottish accents at all.
I'm eating the meat.
I am now baiting the egg.
I'm just going to touch it.
I just said fucking delicious.
I have erned, oh my God.
A bite of the egg and the meat at the same time.
I have earned this, okay?
I have earned this.
Ah.
Is I almost choking on it?
Hey, ho, there's a first time for everything.
It's like a pepper ramy if you're a British.
I don't know what the equivalent is in America
or it's a twizy stick in Australia.
Xio is literally, he's like, I need to rest.
I'll be not at this for hours.
He's sleeping in the hay.
Oh, my mouth opens when my mouth.
Ah, that's cool.
Like my mouth is closed right now,
but because my mouth opens, well, yeah.
Ba, ba, ba, ba.
Sorry, sorry.
A slim gym, probably.
Would you like some sweet chili pea snack
that's been baked?
Ow.
Okay, open up.
I hope you guys stretched.
Because if you haven't stretched,
that's you sat for six hours and you're supposed to stretch.
If anyone's in a wheelchair,
you're exempt from these instructions.
I stretched all my limbs, this is good.
You're not going to fall for that one stare.
Well, you're going to split, aren't you?
Ah, stare.
Oh, my God, I don't know if I can read that out.
When is booty inspection day?
A faint sound of munching emanates from the car.
Hum, hum, hum, hum.
I've got sweet chili pea snacks that are baked.
Two meat sticks and two eggs,
and I've got one meat and egg left,
and I'm just munching on the peas.
Oh, my God.
So for years, I had no idea what Charlie Horse meant.
It's just called a pulled muscle.
And I was like, what on earth is a Charlie Horse?
Like, is this a famous horse named Charlie?
Why is it happening to people?
That's not possible.
I was like, it's crazy.
And then I finally figured it out
because I watched a meme and the guy fell over
and he was like, ah, ah, Charlie Horse.
And because of his body language,
my brain was like, oh, my God,
he's having a muscle spasm.
That's what it means.
Like, oh, I need a burp.
I'm so sorry, I'm eating, so it means a burp a lot.
I'm jammy, if you don't like it.
I don't think a zero or a mercy burp.
I think they have manners
and weren't raised in a barn like me.
Mm-mm, mm-mm.
I was named after Sir Charles of Horse.
Ooh, money.
We've got 3,000 in the bank right now.
Some say that Charlie's still in pain to this day.
Was that a meme on Family Guy?
I don't know what it was.
No, those ones are the difference.
I learned from Mercy the other day
that saying be there, be square
is because you won't be around.
Wait, what?
Be there or be square is because you won't be around.
Oh, that's so smart.
Like, around in a circle, yeah?
And like, you won't be around in the area
if you're not there, because you're a square.
Yeah, oh, I just got that too.
That's good, I like that.
Mercy smart.
Shawnee, it's not manners, it's your cuttlebone.
You're just in to boil and say,
yes, this is my first time on land.
Sometimes.
Mm-hmm, mm-hmm.
Careful, you don't want to make me too smart.
I'll start coming up when you names Fond de la Buse...
I'm never gonna live down Fond de la Buse
when we sucky.
What marshmallow did you want to see Anthony spit at that?
Oh, I didn't open up the marshmallows.
Well, we do it at the end of stream,
because we're actually really close
to finishing the game, like, really close.
Mm-hmm.
Alright, you better be scared of me cooking again.
Yum-yum-yum-yum.
Mm-hmm.
Uh, I'm sorry, but I'm gonna suck my fingers.
I know some people don't like it,
matter-wise, but I don't have an napkin.
Eh.
That reminds me, I need to make the audio.
Mm-hmm.
Okay.
I inhaled the meat and the egg,
and then I finished my tea,
and then we're gonna get straight back
and finish this stuff.
Ah.
Mm-hmm.
Yum-yum-yum.
This is a really good combo.
I need to, like, more charcuterie snack stuff
for longer streams,
because I don't have time to actually make food.
Mm-hmm.
Maybe in a cold pasta dish,
I can pre-make.
The crunchy thing is the meat stick.
It's got, like, a skin on it, eh.
I don't know, mm-hmm.
That's the meat.
Mm-hmm.
I've got protein from the egg,
and protein from the meat and fats,
and the pea snacks are carbohydrates.
Ah.
Yum-yum-yum.
I'm gonna get tons of hydration.
That's way too crunchy to be, it is meat!
It is meat, I promise you, it's meat.
It's, like, an outer skin, like a pepper ramy.
Mm-hmm, mm-hmm, mm-hmm, mm-hmm, mm-hmm.
Okay, all the food is finished.
Yippee!
I'm now for the tea.
Ah.
Um.
Honestly,
depending on how fast we go,
we might actually finish the campaign in less than two hours,
but I'm quite happy to, like, fart about
and do the Borgia Towers after, maybe, like,
so we can, like, streamline tomorrow
for doing the DNA sequence run.
Mm.
Ah.
I'm gonna let a big burp, I'm sorry.
Oh, that was good.
That was such good food.
I really needed that, and I hit the spot.
A battered Mars four-hand count stream.
It's a honey tea.
I'm sorry.
It all comes back up, I've got you.
I was gonna record Isomar, like, your girlfriend
for, like, forgets to turn off the mic,
so it was just me munching and crunching,
because some people, like, really enjoy,
like, other people's, like, munching sounds.
I'm, like, if you are telling me
that I can order McDonald's
and eat it on the mic,
and people would, like, be happy with that,
like, uh, you don't gotta tell me twice.
Oh.
Shawnee, if you're looking for a snack
that's easy to prepare, grapes.
I can't believe it.
I can't believe you're telling me to eat healthy
and look after myself.
Oh.
Cruel world.
Honey tea, you boil those per beat?
No!
I love the bees.
I get to, um, buy my honey from, like,
a, like, smaller shop,
and I like supporting them on their own, like.
Right, I sip my tea.
Oh, yeah, I can't, that was roasting.
It's still quite warm, not gonna lie.
I thought it was gonna cool.
Be a bit cooler.
Uh.
I'm okay, I'm okay, though.
Right, we're gonna go and get our wand taken off of us.
Right, we'll put that on the Herald.
Thank you very much.
Yuck.
You're about to stand in some serious meta.
Chicken nuggets ASMR.
Ooh.
Is 100, does eating 100 chicken nuggets still a challenge?
I feel like you starve me
and I could probably do that, like, in one go.
Have I bought this bank over here?
I haven't!
Investments, people, investments.
That reminds me several years ago,
back when Tumblr was an important platform
that some vegans actually thought bees
were physical harm for their honey.
Oh.
I mean.
Um, vegans just doing their thing, it's fine.
They're nice, I guess.
I just, yeah.
Vegans are vegans.
I completely understand, like, the stance,
like, no one actually wants any animals
to be hurt or all that jazz.
I just, you know, I ask,
have you ever seen a healthy-looking vegan
when they're like, I've been vegan for five years?
They look ill.
I had a close family member
that was temporarily vegan for a couple of years.
And when they finally started to eat, meet again,
they were, like, healthy overnight.
I'm so sorry.
I apologize if anyone is a vegan here,
but please seriously take your supplements,
look at what you need to,
in order to get what you need,
because please, please be careful.
It's very dangerous.
I don't, I'm actually being serious for, like,
for one millisecond.
It is incredibly dangerous
to genuinely choose to be a vegan.
And a lot of people don't realize, until it's too late,
that, like, you are,
like, if you really want to get into it,
like, there's the caveman times
before we discovered what cooking,
what cooked meat could do for us.
And, like, it's like, you know,
once humans had access to cooked meat,
the brain power of humans, like, went up.
I can't remember what all the details
and what it's called and all that,
but, like, this is what I've been taught,
and, like, I genuinely believe it.
I'm sorry, but if you've ever looked at vegan,
they just look like a husk of a human.
And I'm so sorry if it's offensively.
It's just my opinion, but I never said I was smart.
And my opinions don't reflect the agency.
I'm sorry, love you, bye.
I'll stop talking.
Okay, this, uh, Borgia district,
you have to scale it from the rooftops.
It is impossible.
You have to do it via AroStorm.
If you do not do it via AroStorm,
you're just, like, hurting yourself.
Like, it is so bad.
And you can get a flag on the way, so.
So, literally, drop down AroStorm instantly.
And just let that done.
Easiest.
Literally, you don't even annoy any other guards
that are in the vicinity.
There is no one on the rooftops.
As long as you have AroStorm unlocked,
which is what the, um,
which is what the three recruits,
so you need six previous Borgia towers destroyed
in order to get that, but once you've got it,
then you're smooth sailing through the game.
If only Leafs had protein.
Yes, I know deeper green-colored veg tablels
are, like, really, really good in general.
What way am I to go?
That looks too big for me to...
Yeah, I don't have a glove yet.
Okay, this looks like the way I need to go.
Mm, mm, mm, mm, mm.
Did anyone get their, what was it?
What's that organ that blows up
that was used for grass eating?
Like, it literally kills you.
I'll always forget the name of it.
An appendix?
Did anyone get their appendixes removed?
Ooh.
Did you get wrecked with your appendix?
Okay, tea time.
Rice and beans.
Can cover you for the most.
Yeah.
Yours burst?
Oh, you must have been deathly ill.
If it bursts, it can result in death,
because it's just straight poison to your organs.
Holy crap.
Someone said my tonsils grew y-
They stole your tonsils?
Oh, give them back.
I thought appendixes were forbill-
I thought append-
I got some appendixes was for when we used to eat,
like, grass, grass, like, back in the old day.
I'm taking a sip of tea.
I'm gonna try and finish up my apology.
Ah, your gallbladder?
I'm scared.
My mom had a gallbladder issue.
And so did my gran.
Genetically, I am predispositioned.
Like, one day on stream,
I'm just gonna start like screaming and being like,
gallbladder, gallbladder!
But, uh, hopefully that doesn't actually happen.
But I can't say I'm the healthiest being around.
You can die of death.
Did I say that?
I don't wish that pain.
Wait, you know how you guys are guys?
Have you guys ever passed the kidney stone?
For anyone who drinks an energy drink,
have you passed the kidney stone?
Yes or no?
I'm very interested in that.
I wanna know.
Never, maybe?
Did you ever really sort of pee-pee at one time?
We are not 100% what it is used for.
These range from filtration,
to breaking down fiber, to appendix, to a mystery organ.
That's so cool!
Like, how do we not know?
We've got so much history.
No.
I hope I don't.
Yeah, it sucks.
Ooh!
I've heard stories from Whammon.
I've heard stories from Whammon
that are like, I've had a kidney stone
and I've had a baby.
I'd rather, you know, do the baby again.
And I'm like, hey, see?
That's biology in play.
Did you know the brain actually tells Whammon
that they're birth of their...
Wait, where the heck am I going?
Can I climb up here without the glove?
I don't think I can climb up here without the glove.
Climb?
No?
Okay, I can, I can.
Jesus.
I was like, oh, I've just missed out.
I love stronticolors and I heard,
heart kidney stone perils!
Oh my God!
I do have peril.
I have a peril in a very special location.
Are you there, Mercy?
Are you streaming later?
Are you streaming in one hour, two hour?
Three hour, Mercy stream, question mark.
I'm finishing my team, please pardon me.
I need a burp, it's like stuck in my throat.
I have finished my team.
Requiem.
Requiem, cadavante.
Okay, whee!
It's Azura.
Is Azura?
Is Mama Azu streaming in the day?
Wait, where the heck am I today?
Sounds like I need to go up here.
Oh, that's because I do need to go up here.
Only energy drink I've had is Calcius.
Calesus?
What?
C-E-L.
Celsius.
Oh.
I got there in the end.
You just gotta let me cook on some words, okay?
Some words are like, huh?
Huh?
And then you just gotta have full,
netically spell them out.
Everyone is streaming right now.
Oh my god, overlapping corp, I can't believe it.
I literally tell everyone like, go watch everyone else stream
because I'm literally just sitting doing like an
endurance eight hour stream type thing.
I'm just having a blast.
Yeah.
But don't worry when you go live in Mercy,
I always recommend to the girls, please, to go.
No, I always recommend to the brief links
to give you a chance and check you out.
See, we work because odds are I'm still going to be streaming
by the time you...
Oh, I wasn't supposed to be discovered.
Oh well, so we over...
It's fine.
We're doing it to...
Look at that.
Combat cam.
Ooh.
Is that Azura live right now with that link?
Or is that Imi?
Or is that just everyone's link altogether?
Silence discord mode.
Oh, you're not discord mode at all.
YouTube mode.
I'm just kidding.
Thank you for moderating for free.
I really appreciate it.
Actually, all the girls really do appreciate it because
it's kind of like one of those like jobs,
you know, like the silent, unrecognized work,
but I actually genuinely like thank you to everyone
who like applied to be a mod,
and like thank you for everyone just being like
cool at the mods and all that shiz.
Really appreciate that.
But then again, silence, YouTube mode.
With all that said, and all due respect.
Oh, I'm just getting spotted by everyone.
Reisa, we're just in a big fight.
Oh no, they have guns.
Calling their assassins.
Okay, I'm not dealing with them all.
You can kill them all.
I'm not dealing with them.
Whoa, they literally...
Is he gonna see me entering the castle?
I think I may.
I simply have all...
You tell the girls to watch the girls.
No, I said it wrong.
I said it wrong.
They do it for free.
I mean, literally.
Azura and Emmy are...
Azura is online as well.
Oh, if there are any Azura Dulay,
she is officially online as well.
If you're an Azura Dulay, watch her.
I ordered a fresh batch of la Catorre la last night.
Oh, so no one has tasted my Catorre.
But the Pope has taken it all.
Where is the Pope?
He meets with Cesare.
Strange.
He did not tell me.
Cesare had returned.
Imagine being a Mortarader.
Imagine...
Okay.
Now what?
Sorry, I'm starting to lose that little bit.
I was like, imagine being a Mortarader.
Okay, now what happens?
Danny, did anything else?
I'm imagining.
With my mind only, I'm imagining.
Okay, I'm getting a bit delirious.
I think it's like...
Bro, I know I said this yesterday.
We were so delirious during that group collab.
But I'm so excited for our official group game collab together.
I hope you guys like the intro.
I'm going to script it when we start up the streams.
And literally, everyone's going to be streaming it.
So you can see all six POVs at once.
Oh, I'm burping away.
You've been at this for six hours.
Honestly.
You, come here so I can assassinate you.
That's right.
Come closer.
I can sense thine penis.
Okay, sorry.
I shouldn't have said that.
I like that.
I think I'm actually doing the same thing a little bit.
But hey, hope.
It's not just life.
Let's go.
Oh, I don't know why I said that.
I'm remembering just like, hee hee.
Oh, I'm notorious.
I didn't lure my notoriety.
Oh, it sucks.
I almost got caught.
Well, actually, it doesn't really matter if I get caught by him.
He doesn't come.
How do you not see me?
I'm literally on a bookcase.
I'm doing the ballard.
Okay.
God, he's so armored out the world.
I have something on my mind.
Look, all I'm saying is that the marshmallows have been having a good time on marshmallows.
Oh, whips.
I wasn't supposed to jump down.
Hail.
Whoopsie.
Oh, I'm getting in trouble.
I don't remember all these enemies being here.
I'm going to have to remember when I'm doing the, like, do not be detected.
Like, you put that away.
Literally diddle-dee-dee.
And I shall first get wrecked.
This town ain't big enough for the both of us.
Cowboy.
Oh, that's 6,000.
We're getting so near the end of the game.
What has happened here?
I do not know what you mean.
I want to take.
I take.
If I want you to die.
You.
Even those with an army.
You intend to give me money?
No, I do not.
Then I will use the piece of Eden to get what I want.
Your help is not necessary.
That has been made abundantly to me.
That says dad.
Are you aware that the Baron de Valois is dead?
No.
Did you?
What reason could I possibly have to kill him?
Was he plotting against me with my brilliant, treacherous captain general?
I do not have to stand for this.
The assassins murdered him.
Why did you not stop them?
As if I could.
It was not my decision to attack Monteriggione.
It was yours.
Shh.
It is high time you took responsibilities for your actions.
My accomplishments.
Despite the constant interference of failures like you.
You are not going anywhere.
I have the piece.
Out of my way, old man.
Get out of my way, old man.
I gave you everything and yet it's never enough.
Cesare, he intends to poison you.
You have not listened to reason.
Father, do you not see?
I can control all of this.
If I want to live, I live.
If I want to take, I take.
And if I want you to die, you die.
It's so good.
Where is the piece of Eden?
I know where it is.
And you did not tell me he had taken it.
Cesare, it's me, your queen.
You are my sister.
None more.
Where is it?
You never loved me?
Where is the apple?
Tell me.
The voice acting is so good.
It's just so good.
Thank you for letting me share this game with you.
Fun fact, you don't need to hurt anyone.
Oh, no, no, go over, Etsy.
Etsy.
Oh, you're giving me a heart attack.
Oh, Etsy.
Little sister.
I know.
Fucking hell, I was having a heart attack.
Do you see that?
They're related?
Yeah, it's based on history.
I could see.
No, where that bastard is going.
San Pietro.
The pavilion in the courtyard.
Hmm.
Exit through the front gate.
Wait, am I still going to get attacked by guards?
Oh, oh, wrong way.
Etsy.
You've just got such a big palace.
I'll come back for you later.
See you later.
I'll come for you later.
Like this.
Assassino.
I will come for you.
Wait.
Later.
I'll come for you later.
I just like doing that.
Reefling.
I'll come back for you later.
Later.
Yes, I will.
Who's a good Reefling?
Have you been a good boy?
Is it time for your daily milky-wilky?
Oopsies.
Wait, he was in my way.
Am I supposed to just ignore him?
I think I am.
I will remember that for when we redo the mission.
Spiral scare.
Right.
So that you can grab this box because the timer don't start until now.
You have to leg it for this entire next section.
Okay?
You have to do it for the entire next day.
Fucking let's go.
Well, you're stuck in the cutscene.
Give it a second.
Let it cook.
Let's go.
Don't worry.
Leave a faith.
Promise.
Ta-da.
See?
It's right there.
And then if you go in the street of the pavilion, it's the easiest way to navigate to the place.
Okay?
And then you need to do the jump thing.
Jump.
And then just take the main street all the way up to the pavilion.
And just jump every time you see an agility at the bottom of your screen.
You just jump.
And they can't get you.
Jump.
See?
The AI unclogs you.
Jump.
And then you'll be perfectly fine.
Now you might have to fight them at the end.
I honestly don't understand what the development team actually wanted from you at this point.
Please leave me alone.
But oh, he almost touched me.
He touched my ankle.
Oh, he's touching me.
He's touching me.
Okay.
And then they opened up.
And then we just go inside.
And then sometimes you may have to come outside and fight, but it's okay.
It's okay.
Okay.
So we were...
That's a lot of bad guys.
No.
Okay.
We got one.
Oh.
Oh, I'm getting ganged on.
I'm getting ganged up.
I don't like it.
Take this.
And this.
Okay.
Unfortunately we are in range because of that yellow on the map, but we might be able to
stand here.
It should time out because they're not supposed to actually see us.
There we go.
Now, did you guys remember the pineapple?
Did you remember the pineapple?
We did a little eagle vision.
The pineapple is glowing.
I was right there.
What?
I was there all along.
Excuse me?
Looking for this.
Don't kill us, Sino.
My sword will take your life.
Hydration.
Wow.
Those armor clinking sounds.
Good sound effect.
Guards.
Oh, Chasary.
Your time can't last.
Not while I come in with the apple.
Okay, so basically just run
Wait hold on let me let me open the map. Sorry to bring down the energy
I need to open the map because I always forget which direction I need to go in
So I need to keep going dead ahead and then take a right. Okay. Let's go
It is just a waste of time trying to stop and hurt like get rid of all these enemies
There's no point. So just outrun them until you get to the water and swim like your life depends on it
They keep they jump in me
Get off
Away naughty
No, if you follow this street, I think it takes you to the water. Oh
I don't like those brute guys. They're actually pretty strong. Oh
Oh
When the moon hits your high like a big piece of pie that's a morning
Bills will ring ring a ding a ding
Pizza
And that's how you get away from that sequence
Jump on that boat and get out of there. You do not have to attack anyone. You do not have to eliminate any enemies
Jump in that boat and you are safe
Oh
To assemble his remaining support coming weeks
When the moon hits your eye, that's a strongy
It's blinding odd my models not reactive to what happens on screen and he put that back on I love that
That was like the funniest thing
My eyes
We do have no a right a sight to see us down
Flashbang
I think for the loser guards and touch the pineapple without hurting anyone just pop a smoke bomb and getting a crowded bench
I wonder that may be the solution. They are everywhere and nowhere at once
I
We cannot on our own senior you must help us. I am
Idiot
And then you will see how quickly the assassini fall
Delude yourself Chesere
Oh
Right so the apple is a bit funny
Do you see that white one that white line means imminent death the yellow means under my control
and
So we want to basically the apple will take your health
so I have to wait until it restores and
Then wait and then it kills the people who we want to kill and then the others are either under my control
Or we'll fight for me. It's a bit finicky, but once you learn it you get it
We're teleporting all over the map. We're at the blooming
Rose
Yes
Under stress
Any anyone else under stress and we're feeling about a key need not a bit of a
I'm not gonna say it's too easy too easy
So the point of Assassin's Creed is to get rid of the apples of Eden, however
It's always a good good boy and
his
DNA communes with the apple so his bloodline
Kind of has been chosen
I'm pretty sure the guys around this corner actually and I've gone too far. Yeah, there is and
Feel the cardinal
He I think he just runs down this hill and then that's it
You do not have access to your recruits at this time, but you don't need it because you literally have the apple Eden
I will say one thing the more. Oh, no, actually it doesn't affect with the more armor you have
Also on the weapon wheel, you can't select anything when you hold the apple of Eden, but I won't even let you take it out
So we just need to follow him into the coliseum
Okay, no, no, I'm not here. Uh-uh. No, uh-uh. You didn't see me. No. Oh, you're actually a liar
And and I will you you guards just spawned in
Don't lie. You just spawned in rain in front of me
as a see
And a cup
You won't find me because I'm not what you need
I'm
Your end maker caretaker
My bikini ever has to be mentioned enough. It wasn't I've unbended everything so there's no chance of accident or bikini show
I apologize
Borja money has become tainted
Main control apple
I
Okay, again same thing
Unfortunately, this is very awkward and you can call in your recruits, but it's not very good at all. I'm try
Okay, this isn't working wait
He attacked me and he died. Did you see that right? I'm just calling in my recruits. They're not very strong, but
We'll try we'll try I don't normally like doing it because recruits can definitely die at this section
because of the overwhelming amount of enemies that
Letting enemies that come in but again white mark around who you would wish to
Eliminate right off the bat and hopefully my assassin recruits stay around
So he's coming straight for me. So once I've healed up again
You just need to do the white you can also see the white line on their
The horse knocked him out of range. So we'll need to try that one again
So they're now fighting each other
Again white line
Got him
Yeah, see my assassin recruits are getting damaged on their health
I really do not enjoy calling them in on this mission. It is dangerous
You can lose recruits here if they're not leveled up enough. I really did not spend much
Where's the apple?
Whoa, he's like slow mo getting me
Okay, we've got two more to go two more to go let him get up let him get up
But go for him first cuz you actually know we won't cuz my assassin recruit just did that. Oh
Someone's load not good. Not good. This is why I really don't like I really don't want anyone to perish
Oh
Did he survive I didn't get a notification saying that one passed away. I
Know you much of an ASMR enjoyer, but any change your mind. That's fantastic
I like you. You just got to find someone that fits your groove and they can interest you into something new
Johnny miss ma. How are you doing? Have you been good?
Mmm-hmm
We playing assassin's creed up in this house
We're literally about to finish the game after an amazing gaming session you can ignore the guards here the
Campaign should take over once you approach these
So very good another time me. Did you stream today or have you streamed yet?
Are you taking break today?
I mean ASMR was great. It does all
So now we get our cool Avengers moment where everyone's with us helping us and
You can actually
Successfully kill all everyone in this sequence
Oh, I can't use my mouse. I can't use my blades. I'm so used to using them
You're still playing absolutely. We're just about to finish the campaign. I'm so excited. Oh, no, that recruit so low
Oh, I feel like I need to help them. Oh, okay. Okay. Good catch. Good catch. Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
I'm dead. I only have one HP. Oh
I need it to reach in. No, I don't want any assassins to fall
Stop attacking her. Stop. I don't have health to freaking use the apple. Please gang up on him. Thank you. My goodness. Oh
No, oh
Please okay yellow. Oh
Someone's gonna pass away
Okay, so we just finished
Oh
No one perished
Oh, that was so lucky. So we've now finished the sequence and we're all waiting
All five of us avenger style
On your own
We can let us troops must behind me. We will take back my city
This is not your city anymore by order of Pope Julius second. I arrest you
They are crime on the crimes of murder betrayal and incest
No, no, no, no, no, this is not how it ends
James will not hold me. I will not die by the hands of man
Was the manner in which he said it
Didn't know that was a crime back then honestly
true
question marks because all we hear about bloodlines is
You know about Royals and that so was it like
Royals are allowed to do it, but the common people aren't allowed to do it. You know as peasants
I cannot risk it
I must go
Jezary was right. I have to leave when I'm usually my people need me build this brotherhood to last with or without me
Plant a seed
Plot plant a seed
Then keep your money
We will see each other again. You have my bonafortuna
Bonafortuna take the money your meager salary you will need it my patron has been arrested after all
true
Mm-hmm
You've got a lot for China. Oops
V sucky manager game of thrones
There is a limit cousins and relatives seemed okay direct bloodline off
Yeah, oh
Why is my tracking is my why is my tracking stopped hello?
Ah
Is my PC dead or is it just my tracking has gave up hey, you want to recalibrate real quick
I need to play but my thing is not working
Whoo, hello. No, it's not. I have my iPhone on fuck. Oh my iPhone is burning
Let me just pause that real quick. Oh, did you see all of them?
Okay, hold on that am I back up to sink, okay? Oh
Just yeah, it's like in so fast there
Oh
Then a cannonball should appear. Yeah, there you go cannonball
And it got me as well. I
My iPhone's on fire
Hidden blade only let's go. I'm a hidden blade some people enjoy the source some people enjoy the heavy weaponry
I
Double assassin blade for me. I died through I better know I'm died
For the phones about to explode honestly, I hope not, but it's very hot. I think because it's charged like I've charged it
This entire time
Like it's got charger
Oh
The iPhone better get used to it you better not be there raises stamina levels for me
Mmm the cinematic
Like when it does like the cinematic kill it looks so nice and like all the different weaponry
I have to admit so like obviously not matter someone prepare something else
Not the whole oh, wait, no, I lied
I lied I thought all the horsey's got no
I
Completely forgot I thought all the horses go back up. Why would they do that at the end of the game?
I assume I'm allowed to be spotted
Doesn't matter if I get spotted or is this one of them ones where I shouldn't be spotted
No, I can be spot, that's absolutely fine with me
But they're heavy mason heavy infantry
Doesn't matter if I get spot, so I'm just gonna send it I
Can't believe I forgot about that horsey war see I do apologize. I don't like when they do that
He's just taking a nap. He's just taking a nap. I mean I take one too, you know, he needs to sleep off
He needs to sleep off what happened
No, you've not seen me before unless you know
The batteries swelled up
We did I left my Android phone on charge for you and the battery so like
Like pop like a balloon type swell
It's his dangerous
Honestly, pray bruising
Ah
Leave me alone
Unfortunately for this section both factions will target you
So the best advice really is to go at the checkpoint and destroy whoever goes for you
And they will always sign but you can't progress until they leave you alone
So just I can't actually see what's going on, but thank you
Okay, there you go. You just need to wait for them to leave you alone
Any water my battery make sure it's not too cool and it too hot
Yes, it's so the smartest thing to do is to claim the burning
Siege tower you're you're so smart the wooden flammable siege tower
Not sure about that one it's
Like your accent. Thanks spawned in with it
Spacey phone pillow keeps your pillow nice and warm
Do we need to take the rooftops I actually
Well, that was a lot of enemies to appear on the screen
This section is the same where both factions will target you
You need to become an anonymous can I hide behind this and
Be left alone. Oh, is he gonna attack me?
Okay, okay, I
Was trying to see if I can get away with it. It's just a bit like why would they both randomly target me?
I have no
Like fight with them, but I don't even know who they're they're fighting each other and they're the same
They have the same uniform on they found the traitor
I know what wrong when I'm gonna guess
Leave me alone
Right, let's try again this time it's not on fire
My world's on fire, how about yours?
No, I
The water's getting thin the water's getting warm so you might as well swim. Mm-hmm. I don't know the words
I can never remember what I
Can never remember words in order of like actual songs and then the best I can do is go
Ah
The back streets a never gone what you wanna say banana banana, what you gonna do?
That's not a word
Hey, now you're an assassin get your game on cool play
His name's not Caesar Chasry's gonna die kicking in my balls
Hey
That's right, baby
So much to kill so much to do so much assassinate and on the spreadsheets a
Never know when I'm gonna strike a don't know if it's good advice a so much to pee so much to do
Gotta disarm the guard I can't do that so that's fine. I'm taking out the double knife
Trying to pistol whip try again with the tip. Oh
It's actually much easier just to shoot Chasry there if you should have you take a health bar
And removing his armor
He wishes he was a farmer. Oh, he got me first
Oh
You can't
No, run at a time. Oh, he broke my armor. Oh, that's not good. Oh, that's not good. Okay. I actually don't want that
I'm taking it my double bleeds
Take this
Take that in this and take my knee to your boss my knee to your boss
Didn't want to put my balls on your jaws
It's my knee. Oh shit. I'm actually kind of messing this up. I might need to try hard
Hold on. Hold on. Let me get rid of these guards first and then go for Chasry
But then whoa, wait, wait, wait, wait, you can't keep spawning new guards. I
Mean, maybe you can but like
You shouldn't you should give me a chance to kill. Oh, we're getting a bit crowded
We're getting a bit crowded in here. I did it too many of you. This is starting to get a bit here. He's gonna
Can I do this?
Okay, Chasry is that's fine. I expected that
Okay, Chasry's like one seriously. He's like one
Okay
One more reload faster. Okay. There we go
He
That's really how much Nick armor do you have?
Wanting something does not make it your right
That the true leader empowers the people he rules I will lead mankind into a new world
Can this sooner record you do
No man can murder me
Then I leave you in the hands of fate
The throne was mine
What do you know what do you know?
I
Lead mankind into a new world we take illiterally in these parts
You cannot kill me no man can murder me
The apple
The vault oh my god, we're playing borderlands too. It's the ball
So it's he was put the apple of Eden away and the vault left behind by the gods, so it's not in the hands of man
You'll call a sale
We've got it Colosseum we're about to go to present day
gravity claims another victim
fall damage buff
request
Perfect recall so we need some kind of futuristic key it seems to open with a verbally triggered mechanism
It's God kind of why I'm saying it out for back
That'll be quiet. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm getting too excited
Like that European power grid is Italy the only country in your you've got
Problem is he's dead
Okay, if you cut scenes up, it's all trying to be quiet. I'm just so excited. So I do apologize for talking over like
Just a bit of I said we belly
Hey, maybe it has something to do with this
Symbol matches the one on the door to the vault
1419 1420 1421
What if they aren't dates 1419 1420? Oh
My god, what?
God
Tell us already. I am I am that I am the tetragrammaton the 72 names of God
You see they're all contained within three verses
Exodus 19 through 21 and to get this your likeness if you arrange the four Hebrew letters in God's name within an equilateral
Triangle, then you miracle values add up to the same number
72 are you absolutely sure about this?
That's kind of why I'm saying it out loud Rebecca. Yeah, but
Construction on the Colosseum began in the year 72. I think we have our password
Sean go get the van
We
Now know the password to the vault in order to get the apple of Eden
I'm a calibrate again. Hold on. I
Calibrated now my mouth
You know everything
Really?
That's right, I've seen your car that tunnel should lead under capital line hill. I'll help them find another entrance
Be careful Desmond. I'll drive. Ah, yeah, nice try. I've seen your car. Oh
Base the sassans creed said women bad driver
That's terrible dev team you knew exactly what you're doing putting that in
There's a lot of dialogue up heads. I'll try and be quiet
Lucy I'm making my way toward the entrance
I'll keep that in mind
I can't believe I'm actually gonna hold the apple
Wonder if it'll change this whether it can tip the scales in our favor
Me trying not to read it like say every quote that I remember I
Was gonna say tip the scales. I don't know if the make pick that up by literally
What do you think we'll find hopefully a map
Yeah
Hey, maybe this time we'll be lucky
On my first playthrough I never found this for like ages it's so slight and cheeky
Cheeky like my little rhythm so much construction this place is like a maze
I
Know
So at the end of this there's a quote from the gods
And I said a message
No, we hold on
So that's why we're playing this game on my birthday
Because it's October 10th in the present day
It's the door code someone wants to make sure we get it right
Okay
If I don't move the cutscenes not gonna begin
But I just want to say there's a quote from the God at the end of this and she says go forth and
And and I may or may not have said be embraced by the six
Because of that quote and I hope you understand it when you hear it
So be embraced by the six it's cuz it's all in my love
And the other is the six
Just wait for okay, just wait for it. I tell you I tell you I show you I show you
But I hope the six have embraced you dearly
I'm braced us by the no set six number six numeral in those today's quadros
Cincuses, I know it's kind of hard just
We commit to this space the epilogue
Let it be found by he who is deemed worthy let it guide him
Let it shape his path forward
Let it save the world we leave behind
Who are you?
Jino
We're getting close boys to the end. I don't want it to end but
That's been fan half the cleanest campaign sorry went the wrong way dafty and I don't want me to go
I'm getting like really close to getting chills cuz like I know what's up ahead
In the beginning we set our truth to parchment to stone
to the memory of men
These proved impermanent thing. I'm sorry my mouth's open
Blood literally like a child like
Oh clings by fire clings by famine such such like huge dialogue
Just to show that history cannot last on parchment like it's just such
genius
I
Think I found an entrance
You think you found an entrance after the like the freaking floor the pavilion opens up. Okay. Yeah entrance, okay?
Wow
Hmm oh I'm getting chills
I
Let me in I'm coming
But on what can it last took you long enough
What is this? What happens if it didn't have to last?
See those columns. What if we just enjoyed every moment?
On top of the ancient Temple of Juno
I like the ceiling do you like the ceiling you are a fascinating traveling companion
Look how detailed this is there's something up there like
Like look how accurate it is please can we do history games?
Where we can all just nerd about history and like the things like they even bother to do the text and stuff like under the
Paintings to be like this is from
like
Such a good game
Just stay down here then shall we oh
Pray or something. It's appreciate everything. It's so good. It's so good
I'm so glad I get to share the game with you and hopefully you maybe play on your own sometime
You've experienced
That guy is sassy Sean is a very sassy character a
Very British deadpan
Wow ready to speak to the gods
Hey, actually, I'm a he him. Sorry
Destroyed what we could feel the way of
Something's open
Does not take many to unwind the world
Here is a safe place
eternal to store objects words
wisdom
But not life
Almost did we have the means?
But time erodes time. He wrote us
We distract him we can see past him
We left when he strikes right
But his reach is so very long
It's stamina unending
We cannot evade his grasp
not forever
Here goes so she's telling us why the gods perished
Because something constantly is getting them
Just like strutting stamina
Yeah, I reclaimed you like that my stamina's unending
It's a shame you have a refractory period
It must come in with the blood
I'm I'm Sean in this one
I'm holding on to the little knob in the middle
Well, we're doing it
If you want to kill us mate, you're gonna have to try a little harder than that
We're here
Music
Beautiful scenery the details
That is Sean's right that is I'm always right
About that dead end that never happened. I was misquoted music picks up and you can hear the voices
Just a theory all sounding voices
And all
This milk the door is it I'm not being pranked why this is a little in the door
I'm being pranked
It's really a secret behind that the kind of lucid there may be a secret, but maybe it's just a reuse that's it
Think it speaks English just say it okay 72
Oh
There's a field
I
The apple seems to be in the center
I'm to find out where those temples are
Okay, no, this is where the sad part comes in because I always mess up the sequence. I'm really
I
Always mess up the sequence the orb
Big lady
Knowledge
Only try
On a wisdom no knowledge story wisdom wisdom
Knowledge
Of course not fake gamer
Try to join you
Hear the words
I
Have played this game so many times. I always end up failing the levers. I didn't know you could eagle sense the lever. I
Have just literally my brain said maybe one's highlighted and the other isn't
How many times have I played this game and never done that before I?
Always mess up on the lever
I'll be quite
Activated
Did you hear any of that I
Sure do love all my friends equally. I love Rebecca
I love Sean and I love Lucy and I'm sure all will be fine
Wait, where'd I go? Oh
Oh
So where are the temples you want me to ask it or think it
I
Sure, you asked it the right thing I
Know this
That's a frigid cat
It stands for freedom and that that's a Masonic eye
Now those two come together in only one place
I can't move your DNA communes with the apple you have activated it
Let me go on the 72nd day before the moment of awakening
You
Loins and the loins of our enemies the end and the beginning
Abhor and honor
The final journey commences
There is one who would accompany you through the gate. She lies not with our sight
The cross darkens the horizon
Doing the path must be opened
You cannot escape your partners the sales shall be balanced
Stop please
You know very little we must guide you
Please
No
It is done the way lies all before you only she remains to be found
Awaken the six
You
Really don't like that
For those of you who haven't played Assassin's Creed 2 and don't mind spoilers
We were in upstairs goes headquarters and she broke us out
Because she was pretending to be a Templar. She's actually an assassin
and then we have just played Assassin's Creed Brotherhood, which is
sequel and
She got identified as a double crossing agent twice over
Which made no sense
Because why would she break us up and
If you want to know the real reason why Lucy is killed off in it's your story
Oh, yeah, sorry in Desmond storyline
The reason why Lucy's character was killed off is because she asked for
Like the revenue
Not for like a payout for her voice, but for the revenue split thing that they do
No, I can never remember the word
like where you get like payouts constantly like for your voice and
Royalties yes royalties. She she knew she was onto something
She was an Assassin's Creed 2 then she's in a second game Assassin's Creed Brotherhood and she said royalties and
That end sequence was then created
Because at no point do the gods speak of present-day issues and if you listen to the gods words
It was like you don't understand. We need to teach you the gods should not interact with Desmond on that level
lower-wise and
Because she wanted royalties killed her and plot and they said yeah, well, we don't need you anymore
So thanks, Ubisoft absolutely destroyed Lucy's storyline
And
Yeah, I hope your shareholders are happy because you ruin it for the people
But other than that other than that really annoying fact
Otherwise incredibly good game
Incredibly good game
I like to pretend that Lucy is still fully alive and acting as a an assassin and all of that. So yeah
Oh the VA for Rosa passed away, I didn't know that
Oh
But yes, that is the story of Assassin's Creed Brotherhood as
absolutely 10 out of 10 game experience if you ignore
the very
ending dialogue and occurrences
But that was amazing game and I absolutely loved nerdin about it. I'm probably gonna do the board to tell us
I don't think I'm ready to go off stream just yet
So sorry for anyone who's perishing right now and their eyes are bulging out of their skull because of how much they need to
Sleep right now. I'm very sorry. I'm really enjoying this game and
Yeah
Are you still doing the second stream? Yes. So today I was to finish the campaign mode and tomorrow
We're gonna 100% this game because I have never 100% at this game before always wanted to try never did it
I believe I may have a hundred percent of Assassin's Creed 2 achievement wise
Which was like a nightmare trying to get all the feathers, but we can talk about that when we play it on
June June on October 8
A lot keep going I've got a couple more hours in me. Oh, yeah, damn you got a stamina minute
Mmm
Yes, um
All the feathers took so long
Schedules set for October so my birthday is October 10th
Which is when I will do my doughnut on and for my birthday
I would like to play Assassin's Creed brotherhood all over again, but I'm gonna play it see was lying
So on the 8th of October Assassin's Creed 2
a campaign then Assassin's Creed 2 again for 100% and then brotherhood on the 10th and 11th and then on the
12th and the 6th the 12th and the 13th would be
Revelations and we will complete its use storyline
I'm not very well versed in
Revelations I have played it a couple of times, but I'm not as well there. So I probably can't Japanese
About the best strategies for the game
Are you doing the strong you pass out any presented? I don't know like I
Want I've been looking at some ASMR challenges like the eight hour ASMR stream challenge
Maybe I might consider that although my voice
Breaks pretty quickly for ASMR and whispering is the most damaging thing I can do
Oh
You should watch embers after revelations
I would make a reminder for those days I'll be posting my schedule like I've posted my schedule for this week
After the needy streamer overload, I think it's like a two-hour game question mark
I actually need to go and buy the American candy
And those European suits that I don't buy them and then I need to like clean my desk and stuff
For cuz I'm doing a hand-cam stream
Hmm
Stray if mummy go is our mum are you the granny?
Don't look into the lore too much of a real or came to be
Technically there are five children birthed from my loins
I
Whispering bad for your voice. Yes, I
May or may not need a really big pee now that I have just been aware of my bladder
I just sat on my foot
Like against well, you know
Against what and then my brain was like oh by the way sensation. I mean, ah, yes. Yes. I believe I need to pee
Oh
Mother Mary virgin birth, uh, no, sorry, it was the reeflings doing oopsies
That is some are both going wild. That's all I'm saying. Hmm. I don't know how we got it. We didn't get kicked out of that convention
So I am taking jinkies of water which closes tracking and puts my hypnosis on
But yes, we'll take a very quick pee break
And I may make a second cup of well be my third cup of tea, but my second that I'll drink on stream with you
I just need water and drink. I actually don't need any food that those snacks really satiated me
I have been satiated. I thank you for letting me eat on stream
No, no, no, no
Stream elements is how we pay child support. Yeah, I don't know what's going on
I unironically think you guys were given like so much money collectively to the girls
Once the tip page was up that you guys broke the PayPal
Yeah, so thanks for giving us so much money that
PayPal is now investigating the account or something. I don't know
Yeah, if you want to support the girls you can always buy the merch they get a hundred percent of the earnings
None of it goes to the other and all the girls will they say that they own the
Ubu market
Accounts and all that they have logins and it's all their stuff. We did not touch it not to do with us
but yeah
Hopefully monetization on YouTube stats
Statistics update because my statistics were like, yeah, you have 80 watch hours and I'm like, are you sure about that?
Are you sure YouTube? I don't think so
All the merch is so cute. I'm so excited for the key chains to arrive and I'll do tap-tap-tap-tap
Paisa
Dramatic unfortunately the credits go for a bit
and they're unskippable, but I do want to special shout out to
Alex Tremblay for the data manager
Shout out to Robert Mullen the technical writer fantastic job
Thank you fire team lead
Jocelyn Vilex Nolan as if I can say these names be real for real
This software contains adobe flash player software under license from adobe systems incorporated corporation adobe adobe adobe adobe adobe
Okay, we get it
Thank you
Francis page for your gear programming. Thank you Alexander
For your oasis team. Thank you Fabian Noel for your oasis concert
There's a oasis oasis. Is that team name? I must be team name oasis because I don't remember any oasis in Roma
Thanks adobe
Don't worry
You've reached the watch hours someday. I literally already reached them and YouTube's like yeah, give me like
seven to eight
business days to update your stats because I can apply from partnership
Monetization like right now
Well, I should be able to but the stats don't say I have the watch time, but I do have the watch time
so
But hopefully we can get our monetization streams and then you know all that I have no idea how long this PayPal issue is gonna last
You guys give literally unironically give so much money that they can't burst I
Have like 10 watch hours alone. I
Missed it'll be flash player
Binding of Isaac started on it, but I never actually played it at that stage only played it like a couple months back
The Baron
Hey like the enemies in this game as well, have you like made them multiplayer enemies or like
I like as well
The plot line that love all pay is so like I know it's you
Nicolo, I know it's you and like all these things coincidentally happen at the same time
I like stories like that because it's like no no you're wrong please
But thank goodness we did the no swim part that was awful grabbed a poor man's horse
Ran up a side of a building a few times and failed and then like dived across this like beam of rope
Would you consider playing binding of Isaac on stream? Oh boy? You're in for a treat in November the
official multiplayer for a binding of Isaac goes live and I would absolutely love to play with you guys
We will be streaming that game often. I am addicted to it
I've not before anyone asked have you done dead God? No, I've not done dead God
Hey, I currently am at like I think it's like
1001% and it's stop that's where I'm at on one fail
I have absolutely nothing on the two other save files, but I definitely is gonna be a
Consistently multiplayer streamed game from bits like I'll do like 12 hour runs for the multiplayer game of that week
And then like we'll pick up a different multiplayer game type thing and
Which would be fantastic
Whoo bending of Isaac is hardly it is a random eyes kind of dungeon
Crawler, but there's a lot of interesting story in the background of it
I
Really enjoy it. I actually want to make a review on this game Assassin's Creed brotherhood and as well as
Binding of Isaac and call to the lamb
Basically, I want to make like real game reviews
But only on games that I think we're 10 out of 10 because I can't stop yapping about them and like bring it up like how flawless the
In rewarding like the gameplay is and how they've like done the tutorials or what aspects have just really stood out
Like I just really like it anything would be so nice to try it like
As much as we all like to dog on like video game journalists and stuff like it is definitely
Please keep yapping enjoy it if you like the binding of Isaac, I highly recommend no, it's I have never heard of no, it's a
And is it like pixely like Isaac as well?
From how you talking here would be awesome at giving some game reviews, uh
I've got it as a donut on
Like reward it would take a lot of effort though. Like I definitely think after my donut on is finished
I'll probably have a few shorter games back-to-back and the reason for that is because I'll be like working on rewards. I
Literally want to like fire the rewards as soon as possible like once it's done and like all of that
Um
Not here runs can go for hours. Oh Isaac runs are like one hour
Sometimes if you get really good items and stuff you can be wrapped up in 30 minutes with Isaac
Yeah
Start each review with a five-minute hypnosis section where you turn your own your hypnosis say you will like this game
That's so good. You will like this game. You will like this game. You will like this game
Have you considered collab of girls playing?
Battleground three
What's bg? Oh
No, what's bg?
Battleground right up in background
Baldur wait the Baldur's gate is multiplayer. I've never played it
What did I've never played it and realized it was multiplayer
Big Baldi's gate right so we have just done it
We are officially
Goodness gravy. We have a lot of money on our persons
This is a bit more money than I think you actually need it. So
It's given capitalism. It's so it's good capitalism
Put it back and invest in properties and stuff
I am going to send the birds away. Yeah, sorry. I'm going to send the recruits away to level up a little bit
I'm going to do a peep. I'm going to make a cup of tea. So a three-minute break, please
heavily recommend that you
You know get up walk around stretch your legs and do a little pee-pee as well
and we are going to do the Borgia towers next and
then maybe
possibly
and
Maybe some other miscellaneous stuff. That's just wrong
I'm trying to find something that both of those last two recruits can go on. I mean, I'm got a
Oh, you're not strong enough
So I'll send you on a mission on your own and then for a level two
I will send you on a level one mission because I really don't want anyone to perish
He I know you could go up on Baldur's gate. That's so cool
And
Yes, I will definitely look into Baldur's gate collab
I would need to research the game before I play because I really don't know what it's all about
And okay, I am going to go pee pee because my bladder feels like it's about to burst
I will tell you if it's neon or not. Don't worry before anyone asks. I can already read your mind
but I'll do the thing where I
I'll mute and then put the game back on in the background and no one can see from me up here
Like that guy that yoinked that thing from me when I was away for like two seconds. It's sort of it
Okay, please consider getting up and going for a
pee pee in a lake bridge. I will be back
Incredibly short like hold on me. Yeah
So
Oh
Gee sure would be a shame if we put some more sass on the screen wouldn't that
Did you stretch your legs or did you stretch your feet if you're still sitting down?
Go fish, okay
Right first things first on the realest. I'm not
We are going to liberate the Borgia zones as you can see we've done two more
And now that we have arrow storm we can do these extra super difficult ones
So there's five more
Borgia zones
And what we'll do that and we might do layers of romuli romulus. I keep saying romuli. I don't know why
Oh, there's a new assassin over here. We should go help them
Oh, they're across the water
Are we gonna get something I have a honey tea and a wee water
with me, um
I'm not hungry. So I didn't need any snack. There is someone over here that needs our help if I could get there
Oh, uh, yes, uh, I have terrible news
It turns out if you adequately hydrate there were stairs right there
It's you
Um, if you adequately hydrate, uh turns out your your pee isn't neon
um
How what how am I even supposed to get up here? I don't
Uh, so grass patch
Oh
Did he die?
No, he's coming back for more. He said nah, I just dropped I want more
I've had enough of you Borgia scum. Oh my gosh
I was like, uh, he's gone
Nice knowing you mate
I got head to bed. Please rest well anyone who needs to sleep
I also mercy warning in one hour and 20 minutes
Our beloved dark yandere is going live. I believe Azura is still live
And I believe Emmy has wrapped up for ASMR stream and I assume she'd be his so I actually don't know who's online
Where am I going? I don't know
Uh, well, we're way closer to this so we'll go here. Uh, how did I get there?
He's on the other side of this hill. I always get confused on the location of like this hill thing
Hey, wait, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa of wall
I'm not doing anything
And
mom
Azur is still streaming. Okay. Azur is still live. I don't sleep sleep. I need to be
Wait, I mean
At least some people could see the angle where I was going with the sucky
Like oh sucky this blood that kind of makes sense
Okay, so it was up there. I knew it was going to be up there. I always get confused
I
I'm freaking sick. I'm gonna have to run back all the way around again
my apologies
I say Emmy and she bear off Azura is on and mercedes later. Okay. I will give a mercy warning
Um, but Azura duly is live right now with her very sultry voice. So please do not be afraid to check her out
Uh, I understand that uh playing the same game for eight hours may get
Rather tiresome for some of you. So please do not be afraid to support my gen mates at will
Oh, this is one of the worst. You need our storm to complete this one as well
Emmy's ASMR got deleted
Oh, I guess she's on a warning now
Emmy what were you doing baby girl?
Did it actually is it there did she is it like does it say like removed or does it say like
Uh
Or does it say she like put it private
Oh, I said
Emmy Emmy baby girl we try again monetize come on
Yeah, I say everyone play video games. We can do ASMR later when you play video games now
She had a bit too much fun. What the heck did she do in that stream?
Goddamn we memeing on assassin's screen and she's over there doing
Uh, right. We need to wait for our assassin signals to be ready for this next session. It's that cushion
Um, the bed was squeaking
Mouth sounds
She got a warning
Emmy Emmy Emmy do do a stunt. Okay. Go go on your twitter and be like youtube
This is so unfair. You're targeting me or something like that
And then I'll get picked up by vtuber news thing and then uh, I don't know question marks and then profit or something
I don't know
Hmm
I definitely think uh youtube is now considering ear licking sounds
know to be
Sucking sounds of an alternative
variation
And that is why there's this weird crack down
Um youtube i'm a literally neural day wrote them
Yeah, newly debuted vtuber banned unfairly. That's right. Get it written in the papers
teasing i'm teasing
As long as emmy had a good stream and um her pin pals were enjoying themselves
Look things happen life ain't that
Life ain't that serious
That's uh, uh, we do we do have a uh, hold on. I'm so sorry. I need to
You okay. Hold on
Okay, there you go
Uh, sorry um
You have to use the sasin signal on him or he runs away and gets away every time
Um, what was I saying?
Uh, emmy having fun. Yeah, as long as as long as she had fun as long as the pin pals
Pen pals had fun
Then guess what all is good like it's not a big deal or for me. It's not a big deal anyway
I assume she's fine and everyone's safe and having a good consenting time. It's all that matters at the end of the day
Uh, she's happy. I'm happy and if she's not happy, I'll try my best to make her a happy beam
um
I
Requesting one of the girls sing a belly idols song white wedding and all the art is about emmy
I'm gonna be honest. That's going right over my head. If that's something I should know about
Is that like a reference to I don't know if this can content of the song
He's gonna be wow wow
Uh, definitely gonna have to call in my sasin recruits unless
Vanishing act. Okay. Well try again
I do actually need to kill quite a few people in the get in the the the smoke
This is what I think about your long ball
I'm about to get shafted. Take this
And this
No, whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Did my assassin recruits just take all my health there?
I have potent out please
All right, you jump boom
Yeah
Vanishing act stands completely still
It turns out it's he was actually one of the worst magicians and he's just gonna stick to his daytime job of assassinating people
Repfield reference. No, I'm sorry. I don't know
I don't know what a lot of references are, but thank you for showing patience for me
For I am strong
On me and there's a ledge that I can climb on so I have to jump
And then climb up because I still do not have the climbing glove from the anardo's bench
But we're getting there in the end and even the whiffing ish campaign mode
I can't not go any
Oh, I love how goofy I can be with you guys. You're just like, yeah, I'll just start singing when I'll go for
If there's nobody left alive to talk about you you were stealthy
What does that mean?
Are you meaning? Oh, I forgot to burn the tower
It's okay. It's okay. It's okay. It's okay. I love climbing
I love overexerting my body
for climbing
This tower and there were three sides of this tower that are not climbable
And I climbed over two sides of tower
of the forge of tower
Oh
I think I'm getting a wee bit delirious and won't be honest. I don't like something that I don't know
and
Let's see
Uh, I've made the mistake again. I have to go on the platform
Delilah
Where is emi's vod?
Unfortunately youtube doesn't seem to like earlicking anymore. So it's no longer there
And sadly no, I will not get anyone to re-upload the vod
On their channel because it risks their channel
I want these girls to succeed and have moneys and emi would very much like to move to a place
That has a freaking washer machine and ac and uh, yeah, I I really don't want emi sweating it up in her
Uh
Current situation. So yes, I would like to wait. No, no, don't jump off. I almost did that again
You're distracting me. You distracted me to the point where I almost jumped off twice
It's patreon out it is you can find the links in everyone's links
Um, the website might have got updated to have our links on it now. I'm not sure
I'm gonna burp
I'm beautiful
Can I join velar? I want I want ac too
I mean
What you got you got a whole other poll me because if you've got a poll it's no looking good for you
I'm afraid I have no content creation advice if you've got a poll
I haven't experienced it. So I ain't got none
I have no values to you
The day out here, can you help me? I would gladly fight for you
Normal household functions. I mean she was like I've no got a washer machine. I'm like
Uh, I'm starting to think the velar house is looking more and more
Something I want to invest in because these poor girls are like I want to move out. I want to do this
I want to do that and I'm like
Well, I just buy a house and like ship them all out here and then we can just like meme about and stuff
Because like could you imagine those collabs?
like just like
AC bursts into my room and she's like thranny shut up. You're so loud. I'm trying to sleep
I'm like AC. I'm so sorry
Like she be comes in the room
And she's like, throw me. I can't do she be's voice
But I mean could you imagine
The noise complaints it would definitely have to be a detached house
uh
Cause yeah, that's something crazy. I love the idea of a gen content house, but it's hard to actually oh no you need
like
I don't know if you guys like remember in the call of duty days like was it the optic clan
I can never remember but there is like actual streamer gamer houses like that
Um
Can you email for him? Thank you. Um
Right, this is I know
You were supposed to write runny zoom ahead. Um
But like I remember from eons ago being like that's the coolest thing I've ever seen imagine of all youtubers
I watch live together
But I remember I think it was like
Must have been years ago now. No, not the horse. Okay. Thank god he got off the horse. I got scared there
and
Tree you're blocking my view of these enemies. I'm just gonna pretend I'm safe ish
Uh, can no, no, no, no, don't shoot
Don't shoot
Stop the bow
Oh god, there's horses. I'm scared. Oh, I can hear them
I feel like I'm playing slender man with these like guards on horses honestly
Oh, I can't sorry. I'm like trying to finish like one sentence whilst playing this game
Oh
Take this. Okay. Ow
Ow
I fell
Man, I fell off
Oh, I'm just gonna let the recruit steal with him. I guess
Take that stinky
Stinky stinky. Why why are you not attacking him? Don't be scared. It's so it's so I know you've been in the game for a long time
But don't be scared like they're not gonna hurt you
It's fun as roommates in the beginning it gets really
No, like that they're um, sorry to get back to what I was saying
I'm sure I read some sort of review of like what it's like to live with other content creators
And like I'm pretty sure the default is like it is so loud
Um, I so things get crazy and out of hand so fast like you have to learn to live as roommates
unironically because
um
Like who's going to do this chore who's going to arrange for the food who's going to arrange to
Like make sure all is good. Like you don't want to be streaming all the time
Like so you would have to get like business internet, which means they don't
like um
Throttle you if you do too much but business internet is like a thousand dollars per month type thing
Like it's absolutely wild when you start to get to like that level of content house
Like the bills are
astronomical
You find out that emi believes in not flushing to conserve what are known wants to do the dishes to preserve their nails
Like I absolutely do love it in theory, but it is
For me it is not plausible
And it's just like it's not happening. Oh look at all. Oh, we've got level sevens
Okay, we're getting stronger. They're there. It's not perfect, but definitely getting stronger
I am going to send some lower levels away
Um
That's not gonna work
Okay, I'm actually just gonna have to send the lower levels on a level up one
Um
Oh, well, it's not really like they're you don't lose an assassin signal if you have six available recruits
So it's not a problem that I cannot send them on a bigger thing. I am however, we're gonna save this poor guy
I'll send again this recruits
It's a cool concept. Honestly, I absolutely adore it. Like especially
um
Oh this isn't good
Oh no
Oh, no
Yikes, that was that was not how I imagined we'd save the citizen
Uh, anyway, let's move on to the next Borgia Tower. Shall we?
Okay, I think I need to go down
I'll take you. Hello, Mr. Horsey. You're my problem now
Oh
And that might be a good concept that could be for like a smart group club. Yeah
definitely
Like I said to the girls like as obviously relationships progress and stuff like
If you are genuinely serious about like wanting to meet up with each other, um
Like it's a business expense
and like we can do it but obviously like
We've known each other for like two months now, but
Yeah, I guess a bit early to like start shipping each other to each other's houses and that like
I definitely think we should let things
You know some of our relationships form and all that like I I can confidently say like I'm 100%
Comfortable with the girls, but obviously there was a lot behind it. It's like
Uh, because I like hired them and scouted for uh, no scout is not the right word
Oh, I don't want to do a lean or do division
mission
um
I didn't scout for any of them for any of you. So I'm gonna start off now. There was no scouting. Um
Um
Like there's a bit of truth and like I see myself
A little bit in all these girls and like I want them to succeed silly
and
Like and
Where am I going with this?
Whoa
I don't think I can keep this guy alive
He's picking on the guy with the lance first that does the most freaking damage
Please pick the others
No, let me go first citizen with no armor or weaponry. Goodness gravy
Um, you're such a good father
Yeah, but like unironically I do see like a piece of me in each of them and I just want them nothing to succeed
But I feel like 100 comfortable and confident around them. Like I don't feel any
Like any anything, um
Uh
Like we had a lot of um side comments that were like
Sorry, I'm a bit new to the terminology. It was called infighting which is like we're
The girls like we would compare our viewers and be annoyed at each other or something. I'm so sorry
I was quite new to the terminology if I'm getting it wrong and it was like, oh how long until they start hating each other and it was like
Like if you guys could see the behind the scenes of us like memeing about on games
Or having like a fun little gossip or just like having a good time together and I'm just like
I
honestly do not think any of them are capable of that and like you guys already know my stance like if it's
Um, like I just want them to succeed. I just want them to have an amazing time
I want them to like achieve their goals. Um home improvement achievement of love
The fart barrier was broken day one
Funny you mentioned that um
When the girls like when we had the first meeting so I had to schedule a meeting
But I said to them it's not a meeting like I'm forcing you guys to like do
Like, you know when offices make you play games like oh have played this game with your co-worker
Uh, I've forgotten what the name is like forced like get together time
um
I've completely forgotten the name of it like when offices for icebreakers, I guess like
There's a bit more of a deeper team building
Team building exercises. Yes when we had the first meeting I was like, right. What game are we gonna play?
Um, and we figured out a time and we played video games
And we played for around two hours and our first thing and we were all just giggling because I was like
Oh, I'm only going to make it like one hour long because I don't want anyone like overexerting themselves
like it was the first time we had
Um interacted and we ended up going over the two hour mark and we were just like laughing our little butts off and then
Sorry, I'm not paying attention to the game. I'm like literally dying and I'm just like teehee my girl's teehee
And like none of us wanted to go
But I I did it at the wrong time. So ac was like up pretty late. Um, so she had to go
Um, but just like it went fantastic and everyone was so nice to each other and it's just
Okay, I'm calling in the recruits. Hold on. I need help. I'm calling
Um
And it was just like such a fantastic time and goofing off and
Yeah, like instant chemistry like uh, I definitely think um
Because of the nature of the agency as well like no one here is like
I don't know like judging like oh puritan or whatever
Like it's just not a thing
Um
But yeah, like I just have an absolute fantastic. Oh, I was gonna lose body and I've not done the viewpoint
But I've spoken so much. I think my tea might be getting cold
Okay, it's getting cold. I'm gonna hop my tea
Yeah, like we have her for just collab. Um
Wait, wait, hold on
They're destroying that tower automatically update the map because if it did I have
What we will test it on the next boarder tower
I think that automatically updated the map and I didn't have to synchronize the viewpoint. You know that
Oh
How many times have I played this game and I I didn't know that are you coming or not?
Are you
Fine, I'll call in another group of assassins to deal with them because what's going on here
Yeah
Can you guys help her my goodness. Jeez. She almost perished
How ironic the the naughty agency ends up is the most wholesome
Yeah, like I think it's we're all in the same boat and we're just goofing off like
Um, when the girls were recording their scripts for the first time
Like they were so nervous and like oh, is this good enough? Is that good enough?
And I'm like, you have to start from somewhere like um, mercy for example hadn't done anything
Uh, like that before so she was like so unsure and I was like
I was sending her homework and it was literally links on the hub
And I was like just kind of listen to this and give it our uh, what you think and you know, you can add that next time
It is very interesting giving people homework because the homework is literally on
Well, you can imagine where
Um
But like mercy so hot like everyone just like was having a goof off and
so good
Mercy talking about experience to a point. It was so cute. Can't wait to see more from her. Yes
Um, she let me I don't know if you've seen the artwork on her twitter, but she
was very, um
kind to
Tell me about her
friendship with um
In being you I think it's Celestia. I'm so sorry if it's not Celestia
um
And I was like just so touched by her story and I was like I might get her a little doodle and surprise her
And like I sent it to her and I put a little message and I was just like your story really touched me
um
And also red string theory is when you were always gonna come together no matter what
So I had like a little string in the picture
Uh, and she sent me an audio over crying and I'm like, oh my god. I just made her cry
I feel so bad
But she was like it's happy tears. It's happy tears like thank you so much
Um, and I was like, oh my god. It sounds so terrible at a context like I made her cry
My girls are all lovely, um
Definitely great. I'm looking forward to their one-on-one collabs
Yeah, I can say that we have a group collab and one-on-one collabs this month. Um
Because we
Just everything's just gone so fantastic like so amazing couldn't ask for better like
Um, they've like recorded their video game lines. So that's kind of like the next big thing
I hope it can be done by next by july. I don't know at what point maybe
I'm gonna burp. Oh, pardon me for being so rude. It was not me. It was my food
It just came up to say hello and now it's gone back down below. Um
Sorry, uh, what was I saying?
I have completely and truly forgotten what I was saying
um
Yeah, the girls have one-on-one collabs this month, which I'm excited and then we have a full big group collab, which I'm very excited about
And then after that it might kind of be like trio collabs or four man collabs
Because not every game has six persons possible. Like it's just not happening
It's not happening
I don't know why like they watch me just like annihilate all those people. Can I go on this? Can I go on the gay bail?
Let me hide in here. See they can't get me
Um
But yes, unfortunately not all games are gonna come as a date
Um six people so we're just gonna have to see what's in there the lethal company among us like basically we are so limited
Uh, I probably shouldn't actually claim this. Yeah, I was gonna say I should not be claiming this right now
I need to wait until I can get my recruit
Uh, wait, can I get lost in the hay bails? Stop
No, you're not supposed to recognize me in the hay bails. Hold on
I just I need my uh one. I need one assassin recruit. Oh my goodness. I need to buy armor. You know that
Because that's that is like scary that one. Wow
Hold on right. There we go. I can actually finally attack
The problem is if you don't have like got a assassin recruits to help you like they properly go for you
Sorry, I'm a bit slow. I'm like try talking. Oh my tea. I forgot my tea already
What's going on? I can't see because of the camera angle
Yeah, take that as we get for annoying me
Sir lands a lot more like sir
Sir spurts a lot of blood
Ha ha I got him. Okay. Let me finish my tea. Oh no momento, please
Yep, that's honey tea. All right made by myself
Um
Um, I think it's just called black tea or uh regular breakfast English tea is what it what it is
And then just some milk and honey
Uh
Right, I need to climb this so I will I will
I will claim it by identifying
I really need to buy the Leonardo glove because this stuff would be so much easier
Right, we are going to test it. The map is not unlocked. I repeat
The map is not unlocked, which means
Then you go left then you go right
No, I can't go right. I have to go left right. I'll go left then. Um
Wait
Am I going crazy or can I not claim this without gloves?
Hey
Wait, I actually need gloves to work. I don't recall needing gloves to do this. Is it this?
Okay, this looks like it. Yeah, this looks like it. Holy moley moley. Wait up. Wait up over here
My goodness, this tower is uh, very uniqueness nature. That took me a whole second together
You burp from tea a burp from everything if I eat a burp of a talk a burp
Uh, I seem to like gulp air when I breathe unfortunately, which
Leads to all of this
I knew I could hear that. Yeah. Well, I don't want to go get it right now. So
Bye
Uh, yes
Hmm
Okay arrow storm is back
Okay, we are not doing the viewpoint because if I ignite this and it unlocks on the map
I've learned something new about my game yet again
I'm learning I'm learning does it unlock the map
Uh
It's true
It unlocks the map. Oh, I just realized I'm covering up the map, but it unlocks the map if you do destroy the tower
You're still playing. I never stop them
We've got one more board just on to liberate
Yeah
It appears there is a citizen that requires our help
Allow me citizen
Let him go eagle sound
Oh, that was not an eagle sound at all
Hello, I am your knight in training armor. It's the auditoria da fedenze
Deliberation of roma has begun
It's running built
Yeah, allow me to follow you
Started streaming squints eight hours ago. Yeah, I like my game
Uh, especially if it's a video game that I have an a tendency for uh, this game
I probably played it the most out of all games. So
So it's very easy for me to be like
With the game actually I should be unlocking these tunnel entrances
For fast travel, but I'm a bit lazy. We'll buy some buildings just because I have so much money in me pocket
Uh, how many runs in this game it is impossible to say like
I probably could comfortably say like over a hundred times just like casually
Playing it doing different strategies like some
Strategy I'll say strategies and brackets. So when the game started
I would like purposely buy all the areas I possibly could and then finish the next act and then unlock everything in that area
then
um
Like completely ignore all the monetary aspects and just go with the weakest weapons or like fully equip them out and
Like just all these different variations
Um, I did try black flag. Sadly I suck. Um, and I really struggled to get into it
I am very by I I just absolutely mogged to that older woman there. I don't know if you saw that
I just smashed into her. Um, I did play black flag. I'm rubbish
If someone has never played any assassin screen games, should I start at the beginning of the series or the series?
We can jump in at once. Ooh
That's a harder question to answer
I
Think you're
Hmm
From my completely biased standpoint
Um, I believe you should start at Assassin's Creed Brotherhood to understand the type of game it is
Assassin's Creed Brotherhood is the easiest game to play in the series in my opinion
However, you are going to start in the middle of the story of Ezio
If you do want to play Assassin's Creed 2, it's not impossible
Um, but you don't have assassin recruits, for example to help you out in a fight. Um, you are on your own
You do have mercenaries that you can buy on the street
To help you out. It's not impossible. Definitely don't be discouraged. Um, but my recommendation is
Ezio's storyline
Which is Assassin's Creed 2, Assassin's Creed Brotherhood and Assassin's Creed Revelations overall very easy games to play
Revelations got a bit
um
In my humble opinion, uh revelations
Kind of went a bit too far with the notoriety aspect
um
I understand that you can't just have the same game over and over in every installment. I do comprehend that
but um
The way they did notoriety and revelations was every time you renovated a building in the district
That the assassins owned your notoriety goes up
And the district is more than likely to be attacked and if you don't defend it you lose it and
And
In the nicest way, I don't like gameplay like that. I like to be like, ah, I feel accomplished
Like I've just renovated that aqueduct there
I feel accomplished because I know I don't have to redo it. It's not gonna get lost
I'm not gonna have any issues
Um, but I do understand that people like a challenge in their video games or they might enjoy
um kind of that
Aspect of having to fight back for something like you it's not just earned and it's not just that easy
Like no, you have to fight for it. You have to
You have a chance to lose that you have an opportunity to get in trouble type thing
Um, jeez. What was that achievement airstrike maybe?
um
I know 73 florans
eh
The game's having a rough time right now. I think I'm I'm asking it to do a lot
Oh, I'm going past the tower. Oh well
Hello. Bye. Bye. Hello. Bye. Bye. Hello
America
Uh, I hate this part with oh my goodness. It's a party on the rooftop, huh?
Let me get this tower. Ow my back. Hello. You're hitting my clavicle from the back. That's not very nice
Ah, stop it
Oh freaking sick. He didn't die. Oh, I need to wait for my recruits to come and help me
Why why why would you change camera right there game? I'm getting trolled right now
I think I'm just getting tired as well
Oh, I love to kill cams
No
Off him right. I'm calling in my recruits. They're gonna come help
As soon as like the AI can pick on someone else
It just becomes so easy to take them down one by one. Ow my back again
Would you kindly stop my goodness?
And I got a thief's guilt for that
Oh, I've still not done poison. That's a really easy one
How many okay, I have one bottle of medicine left. I was gonna say I actually don't feel like I've like
Looted at all
Hmm
I've never heard of a scotch video game nerd ran and it's perfect
Oh, literally like, uh
Skyrim's probably the next rambly game. I'm gonna play
Um, and just like tell you like all the things I know about the game and like uh gameplay that I've found interesting or good
um
I wouldn't mind playing cult of the lamb again. That was very enjoyable
Um, I can't yapp about it much though because I'm not I don't know much
I've only played it once but I really enjoyed it and it was a 10 out of 10
pardon me experience
Pardon me for being so rude. It was not me. It was my I have played shadow of mordor
and
I haven't like perfectly completed it or anything
But I would absolutely love to play that again
I want to give the golem game a shot as well
It's like such a oh, we got an achievement called tower of fence by the way because we just successfully
renovate renovate
um
destroyed all bourgeois influence on roma
So now we can successfully renovate everything on the map like on this part of the map. We can like buy everything
um, so i'm gonna fill up the recruits and uh, we'll buy some
locations and stuff
Was it literally everyone hated the golem game, but I'm like
I mean I assume they've had a few updates
from the bugs of the game
Oh, I've got a lot of baby assassins right here. Hmm, right. Oh
I'll recruit the last assassin wherever they may be. There's no one nearby
Um, we will start this top corner. Why not?
Uh, and we'll start renovating unless we do a layer of romulus
We could maybe do that like now
I don't mind
Well, you've been streaming the entire time I've been awake. I've been
At correction you fool. I've been nerding about my games that I love for eight hours. Haha. You think this is work
I'll show you work
Wait, um
The only reason like I'm able to like do it for so long is because you guys literally listen to me
Yeah, but about it for so long
Like it's just a good time. I'm having a good time. Um
And it's just nice being able to um
Just share like what I'm passionate about and
Graphics wise this game looks better than golem like does it actually this game is 14 years old
Unless yes refling we will fight back
No more shall we be
Uh, right hold on
I don't
The best way to go about renovating I think is doing the districts
So we're gonna start with this district first. Okay, so we'll just take it from the top
And we're gonna buy everything in the game
I can't believe assassin's creed brotherhood is actually just capitalist simulator
Because look at us now. We had no money at the start and money begets more money
You know what I'm saying and don't be confused with baguette
Beget baguettes as in
more
Um, I can't believe this game's just hidden money maker similar
They've sucked me in
I like really enjoy money making games
I just think I'm so fun
um
I did want to get into
Not me game developing
But me commissioning a game like being a studio
But I don't know what that's called
It's not like a publisher because you don't need publishers because publishers are what used to pay for the hard copy of like the xbox games and stuff like that
um
Like I might get into that at some point not right now. No, dude. So it's not right now
Um, like an investor. Yeah, like I will like go to like a gaming
Um, like developer and be like, hey, do you want to make this?
um
And basically they go, yeah, this is how much and I'll be like, okay
We will do this deal where you get this much and royalties and I get this much like that
I think it'll be kill
Make one scrawny
million dollars
any
scrawny stonks
I could listen to your ample of games for days
Hmm
What game ideas do you have in mind?
Well
So I really enjoy cookie clicker. However, I don't enjoy the aspect of cookie clicker
That is the game is so hard to finish and feel like ah, I have achieved the ending of this game
I am satisfied
So I wanted to develop a cookie clicker
That's like a four hour game because because because
VTubers and streamers need games that kind of wrap up in four hours
Like I think and I think there's definitely like a market for that kind of thing
Um, so it'd be very interesting to like find out the formulaic thing in the background
But obviously you need like more of a twist. You can't just make cookie clicker and then it ends fast like that's not how it works
uh cookie clicker game
is a number
game
where
You start with like no money for example or no cookies
and then you upgrade stuff via the cookies and
It makes more cookies and the numbers go up. I can't remember the type of game
it's called
uh
incremental game I
an incremental game
Is what cookie clicker is and I think there's definitely a market
For an incremental game that you can wrap up in four hours if it had a storyline of some sort
um
As well as like a replayability factor as well. I definitely think
There's a market for like four hour games, especially for VTubers and streamers and um
It would definitely be interesting to like go through it together now. I'm definitely nowhere
near doing any of that and
Like I don't even know where you start and it just becomes crazy legal stuff and
uh
Just to say the development of VLR took over a year and a lot of stress and a lot of like
Issues on the road like things are not straightforward. It's just impossible
to be straightforward
Uh when it comes to these things and I'm not wanting any stress right now
I just want to enjoy streaming like it took so long to get here. So no, we're not doing VLR
Uh game development arc. No
And for the game the free to play game that does come out
again, it was created by
Not like an outside source studio
Type thing. So I guess I've technically already done that. I mean
This game isn't for profit though
So I guess like when it comes to like profit games like marketing would have to go into it
Like all these different factors would have to go into it
But it's definitely something like I'm happy and open to talk about like especially the newest game that we're developing for VLR right now
and
Once it comes out. I'm happy to talk about the development, but I don't think it'll be surprised to anyone to
For me to not be able to show much of the content of the game
Oh, I don't think anyone's gonna be surprised. So don't think I'm gonna get like charts out and show like
These are the mock designs behind the scenes. No
I can't show that
It's not appropriate
Um, yes, it should hopefully come out in july
Um, it still looks like it is gonna happen in july. So that'll be our big announcement in july
for be a lower
And then we start getting to the other stuff
Just we've linked some vibe and literally there is a lot of lost time
And yeah, I surely it's uh able to play it on stream. Yeah
totally
Yeah
Yeah, no the game is absolutely fine to be streamed absolutely no issues at all empty faction building
Mm-hmm
What platforms um, it's gonna be itchio
Which is not how anyone reads it, but that's how I read it
Uh, so we're at the mercenaries location
So obviously the only logical faction
For like the mercenaries place like where all the the beefed up macho men are a bit stress relief for the courtesans
Eh
I have always put the courtesans here
Uh, you know, come on these the mercenaries need some
Some tlc and we'll bear to do that than the courtesans
Uh, we do have an aqueduct in this area
I know it's like we've kind of done this little quadrant here as well
Uh, and we did do that
maybe we'll like do the outside of the map and then
Where the heck am I supposed to go?
Wait, it was highlighted. Why can't I see on my map?
eto
Hello, I know
A brotherhood are you showing your age?
Oh
I was bam boozled. It wasn't highlighted properly
Mercenaries could have been a good mercy fan name
Would a young dairy have guns like that like
She'll have gunners
but guns
nah
Yeah
I could see you doing a game like ducky ducky. I've never played ducky ducky
I think a lot of youtubers have though. Um, but maybe like I think there's
Four girls in that game. So maybe uh veal or like reading voice over thing could be a thing
Hey
Uh, right we've done this kind of section this one here. So we'll do this bottom corner. Oh, there's Leonardo. We go
We can purchase the glove
I need the glove for climbing reasons
No other reason
I promise the glove is for wholesome intentions
And to suggest otherwise
Wait, aw
Riding around in my game looking at the sun is so bootyful
What a beautiful
Recreation of roma back in back in yield days before the internet became a thing
But how would uh, how could you stream if you were back then?
I guess be a stage presence. Excuse me, mr. Horster in the way
Friendly reminder to not lose sleep. Yeah, if you guys need to rest or you need to go, please don't worry
Mercy's going live in 30 minutes any mercy modist watchers also known as karambit
Uh, any karambit warning in 30 minutes, but please do rest if you need to
Or hydrate to you know, actually I'm going to take a sleep
Oh, I'm me. Oh, sorry
Okay
So you cannot access this viewpoint if you do not repair the aqueduct here
Which I thought was a pretty neat thing because the game's kind of like hint hint mate. You need to repair stuff
And then you'll earn income because I'm sure a lot of people kind of played and missed that part of like you can
Renovate buildings and that's how you get money in the game money
We
This game is my second fave before black flag. Yeah black flag certainly captured a lot of people's hearts
Like oh no
I forgot it was that jump. I normally struggle to get out of this place so much
Oh, can I remember how to get out?
Wait, was it that easy
to get out
No
Yes
Okay, it must have been chilled me because I like never do that like I never go down there
So it must have been chilled me that really struggled to get out there. I just remember being like
Back for more designs again
The Scottish accent making me think differently. What is rest streamer don't
stream now there we go
Claim leap glove this reinforced glove allows for faster claiming giving the wearer the strength easily grab handhold many mid-jump
Handholds mid-jump. It also deals more damage to enemies when fistfading
Wait here, I'll be back soon
Yeah, maybe we should get black flag like a really good goal
Because people seem to just adore it and I've tried it twice to get into it and
I don't think I beat like an hour now. Nothing will be out of my reach
No, nothing going bring out on my match. Uh, I think we can oh we can I was gonna say
I think we can buy the poison darts as well
I don't know if there's like a sea shanty or anything
Only a fool could walk past my shop without a decent quick look
Only a fool
Night night rest well those who are resting
Please don't worry about not making it. Uh, I'm very
I'm very uh, unfriendly
Uh, right, we're just gonna run buying things. Oh my goodness
Society all norms. I can't get away from that. I'm such a girl going around buying things man. These gender norms go hands
ah
Stop it. Stop it. The gender norms are winning
Wait, is this the game where you get the wish and well achievement? Oh it is
I just remembered that holy moly moly. I just remembered that wish and well achievement
Okay, uh, this looks like a thief's district. So I'll just make it thieves
Nine thousand florins every
20 minutes. I'm in the money. Right. I renovated that but it's not
Updating on the map, but that's okay. And then we'll kind of sweep around these section
Like maybe we should go outside the map and then in the center. I'm not sure
There's a war going on for their benefit
Did you know there's a war going on for their benefit?
I think odyssey might be my favorite. I didn't get chance to see
Yeah, I'm you still playing mommy. I mean mommy. I mean mommy
Yeah, we finished the campaign. So now we are going around and buying everything we can in sight because these gender norms have hands
um
But it means
We are getting more progress to the hundred percent
For tomorrow because hopefully we can hundred percent the game
Which is actually crazy because I've never done it before after considering how many times I've played this game
I I'm going to send my recruits to get a bit stronger because
They aren't actually all that strong right if I take you
Can you take some of these?
Pete maybe
Do like that
Do you get hundred and sixty five each?
You know what that'll still level up her that's just fine
Level four and then do that
And that and that and send them away
And then do a level three mission
Don't be shy level three mission. I know you're out there
Don't be scared
Okay, level one you go with level seven and you share the xp
And then level three. Yes take two together
Okay, just take her as well
And then level one mission off your pulp. Okay. We did it
Our assassins are all being leveled up and we're getting all the money for
Oh
I've been trying to think of a marrow to send you but man excited go ahead. Don't worry. I'm brain dead
You don't have to be scared of me. Um
Some people came to get like brain worms or they're like, oh, she's gonna hate me because I said this or I did this one thing
I'm not like that. Um
Hopefully if you are nervous and you're just watching and you're just a lurker for now, that's fine
But hopefully over time you can kind of just see how we're vibing and
You maybe get the confidence to talk but uh, hi lurkers. It's okay if you're shy
I'm not gonna. I'm not gonna like call you out or be mean or stinky or anything. It's perfectly fine to be shy and um
If you're needing to just hang out and have some background noise on I um
Uh, very thankful that you picked me to be your background
I
Like the vibe so far just being child. Yeah, listen. It's casual. You don't have to
No audience participation necessary. You can be as close as you like
You can be attached at the hip or you can be an arm's length whatever is comfortable for you
I'm just happy that you're happy and if you're not happy
I have five
Lovely girls who would love to also entertain you in their own special way
And I would love for you to check them out if you're just like, ah, I don't think this is quite for me
That's perfectly okay
perfectly, okay
Yeah
You are my oh
I don't know how I don't know how I
like just
The just being so inexperienced and like being so
Unknowing
And like you guys are just so overwhelmingly kind to me when you could have
Could have easily have taken the other avenue of being like
Oh, this this person hasn't done their research
Uh, they're just doing it for this reason that reason and instead you just showed me nothing
but like endless amounts of kindness of patience of like
Even excitement just to tell me what's what like literally like t s k r
And I say tisker
And it becomes like a meme instead of like someone could have easily have just been like
That's so pathetic. You don't know like the most common phrases
And like you you guys are just like so kind to be like yeah tisker. We love tisker
And it's just like such a a good freaking time
You know, you could have been cancelled for that for a lot
and
What if I can't choose between all of you I actually have
Solution if you can't choose and you're not gonna like it
And this is terrible of me to say out loud
But whoever caters to your
Your willy the most is who you should oh she
There's no other way to say it
But whoever caters the most is how you should oh she have your struggle and to pick between us
Um, yeah, because there's no other way to do it there isn't
Like come on, you know, I'm telling the truth
Don't let your brain do your thinking let your head do the thinking
Why think when your head can do the rest
Hey
Another we're at 9.4 k floren's every 20 minutes. Thank you
Uh, okay, we're getting really close to doing the outskirts fully a got this
Uh the lair of romulus. Um, I'll try and buy everything. Are you okay?
Are you okay? Do you need help?
Oh, she's being chinny. Oh, she's oh, she's calling me over. Yeah, you like the assassin style. Yeah
Oh
What's it? Oh
Oh, she's
Oh, she's okay. She's at the war. We'll leave it. I don't know what she's doing
It's really fun to like sit and watch NPCs in this game. Um, um, oh
Huh
I've just remembered another achievement
We'll need to do it where there's enemies
Because we can't do it here without enemies
Um, maybe I should get on a horse
Look at my horse. My horse is amazing
Yeah, I like oh, it just tastes like raisins
There's that hole. I can't remember
She's washing your feet
Oh
Honestly hashtag spoiled
What nice lady I didn't even tip her should I go back and tip her? No
Spain it's fine
Oh
polishing your shoes, whatever. Yeah my my uh
Ah, what's the name of the armored shoes if I go to the the the um
Blacksmith and keep going. It's not enough money
Oh my goodness I've blown through the veal or budget
Quick get me to the bank
Get me to the bank. Where's the bank?
Get me to the bank
Right mr. Banker. I have a really good idea. We take
Five girls
Okay with me and we do really cute streams
Okay
And we get to nerd about our games that we really like and we get to have a good time together
Are you in or out mr. Banker? How much will you invest?
Tell us how much is it gonna invest lads?
14 000 okay, I'll take it. I'll take it. He invested 14 000 better than none
Better than none. Right. Let's let's renovate the stable right now
I'm all in 50 trillion dollars
Let's bet everything
I quit years I quit or you're getting stabbed
In order to avoid this heinous act
Okay, um, we're getting close and maybe we won't do landmarks landmarks are
insanely expensive
We might maybe it's better to do these
See the landmarks all come together here like in between these like five is oh, yeah five is like 100 000 florins
Now don't get me wrong the banks make money but
nine
Nine squillion
Florin nine thousand squillion florins isn't gonna do it. You're gonna cut it
So we can't invest just take on them a blank check. Oh don't mind the bad
Uh, uh, you ready for this achievement?
Thank you very much
Ready
steady
Spring cleaning feet on with the broom
Can I parry with a broom?
Ah
pocket sand
You can parry with our broom. How does it not break?
Achievement name clean sweep. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah
That's what I'm talking about. What's that? You're too small enough to remember the secret achievements. Uh, yeah, what do you mean? You're not
Oh my god, you're not hashtag as
In love with this game. I'm just kidding. It's not a competition of who knows more about the video game
If you enjoy your video game, that's fantastic. We ain't here trying to give you a quiz
To prove that you've played the video game. That's not how it works out here
Not from around here
Oh, my assassin recruits gave me tons of money as well. I already forgot that part
Do your business with them and broom them fast
Is it possible to beat the whole game using a broom, uh, no because it won't spawn in all locations
Uh, you cannot do it in all locations. Take a little sip of water
Oh
Mercy going live in 10 minutes. Mercy going live in 10 minutes
Did mercy's fine name?
Mercy's fine name snippets
10 minute warning to all snippets. I repeat 10 minute warning for all snippets showtime is upon you
Uh, I always struggle to get out of the section of the game. You know what? I'm I'm gonna just jump down the hill
I'll just do it and I'll call the horse a bit later on
Hee hee
I really wet your whistle. I do need to wet my whistle
Did you know in Alice Madness Return the old lady says wet your whistle
And it used to scare me so much when I played that game. I used to be terrified of Alice Madness Return
You know, I'm starting to think I'm just a scaredy cat altogether. You know that
I think I'm just just a little scaredy cat
Right, let's just buy this
Oh
Wait, please give mercy my company allocated a mental well. Okay. Good night. Ha ha. No
No, not American McGee's Alice. I I tried to play it. I suck
And not the good kind. I just was not good at that game
I got stuck at the very start on the three-door portal thing
I don't know my game was bugging out or I was just too dumb, but I am very dumb
So that's the most plausible answer
Hi, Johnny. Oh wait, sorry. I just said hi. Johnny is if I was saying your name. Hi, babe
Congrats on doing it. Uh, congrats on you
How how you doing?
I can't believe I said that. Hi, Johnny. Wait a minute. Wait a minute. Johnny's me
We're playing uh, thanks for saying congrats on doing it. Uh, thanks for watching us
Yumi plus was literally one of the only agents one of two agencies that responded
Uh, no, I tell a lie. There was a third agency, but due to taming it could not be possible
But um, there is very likely to be a third agency as well that we will interact with a lot because they were kind enough to give us the time of day
And I'm definitely a
Someone that's like if you scratch our back we'll scratch yours, you know
Like if you give me the time of day, I'll give you the time of day
Anyway, that's that's just my two cents. Anyway, that's just my two cents
I just said yumi plus like a dumbass you're being you
Sorry, there's a few girls from yumi plus that came in and I have been
Streaming for almost nine hours. So my brain is getting out there. But yes, thank you
It made again. I apologize from b and u not from yumi plus. I apologize
I'm I'm uh getting a bit h2 delirious
At the moment just because I love I've been playing
But me love me love
Prit me praying I say your name right? I like when my accent does it change? But no, I don't
Uh, I'm actually gonna
Don't want to hear
Aren't you supposed to be the one
Aren't you supposed to be the one with a mushy brain?
Yeah
Did you know my biggest weaknesses are mirrors?
And I can't wait to be close, but it's terrible, but it's true
Is it terrible to tell the truth? I don't know maybe
Maybe baby
If you tell them the truth
I
Was juggling three debut watch along the whole time. It's a wild ride. Wait, did other people debut on?
Or do you mean? Oh, do you mean their watch along? Yes?
You said the word watch along and then my brain completely went over that. That's exactly what you said
Yeah, that makes much more sense than what I was originally reading
Gee willikers. I'm losing the plot
Right, uh, we've kind we're gonna ignore these big buildings
Um, these cost a lot of money money. We do not have at the moment
Uh, all the funds went into developing the girls sorry tihi
We've arrived at seems great now want to see stormy looking in the mirror, which all that
Uh, someone suggested it and I'm like
Um, because like one of my like top 10 is like
Lost
Um, and I was like, it's literally perfect. It's like too perfect
Um, could you hit the size on yourself in a mirror only by accident like I wouldn't do it on purpose
It would be like an accident thing
I cannot wait to like do the donathon because I have so many panel like comic strip ideas
Um, if you've seen the one posted on twitter, um
Uh, that kind of panel comic stuff thing. I love it. I love it with my tongue out
of it
Cannot get enough of that like like one shot dojin type things
I just adore it right um, we're gonna do this viewpoint here. It's not too finicky now that we have the glove. It's not
Did I not just select that viewpoint?
I did select the viewpoint, but I guess I did it so fast
Um, but yeah
how would
Get out of him it just wears awful retain like my
Like my preference for like hypnosis is like it doesn't last forever
but I have recorded an audio that removes like any
um
Effects that I may have given you because I have gone the finger snapping route
Um, I quite like the finger snap in both ears
um
That's just me personally though
Um, and I also like the banyuril
repeated uh under for subliminal angle as well
So I've kind of like done that route, but that's just for me and uh,
You know, hopefully people enjoy it very new
But I just kind of did what I like because I find if I do what I like
Things come out very enjoyable
Uh overall whereas like if I kind of feel like forced it's like I doesn't really come out of the way I wanted it to come across
You know
This is just a viewpoint
Uh, aren't you going to condition as well?
That's why I've recorded an audio to undo it at any point. So if
You don't want to experience it anymore from me
Uh, you can definitely listen to it and undo all the thing because you got to be safe when you do hypnosis
I did my research
And definitely got to be safe got to make sure you're safe
And all that jazz so yeah, but uh, I don't really do anything
um
very
Out there um when it comes to the bit mnosis community a lot of things are
Like
In that and I'm not really
Going that route
Doesn't mean I'll I'll never say never never say never because I do like try in my hand and like everything
I'm kind of like a finger in the pies
Um, I just love kind of challenging myself like that newest audio
Uh, I have never really
Uh done anything to that degree before I was about to jump off there. Yeah, you won't hey bell. That's fine. Um
I have never done that kind of audio before
But I enjoyed doing it even though it's not like an interest of mine personally because it was a challenge
It was something I had to like go out there and learn about right. Okay. What aspects do people like about this particular thing?
Okay, I'm going to incorporate it this way
I've seen from like this video that I'm researching they did it this way
But I don't have a preference that way. I'd rather it be this way like I like that kind of challenge
um for me personally um
Which um, I like variety
Um, and all that good stuff. Sorry. I'm Emily. I'm kind of a bit passionate about that stuff too
But we can talk about it at a later time
I don't mind
Yeah
But yes, that's kind of my thing um, mercy
Snip it
Call out in three minutes
mods
You are given permission to link the stream once she goes live and then you're unpromissioned to talk. No, you're too quick
You're too quick once she goes live unless she's live. Is she live? She might be live
She's probably already alive
um
Okay, we're gonna do this section. This is actually quite a big section
Like you can see these contract missions
They go away as soon as you do them so we can 100% like do that, but we'll go for renovation
um
Yes
I am new for anyone who's like I can't wait to hear your stuff
Please give me the benefit of the doubt. It's like we kind of
You know get into it because
I'm new but I am passionate. I've actually always had a thing for it, but I've never
The problem is I needed to research it
But the rabbit hole gets so so deep
Like the first thing I learned was like the safety thing
Like I need to do an audio that reverts anything that I might have given someone
um
Like that was like the first major thing I learned and then the things were like the conditioning like what's your condition thing going to be
and I personally like
um
Double whispering is what I call it and snapping fingers and both ears like fine neural
It has to be by neural. It can't just be mono like in the center
Um, I like that. So I've incorporated that
It's almost 5 a.m. I should
Uh get back to the reason I'm pulling on all night our oopsies
Please rise well. Thank you for hanging. I apologize for taking on your sleep
Yeah, I like subliminal whispers as well that are by neural
Oh, I love it, but my goodness golly does it add to the overall like
Duration of how long it takes to make an audio, but that's fine
Like if it's a passion project type thing just a small sting and my enemies would fall
Okay, we've just unlocked poison darts, which are fantastic. I'm a bit late to the story considering
Uh, actually we need to poison five guards in order to do a mission for not mission
Uh, you can like oh, he saw me. He saw me. Oh man. He caught me. Oh
Can you stop my good? I really wish
Oh, fine. We're just gonna grab his weapon. Oh
Well, we can also do that. I guess jeez. Let me heal up
What was my awakening
The jungle book muggle the snake scene in the jungle book
Which is terrible, but it's
I was just kind of like oh wait, wait, wait. Why did I really like this like really like this?
I
Right did I get more poison
I'm listening to stream. Anyways, luckily I had to open another tab where we got taken down, but
Uh, this and I got asleep. Yeah, please rest. Well, don't worry. Uh, I'm benchy. I don't know my
My streams are very long. It's quite hard to stay up unless you like wake up at the same time as me
Go to sleep at the same time as me. It's a bit hard for my endurance streams
But I don't always do endurance streams like I've got needy streamer overload that way a short one the hand cam stream will be a short one
Um
How many hours is this I've probably got like one more hour
I'm just gonna try and buy all the buildings and then tomorrow we can tackle the layer
Of romulus and I can show you the armor, which I really like we'll get a big armor upgrade
Um
And leonardo missions and then
We try and hundred percent the game for the dna sequence, which I'm very nervous about because I've never done it before
And someone said the tank mission and I was like the tank mission and they were like, yeah the tank mission
And now I am scared of the tank mission
Because I don't know what the hundred percent is on it and I'm terrified
Uh, I think I'm gonna poison those guards, which sounds really mean
Yeah
So is it more about being in controllers at more of a
Thing I definitely go both ways with my interest in hypnosis
um
I do like the idea of being like
It backfires. I really enjoy the idea of it backfire. We're just gonna
No
Okay, we did it we poisoned all those guards. Oh, they're beating each other up. Oh
Oh, they jump in him hydration check
You really like mirrors, huh backfire. Yes
Um, so I like the concept that my like hypnosis that I'm supposed to do on you
Um, like backfires on me like if I look at a shiny object or reflective objects
Like I like that that's
But I do like the idea of being in control and like
Telling you what to do because like that kind of power is
Like insane that power feels like
I know that's not even like a word or anything, but like it just feels very like
Hot in here
Because it's like, what do you mean I'm in control of you?
I'm just an echo
Oh, how the turntables basically I enjoy that too. Yeah
In
But I definitely need to do like more research like secret subject has been fantastic
If you didn't know like secret subject like has done
uh, like reports
and
like essays
and just like explains like stuff on
Oh, I don't have enough money
I spent it all
Goodness gracious, right hydration system secret subject mentioned. Yeah, I love secret subject
Oh
Yeah, it's like she
Is just so oh, we made a living cave right where's a bank
Like she is just like doesn't gay keep like, um, she actually quote tweeted me on
Twitter which sent like a bunch of followers
Um, and she was like just so happy. There was another hypno beach of her and I'm like
I hope I don't disappoint her
Um
Just like I hope she's like oh like a secret subject has never given any indication of being like a mean person at all
and I would never ever think that um
I just hope like no one thinks like on the hypno side of things like I'm a poser like I'm just someone who genuinely does have an interest
I'm just not well versed
And like I'm at the learning stages of things
um
and like
Again, just like as long as you've got some patience for me
Uh, like every time I do something I'll gain more experience. I'll gain more understanding. I'll see the feedback back. Sorry
Um, and just overall have like a really it says down
The map says down
Pardon me, sorry
Um
No, I'm like so appreciative for like secret for just like not even being interested in
like gatekeeping isn't like a word but
Being so interested in what she does and being so passionate about what she does that she willingly shares and educates
Like it's just so nice
You know
Are
You going to once at this game? Oh
Uh, do we tell you that we already finished the campaign and we're now just doing renovations on the buildings on the map
We may have already finished the campaign
Hmm
Why do you care so much about what other men are doing? I don't understand what that means
Sorry, you're gonna have to rephrase that I don't understand
That was way too fast. Oh, yeah
You finished it like an hour ago
Yeah, I'm just trying to buy everything like renovation wise
and
then
line
We shall
Uh, do the romuli and all that you're mister earlier message. Wait, what sorry, sorry
What did I mean?
I'm actually literally landlord simulator right now. Like this city owns me so much money
Oh, mercy's definitely up by now. If you're a snippet or want to give mercy modest also known as
Slava thought if she was slavic and that's absolutely
outrageous name
Racial emotivated name unironically that's absolutely atrocious. Um
Then she is live and she is playing killer seven if my memory serves me correct
So, please do check out mercy. Uh, right now. We're literally just rambling and renovating
We have passed the campaign stage, which means my ankles for one
We are
Mocking about at this stage if you're here for progression progression commences tomorrow
Right now we renovating and getting rich baby. We're playing rich simulator. We probably should have done that pigeon thing. That's fine
I
Don't do that
Yapping inland lord and honestly by nightfall she will own the city
Have you heard of sav lit? I haven't no
I'm happy to like to take any suggestions and
Marshmallow if you never want me to check anyone out because I read marshmallow
What am I doing Taylor?
We're going to the table
We is that empty
Can't reach it
Super good. Let's say today rumor tomorrow the world
Um, well happy hunting
We'll see you if you're still on a little there if not problem other time either way good chill and see right future
Oh, thank you very kind. Thank you. Thank you very much for your kind words
Mercy is live. I'll repeat again. Mercy is live. You can find her link in the description
Or I can give permission to a youtube mod to post the link
He
Right, uh, if you do doctor and then go nor then yeah
Look at him. He's so mad at me because he dropped his box and it disappeared into nothing
There's the doctor over here doctor doctor I miss it. What was that song 10?
Five monkeys jumping on a bed one fell off and bumped their head
Wait, is there doctor mentioned first came love? No, right. My brain is just crossing everything right now
Is that the same tune? Okay. Yes, I signed the first came love second come marriage third comes baby in the golden carriage
Okay, empty faction building and coming for you
Oh 13 out of 15 medical shops
Renovated we getting close
Um, I I'm actually going to send my recruits away again because they're the money makers and
The money pile is getting smaller and smaller
Haram beat was
I know I wasn't Haram. It was Karam
I think I don't know I'm Karam's
Karam nice and easy to
Money money money
It must be funny
In a rich man's world
Oh
All the things I could do if I had a wee bit money
Must be funny
A little bit delirious
That's okay
Uh, right what we're doing four. Let's do four
You level up you guys because you guys are pretty weak sauce
A hundred xp is not good
For you
Right I like those odds
How did this turn into
Vantian business taken?
It's literally just like a side part of the game
Um, I just kind of like comes out and over honestly, uh, like send them all off
Money money money money money money money money
Okay, well just do that
For them. They're unfortunately a bit too weak. I'm just gonna safely send them all together
I don't want anyone to perish at this stage because everyone's getting pretty leveled up at this point
And uh, okay. I've got 12k for doing that. That's fantastic. Uh, right. Okay. We're gonna renovate this
We're gonna look at this view point. There's 24 view points in brotherhood and the borja tower's total
I believe is
10 no 12
Maybe 12 maybe 11
Mmm, so already 11 view points have been
Uh dealt with
Is this where I'm supposed to go?
Hello. Hello. Can I purchase you? I would like one courtesan tree
I do have the stamina to still be playing I love my video games and I love yapping
So I may or may not
Still be here
Um, I think I'll try and buy everything on the map and then once I've done that and
I think we'll retire for the evening
possibly
Or do we just go for it and send it? I don't know. How are we at?
We're at nine hours. So we technically have three hours before the vod starts
And feeling a bit special
So, I mean maybe my first game stream could be 12 hours
Hmm me honestly
Honestly for I'm feeling all right right now
Like I'm feeling out where the heck am I supposed to go? Am I supposed to do this thing? No, I'm not. Is that building?
um
Absolutely legendary feat. Oh, yeah, like I just love the game
Uh, obviously
The company of the reeflings make it absolutely fantastic being able to just blab about this game and
Ramble away about anything and everything. What the heck am I supposed to be doing here? I supposed to jump on the
That can be right up like this. No
Must be that one then
um
Okay, yeah, there we go. Um like
No, I won't say that that's not nice. That's not kind
Um 12 hours that's impressed. Yeah
Please understand if I hate the game I'm spending 12 hours on it
The fact that I have much stamina right now is because I absolutely adore this game
And I'm so glad I like get to share it with you
And just like show you everything about it like right now
We're playing landlord simulator on it you can do this as you progress through the campaign mode
But obviously we we finished the campaign mode. So never just don't landlord them
uh
Um, I don't know
If I maybe I could order some food
And then we take a break and I eat it
uh
Yeah
You got to do what you love reeflings Johnny loves brother
Oh, no if any of yousers stay enough. I'm so sorry. Yeah more content for eu frogs to just woke up
That is hilarious because someone was like are you gonna stream earlier to be eu friendly?
Um, and it's like well dependent on the game
I might be online when you wake up
Uh, so yeah, hi. Good morning. He you. How you doing?
Um, I wish youtube would fix the 12 hour
streaming vod issue
Um
If they did I honestly think I could do 14 hour streams like literally wake up
Very quickly, you know toilet brush teeth get some food ready. I think I could genuinely do that
Obviously my voice is croaking like a frog, but
I don't want to stop like I'm having a good time. I don't want a fun time for pause champ. That sounds bad for your health. I mean
I'm gonna say something controversial. I hope it doesn't come across like that, but for me
To talk and play video games. I don't
Feel I am over exerting myself as long as I have no current
issues going on such as illness dehydration possibly
um
Or
Other elements such as this that may prevent long-term streaming, but I am quite a happy bun
My blood flow is good. My heart
Is good to go
um
You know, I understand that some people may find it negative for their health to maybe
Not like sit and play games for 12 hours, but me
Of kinder I kind of done it for a long time like when I was um
When I was younger I
Had a rough time at high school. You know how it goes yawn yawn
um, and I very comfortably played xbox all day long. Um,
my parents were very understanding about my
situation as best as they could when it came to high school and um
Kind of not fitting in so I had a lot of days just to myself
Left of my own devices and
I used to just play xbox all day long and uh, yes, I'm very lucky to have the parents that I do
and
like I
hear stories of parents that don't quite understand like maybe what anxiety is or what
agoraphobia is or
kind of
these elements that may
Make up parts of your being and
kind of to have a parent who
Who loves you who loves you and but just unable to comprehend
How you are in the moment. It's rough and I do genuinely feel for you if you're in that situation
I hope that you feel comforted in the fact that like here you're accepted
You can be as autistic as you like, okay
and
you can
Just be yourself. I know you might worry about messages and oh my goodness. What does she think but
She thinks like herself, you know, I was in your shoes once most likely where
I was terrified of the world. I was terrified to leave my room. My life was in my room
Uh, and I was in my head and it's terrible when you're in your head. I wish I could pull you out instantly
I wish I could pull you out overnight
But guess what if watching my stream slowly pulls you out?
goodness gravy
Goodness gravy. Um, I am so
Lucky to be the one that can show you
That yes, the world is a scary place and guess what if your therapy is
some random scots
Playing the sassan's green brotherhood and nerdy now and then occasionally
It's throwing out a joke here and there
Let's get it. Let's get to it. You know
The world is our oyster. Okay
Like don't
Take your time
life
As they say Rome wasn't built in a day get it because we're in Rome. Huh, huh, huh?
And you know, you're not gonna figure out life in a day. Don't be silly. You're not gonna figure out in a week
You're not gonna figure it out in a month. You're not gonna figure it out
Until maybe you're even on the other side of it because how do you get life exp by living life?
okay
and
I think if you might be someone who struggles to go outside maybe at the moment or
with other areas
If you want to see it like a video game
It is the best way I could ever explain it
Is that you're always gaining exp every day. You might say to yourself
You know what? I'm just rotten in bed. I'm just watching streamers. I'm doing nothing. I'm not progressing
What if I told you that even though vtuber's may be entertainers
They can still teach you a thing or two about life like
Communicating with people or listening to people communicate and hearing their opinions
Giving you a new perspective on things you might never have considered before
Like please don't ever think you genuinely are stagnant and rotting
I know the terminology is rotten in bed and I've rotted all day. I've not done anything. I've did it
I did it
Well, I was told you you don't have to do anything
Who said you had to do anything like
Just
One breath at a time one day at a time you have come so far and you have
genuinely
Um, like gone through every worst day of your life and you're still here
You have no concept of how strong you are and like I'm like tearing up thinking about you. Oh my god
Like um
I'm happy to like share this like thing of the past, but
I was having a rough day. Um
And we listened to a song by mr. Kitty
And I said the phrase you feel like this all the time and like oh i'm actually crying
I don't want you guys to feel like that. Oh my proper crying. Hold on
Oh, I need breathe. Hold on. I'm just being dramatic. Okay
But like I don't like want you guys to feel like that like it's so
like it just makes me feel so sad because
Like I know how sad I used to feel and like
Oh, I just don't want you to feel it. Right. I need to stop crying. I'm like, I'm literally such a baby
No cry. No cry
No cry literally happy tears like
Oh, I think like there's just so many emotions like especially with like recently
Like debut and like all these girls are
Just like so fantastic and they all had faith in me and you guys all had faith in me
But like it took so long to get here and there was like so much blood sweat and tears and it was like
But I did it like I did it. I got past all those bad days and you've got past all those bad days like that's a fact and
You know, I always say the phrase if life was easy
Then how would the good times be so good if you wouldn't appreciate the good times, you know
And like some people say the phrase like
I've got any money
Um, some people like say the the phrase um
Like
I've completely forgotten where I am because that stupid bank interaction
um
I've forgotten what I'm saying
Maybe I should forget because I don't want to like cry. I don't want to make you guys like upset or anything
I just like wasn't a happy times
Good times coming and hopefully like
This is the start of the good times coming. Um, like you don't need to worry about me being like an endurance streamer or anything like that, you know
She assassin don't my creed until our brother. Okay. Okay. Okay
Yeah
Okay
Okay, memer memer's memer's lock in we need to be back on the memes. Okay, right. We've got a level four assassin
We'll send them off on a level two mission
Unless it can do like level three 10 out of 10 10 talk stop
I don't want to make you guys upset like talking about that stuff right send them off send them off
dumb dumb
I have a new oshi now. Oh, no, you can't be your oshi after that. I literally just went oh
And you want to go? Oh, yeah new oshi
No, you're such a gift for honestly
Um, right, we'll do this viewpoint
Not making me upset feel inspired instead. I hope so like I never want to say anyone like
Yeah, uh, I missed something important but heart. No, it's fine. It's fine. It's fine. We're memen
We're just
I'm glad I was able to watch all of the debuts you and the girls
It's an amazing job. Each one of you has made my week better and look forward to future streams. Oh, thank you very much
I'm glad the girls could entertain you
Here we are now
We are beach ever
entertain
Uh, I think if I climb up to the left side, you actually can climb up right in front of the pavilion
Shawnee I got the dumbest smile on my face from the wholesomeness. Thank you. Oh, bless you. Bless you
Mmm, it makes me want to cry because you are right. I did make it this far. You did
You fucking did it
And literally like oh, I'm gonna start crying again, but you're so fucking strong
Don't think of your like don't ever think of yourself like oh, I'm weak. No motherfucker
You're a rifling
Well, maybe even if you're not rifling while you're listening to this that's fine
But you are very strong and you don't know it. You don't know it because you know
If you haven't been presented with that idea or the concept that strength isn't in physical
Uh, like brute, uh, not brutish ability, but physical physical strength
Then how are you gonna know that you're like this strong until you've been told that you don't know any better until someone goes
Hey, numb nuts
Wake up my goodness. Look at everything you've achieved. Look how far you've come
Like how many days can you remember where you were like my goodness? I just want to give up
I don't want to get up out in bed anymore. I don't want to do this
And yet here you are
fucking crushing it
and like
My god, what a blessing what a life like I don't believe in religion
But if you do what a blessing like hey like talos his blesses, you know
Hey
Came here after watching emmy vaude cuz youtube nuked it did not expect the motivation
I'm so sorry. I didn't mean it to come across like that
um
Yeah, you made me more confidence be myself. Yes. I hope so don't don't
Don't knock yourself because yeah
Talos the one true God. Yeah
When talos is a god in skyrim before anyone thinks i'm disinonia nah talos is from skyrim
and
He is for nordic
um
Nordic people um, oh that sounded weird when I said that didn't mean it like that but yeah
I still have days like that, but knowing how strong I am is like knowing the sun will come back. Yes
Just because the sun is hiding behind the clouds right now
Doesn't mean you will never feel the warmth of it on your face ever again
The sun will hug you
The sun will embrace you like the six
Um even on the cloudiest of days the sun is always
Shaming even if you can't see it or feel it's warm. This is true
Hey, these are facts. Yes, but straight facts
You need to make a motivational speech and we'll all jump before asking
Hi
Oh, that's so cute. Can you just feel the sun? Oh, are you are you ready for this?
Speaking of the sun
Oh wait, hold on. I've done it wrong
Mm-hmm
It's a bit wonky
So please don't take my refling away, but if you're not a refill and that's fine
I
Have a music box that does you are my sunshine. Did I not send away those recruits?
No matter how
Oh, hold on. I want to read that one. No matter how shit my life will and can give me knowing that I can be really fucking funny and awesome streamer
I will eat like what wait did I have to come to completely misread that message?
I'm so sorry. I bitchered your message and I can't scroll back and chat or it breaks my stream
Sorry, I'm sorry if you get me. So I'm really wholesome to read. I apologize
Uh
I can only think of LeBron
Hey LeBron
LeBron
Yeah, play sunshine on a ukulele
Wait, no more motivation on this. Let's let's get into the the meat of this game. Okay. We're making money. We're playing
Landlord simulators everyone away
79% surely they're not gonna get in trouble for that
Mark my words. Shawnee will become the strongest the most wholesome feature brah
Oracle of the view flings lego
My shells shame. Yes. My shells are reflect. They like move about they're like parallelism
I think you should burp if you want to make us forget the crying and wholesome speech. Uh, I would need to call it for that
But
How much money have I got we need to invest in the black?
No, we need to invest in the bank because the bank might have investment money in it
Give a burp any burpers
You know, I didn't think Vsucky would be in most here
Okay, you're done
Look
At least some of you could appreciate the naming angle I went with because there was like the
Because there was succubus blood running around
Okay
So at least some of you saw the vision. Okay
Oh, we made 13k we can definitely invest that money
I
Made google start playing you are my sunshine
Hey, Alexa
Play you are my sunshine
Please
I don't have that by the way before
I'm not I'm talking to you're Alexa. I don't have an Alexa
heehee
It makes me curious about the MGE knowledge within VLR
What's MGE you must tell me and I will tell you what I know
Because I don't mind questions at all. Whoo 75 percent of this district
Has been renovated. We're getting there. We're getting there. I think there was a blacksmith up the staircase somewhere
A little bit further away, but yeah, that's fine got horses in that dinner
The monster girl encyclopedia it depends
To what degree you mean. Do you mean like I know what a slime girl is or this type of girl is then yes most likely
But if you want me to get like super specific and be like did you did you did it? No
Um why are you wanting a gen 2 to be someone out of that if you say slime girl
As much as slime girl is beautiful in nature and in design
For a vichy bar
It does not make
It does not make me sprung um
Which is terrible
Oh the series. Oh, no, I don't know the series of monster girl. No, no, sorry. I misunderstood the
The uh explanation. No, I do not know monster girl series. I apologize
I went to sleep and you were streaming and I woke up and you're still streaming. Hell yeah
Uh, we're actually gonna do 12 hours. So t minus
Two and a half hours. Uh mersey modest
My gen mate is live right now on killer seven. Please do not hesitate to check her out
I am an endurance streamer. So I am going to be online for a very long time
We have officially finished the campaign section of assassin's creed brotherhood
We are currently going around renovating all buildings that we can at the moment and then we are likely to either do
The layer of Romulus
First due to its easy nature in comparison to Leonardo's
Missions, we are not going to do Leonardo's. I think we might run out of time for Leonardo's mission
I want to say I think we will run out of time. Um
I will
Uh go for as long as I can though. Uh, I might call a water
Cola pee pee break and I am going to order some delivery food. Um, I'm not sure what I should order though
I want to say right. Okay. So I've had mcdonald's in america and I've had mcdonald's in scotland
I've had mcdonald's in australia
Do you want to know which country's mcdonald's makes my ass blow out?
Australia
Not america
I don't know what is with australian mcdonald's
um
But for some reason it destroys
my
intestines
They genuinely cannot handle
A maca's. I don't know if it's because they don't change the oil maybe. Um
Not beating the change of the oil accusations, but it's very plausible because yeah
Hungry jack possibly I've never had a problem with hungry jack with my tummy
um
Hungry jack is burger king in australia
Uh, yeah, like I have no desire for maca's here
Because of that fact. So honestly, thank you
Australia maca's because I don't really consume your your foods
Mm-hmm
We are at 8 000 florans. We're gonna weave it weave it low. Actually, I need to send those
Assassins on a mission because they should not be sitting in my bar right now
I'm gonna do uh an arrow storm because you have to do 15 arrow storms 12 12 tailors renovated
I did an arrow storm and for some reason it didn't hurt him
No
I'm really happy. I found you. I think you're one for all and you're 100% my oh shit is
Ah
It's not that I don't believe your words. It's not that I don't believe your words
You cheeky man. It's just
Out of all
streamers
You mean me
It's why
I will take your word for it and I will exchange for your words
my gratitude
for being open to a new
person's content because
it is very natural to
Um, find someone you enjoy and not deviate from them. So the fact that you were willing to
Maybe deviate from who you consume. I appreciate that and I
Exchange my gratitudes and I'm very thankful you gave me a chance and I am glad I
Even in my own way
Like I don't feel pressured in the stream to like perform to do anything to to crack these jokes to do this to do that
Like I am so glad I can just be myself and you're like, yeah
Yeah
I'm like, yeah, and you're like, yeah
And I'm like, yeah, yeah
And you're like, yeah
I'm like, oh
Okay
Feels good man. It feels really good, man
It's like, yeah, yeah, but yeah, yeah
Um
Righty who we do have a viewpoint down in this district and a few missing buildings
I might go get a cola just to energize me and quickly order some
Take away
um
We can have a little nibble very quickly and then we can explore
The uh, I'm actually gonna poison these guards. That sounds terrible, but
um, and
Actually that reminds me why haven't I got the court is on sorry. I'm getting sorry. I'm getting I'm getting hit on purpose
I'm not just playing bad like that. I thought there was a court is on poison five guards. Is it poison 15 guards?
Maybe it's poison 15 guards
So it's scheduled successfully ruined. I still don't know if she can feel her. I've been my new obsession. Oh, I'm so glad
Thank you
Uh, I've been around too many people who made me feel like fresh
sorry
Of words are hard. I've been around too many people who made me feel that
Pressuring myself was normal. So nice to see people your mindset. Just be genuine
Literally I'm gonna cough um
Yeah, excuse me. Uh, I'm actually pretty low on water. So I will need to call a break very shortly
Um
Yeah, um
Yeah, definitely like
Is it weird to say like autism friendly streamer?
Oh, we've got a nice bit of money with that. Uh, what we are we are level eight
Oh, we've got our first level eight assassin, which is fantastic
Uh
Yeah, okay, uh, we might be able to do a first five star mission
Nah
No, maybe send away you two to get promotion send away
You three or you you three to get a promotion
a level four with a seven a five and uh three good good good good good good good
And we'll do two level three missions and we'll should be back in the money
Okay
I am going to go get a water and a cola. Um, and a
Little pass
Probably um, I had a I've already had three cups of tea. So I think that's been done for tea for the day
I was like cling my teacup
um
But yes, I'll be three minutes
I highly recommend that you get up and stretch your little legs
Um, get a little stretch go to the toilet get any more hydration you may need
Um, I do have a bit of a different
Conclusion to the end of this stream because I got a unique marshmallow. Um
But I'll talk about when I get back. It's nothing bad. Please don't panic. Absolutely nothing bad
No one's done anything
Uh, but I would like to talk about it and we will try our best to help each other out as we do
Um
Okay, I will do the thing
I always do it where I'm actually going to claim up so a thief doesn't take any of my money
Because I would like to keep my money so I can keep renovating buildings and all that
Uh, so I will give you this beautiful sight of roma
Look, there's a look that man down there serenading that lady by the cat pole
I will give you this beautiful view. Oh, you can't see it. Sorry. Maybe you can see it now
I was probably covering it up with my bf. Hey
Okay, I will give you this beautiful sight of roma
Hey, I'll mute. I'll be roughly three minutes. Uh, please do get up and stretch get some water in here
Hey, if you need some more some drinks, maybe some snacks
Uh, there's still another t-minus two hours to the stream
um, and
Merci modista live right now if you want to get in on the action her link is in my description
And you can check around
Okay, I'll be back and three minutes roughly. Uh, let me do do the old close my eyes before I uh
Walk away type thing ready
Okay, there we go
You
Oh
You've been enjoying the background music of this game. It's goaded
It's goaded up all the time
Uh, it looks like we got one recruit back so far
We do have 10k. That's good money
I have water and I have a can of cola got better better fizzy juice
But if it's a juice for me, it's probably the worst thing I could do for my throat right now, but
Honestly, honestly
Does it even matter?
Like I can already feel I have nodules in my throat who cares it's too late. Leave me behind
Mmm, we do have very high. Okay. Yeah, levelly. He can just absolutely beast that
All right, let's go on business. What's your opinion on iron brew?
Did you know the most popular fizzy juice sold worldwide is cola?
except
For in scotland the only country where the number one sold fizzy juice is iron brew
And I do like iron brew. It's very good
Um, vim too is also very good if you have a uh, we're going this way. I remember now. Um
If you have fish and chips, vim too is very good for cutting the grease like
Sprite as well. It helps to cut the grease of your takeaway
Never had iron brew, but I want it
Um, if you are in australia, you can go to your willies
And they actually sell it in the british section
Unbelievably, it's at a premium rate, but make sure you refrigerate it iron brew should never be consumed at room temperature
Please do not do that to yourself and please understand. It is an acquired taste
But children of scotland were basically raised on neon orange
drink
So, yeah
Um
What does it taste like so iron brew themselves have said it's supposed to taste like ginger and bubblegum
It absolutely does not at all
taste like that i'm actually going to hire these because I need to do
distract
Um, it does not taste like this at all
I don't even I could not tell you anything remotely what it tastes like other than battery acid
Yeah, if you've ever smelled battery acid
Uh, that's what iron brew tastes like but like not bad
battery acid
You're still alive
Yes, sorry
We have finished the main campaign. We are currently renovating all of roma
We've started our serious landlord enterprise. It's going pretty well if I do say so myself
and
Willy Wonker and iron brew no
So basically mountain dew um
I did get an opportunity to taste mountain dew
I
Honestly wouldn't fault you. Yeah, I would say that's probably the closest ever
Taste you would get to iron brew, but it is still different. What are you mining?
Play minecraft out here
He's tilling the soil with a pickaxe. You're supposed to use a hole for tilling soil
Wait, are you beating the whole game? Uh, I have already done the campaign
Uh, like which means the story like chesery has been perished to fate itself because no man can murder me
We are now going through the map and renovate renovate and combine all the buildings
And then next we're going to do the layers of romulus which are these little wolf marks here
And if we have time we will do the leonardo missions
And the catarina missions and the auditory family missions
We are going to stop at the 12 hour mark very sadly
Not because I don't actually want to stream more
But because vods for some reason freak out
After the 12 hour mark and it is such a shame because if it didn't I think I could confidently
Finish all the mission
Which is a shame
Because definitely could do it if it wasn't for the
BOD issues so uh mercy is live right now. I am t-minus two hours
um
Start a new stream easy peasy
I am tempted however, um, there is a yumi plus member waiting on my side of an ace marco lab
And I don't want to leave her waiting. I also have to contact dempo fish
about the ace marco lab
Um, and I really don't want anyone to think I am taking their kindness and their time for granted
because on top of streaming
If someone comes to you asking for an ace marco lab and you do this and you do that like these girls are so hard working
and
I know some people might find streaming looks very easy on the surface
but people have lives and they have things going on and they have ailments and
They have family issues
They have they might even not even be able to stream as much as they like due to their living situation like
I just want to respect the time that I ask and
Give the girls like these ace marco labs like get it all sorted out and
Because if they've been kind enough to give me the time of day, I want to completely wholeheartedly respect that. Um
So hopefully tomorrow
um
Before I stream uh yumi will have a collab of me and her on her channel
If all goes well, sadly the ace mar
Memes for all violour members is paused right now until I know what's going on with monetization
and culling because
um
The memes are quite fun
But the nature of them depending on how mean youtube want to be recently with ace mar. It's quite uh nerve wracking
at the moment
Talking about ace mar. Did you give any of the girls advice for their first ace mar streams? Um only one girl
uh came to me for
Advice
I don't think she'd be embarrassed if I said um
Lovely azura has never
So she's she's never made ace mar herself. However, she has consumed the content
um
But because she's a yapper
She's like I can't really focus and know what to say
So I gave her a very small page of prompts that she can say just to help her out
So please do enjoy her ace mar stream when she does it to the full extent
um
Because she's just very lovely. Um, I think she's just a wee bit
Unconfident, but I am sure with the love she gets from
Her bleeding hearts. I don't know if bleeding hearts is getting changed
But the love that you guys will show will instill
The confidence that I know she will have one day
And you know doing this and uh, yeah, as I said, I've got faith in it
Gonna have to try and someplace around here that sells. I'm bro. My interest has me peaked
Willys
Willys go to the british section or the indian section at willys. I kid you not. They're at the same section
Um
We'll take great care of mama as yes
Um, she is very caring naturally like I kid you not like it's not a role play
Like she is very caring naturally
um
And as her confidence grows, I think it'll very it will come across
Um, and I'm just very excited to watch her blossom as a streamer because
She she's just
She's being propelled
Not into a new world. She has had very
Long history of streaming, but she's definitely been propelled. I think is the fair word to say and um
You know, she's trying out new things and I'm I'm absolutely I'm all for I I hope um, she feels
Able to reach out to me as I said with all the girls they have reached out to me at one point
And you know, I advise the best I can but the true fact of the day is all the girls have more streaming experience than me
so
There's like only
So much value to my words
and it's like
my darlin
My darlin, I love you, but I can't give you advice on this because the fact of the matter is you're more experienced than me
And like it's okay to experiment. It's okay to find figure things out. Um, it's okay to do these things
Um, I think we've fully renovated everything but this missed aqueduct possibly uh other than the
Location so I think we'll actually do a layer of romuli. Uh, there's one down here. So we'll do this one first
My darlin. Yes, like I'm kind of like my darlin
There is a point, uh, which pains me to admit but
There's a point where I'm of no use to you
Um, there's only so much my knowledge so far goes
Like I definitely have knowledge of the ASMR side of things audio roleplay side of things
But stream advice
Uh, my stream advice is I've just done what I want and it worked out
And the truth of that fact is that is not how it works for everyone
And it's just not possible and it is not responsible either for me to give streaming advice
like that
Knowing full well, that's not how it works for everyone and I think it's um
Um, I think it's perfectly okay to admit um
I'm sorry, but I'm not knowledgeable enough. I can come up with fun stream ideas. I can come up with fun collab ideas
I can come up with fun event ideas
But to actually sit on stream
I'm not the streamer. You're the streamer
You know
And uh, I have full faith
They will do make they will do nothing
Less than make me proud. Do nothing but make me proud. Yeah, do nothing but make me proud
Um, not that it's their responsibility to prove themselves to me
Because they proved themselves to me long ago. I saw myself in them and uh
Different ways for me. I saw the shitposting side of me for she be I saw the side of me that
Literally just needed a hand up. That's all I needed. She be as fully stacked to go. She just needed a hand up
Um, Azura just needed a chance. Um
mercedes
Determination that her unending unending stamina
um
And I say her experience to hone her craft like I see
myself in these little
little
parts
Which made it so easy
to relate to the girls to have trust in the girls to have faith in the girls and
um
That's just the fact of the matter
And all of them have so much potential and I really hope that viola gives them
that opportunity
to
Bring themselves to the next level and achieve what their dreams are
When it comes to being a content creator a streamer oopsies ran off the wall. Um
And yeah
That's that's just me
I'm just so happy. Uh, yes, this looks like I'm going around in circles
It's part of the map. Um, so this is before yellow paint is a thing
Uh, because Assassin's Creed use torches for these parts of the chambers if you go the wrong way
Then you're just going to get money
Which is fine if you want to collect boxes. There are flags as well, but we're not doing the flags just yet
We're doing that tomorrow
But for now
Did I need to go that way?
Mom me what scrawny sounds like a mom gasping up her kids
honestly though
Like I didn't really know what to expect them to like call me and stuff and they all call me mom
Which I adore um
And they're all like, oh, I love you scrawny and I'm like, oh
We're passing around the L word and I'm like, oh because like I didn't want to be the first one to say that
But like
I love you too. Like my god
thank you for like
believing in me and seeing the goal and and believing in yourself to like reach out and grab it
um, if you've ever kind of looked around on vtuber applications like applications open now
the most common tweet under these things is
Like I am not confident enough to go out and reach for this and it is such
a shame
Because truly it is you miss a hundred percent of the things you don't go for and like it's just
I almost fell down. Um
it's just like such a shame
but
like good on the girls for reaching out and basically letting me grab their hand like thank you for
letting me do that for you. Um
type thing
Like thank you for enabling yourself to enable me. It's what I'm trying to say
I like your stamina. I wasn't expecting it. You should see me in the bedroom. Sorry. I was just
I'm sorry. I apologize
She's still streaming. Yes or e
Finish the campaign. We're now doing layers of Romulus which unblocks the special armor
Sorry, it was too easy. It was too easy. You made it so easy
I just checked
Oh
Opsies, I just realized this is not a jump down and I realized the second I launched at that skeleton
You can
Drop and grab at these sections
I really do not like dropping and grabbing because it's kind of hard to judge where you're to go next
um
However
The camera does assist you mildly
And it's a bit of a really do you have to do it like that? But yeah
Yeah
Aren't you a quick show though?
You shut the hell up
You freaking freaks
I tell you that in confidence and you throw it on my face
I'm trying to remember which one this is again
Just follow the light if you ever get confused at the section of the game
Uh the game when you're in catacomb like levels the game will unironically light the way to tell you where to go
Again, we're getting teased by that flag, but we don't why did you not grab that?
Is anyone supposed to go there?
Am I not supposed to go there? No, I'm supposed to go there. It's you. You're teasing me
Such a naughty naughty. It's you grab the ledge. Yeah, so you were supposed to grab it
I've never played assassin you bought games, but haven't played them
Hey, it's all
Um, maybe you work a lot and you think the game looks good and then you say to yourself
I'll play it when I'm not tired, but then after work you're like man. I'm exhausted
I don't really feel like playing a new game
And then you feel like playing games that you're familiar with and that is the power of nostalgia
Very powerful drug
And that is why media today is regurgitated a lot
Because of the power of nostalgia unironically, that's why they have Beal just who coming out
It's really interesting learning about marketing trends as well
Hmm, maybe we could do a business
Analysing stream. I wouldn't mind yapping about that. I wouldn't mind yapping about biology as well. Um
I wanted to test an
Educational stream
um
I thought we could do a
Full stream day
And it's like literally like a full day at school again
and
Because I would be like, okay, we're doing English and then we're gonna like
And like I'm gonna wait unironically. I'm gonna ask questions and I'm gonna wait until someone gets it right
Who the heck just rated it in me
Rhea, how dare you Rhea? Hi Rhea. How was your stream? Hopefully I'm saying your name right. I apologize
But hi
How was your stream with a heck where you's dating?
I'm so sorry to uh raise uh viewers. I am Scottish. I apologize if you can't understand me so well
But hi raiders. Welcome in. We are playing Assassin's Creed brotherhood and
Jot invasion jot jet oat
Is that how you say it?
Uh any joters? Well, hello joters and you come
Um, what were you playing or were you yapping? Were you speaking Japanese on on stream?
Although you're probably exhausted after stream to be honest, you're like, please strongy. Don't ask me any questions. I'm exhausted
That's fair. That's fair
Uh, we are playing uh, Assassin's Creed brotherhood
Uh, and we're doing the catacombs which have been lighted lighted the path that they have been lit
Um, and it tells us where to go
Strongies 365 so in Scottish, but it's actually
Yeah
Um, but yes, thank you so much for reading to me. I appreciate that. Please relax and rest well after stream
Uh, you've done a fantastic job pat yourself on the back
And for the jokes, uh, my name is strongy culls. I am part of valour
Umie plus were absolutely
Lovely and did a watch along of our debuts. We are incredible new
Um, and I am strongy the scottish cuttlefish. I am an endurance streamer and today we are playing
Assassin's Creed brotherhood. We have completed the storyline the main quest line the campaign
Uh, and we are currently doing what's known as the lair of romulus
I just got stabbed if you saw that by throwing now
Uh, um, unfortunately the camera angles are a bit
However, uh, the games have held up quite well to the test of time because Assassin's Creed brotherhood was developed in
no
was released in
um, and
um
It's a childhood game of mine. So I'm very happy to play it for a very long time. I'm just waiting for the sky to attack me
Apologies get a little distracted there
Okay, he just fell to his death
Hey, yeah
So development most likely was 2007, which is crazy to think about
Although it might have been on the back of
Assassin's Creed 2. I would 100% believe it was off the back of Assassin's Creed 2
Um, all things considered because brotherhood
Definitely. Oh, I'm tamed
I just I have seven seconds to complete the memory. Yeah. Good luck with that. We'll be replaying this one
I didn't realize I got tamed on the other ones as well
Filling me. Okay. Well, he just dodged that
Uh, can you maybe attack him? Gee, Louise
Oh my god, that was brutal. I just took his weapon from him and then uh ended him with that weapon
Rather brutal, but I'll take it
Restart time
We will rock you
Do
None of you are a big boy
You got mud on your face. Yeah, wait
No, I was so close to being the tame. I didn't know I was deli dalyan
I was deli dalyan so I didn't get 100% I can't believe it. I can't believe yapping has cost me 100%
Oh, no, it results in me having to stream more. Oh, what a punishment
We actually will open the chest because we're a bit low on funds
Yeah, I saw you at the beginning last night and now in the morning you're still here. Good job. Thank you
We finished the campaign
Doing layers of romuli. We're going to unlock the special armor in this game
Uh, not much treasures in these chests
So close and yet so far such a fake assassin's creed. I know I'm actually an assassin's creed fake fanboy
Oh, I can't believe it
I can't believe I missed that by a ball here
So say you missed something very closely in scots you say by a ball here
Which means exactly what you think it is by a ball here because of how short they are
So I missed it by a ball here
Angie, Angie, take a sip. Please remember to hydrate
Wow
That cola is chris b is exactly what one I wanted my good morning burp so bad on his floor
Imagine burping me after every time like
Like patting my back. Wait, where the heck are we? We didn't start in here
No, we were down here and now we're here. Okay. Are we closer to another layer?
That is where we get the treasure
There's one to the east. Okay. We will head east
Never eat shredded wheat is how you remember your north east south west
I won't lie. I've been studying a wikipedia list of scottish slang
Oh, there's so much but a lot of scottish slang isn't
used
So you might be studying
Too hard for the test that doesn't exist yet
But I do appreciate it
Uh, I do apologize for those of you whose english is not your first language
I can be a bit mumbly and hard to understand but I do try my best to enunciate words on stream
Just because my natural speaking voice
I kind of sound more like this and a bit more monotone
And it's no that i'm no interested or i'm disinterested but
I just kind of sound a bit more like this and it doesn't really sound that exciting
But it's not because i'm not having a good time
It's because i'm a mumbly
Bampot and I know i'm a mumbly bampot
So i'm undoing that treat
On the music the music is going to do the
Glorious soundtrack glorious soundtrack
I cannot recall of sassans 3 2
Uh, it's you it's the lever
Is it is it being pulled?
Okay
rude it's you
I'm going to scotland later this year. You're gonna look for nessie. Are you gonna lock lomond? If you guys didn't know
Nessie lives in lock lomond
And it's totally not
Uh, a capitalist ploy to get you to visit that location and support the
Piring a boat and buying drinks at that location. It's not a ploy
Nessie is real
and
Spend your hard-earned tourist money on us. Thank you
Three week round trip. That's so good
Blockness monster lives in lock lomond. Yes
Oh
Is this one? Okay. Okay. This one isn't bad
Thankfully, there's no timer. We just have to not perish
Can you swim with nessie as a weak cut off fish?
Nessie was friendly
Um, nessie means no harm lower wise
um
And as long as you are good and don't pollute
Nessie couldn't give a hoot. Oh my god. That's the new motto. Thank you
Tourism scotland. I have you a new motto as long as you're good and don't
I've already forgotten it. What did I just say? What did I can you guys help me for meant for what I just said?
If you're good and don't
letter
Nessie will like you
Put put and I didn't even know it. Let's have already forgot I forgot
I think there's a flag behind me. It's right behind me, isn't it?
I knew it. I knew it. I remembered
If you're good and don't pollute now nessie will like you
Uh, there's nessie won't give a hoot. I'm so sorry. Wait. Is this not where I'm supposed to go?
Oh this
Wait
I just came from here
Am I not
Ah, I understand. I understand. There's a way this way. I could not see it. I could not see with my eyeballs
If you're cute and don't pollute nessie won't give a hoot. Yes. Nessie is cake. Nessie's not me
Okay, we did it. Yeah
Now these leaps look very big. That's because they are you have to hold grab while you do these leaps or it's you will not grab on
Oh
slow motion
Nessie everyone nessie is ugly people. Wow. Wow. Wow. This is news to me
That was crazy just coming out with that. Oh, there's a flag
I
Don't know how to get up there though. We'll do it later for now. We are just going to finish them
and then
Is that how I get up over there? No
Oh, I jumped from there. Right. How do I get up on you? Did I claim your hands?
Thank you for letting me claim your hands
I'm actually going to grab this right now because we might be able to get all of them from this level since there's no timer
Good catch. It's a very good catch
You have to be cute and not pollute. Oh, I get it now. I'm sorry
What's that? I already forgot me
Am I supposed to jump over there?
Ah, okay. Oh, okay. It was that way. I did. It did not look like I had to jump that way, but I guess I did
It's nice that I can continue watching you from the stream last night. Heck. Whoa. I thought I was about to go up there
I'm not gonna lie. I felt the gate brush against my butt. That's how close it was. My goodness. I was very nervous
Oh oopsies
Are you still no pan all this time? I'm so sorry. I don't know what that means
I apologize
Please may you give definition and re-ask the question kindly. Thank you. I appreciate it
Uh, right
No, panty. Oh
Yeah, I never put any more clothes on I don't need to
I almost jumped in there
Yeah, I don't really like I'm gonna say something are a little gross
But I don't go outside much. So, you know how like all the girls did those like smelly things
I was gonna do like what my smelly thing is and it's like deodorant optional basically because I don't go outside much
Which is kind of gross but I mean
If you want the truth
You can't handle the truth
Wait, we must just go up or in no in. Okay. No up
Is there a hidden thing back here? I keep thinking they're hating like a flag back. Oh, sorry. I wasn't paying attention
I apologize to that startled anyone. Bye bad
She's just like the cuttlefish mask. I'm sorry
I just like if I need to go out
Then like for example, I need to go buy those
Sweets. Whoa, I see. Oh, no, it's just the box. I thought it was a flag
Um, like I need to go buy those sweets. So I will get a shower and like I'll
Put deodorant on and wash my hair like I don't go out greasy or anything, but uh
I'm gonna be honest
Uh, Merrow. Oh, thank you for writing into me
Uh, we're how is stream Merrow? How'd it go? Did you enjoy it? Did you like it?
What were yous up to?
Unless you're tired, you don't have to answer any of these questions and please rest up because you've had a fantastic stream
You probably yapped your head off more than enough for one day. So please don't
Feel like you have to stick around. I I send you away
I send you away. You do not have to talk. I know some people feel obligated to talk to the streamer
Like that they've just rated it into please do not you're probably very tired and you have had a fantastic stream and a
I did your nails
I didn't do your nails. You did your nails. I read that wrong. I did not do her nails
I oh, that's adorable. I hope you have fun too. Yeah, we assassin three brother and up in here
Uh, did you have cute nails cute nail check?
I'm sure they're I am sure they are adorable. Thank you very kindly for uh re directing into me
And I can't wait to talk to you in dms for my super secret project that involves you
Please rest well and thank you for all your hard work on your stream
Is there a why starting so cute you stop that you start you're gonna make me blush you're gonna make me blush
We are for anyone who has just joined in I will do a quick recap. We are playing the greatest
And undeniably the best game of all time assassin's creed brother hood
We have successfully in our 10 hour stream
Have endeavored to
Complete campaign mode
We have also bought all renovations bar any tourist stick
Locations because of the price
We ran out of money. Um, so we are now doing the layer of romulus which unlocks the special armor in the game
Now this game came out in 2010
And it has done very well. Um, it has done fantastic
You're all breathtaking. No you
Uh, we are going to climb over here very carefully
We do have a bit of scary parkour so
For anyone who does not like heights sadly this section gets even worse than this bit
So if you suffer from any, uh
You know, uh, how is it vertical when height makes you go woozy?
Uh, not recommended that you watch this section
Have you ever you are oh no, is mercy still online?
Yeah, I think mercy's still online
Did you have a good stream today azerah?
I very sadly didn't get a chance to
uh
Watch any of it. Um, because I was too busy
Uh, well, I was too busy is not the right terminology. I apologize
I was streaming at the same time, but I did chat will vouch for me my little reeflings
I did tell them
To please enjoy your stream at will because I am an endurance streamer, and I'm glad you played the game too
Yeah, well, you're all know your game crashed
Do I need to teach you the in-video?
framerate
Uh, little thingy my bobber. I wonder why you crashed
Hmm that pc. Hmm. I'm wondering
Naughty pc we give it a few spanks for being naughty
I can't wait for azerah ASMR. Thankfully, uh, I'm pretty sure I can vouch for your pc azerah and say it's not going to explode
Uh, when you do ASMR because it's just you and the microphone
Um
We can give you white noise plugins as well if you would like to use that or if you want to just
ASMR stream is ASMR up to me. I wish I was that pc right now for a throw
We had fun chan. Oh, did you end up doing that too talking stream?
Where do I go from here down? Oh looks like I go down
Oh, did the gate open? Sorry. I'm too busy yapping the gate. Yeah, okay. That's swung open. Look at that
Oh, it's even got the sound effects. You know, this area is given Elden Ring. I said it
What do you mean that any sort of medieval esk type build is like Elden Ring?
I can't believe it the Elden Ring allegations
No, what was it?
What was the meme game where everyone was like this game's just like oh dark souls
That's it. This game's just like the did it is it of dark souls this game's like the did it did it of dark
I almost jumped down. Oh, thank god. I saw the ladder anyway
Yeah, I just talked afterwards. So it was yappy. Oh, that's good
Yes
Okay, we have collected the third scroll of Romulus only three more to go even though that says number five
So I'm doing it in the wrong order. I didn't know there was an order. I apologize
I thought the game kind of automatically like gave you this number that number
I'm not going to bother with the treasure chest because it was just so little
Wow
Have a little separatism
Gamers will see a Scottish castle and be like dark souls in real life. Can I tell you the dumbest thing ever?
One man wreck in Korea. That's a good thing
um
Was it modern warfare had a map based in scotland like that castle map?
In my dumb ass played it and I was like, this is so weird. This map feels so Scottish
and it was based after scotland and
Yeah, it didn't click until like after I looked it up
But I was like this feels so weird. It feels so Scottish. Why like why would they do that?
And I was like, oh, it's because it's based after gotland and castle and stuff. Yeah
Not very smart am I but yeah, I didn't I couldn't name the map out. I'd know it wasn't a black ops map
Because I pretty much know all the black ops map names, which is really sad
But is it sad if you enjoyed yourself? Is it sad? Oh, wow the bank has 31,000 in it
Hmm
Where's this Romulae? Is there a bank before it?
Ah, there isn't a bank right? We'll go back and pick up our money and then
we'll go
He'd been college at ghost plausible. I did play ghost
Very plausible. I shan't deny
I'll send my assassins away again because there's no point in having the assassins hanging around
When they could go be making like money and XP have we got another level eight? Yes, we do
We've got two three level eight four level eight. So that's fantastic. Okay. The assassins are definitely
getting very
potent now. They are getting very
Deadly which I'm quite happy with
Stonehaven that sounds like it
Yeah, me be me
Very dumb and be like, hmm. You feel you feel so familiar. I wonder why I just can't I just can't put my tongue on my
Uh, brain on why it feels so familiar
I'm a dumb dumb, but that's okay
I'm allowed to be a dumb dumb
Dum dum you give me gum gum
Oh, we're gonna watch night at the museum. I've not seen it since a child
So I'm gonna be laughing my buttocks off. I think watching that maybe
Maybe they do
Man no problem
Yeah, the map was every sniper heaven at heaven
On sniper heaven. Yeah
Wait, no, I need the money out of the bank. Goodness me. I'm getting distracted
silly silly
I learned once and I learned only recently that night at the museum had sequels
I don't
No, if I remember sequels
Hmm
Uh, hello horsey
All right, let's grab this horse and we'll go for a midnight stroll on our little horsey
And giddy up little I don't know what I would name a horse if I would one
Uh, what do horses do?
They gallop, let's go mr. Gallop giddy up giddy up bullseye
Look at the speed of you you're such a
And we've gone the wrong way, but that's okay because that was me that gated you there. So that's my bad. I apologize bullseye
Little little little
Oh, you're going so fast speedy Gonzales
I would name a horse Gerald
Gerald
Horsey make horse face true. Are you a winning son? Absolutely
I never lost yet I say that as I have like
De-synchronized a couple of times now and done like 50 percent passing on missions instead of 100 percent synchronicity
Where is it is it in here?
No, it's just really awkward one. Um, wait, what?
Is
This this one I remember from childhood and there's a like invisible ledge. Yes
Uh
Oh wait, I'm a dumb dumb. I thought the water was a lot higher
You you didn't see that you didn't see me try to figure out how to get in water
My pardon you're pardon. I beg
Yummy, amicola. I probably have some water too actually
Oh, what's this one do not lose more than 10 health squares they jumping me
Because if I'm losing health squares is a thing
Uh, I'm gonna need to be on my best behavior if I want a hundred percent this one and want to go
They obey
Bene, Bene, Molto Ben
Followers of Romulus or Ujiparis. Oh my goodness. There's snowberries
He he he I'm teasing I'm teasing I'm teasing and buzz-squeezing
I'm num, num, num, touch my body. I mean girls. Oh, that's not the words
This is the part where the rat breaks down. No one moves. No one makes a sound
Back from reality. They go grab it
I
Hate I hate tailing missions when they can attack me. I'm so sorry. I get so stressed
Yes, yes, yes Romulus commands the death of xy wild atory. Good luck for that mate
Get your wee knife out
And then wait for them to attack you
And then just chain attack whoever goes up
White is going to attack you next
You can lock on to them first, or you can counter as they do it.
No hit.
Yes, okay, I understand now why the 100% was don't lose health squares, because these are a lot.
Just wait for them to attack, and then counter, and then just go for it.
And then we need to run because it's a chase mission.
Well how do I do it? I'm just going for it.
Oh that was lucky I even hit that.
Please don't hurt me. I would like to get this 100%, so I don't have to play this one next.
Oh, he injured me. Oh they're jumping me, there's somebody.
Stop it, stop it, stop it.
stop stop stop.
Please.
But how do clips work on YouTube?
So if you clicked me, I can see what you clipped and then send it to an editor.
Basically.
There was the possibility of submitting clips on the Discord.
But then people would have to have speed peaking permissions.
Woo!
Oh, I'm not ready.
Oh, they're jumping me!
Oh, that was like insane reaction.
I just select the attack option in order to counter that.
Oh, I had a little mini heart, right?
I struggle with this area to know where to go next.
I assume this little lamp is telling.
Yeah, okay.
This little light of mine.
I'm going to let it show.
Please don't leave my health bars.
I'm jumping them.
I'm just, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, you can't see me?
I can see.
Can you get your gun out?
Oh, I can see you.
Get wrecked.
Right, where am I going?
Actually, let me get my wee knife out again.
If it's all going to be wolves, there's
no point in no having.
I'm just going to get this real quick.
Don't mind anybody.
You're still going strong, eh?
Yes, sir.
Oh, there, hey, see that flag?
We're going to get it.
I'm getting up for the head of the event.
I wish you could climb in this little hole, but you can.
Pardon me, I'm sorry.
For being so rude, it wasn't me, it wasn't my food.
I say that as I've happened.
Right, remit.
Jesus, did not let me select a small knife there.
Wait for them to attack, and boom.
You just can't attack.
Boom, boom, oh, I'm getting, oh, they're jumping up.
And then boom.
And yeah, they're guarding.
That's fine.
We are going to do crossbow bolts.
Until they get too close, my goodness,
they get close fast.
Yeah, OK, OK.
Well, what are you aiming at, SAO darling?
Darling, they're in front of you.
And I don't want to replay the section
if I can get 100% first time.
Thank you.
Thank you, Etsy.
By the way, are you going to be playing Silent Hill?
I am very sorry for those of you who
might be interested in me playing Silent Hill.
I'm under the impression Silent Hill
are those games where you can't.
Oh, that was really rude, and I don't appreciate that.
Don't do that again.
You've literally just put me in the water,
and now my robes are drenched.
Oh, I really don't want to desync.
I think I still keep 100%, even if I desync,
from trail distance.
Oh, see, that's the problem.
They instantly throw a knife.
Bit of a problem.
My goodness, they are on me.
Oh, that's not good.
I think I'm OK.
Oh, not good, not good, not good, not good, not good, not good.
If you get knocked off, they can just spam throwing knives,
essentially, just like what they're doing right now,
but I think we're OK.
Oh, oh, OK, we're good.
We're good, we're good.
Landed, literally landed in the water.
Oh, goodness me.
Give this to me.
Me, I think we're on this last section
of being able to be vulnerable.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
You're going to have to attack me.
Ah!
OK, that's fine, that's fine, let me cook you.
Oh, see that, that's throwing knife.
I don't know how to counter-throw a knife if you even can.
Like other than, like, move a little to the left,
so Tanzu's ult just moved to the left five head.
I actually don't know if there's a counter-throw.
Would you like to send any more?
Fight me yourself.
It is you who tell the people lies.
Tell them lies.
Give me the code sheet.
All I will give you is death.
Really?
There's 20 dead bodies, and you think you can perish me?
Good luck, mate, good luck.
I'd like to see you try.
Oh, oh, OK, we doing this?
If you're just going to counter me,
you're getting kicked to death.
I ain't tolerating this.
If you won't let me stab stab you,
you're just getting kicked to death.
There is no other option.
I will put you in a circle, I'll
hoof you in the balls until you're dead.
Literally exploded your testes.
I'm sorry to even put that thought in your head.
I apologize.
There is a flag over here.
Do you want to know how to access it?
You go for a little dive, and it's that simple.
Why do I say it's that simple?
I may or may not have got that flag
after crying for 20 minutes.
I'm trying to find it, and I'm pulling my hair out.
I break his chances of ever having children now.
I believe that's all in this room.
I see a climbing thing up here, but I'm not sure.
Oh, that's how you actually progress.
My pardon.
Your pardon, I beg.
You used your cuttlefish powers to dive.
Yeah.
I cast mulch.
I think mulch is still my favorite cast.
I don't know if there's anything that beats it at the moment.
We are now four of six.
We are very close to unlocking the armor.
What are we looking at?
Oh, the clock is ticking for this mod.
I shouldn't have looked at the time.
I'm getting nervous.
I don't want to get too close to the hell forever.
I don't want it to explode in a fire for my vod.
Nice money for doing the side quests.
We're at 49 Florence, so we can probably invest in some,
how you call, tourist attractions.
I can't remember what their official name is.
I think they just get named by what they actually are,
because they are from the Oracle buildings and locations.
I can't remember even.
My cast is still streaming strong, hey, yeah.
So I was like, go to bed.
Oh, don't you worry.
Oh, shit.
That's just inhaled my spit.
Pardon me.
I didn't mean to cough.
OK, Romulai, Romulai, Romulai.
Can I see it?
There's one here.
That's quite far away, though.
Oh, there's one in the Colosseum.
I never saw that.
OK, we're going to do this one up here.
Obviously, your successor is going to still go in.
You never met a girl with such stamina before, huh?
It's a pleasure to be your first.
I can't set the bow.
I wasn't kidding when I said I'm an endurance streamer.
As long as my voice doesn't crack and I lose it,
I'm happy to stream long.
No, obviously, it does depend on the game.
If it's a game I don't like, then, yeah,
definitely do not expect me to be on 12 hours for the game.
But yeah.
What's that supposed to mean?
This is the longest a streamer has lasted for me.
Wait, seriously?
I'm breaking your first-time records?
Will?
I love long streams.
It's so nice.
Ah, I'm glad I can keep you company.
Whether you're at work or you're bing-chinging, don't show
me.
Bing-chinging.
I'm glad I can keep you company.
My record is like a one and a half.
Wait, of someone streaming?
No.
You mean how long you've watched a streamer
when you say that?
I mean, have you ever watched a streamer that's
streamed more than like, what's the average stream time
for a VTuber?
Oh, that would be an interesting statistic.
Average stream time for a VTuber is three hours?
Two hours?
I called in sick to have time to watch streams and catch up
and go, stop.
You're going to get in trouble doing that.
You can't do that.
Don't get yourself in trouble at work.
The votes are always here.
And I plan on streaming for a long time.
My biggest concern, I'm happy to talk about this concern.
My biggest concern with streaming was I wouldn't have
time to stream and technically manage.
But I've managed to get a script manager in place, which
means that my only responsibilities are
streaming for myself and arranging
shorts for the girls to make, like,
Mercy's shorts that have been coming out.
I scripted them and got her to say them.
And I don't know if you enjoyed her blonde one.
Obviously, Mercy couldn't suggest talking
about behind the scenes content.
I gave her the script, she made it.
And then I got someone to edit it type thing.
That's my only responsibility is, like,
organizing clips, basically, that go up in the girls'
channels, because I didn't want them to feel stressed out
dealing with that kind of stuff.
The only problem is I'm facing the issue of clipped parts
of stream turning into shorts.
Because obviously, I don't have time to scrub through
their content in order to find, like, a funny thing.
So when you clip a girl's, one of the girls' streams, on the
account, I can see what people have clipped.
And then I can send that to an editor.
So don't be afraid to clip something you like.
Because on my end, I can see that.
And then I can send it on to an actual creator of the
clips, like, for a short.
Did you see that?
So I can get away with that stuff.
Yeah, that's the only thing.
I think your personal best is back-to-back 12-hour of odds.
Yes.
We're probably going to do it again when the DLC comes out.
I'm not sure if we'll do the Butt-Bump adventure for that
part, though.
I know it.
Wait, what was my 100%?
I wasn't paying.
Not another timed one.
Stinky.
I'm not going to rush it.
I'm just going to go through it, so I know what we're
looking at.
Ooh, I remember this one.
I have desynced DLC, downloadable content.
The video game Elden Ring has official DLC coming out on
June 19, I believe.
And I plan on doing it multiplayer with you guys, so
I will put down marks where, what the heck?
What am I supposed to do?
Unfortunately, I desync a lot in this.
So I apologize if you're expecting perfect gameplay.
It is not possible with me.
I just realized what DLC means.
It's downloadable.
Wait, no.
Downloadable content?
Wait, that's not what DLC means.
Yeah.
OK, it does.
I was like, second guess, because I was like,
demo mode is one word.
But maybe back then, it was two words.
Stop moving around, ya bam.
He just sold spells.
It's been a pleasure, but I finally reached the end of
my endurance.
Not by my choice.
Can't be short on my sleep before work.
Yes, please rest well.
If you guys have work, if you guys have responsibilities,
please do not sacrifice your sleep or your
responsibilities to watch me.
I will be streaming all the hecking time.
And there will be plenty of VOD content to watch.
What?
That was like two seconds.
That was so quick.
That was unbelievably quick.
You know how earlier I quoted and said, this game is so
forgiving?
Wow.
That was like instant red bar pool.
I did not expect that.
I apologize.
I don't know how I was going to make that happen.
First time watching the stream for this long stamina
queen, I kneel, but I have to hit the bed.
Please rest.
Good night to those who sleep.
Goodbye to those who have a few things to do.
And get done.
Yeah.
Don't feel bad that you have to go do your thing.
Whoa, no, my controller died.
Oh, I can't play mouse and keyboard.
Oh, it's not even registered in mouse and keyboard anyway.
I'm going to have to go get my freaking charger.
Wait, is this a charger?
Oh, you spin me right round, baby, right round.
When you go down, when you go down now.
You spin my head round, round, round, round, round.
Is there a charger?
Hold on, I'm going for my cables.
We are going to desync because of distance.
I don't even think I have my charging cable in this dying
room.
Oh, I am so sorry.
I'm going to have to like back out and go quickly,
go get our charging cable.
I'm so sorry, but BRB, I'll be a second.
I can't believe I've played so long and drained my battery.
Oh, no.
Wait, what's that for?
What's that wire for?
Sugar.
Sugar, spice, and everything knife.
My headset is the front panel.
And the second USB port is taken up by the controller.
Hold on, hold on, let me get on my hands and knees.
Can I stop myself?
Can I?
Is there even a port back here?
Hello, is there a free port?
I don't think there's a free port.
Wow.
Um, do I need some light for face tracking?
I don't think so.
Goodness me.
I actually ran out of USB ports.
OK, um, wait, no, I'm very dumb.
I do not need the Bluetooth, the Bluetooth device is connected.
I don't need the Bluetooth bit because I will have the controller
plugged straight into the PC for charging purposes.
Yes, I figured it out.
One second.
Well, I apologize for the unprofessionalism.
However, I fixed the problem.
Thus, I am a trust me, I'm an engineer.
What the heck just happened here?
Because trust me, I'm an engineer.
I'm a very, very smart beat.
Yay.
Oh, have I desynced?
Oh, oh, I desynced because I was out of range.
That was a mistake on my part.
Whoopsie daisy.
OK, we'll try again.
The all the holes are filled.
Hey, yo.
How do you run out of USB ports in this day and age?
Nicola, wait, where am I going?
OK, let's hopefully not desync this time.
Because that was so aggressive, though.
I'm wondering if that should have been patched.
But because it was a layer of Romulus,
like not a lot of playtesters got through this part.
Because it was like the later content, like not main.
So that'd be interesting.
OK.
Got the gold.
I see you.
I'm just an average man with an average life.
Wait, where is it?
Lost him already.
Go in here.
Please don't desync, because that was so fast.
It's giving one thrust is all it took.
Oh, I'm not hiding.
I'm not hiding.
OK, I'm hiding now.
Don't do that again.
You're scaring me.
I think he goes over there.
I'm wondering if I should beat him before he moves.
Like this?
I think he goes through that gate right there, dead ahead.
So I'm.
Oh, no.
Distance.
He's not that far away from me.
I need to get back to work.
Have fun at work.
Please don't worry.
Veal, what's their hard work in?
Heck yeah.
And you know what they get?
Nothing.
I actually feel really bad about that.
Feels bad, man.
Ah!
Ah, that was not fun.
Don't turn around again.
Do I make myself clear?
Yes, ma'am.
OK, easy, easy.
Take it easy, easy, easy, easy.
Bit closer, bit closer, bit closer.
He doesn't know.
Chat, he doesn't know.
So what hurts him?
He doesn't know.
Wait, what he doesn't know doesn't hurt him.
Yeah.
Good night.
Rest well.
All of those who have to go, please sleep well.
Make sure you deliver them convincingly with passion.
My passion.
Hey, hey, doofus, you're having a sad son following you.
Does he now?
They don't now.
Do you have the key?
Yes, ma'am.
Ma'am.
May the Lord be with you.
And also with you, ma'am.
I have a callus out.
He is five.
Remember the passion.
Passion for passion.
Right, I believe we can get caught now.
Oh, god.
You can't hear me.
He has air pods in.
Ah!
Asasino, you will not get me.
So this is the funniest thing ever.
He's in full gown and all of that.
And he's so agile.
And I'm not being funny, but if you've ever
worn a skirt before, it is so restrictive.
I think I've worn a skirt twice in my damn life.
Oh, there's jewelry down there.
Not jewelry.
Trita.
A bit of Trita.
These are one of the chase sequences
where he doesn't actually get out of range of view.
I'm like 99% sure.
He actually holds back if you're taken too long.
I've come out the wrong window.
But yeah, he actually waits for you, which is very nice of him.
I do appreciate when game devs do that.
I understand for the immersion you might want to actually
chase, but it's kind of nice not having your gameplay
interrupted because of kind of like small things like that.
I have to say Assassin's Creed definitely.
Gameplay isn't horrifically interrupted
if you're a bad player, which I do appreciate in video games.
Oh my god.
He said, no room at the inn.
Mother Mary.
No, little donkey.
Carrie Mary, then the dusty road.
I can't believe I've got the ninth sanctuary in a church.
Did you know that if you went to a church
and you were like a wanted criminal,
if you cleaned sanctuary, they couldn't get you back
in the old days.
But now, if you're a criminal and want to get away with it,
you just have to be super rich or no.
And have blackmail on them, that's pretty much it.
Sorry, I don't.
Wait, wait, that was supposed to happen.
OK, that was supposed to happen.
I was supposed to split.
I was like, oh, no, the camera angle's
a bit funky for claiming.
Oh, I don't like that.
Ew, ew, ew, ew, ew, ew, ew, ew, ew, ew, ew.
The key camera angle.
He is so agile for this old man pope.
Are you sure you aren't in the fast on yourself?
Well, this is getting a bit ridiculous, me.
I'm going to, me.
This is getting, I don't know what they are putting in your food,
like what they're blessing the holy bread with.
How on earth are you achieving any of these stunts?
My goodness, what is in that wine?
Oh, I'm confused.
Where am I supposed to go?
Oh, no, I missed it.
Oh, it's the light.
I'm sorry, it's the light.
Literally, rule one, follow the light.
And I couldn't even do that.
Where the heck am I going?
Oh, I'm getting so confused and turned around now.
Oh dear, oh dear, oh dear, oh dear, oh dear, oh dear.
Oh dear, oh dear, oh dear.
Right, there we go.
Watch me.
I didn't even recall him doing that.
Where the heck am I going?
OK.
We've done it.
I can't wait to be rich to get away with things.
What on earth are you even for?
There's no order at all.
Oh, is this he's going to counter me?
Hey, right, you know what time it is, time for?
You don't need this, anyway.
You're devoted to God, so you don't even need this.
I'm doing you a favor.
And I'm probably, no, I'm not going to make the jokers
too obvious.
Da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da.
Can I push him over the edge?
Push.
You saved me.
Oh, my god.
Oh.
I must have subconsciously known
that you could push him off the edge,
because how on earth did I remember that?
Oh, my goodness.
That must be main story.
You must always push him off the end or something,
because there's no way I would have thought of that myself.
I must have done it before in the past.
I don't remember much of Romuli, because I don't do it.
When I replay the game, I'm actually anonymous.
I am wired in.
Wait, did I do that in time?
Is that 100% that?
Did you hear about this?
Did you see this news?
I did!
Okay, we don't have to do that.
Are you sadistic?
Yeah, I'm like, how would I have known that?
But it must always happen plausibly.
Easy clip.
We've got one more layer to go.
Catching a flight.
Safe travels, Landstrider.
Thanks for hanging.
New outfit unlocked in the inventory menu.
No, I haven't done anything to earn that, so that's not correct.
Okay, the next location is Il Colosseo.
I'm just going to check.
I think my takeaway got delivered.
So if you just give me one second, we are going to go to the Il Colosseum,
and we are going to do the last layer of Romuli and unlock the armor.
The armor looks pretty cool.
You can see my health bars now, how I haven't invested in any armor at all.
Once we get the armor of Romuli.
Yeah, you're going like it.
Give me one second just to check.
I think it has been delivered.
Let's go.
Guess which fat bastard got a takeaway?
Give me.
I have a spicy chicken burger in chip and sprite.
That's what I got.
I'm going to take more drinks of water though.
But we're definitely going to get the armor.
I don't know if we're going to get anything else, unfortunately.
I'm going to eat it now because I don't know if you have this problem
with delivery where you're from, but the driver hangs about at the restaurant
to try and get a double order, and then the food arrives cold
because they've waited so long to try and get a double order.
And it's so annoying, like it happens all the time.
And yeah, I'm like 99% sure it's happened
because that took so long from the last break I had to get here.
That happens to you too.
Okay, I've got chicken burger, spicy chicken burger and chips,
and I've got sprite.
Or my fizzy juice.
They added the prioritise option.
What, instead of just getting actually telling the drivers to deliver the food hot?
That's pretty ridiculous, honestly.
And hanging around.
Sorry for those of you who don't like eating.
I've been streaming for 11 hours and I need to refuel,
and this is my food before bed.
Literally, I'm going to brush my teeth.
I'm going to check the girls are okay on the discord.
And if all is good, then bedtime for me.
I was up around two hours, no, four hours before stream.
And then I managed to speak to Mimosa from Yumi Plus about the ASMR.
But that was like one hour before stream,
and then I had to send Clippers some stuff for the girls.
But things are settling down, they're calming down.
It's a bit chaotic, but you lead.
A little bit busy, but it's going to calm down.
And especially when the script manager comes into play,
I literally don't have to do anything.
So yeah, if you hate any of the scripts that the girls do,
you're welcome to just send a marshmallow and be like, you suck.
But yeah, I know, that's fine.
But yeah.
Hopefully for those of you who have never seen Assassin's Creed Brotherhood,
I may have given you a new opinion of the game.
Or maybe I've influenced your opinion of the game.
Better give them time out of time for me.
It's so annoying.
Like, I don't know when YouTube will fix that.
The thing is, YouTube is slowly becoming like a much better platform
to live stream on than Twitch.
There's no doubt about it in my head.
They are just so slow to catch up and implement things.
Like, so slow.
But I hope they fix that 12-hour reward thing.
Because if they do, then strapping for 14-hour streams!
Next paycheck, I'll pick up Assassin's Creed Brotherhood.
And two.
Mmm!
Actually, on Steam, you do require a Ubisoft account once you get it.
However, on Steam, Assassin's Creed Brotherhood is on sale right now for $5.
If you have it on your account, I think you can grab it.
But that's just for Brotherhood.
I don't know about the odd guys.
Sorry, I'm itching my face.
Good morning!
No, I didn't lie, I'm still here.
I thought I was going to do 10 hours, but I'm like, ah, we can do more.
Good morning to the sleepyheads and goodnight to the sleepyheads
because you're all probably sleepy.
It depends what you make for YouTube Discoverability
for streaming-only content for Discoverability.
Yeah, if you do Shorts, however, and ASMR, for example, then you can be discovered.
I don't know about how Twitch's Discoverability works, unfortunately.
It's 5pm here, I passed out most of the day.
Sounded like you needed the rest then.
I can feel deep vein thrombosis sitting in all right-
Do you need to stretch?
Maybe I should have told you to stretch.
I'm eating all the chips first because they're getting cold.
Twitch has very low Discoverability.
That's what I thought.
Whereas like YouTube, at least I know how YouTube works.
For the most part, I say that as if Emmy didn't get a warning on YouTube.
My brain's so American I thought you meant actual chips.
Ah, um, deep fried potato in a vat, in a rectangular, skinny, rectangular shape.
Yeah, man.
French fries.
Managed maggot, no, I'll get 100%.
I thought that was my cup for setting this all up.
Stinky management.
Imagine if I got graduated by my own management.
Uh-huh.
Um, they're not flavor.
With salt and fat, maybe.
And maybe large oil.
Is it management hate time?
Oh, is it that time already?
Scottish food stream.
I don't even think I have access to haggis here.
Which is a shame.
But I'm doing a Scottish game show on St Andrews for the girls.
I'm gonna like get them to guess Scottish memes or spell Scottish words
or tell me what the, the Scottish phrase says type thing.
Absurd.
When I eat, I burp a lot more.
I put all the junk in.
I'm so guessing.
School of rock.
Okay.
I finished my chippies.
I'm now going to inhale the booger.
I need to know what food places are good in Scotland.
Greggs!
That sounds terrible.
It's a British UK chain called Greggs.
And they do this thing called a cheese, bean and sausage pastry, pastry?
Pasty.
And, oh.
It is.
You know, it's so good.
I like the cheese and hamburger from Greggs as well.
Very good.
Very proof.
Mmm.
Tesco meal deal.
They used to be three quid, but they're not anymore.
Are they, are they 350 now?
Or is it going on more?
Oh.
Hold on.
I, because I laughed, a bit of dry chip went like up back my nostril.
That was very painful momentarily.
Ew.
I've never had a chance to try protein.
I believe it's cheese and chips.
And gravy?
I'm taking big bite of burger.
Do you want bite first?
Go, ah.
You can get bite of burger first.
Ah.
Do you like, you're actually putting, oh yeah.
A and W is pretty nice too if you get to try them.
I don't know what A and W is.
I'm sorry.
Is it a supermarket or is it like a takeaway place?
Oh.
Oh, the burger club.
Chicken burger.
With crunchy lettuce.
Mmm.
Sorry, I've been traumatized for going, oh.
I didn't know she was going to do that.
I was like, oh.
Oh.
A and W is almost bust, really?
Protein Canada mentioned, yeah.
It's chips, gravy and cheese.
And you can customize it with bacon, sausage, egg,
or any food you can think of adding.
Mmm.
A and W is a fast food chain.
They have good chicken burgers.
Oh, I like chicken burgers.
When I was a child, I got to visit America.
Americaia!
Hello!
And I got to try McDonald's.
And we went to Red Lobster.
And there were real live lobsters in the tank
that could be picked out.
And we didn't like that.
We're not used to that.
And it's a unique thing.
But I completely understand that markets exist.
Obviously, there's fish markets.
You go and they're live fish and stuff.
All sitting about ready to get bought and sliced and diced.
I understand that's how the world works.
I would just have a soft little soul.
I say that as I eat chicken,
which is from a breed of chicken
that purposely grows meat,
weight at a really fast rate,
and is probably no older than 12 weeks.
I understand how hypocritical I'm being.
I comprehend that.
I do comprehend that.
I've got to sleep.
The Sandman calls me.
The Sandman from Spider-Man?
What kind of demons are you fighting?
If Sandman is your nemesis,
are you good?
Do you need help?
Are they jumping you?
Sleep well.
What's the Sandman?
Is it that song, Mr. Sandman?
Give me a dream.
Bum bum bum bum.
Make him the cutest that I've ever seen.
Yeah, but who is Mr. Sandman?
Is it Sleep Demon?
Is it actually?
I'll believe you.
I will believe you.
The Sandman is the one who puts fit...
I ain't reading all that.
Wait.
He puts the sleepy sand in your eyes
that make you go,
are you trolling me or is this real?
Sandman from the store?
American stories?
I have not heard of Sandman like this
in this content.
It's real?
Okay.
Wait.
So, is the song Mr. Sandman?
Give me a dream.
Bum bum bum.
Make him the cutest I've ever seen.
Is that someone asking Mr. Sandman
to give her a dream about a man she really likes?
He puts gunk in your eyes.
Okay, I'm starting to believe that's actually the lore.
Yes!
Today I learned.
Okay.
Is it like a story book
or is this lore from the song only?
The Sandman is a mythical character in European folklore
who puts people to sleep
and encourages and inspires beautiful dreams
by sprinkling magical sander.
Okay, that song makes complete sense now.
I've never heard that story.
I must love Mr. Sandman.
Give me a dream.
Bum bum bum.
Make him the cutest I've ever seen.
Give him two lips like roses and clovers.
You've never watched Rise of the Guardian?
No.
I've watched Guardians of the Galaxy, though.
Baby, give me one more chance.
I eat more burger.
Sandman's on Rise of the Guardian.
That's cool.
It was Rise of the Guardian.
Sorry, I feel like every time you guys reference something,
I'm like, what's that?
Oh, what is this?
I've never heard of this before.
Hee hee.
Is it like Power of Alanis?
No.
The Secrets of Alanis?
Alanis.
This may be the name of the movie.
It's a movie with Jack Frost in it.
Okay.
Hmm.
Where this Sandman, Tooth Fairy, Santa Claus,
the Easter Bunny, and Jack Frost team up
to kick the crap out of a Nightmare Demon.
Ah, that sounds like a good movie.
Hmm.
Is it like Nightmare Before Christmas?
I love Nightmare Before Christmas.
We should watch Nightmare Before Christmas.
We have so many things to watch.
Life is good.
Hmm.
They put so much hot sauce on my boy boy.
Basically form an Avengers style team up.
Yeah.
I love Avengers one.
I know it's cringey, but I like it.
Hmm.
Ah, the sauce is burning my face.
Oh, she's buzzing.
She's buzzing.
Hmm.
Wow.
Oh, I can share my family's movie.
On Christmas.
The family movie is Trading Places,
and there's booba in it.
I used to watch it as a kid.
Look, there's booba.
Ah.
Hmm.
It's delicious.
After all my hard work today,
it wasn't hard work.
I literally got to just gleam about
my favorite video game.
It's not work.
I promise you, this stuff ain't work.
If each of them feels like work,
then...
then I will give you the advice
of just do what you want,
and then it doesn't feel like work.
Hmm.
But oh wait, no, that's a responsible.
I shouldn't say that.
I'm not kidding.
Is there a sneak peek of the Eat Sweet Stream?
No, I don't even have the sweets.
Um.
I might have to get my nails did for it.
Ah.
Jamie Lee Biba?
I mean Biba Lee Curtis?
I used to think that Jamie Lee Curtis
was Princess Leia,
because I grew up watching Star Wars.
So when I saw her, I was like,
Dad!
Like, I was a child child.
I was like,
Dad, why is Princess Leia's boobies on the tail?
Um, basically.
No, no.
Okay.
I don't think I can eat any more of the burger.
It appears I don't have a large appetite,
but I wonder if it's just because
I've been having such a good time that, like,
I did actually have that fruit,
which fruit is actually really good for fiber,
so maybe that's why I don't feel like eating the full thing.
Oh, I'm such a skinny legend.
Okay, let's finish up this whole layer of bromelain.
I think I was gifted this game a long time ago
and never ended up playing on it.
Mmm!
So, Assassin's Creed Brotherhood is the second
installment of Ezio Auditory's story, The Assassin.
Um, it's my favourite game of all time.
Um, I can only recommend it if you like,
kind of role-playing and you like games that hold your hand,
like, it's perfect.
We've finished the campaign already.
We finished it a couple hours ago now.
Um, and we're just finishing up a kind of side quest-esque sequence,
which is going to unlock some very OP armor.
It's a really good game.
I do recommend it.
I don't know if it's a game for a stream for the first time
you've ever played it.
I don't know, like, I mean, I love the game,
but obviously it's really hard to tell, like,
what kind of game someone would be into.
And Emi, I know you said you weren't the biggest,
like, strongest gamer, but you're like a weebo
or a gamer-type thing.
Um, but this is definitely friend.
I would say Brotherhood's friendly to, like, new gamers,
is once you understand the controls,
but then again, I have played the game like a...
Oh, I did not mean to do that.
Um, but I have played the game, like, a billion times over, so...
Can people stream through 12 hours on YouTube?
Sadly, no, the VOD ends up getting really broken
at the 12-hour mark, so I will be...
Oh, I don't want to end...
Oh, it's becoming my bedtime soon, though.
Oh, I don't want to end.
Right, well, very quickly do the last layer.
I didn't realise how long it took me to eat that food there.
I apologise. I should have... I should have sped that up.
Sorry.
Right, we will take a... this to the tunnel
to go where we need to go for this last...
to the Il Colosseum,
because that's where we need to go last,
and then we will get the armour,
because that's why we have had a fantastic
first official stream,
um, debut stream,
and the exposing wheeler and all that.
Don't count, um...
because I said they don't count, smile.
Um...
This is, like, actual stream.
This is just me doing my hang.
I know I said I...
Oh! It's you! You can't just jump on folk like that!
That's inappropriate of me!
You're going to get done for that.
You're going to get the jail.
They're going to give you the jail. They're going to take you away.
Eh, see, they need to do that again,
because that was actually really scary.
That was, like, a vampire launch.
Like...
What would Colosseum mean?
Randomly tops.
Literally, like, uh...
Eh, see, that's dangerous.
You're 35 minutes away from the travel.
No, don't say that!
Hmm.
Uh...
Uh, hold on.
Uh, I'm using my thigh to run right now, like a five-head.
Oh, hold on. Hold on.
You can tell. You can tell I'm not using agile controls.
Oh, it's on the outside. It's on the outside.
Here, here, yeah.
You walk past it when you actually deliver...
Do the deliver the male one.
Um...
Okay, boom, boom, boom, boom. Already there.
Already there!
At least this, we're gonna get our armor,
and then we are done, zoop.
I cannot for the life of me
remember what's behind this whole, uh,
of this layer of Romulae.
Romulus!
Keep saying Romulae.
Is it because of Star Trek? I'm saying Romulae.
It is!
It's because of Star Trek.
I think he doodoo-ed Star Trek.
Yeah!
I also watch Star Trek.
What?
Star Trek Voyager?
A bit of Deep Space Nine,
and, uh...
Captain Picard?
I cannot remember.
I wouldn't say Star Trek Original, but that's...
I don't think that's right.
Star Trek Origin?
Bet that too.
Would be Romulae.
Yeah, that's why I keep saying Romulae.
Instead of Romulus, it's because I watch Star Trek.
Um...
Oh, I wonder why you watch Star Trek.
Oh, surprise, surprise.
It's my dad, yet again, got me into it.
I can't believe it. My dad's the reason
why I actually have a personality.
That is terrible.
That's not nice.
Don't say things like that.
Assassin must suffer as we must suffer.
I forgot
what 100% was.
Do not lose more than three health blocks.
Easy, peasy, lemon,
Please don't launch at me.
Okay, there we go. We got the small knife out.
That's all we need.
Right, three health blocks.
As long as they don't do throwing knives,
then it's perfectly fine. Did you hear that stress
when I had to counter that attack there?
Okay.
Come at me.
Never.
Gee, that sure makes you look innocent.
Not.
Uh, again,
I believe this is time,
so I might try hard a little bit.
I can't believe it.
I'm such a sweat.
Who goes there?
Identify yourself.
I was on him.
I guess this sequence,
you're not at all supposed to catch him,
but I'm actually just such an MLG gamer
that I caught right up to him.
I literally could yank on his cloak like yaga.
Thank you.
Yeah.
Oh, okay, I remember this.
Yeah, there's like a party going on.
Oh my God, that lag because it's loading the area.
Jubilee Performers
has an access database.
I never sat in red.
What's up with this game?
Oh, what am I supposed to do?
Am I supposed to follow in that way?
Uh, right.
Go up the ladders.
Clearly, yeah, clearly he's going to shut down that wall.
I'm so sorry.
I bless your dad.
Literally make me...
Oh no, I've never correctly done this
horse sequence.
I just want you all to know.
So you can catch him in this sequence.
I never seem to catch up.
I don't know what I'm supposed to do
to make it happen.
Um,
but yeah.
Gee, I wonder why I've never made the sequence.
Me who does that.
I'm like pretty sure at the end
you're supposed to be able to jump on him
and I never make the timing.
It doesn't matter what happens.
Oh,
Gee, I wonder why I never catch up to him.
Surely it's a mystery.
No one
can solve this mathematical equation
as to why I've never caught up
with this guy.
Right, this is when I'm supposed to be able to do it.
Hi Jack.
Please.
What is go...
Exio?
Exio.
Son.
Son, do you want to talk about what just happened
or are we just going to pretend that didn't occur?
It'll literally...
Oh, I do not want to get in a fight with him.
So we're just going to sneak on by.
Sneak on by.
Oh, we've been here before.
We have been here before.
Wee.
Eh?
I knew under the stairs
looked like a game,
like an addition.
I knew it.
I forgot.
Ah.
I knew under the stairs
it looked like there was something there.
Oh my god, I'm actually just...
I'm just so smart like that,
like seriously for real for real.
Did Exio just
stuff him in his pocket?
Literally.
We did it!
We got the armor.
Codex sheet acquired.
Return to room.
Galaticator.
On the escalator.
Animal crossing villager attack.
I did it! We did it!
No, I'm going to show you where
the treasure room
is hidden. It took me a very long time
on my first playthrough to figure out
where on Earth this treasure room was.
Have you seen the movie Gladiator?
I haven't!
You want to watch this together
sometime with me?
What happens if we
did lots of
watch-alongs of all the movies I haven't seen?
Because I haven't seen a lot of mainstream
movies.
Because I'm
a gamer and I kind of just play
games and that's all I do.
I don't really watch much
anime.
And I hope that's not
disappointing to anyone, but
I think it's good that all of us have a mix.
Some of us are clearly a weeble
gamer type thing.
My strength is like
strength in quotation marks.
My strength is that I can play
games.
No strongy.
That's not what strength means.
However,
my
accolades,
I just always enjoyed gaming.
I did get very lucky.
I've heard some stories from
girls being like,
their parents actively discouraged them
from gaming and I'm like
I just feel so bad
because I am very
lucky and I get so much enjoyment.
So much enjoyment
out of the games that I'm about to
sneeze about to play.
I just went away because I called it out.
I have absolutely no idea
where I'm trying to go to get to this.
Okay, I just need to go around the hill.
It's fine.
I've heard some stories about girls being
like I just called it out.
It's just such a shame.
Actually, you know what?
I take that back.
I've also heard stories from guys
like their parents are like,
you're just wasting your life on games.
What am I supposed to do as a pastime
in a hobby? Everyone has something
that helps them get through the day.
I'm not being funny.
I'm really happy to get into the subject
of how humans
recreationally need to deal
with daily working life.
So some people use drinking.
Some people use smoking.
Some people use recreational drugs
in order to cope with the stresses of the day.
And like
folk who act like
gay men is like this.
Oh, by the way, this is where the treasure room is hiding.
It doesn't look like it, but in this little room
where you kill the captain for this
bourgeois area, you
climb up and then you find the treasure room.
Um...
And like, literally, I find it like such a shame
because like,
you don't really realize how supportive your parents are
until you get told stories.
Right, I'll show up, because it's big.
Wow!
It looks like shade.
Honestly, this is pretty bad.
I mean, it looks good, but it looks bad.
At the same time.
Oh, Jesus.
I mean...
I mean, it's alright.
I don't...
I much prefer alpires.
Armor.
From AC-1. AC-2.
Um, when you unlock all the seals.
Germans? Oh!
I read that as
Germans truly are the most repressed group in society.
Gamers are the most repressed
group in society. Even alcohol and smokers get more, right?
Yeah, literally, games are the reason
why you can use the right side of my body like normal.
Yeah, like, everyone
needs something that helps them de-stress
from daily life.
And like, I just feel so sad that people
like, genuinely have like...
I suppose if you get into the conversation
of like, loved ones and...
Like, nothing they have to support
everything you do, like, that's not how it works in the real world.
But like, I don't know, I just...
I couldn't imagine
like, my mom and dad
being like...
Or...
like, you're on the Xbox.
Well, actually, so they did kind of say that, but
I was having problems with social anxiety and all that
and I couldn't go outside in that. So that's different.
That section's different.
But, like,
genuinely, like, at no point
where like, my mom and dad disappointed in me
because I liked the game. And they like, supported it.
Like, my mom
she played the original Lara Croft
Tomb Raider and like, my dad
obviously showed me a whole
insane category of games
that got me used to like, all these different categories
and...
that kind of thing. And it's just like, really nice.
Like, my dad, he absolutely
loves to tell the story about how he gave me an Xbox
and
he'll probably tell it
when I do my interview with him.
And I say
interview. I'm just getting my dad to talk
about it.
But talk about, like, how does it feel
that your daughter's a slag? And then
he goes, it feels pretty good
because I'm going to retire
and da-da-da-da-da.
Um...
I don't know what's going on here. Like, some people know this.
Like, I managed to...
Because of the banks
and job issues and all that kind of thing
basically, the house was going to get repossessed.
Like, the family home was going to get repossessed.
Because, you know, they kind of keep up
with mortgage payments. So then I bought it.
Like, I don't own it.
Like, my parents own it. But, like, I
did the difference.
Um...
And my dad's like...
He's kind of joking when he says, like, the only reason
that, like, you're
like, so successful is because I got you that
Xbox, isn't it? And I'm like, yeah, dad, yeah!
Yeah, you made me cool, dad!
Yeah! Like, we're hyping each other up.
And I'm like, yeah!
Um...
I was, like, really cute.
No, my dad's, like, such a good
sport about everything.
Um...
Like, we're gonna do an interview.
Um, and he knows
about, like, Vila and that.
Um, he was like, how did it go?
And I was like, dad, dad!
Almost 3,000 people watched
me at once in one stream type thing.
Um, and he's like, is that
good? And I'm like, it's way beyond my
world! The streams, all the girls did
amazing! And he was like, oh, I'm so
glad you're girls are nice to me. And my mom
as well.
My mom really likes the girls.
Never spoken to them.
They've never interacted. But my mom's
like, oh, I love
your girls so much. They're so...
Like, send me their links. I want to hear their voices.
They send me, like, all this.
Like, it's so cute. It's just really nice.
Um...
Hopefully it doesn't feel like I'm, like,
rubbing it in anyone's faces
if they maybe have parents that are not
quite so understanding.
Uh...
I really don't want it to sting
if I talk about the subject, but I'll
move on and we'll
see what we're dealing with next. We're going to
arrow storm here because
we need to unlock
the
Assassin's Upgrade.
We're, uh, right.
We're trying by this building. How much time
have I got? We've got, like,
a cut in it quick.
Meracy's not online anymore, is she?
Is anyone from Ymir? Oh,
I don't want to do that. Please leave me alone. I'm not doing that mission.
Meracy's still on. Um, can someone
be a kind soul and say
Strone's asking if you're still
going to be online in 20 minutes?
Uh...
She should redirect into you or not?
Um, and then
get back to me if she's still...
if she's still doing it or not.
We're just going to buy these expensive things now.
Um...
They're so... they take such a big
chunk of the money, though.
Literally, I'm back to 32.
I think I'm going to have to send my recruits on missions
again.
Just came back from Shum. Ain't no way she's still going.
Ah, yeah.
Uh, the only reason
I'm going offline in 20 minutes
is because of the VOD issues.
If there was no VOD issues,
we would be doing Leonardo's
missions right now.
Right now!
Right now! Uh, I'm serious when I say that.
We'd be on Leonardo. We'd be in
a tank right now. We'd be on a
paraglider. Okay?
But no.
No, no, no. Had to...
Had to have VOD issues.
Yeah, yeah.
Right, let's level up these
assassinos.
Mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm.
We've got quite a lot
of level 8s. We can probably
do quite dangerous
missions. I'll send...
No, I won't. I'll send
two 7s
away together.
I've got a big one. More 8s.
One, two, three, four, five.
Oh, you're not even fully successful now.
I don't want to risk it. I'll send the 8s
on...
Yeah, that'll be fine.
I'm literally have no worries that
they're going to survive.
Mm, yeah. I was kind of into
that awkward levelling upstage
where...
I'm not wasting time sending
them together, but
it would be nice
to get the strength to, like, go on
their own.
YouTube, give us YouTube take away.
YouTube can stop me. Literally
if I would do 14 hours,
I would be doing Leonardo,
and then I would be pretty
satisfied. Maybe the auditory
memories and Christina memory, because
that's actually really quick as well.
Um,
I honestly would love to say
I'll make a second stream room, but
I do have those 8s in my collabs
and those clips to get
clipped and edited and that.
Oh, I can't believe it. I have responsibility.
Who would have imagined
that spawning a VTuber agency
meant I have responsibilities?
Oh! Oh!
Truly a shit. Please, excuse me, sir.
Um...
Oh, what is that? What is it?
Uh, right.
Um, I don't think I have enough money
for, like, anything
else.
Wait, how much money do I have
on my persons?
13K, that's not enough
to do anything else.
We'll arrive at work any day.
Can't wait for the birthday placer.
Can't wait for yapping 2.0, where I
regurgitate all the information. Maybe
I should look at the development
behind the scenes and then I can tell you about
the development behind the scenes.
That would be interesting too. What time are we
at? I've got 20 minutes.
Maybe the bank will...
Hmm...
Right, let's do Christina.
Let's do Christina. We've got time.
It doesn't take 20 minutes to do her.
Oh!
That's what she said.
I don't know if we'll finish
her storyline. I believe she has
three missions and the last
mission is a punch out.
Punch out?
But we'll do
a? Ah, Christina.
Christina mission.
I'm claiming
the building.
Claim me, claim me, claim me.
Best I can do is do.
Doesn't take to it.
Just like,
nevermind. I know, I know.
I make it too easy. I don't even
mean it. If I do it, I don't
mean it, but if I do it to you
then I mean it.
Oh, look how much my armor
but my health bar went up. I just
like, literally noticed that.
How did I not notice that?
Cause it's massive.
It's like halfway across. It's like
the Elden Ring.
Oh!
Okay, we're getting stole. I see the
game is trying to stall me from
achieving my...
Jesus, that's brutal.
Oh, that's brutal.
Is that a new knife as well?
I must have unlocked a new knife
cause, yeah, this must be a
Romuli knife. A Romulus knife.
Cause I, that does not look like
the default knife.
Yeah, with the hook.
Excuse me, pardon me, coming through.
Tihi! Tihi, I'm just
the normal average citizen.
Christina!
My love!
Hello!
We'll be climbing a coast with this
mission.
Does it
vaude explode after the 12 hour
mark or is it like
it gives a few minutes of grace
unironically? Cause I'm worried
about it exploding.
Ha ha!
This doesn't take long, it's a punch out.
What about that one?
That's my brother!
This is baby, it's healing.
I think it explodes right after
12 hours.
What?
Why are you just standing there?
Oh, um,
because I
wanted to ask you
which is
what's your name?
Not one you'll ever meet me
without.
I wasn't ready.
I'm planning on being really charming.
Negative riz.
Whoa!
I have terrible news, please do not
take the advice of Ezio.
Do not ever follow a woman home.
That's not
socially acceptable.
Don't worry, I'll teach you what's
socially acceptable and what's not.
If you approach a woman
and then
she, you know,
doesn't reciprocate interest,
do not follow
a woman home. That is no-no
in society.
More societal,
social...
Oh! See?
Wait, get back here.
Oh my god, she wants me for real, for real.
That's how you get a restraining order.
Yeah, this is...
I understand it's a video game,
but
this is...
Yeah.
Yeah, this is...
something alright.
Like,
I know Ezio's harmless,
but this is... it's given, like,
yandere simulator or something.
Like, that kind of negative thing.
Restraining order speed run for real.
The best thing you think of to get around 12-hour
problem is to close the stream when you...
Oh, I wasn't paying attention, sorry, I was reading chat.
12-hour problem is
to close...
to close
the stream when you have to take a long
break and start a new one after.
Okay.
Do you mean, like, actually go offline and rest
and then come back online again? Is that your solution
to my 12-hour stream problem?
Instruction's unclear, I'm hiding in her closet.
Oh!
That's terrible!
You're not to make those jokes!
That's naughty!
Oh.
Okay, this quest has taken
a bit longer than I originally anticipated.
But I think we're about to do the fighting
part and then we're done.
You achieved 100%
in problem
solving.
Okay, we're here, we're here, we end this.
We hate him!
I think not, I'm already here.
I've decided, I'm tired
of waiting for you to open your legs
on your own.
Oh, the area, I thought his name was Duccio
for some reason.
Oh my god, we're the knight in
training armor, we're not creepy anymore
because we're saving her.
Take this!
Leave the lady alone!
Thank you.
That was very kind of you.
Are you alright?
Not only is her...
I'm sorry.
He looks like such a baby there, honestly.
Looks like you got yourself a second chance.
If she kisses and not even
on the first date,
we're in, lads.
We're in, lads.
We are in.
You stalking wha- No!
No!
Absolutely not!
This is fictional game.
Literally when you build up the game,
it says fiction.
Okay, I think
I'm gonna have to close the game there
because the void
is literally about to explode.
Did you guys tell me if
Mercy is still strumming?
They'll be strumming her in a minute.
Stop!
Stop.
Unappropriate.
No HR though.
Mercy is still on.
She's still gonna keep playing.
She's still gonna...
Remember that time donations were on?
And then you guys broke the donations so badly
that no one in Vehler can get donated to right now?
Because you guys were so supportive.
Yeah, she's still yapping.
She's post-game yapping.
Alright, well...
I'm gonna get her link.
Mercy, can I get your link?
That's how I spell Mercy Modest.
That's right.
What are you gonna do about it?
Are you gonna fart?
Yeah, that's right.
You're not gonna fart.
You're gonna do nothing about it.
Come on.
Stop it!
Analytics? No, wrong one.
Details. Customization.
Redirect.
I'm gonna link right in there.
Save.
Okay, when I end, it should redirect
into...
this encyclopedia
of Would You Want to Quit the Game?
Righty-hoo!
Should I go bigger?
Hold on a minute.
Why is chat wrong?
Chat isn't disabled!
Well...
What is this?
Why the heck?
You know what?
I'll just stand here then.
Hi!
I say hi
if we're not all about to go a bit.
Thank you all so much
for letting me go
turbo mode on this game.
It has been nothing short of a pleasure
and I hope
we can 100%
tomorrow.
I don't know what the tank mission is.
I don't know if I should look it up
or if I should just
wish myself good luck on the tank.
But yes.
Thank you for hanging.
Please don't worry if you weren't here for the full thing.
I don't think anyone was here for the full thing
other than me.
Please.
I miss her already!
I'm still talking!
Have I even gone yet?
We are 52 minutes
so less than 7 minutes.
I'm stinky.
I'm going to end it
so it can successfully raid into Mercy.
But thank you so much
for keeping me company.
I'm so glad I got to share one of the...
one of the? No.
The greatest game
of all time.
I have no idea how long tomorrow
the stream is going to be.
But really
we pretty much done everything other than
Leonardo missions and then we just go back
in the DNA sequences
of the chapters we messed up
and by we messed up I messed up
but I'm putting the blame on the both of us.
Okay?
Um...
Can you give us a peek at those eyes before you hop off
as encouragement for showing up?
Oh go go go! I like it.
I dig it. Ah, new subscriber
you're in the way.
You're such a silly goober up there, new subscriber.
How do I get rid of you?
Just for now.
Okay.
You ready?
Even though my Assassin's Creed sounds are still
in the background? Just pretend the backing
track to the menu of Assassin's Creed
is Hypnosis space, okay?
Wow.
You want to come to stream tomorrow, don't you?
I'll be waiting.
And you've done very well today.
Holding on for
too long.
Can you do it again
tomorrow for me?
Yeah?
Fine then.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Nya!
But for now
you can meme in me, okay?
You can meme in me.
Okay.
Thank you so so much.
We're gonna go to Mercy.
Should have picked
any kind of support.
Right. I love you so so much, Reflings.
And if you're not Reflinging
don't worry, I still love you too
because I'm really appreciate you hanging out.
I know some people don't like being referred to
as Fannins, but I like Reflings.
No.
Not that.
Reflings.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Bye bye. I go sleep and brush my teeth.
No, I brush my teeth first and then I go sleep.
But first,
Mercy.
I'll then brush teeth.