No time to wait for my days, we're getting longer in peace
No time to wait for my days, of all the time
Right, this is British lore
Oh wait, hold on
Dule Lover, thank you for becoming a member, I have no idea what it's like even says I'm online yet
No it doesn't, oh this is the thing, whenever I look back on a board
I'm like rambling to myself for a full minute, because for some reason it doesn't bring itself up for a full minute
Even though I'm sitting here, meh meh meh, but when I look back on the board
And all that, it's all fine
It's all fine
The fine line
Right, where are we? Nope
Nope, not yet
Not playing the game yet
Good morning, good evening, good afternoon, I am your host, Ronnie Cuttles
Coming at you with a fried voice, thank you
Dule Lover becoming a member in case that did not register
She loves it, she loves it
On time question mark, yes I haven't been lurking in the shadows
I had to do some bit of background work
What's the background work you ask?
I put Shabby Cottonbombs memberships live, so if you want to be a cheeky harem and get in
But she might not say your name during the stream though
You're probably better waiting on the stream in two hours time
Shabby Cottonbombs, maybe I should be a bit bigger, can I talk in a minute?
I'm looking and looking
Well I'll just stand right here, like right over the text and everything
Why not? Why not? Why do I have to be professional?
Hold on, I'll actually go weave, because BOOM!
Good morning, good evening, good afternoon, little reeflings
What is on the agendination for week three?
So we're starting off strong with an ASMR stream at the usual time
And then after two hours I will go offline and have a 15 minute peace break
Because we're going to be doing our first membership watch-along
Which is none other than the first Transformers movie with Sam Witwicky and Bumblebee
Sweet little Bumblebee, I know what he wants from me
To kill the Decepticon and stop them from ruining the planet
And then the following day, on a Tuesday for the rest of the world
We are playing Zelda Minish Cap
Now statistically this game takes roughly eight hours to finish
Whether or not it takes me eight hours, I don't know
But we will be taking a pause 15 minutes before because for a member stream
We're going to be doing the forbidden tear list
Not the way you want, the big yin
And I get to answer it honestly this time
Because I'm allowed to say what I want to say
If we do not finish it in the first day, which is unlikely due to the member stream
Then the rest of the day on Wednesday is dedicated to Zelda Minish Cap
But it's the only Zelda game I have ever completed or played
I know it's shocking, hold on, wait
Whoa, it won't let me stretch out chat
Chat, you'd let me stretch it
Why the frick frack diddly-dat-tick-tack?
Does it not let me stretch chat?
Wait, is it because I normally have you on the screen?
Oh my god, let me stretch you, why is it locked?
Chat is locked for me, so I can't even read just properly
Brev, Brev
I'm trying to explain what we're doing
Anyway, I'm going to-
Eh, you be next, thank you for becoming a member
Oh my god, is that the mascot for, um, we Louie Vuitton Inc?
I'm so sorry, her name evades me right now from all the live, Louie Vuitton Inc
Oh my god, why is her name not in my mouth?
Purple, with the most adorable little sea ears
Oh my goodness
Anyway
Um, we are going to do Old School RuneScape on Thursday
Oh, and now my chat's broken completely
Oh, thanks OBS, no really, thank you, please don't ever cook again
Oh, it finally worked, in on, yes, in on
Oh my goodness, I don't know why chat wasn't working
Chat, yeah, well it's fixed, I can actually read chat now
In on, yes, in on, in my whole, thank you
Um, let's see, so then we're going to do Old School RuneScape
However, check it, I'm doing my first ever one-on-one collab with the other girl
And guess what, it's with Mercy
I should have picked any kind of yandere
But I got Mercy
And we're going to be playing Goose Game, we're going to be playing it at her time
So we're only going to do a little bit of RuneScape
But if I can get a couple of levels in, I will take it
Um, so a couple hours of RuneScape and blabbing away
And then I will go offline for a few hours to recharge
Because I want to give Mercy my all, she's not ready for the Rotism Your Honor
Hey, thank you, Omarum Simpson
It still doesn't display properly, even though I have the full chat up
Memberships are showing up for me on YouTube mobile
For a sheebie cotton bum, they better be because we are redirecting into her
If you didn't know, sheebie has posted pictures of herself in a self-made cosplay of sheebie
Yep, that's a full sentence
You may check them out by discovering the alternative twirers
If you don't know what the alternative twirers are, feel free to check out who the accounts are following
But yes, at Mercy's usual stream time, I wanted to make the collab super easy for her
So I am going to have to rest and snort
Some...
I shouldn't have said that
I'm going to be taking lots of cola, okay
I'm going to be slurping my cola for any caffeination
Because I'm probably going to be a wee bit
I'm going to start lagging a little bit there
Are you squiddin' me right now?
Ain't I meant for you either
You don't have to give me money to tell me this
You just realise that, Omarum
You don't have to give me money to type things in chat
Scotland, whatever
Yes, erm
Well, I was originally going to do a heart rate monitor this stream
Count up for the life of me, find it
I bought a new heart rate monitor because my other one was bust
And it's already gone
So I think I'm about to purchase a third one
Lucky me
I'll probably...
If I send a care package to the girls like for Donothons
Others have cubed mascots
We have a cubed Scottish girl
What?
Wait
Did Brian talk?
Did Brian say...
No, did Brian say anything there?
Oh shit, I didn't see that
Aren't...
Others have cubed mascots
We have a cubed Scottish girl
Thank you for the five iron report
I appreciate it
Oh, I never heard that
Sorry, I have my headset muted
Because I have the freaking game sound in the background
It's so loud
Are you squiddin' me right now?
Can't wait to see Strone as the imposter in this game
Wait, what?
No, wait
We're playing Nero
We're playing a game called Untitled Kiss Game
If you didn't see AC actually revealed that she's playing with Emmy
On a game called Don't Starve
And I'm like, jeez, that's a bit brutal
That's exactly AC's lore
Because she had to hunt for her food
So, rather curious
Rather curious, aren't they?
Okay
What else? Elden...
Yes, Elden Ring the DLC
Elden Ring the DLC, okay
It launches on Friday
I'm like 99% sure
Even if it doesn't come out by the time we start playing
We have a lot of areas to clear anyway
And I am under the impression
We have to perish the enemy
That's at the top of this elevator
In that graveyard
And ironically Ryan Goslin was the one
That vanquished him
Because I couldn't do it
I kept getting attacked
So the reflands on a freaking debuff
Like a severe debuff
Whilst I was running away from this boss
All came flying in
And I'm like 99% sure
Ryan Goslin killed that one
I do say shortcaller
Now I do have a shortcaller
We're gonna test it out at the start stream
If I can handle it
I will permit my reflings to zap me
Every time I cause us to die
I will try and keep the heart rate monitor too
Just so you can see how freaking messed up I get
Whenever we get near an enemy
Now
I need you to open your eyeballs for me
Because members asmr stream starts
One hour earlier
Than my usual start time
The reason for that is
Emi
Azura
Mercy
Strawny
Are doing a four man uno collab
So that I can't get away from mercy this week
I'm already entangled in her snare
And then
So that's two streams that day
Yeah
And
And then and then and then
Sorry I did apologize for your head
I didn't get a good sleep last night
Again
I'm getting very tired
Actually I'll tell you something really bad
So I had to take sleep medicine the other day
But whenever I take sleep medicine
I have problems going number two
Okay
And
And then I hurt my butt going number two
So
If there's any
Anyone that wants to help kiss it better
And then Elden Ring part two
We again will have a full endurance on that
I am literally weaving
So much content in between this as well
Because I'm also starting up
My thank you series
My one ASMR video pair
1000 views thank you series
I am absolutely
Delighted and exhausted
To learn that I
My
Scheduled
Uploaded ASMR for 1000 subs
I've already reached 7000
Which means the debt of six is still to be paid
I'm very thankful
Oh man I'm tired
After this stream today
I'm actually going to record
Three
Collab ASMR's from my side
Because three girls have given me their side
So
I need to edit that
Unending ASMR's
Back to back to back
There's so many replays now
I know my mum is very busy
If you didn't know
AC's meme ASMR has gone live
It is sniffing ASMR
If you like that trigger
Mercy's ASMR has
I got a fucking cat here in my mouth
All the time
You really do get used to it
When you get cats honestly
You're just like oh that's just another part
Mercy has released Yandere ASMR
Please if you absolutely despise
The meme ASMR's I got them to create
Well guess who fucking
Created them for them
So if you hate them don't be like
Mmm this video is stinky
Be like mmm strongy stinky
Because she came up with a concept
So don't if you didn't like it
Don't worry it's not like it's the only ASMR video
They're ever going to produce for free on youtube
Like fucking relax
For one
I'm sorry I'm literally fighting imaginary people
Not one person has said that
At all I know for a fact no one has said that
And I'm like already swinging
On behalf of the girls
Like don't say nothing about my girls
But yes
Mercy's ASMR actually
I was influenced by well
So I had already created this
Over a year ago
And I think this was before the creator
Of Yandere Sim got outed
For all of his
I'm 32
You have so much power over me tweets
Or whatever the tweet was
I can't remember the ins and outs
But
If you didn't know
In Yandere Sim there's a mechanic
Where in order to lower your craziness levels
You need to laugh
You need to laugh very loud
And very startling
And if anyone is around you while you laugh
It alerts them
And I was like how did I do that for Mercy
So I did an intro
A little setting up the plot
She comes and finds you type thing
And then she laughs like a maniac
Ear to ear in the mic
And I absolutely love it
But I think that's cause
I knew about it. I've never actually played Yandere Sim
But yeah
Preemptive defense is a good strategy
Literally just smashing people's skulls in
No one has said a thing to me
But the rage has already taken over
The only discord group with speedrun pan records
Honestly
Also Emi and Momi's ASMR came out
Oh did Emi release it
So
I went the complete
Meme route for Emi
But Emi isn't quite
With me on the same page
Which is fine, it's completely fine
She has complete control
So I was like upload it if you want it
Oh wait she did upload it
Okay
So she kept the thumbnail the same
Okay I thought she wasn't gonna like it
Okay
So she's called the video
Alleyway Tingle Dealer
Sells you completely legal tingles ASMR
That's good title
I like that title
My title was
VTuber Sells You
Tingles in an alleyway
I think or something like that
We did have to
The artist at the time drew
Emi
Sorry they're twins
drew Emi
So we had to put a little
Sutton Sutton over
I loved the 30 minute Japanese one
I'm glad you enjoyed it
That is basically what unscripted
ASMR turns it into
If I don't have a script I will
YAP my head off
So Emi also has her meme ASMR
Now that she's monetized which is
Fan Tiddlyastic
The next
Meme ASMR
Which I'm actually gonna ask her permission
To do it once
Once your monetization stream
I know professional streamer by the way
Has finished
My dear Shubu
Would you like me to upload
And pub
Is it publish? No
Upload and
Put live your meme
ASMR
You guys are gonna freaking love the plot
Shibu's plot was so unique
I had to go away and record
Folly sounds which is rare
For me because I have a massive bank
Of sounds that I can
Come from
It was great
You were loving the ear mask
Oh you like the 7 girl
Collab
Oh yeah you like 7
Ovens being together
Whole Neckos
Well if you're excited for that
There's another
Next week there's another 7 man collab
I'm gonna have to edit it
The work never ends
I don't know what you're saying
Anonymous
I love the ASMR you did with DTW
And the rest oh thank you
It was so hard to put together
You know she's such a busy person
I was so excited to see that
Oh I'm glad you like it
Thank you for the tip Anonymous
Yes
7 man
No 7 person collab
With another girl
V.A
Surprise surprise you've already guessed
What channel it's going on
There's no way in heck
You don't know who it is
And then after that for next week
There's another 7 man collab
I need to put together
The work never ends
But the work is good
Wait I'm gonna need confirmation
Right think of one V.A
That I talk to all the time
And burst in in this chat all the time
Thank
That's who's next
And then the next one after that
Actually did a watch along of us
But
Because I have the artwork so I can edit it
But then the fourth
7 man collab
I'm waiting on this animator
To animate the artwork
And the worst part is
Well actually
It's not the worst part
The animator that I usually use are like
Oh I've just had a wedding
And I'm like oh my god congrats
Meanwhile
My stuff has been unedited
And the deadline has slipped
Almost 2 weeks now
And I'm like congrats on your wedding
But your honeymoon phase is over
Please get off of her and let her have some rest
Okay and do my work
Thanks I paid you for this
Can you just do it that'd be great
Because I'm currently freaking waiting on
Oh mama yunya what's up bro
No not mimosa
No I do have a collab with mimosa
But that's a one on one collab
I'm jumping on her
Remember of yumi plus as a 3dio
I need to write the plot and send it to her
And another piece of work that I have to do
By the way
And shibi has
Finally got a new short
Pro shibi only has two shorts
She finally has a third
And all of harem are welcome
Who is that shleg yeah
That shleg right
Harem
Is
A harem is
Very thankful towards strawnee
Because strawnee gave shibi the script of praise
So the reason why you hear shibi praise you
In that short
Is because of strawnee
So all of harem
Please say thank you strawnee
You're welcome little harem
I'm looking after you
Not only did I get her to say a short
Where you discussed her but also
Hi lots oh my god is that the real sin
Sin star
I still need to message you about
Rearranging that
A collab
Because
My dad
Is coming home
In July
So
My dad's coming home
Our father-in-law
Oh do you want to meet your dad-in-law
I'm not getting him to come on stream
Because he'll be like
Hi Reeflings
Hi full legal name and address
So he's not coming on stream
But yes
My dad
Is coming home
For two weeks
Yes all of our dad collectively
Is coming home
I thought about a few stream ideas
Like you know how some folk do
Like oh my dad goes through
Like
Reefling applications
Like I don't know if maybe that would be funny
Or I don't know if people wouldn't like that
I'm gonna make a video
With him about like
Being a gamer and like
People can ask him questions and stuff
Being like oh what is it like knowing that your daughter's
A full blown slag and then he was like
Well I'm retiring next year so it's
Bloody good the house is paid off
I'm retiring next year like name and geese
I will be dead in
60 years anyway
I'm gonna let Brian talk
Okay
Sorry I can't hear it
Because I've muted the desktop audio
I don't know if you watch football
But I wanted to let you know that in the game
Germany against Scotland
We won 5 to 1
That was 5 to 1
We kicked off the
We kicked Scotland off the pitch
To all Scots sorry not sorry
We got pumped 5-1
Didn't Germany and Brazil
Not have that am I going to
Am I misremembering
I'm gonna need at least 8 more years of content
Yeah damn
You want 8 years more of content
I feel like my voice
Will be like fully even you can't bring
Your dad on stream
Make sure he still calls you the radish boys
And I'm like dad they're called Reflins
That Reflings
Their name actually didn't change
Just the spelling
And he's like
The radish boys are they looking after you
And I'm like yes dad the radish boys are looking after me
They always do
I was telling
I'm like oh
One of my meme videos
Like I got a meme video
That went a bit viral
And he was like oh what happened
What's going on in the video
And I'm like
That's for me not for you
Um
Can you tell them
That a yeah video
Of me ASMR whispering
Into a $500
Microphone
Was because I was begging to hold a pee pee
For someone's peace
Can I tell them that nah my dad knows
He doesn't know the channel
But he knows like
Because
What pays bills
Let's still pretend
I wonder if my dad sounds like me
Oh his accents even stronger than mine
Um way stronger
One day we'll get to call
We'll get him to call us
His radish sons
Do you want me to get him to say that
I could do that usually
Does your dad talk in scots too
We are so bad
Oh yeah no my dad's like got a harsher accent than me
Um so my mum
My mum told me
Not to speak in slang
But my dad does
Cause he
Is a
I mean he just speaks
Slang but my mum doesn't
So I don't really do it cause
Is your dad single
No
Oh my god are you trying to be my mum
What is going on here
Hold on a minute
Refling
What's going on
That's fine by me
Imagine Strani introducing a
Refling to her dad as her boyfriend
And he's sitting there all stern
Threatening us not to hurt his precious
Cuttlefish
Wait let me read that thank you
Imagine Strani introducing a
Refling to her dad as her boyfriend
And he's sitting there all stern
Threatening us not to hurt his precious
No my dad's like super nice and approachable
You don't need to be scared of my dad
Honestly
Like he'd be like
Oh are you looking after Strani
And then you go
In your voice cause you're like scared of him
And then he'll go
Is she happy
And then you go I think so
In your wee voice cause you're trembling
And then after that
Oh good that's it
My dad
Me and my dad are on the same page
Where as long as my dad's happy
I'm happy
As long as I'm happy my dad's happy
It's super
Super duper simple
Like that
It's nice to do that
Reflings are happy I'm happy
If I'm happy
Reflings are... wait did I say the same thing
I'm happy
Refling happy
Yes like this
I think she's happy
She cusses me out regularly with a smile
On her face oh that's terrible
What is the Scottish
Shotgun and how's it different
I don't know
There's haggis in your face instead of pellets
Papastrone
Looks like
The dad from how to train your dragon
Wait hold on
How to train
Your dragon
That exhibition
No
No he doesn't have beard
No beard
Although he doesn't have beard
But he has not stubble
Although he does
One to actually
I'll tell you this is really funny
One time my dad tried to grow a beard
And I was mortified
I was like oh no
It's my mom's single
No
You're teasing me refling
How do you think your dad would respond
If
Refling said
Or calls me daddy too
Would I call you daddy
I wouldn't think I'd call you daddy
Like in my accent
Daddy's pretty jarring and cringe
Like oh yeah I like that daddy
Mmm yeah
Like no
Do you want me to tell him
Like oh dad by the way
The refling's call me mummy
I don't
I don't think he's going to get it
If I explain it
I think he's going to be like what
Oh I don't think he's going to confirm
That would be amazing
Oh yeah daddy
Give me a spicy sausage
Literally no it doesn't work
You've been lie
I think every
VTuber calls you mummy now
I have to admit it is an absolute cheat
Code if any VTuber
Is like you know
Code name mummy I'm like oh
I'm cool with you
Hearing you say mummy or daddy in your accent
Sounds hot a f
Anonymous
Hearing you say
Mummy or daddy in your accent
Sounds hot a f
Are you sure you're not listening
With rose tinted hearing aids
Because
Mummy
Daddy
Oh yes
I'm feeling a bit
Yeah you like that is that what you want
Tisker
Yeah no don't tisker that
That was cringe
Alright I'm just going to make sure
I'm redirecting into none other than
Shibikotunboom
I don't know how
Three of us has ended up doing
Feet related celebrations
Which is absolutely hilarious for monetization
That three of us has ended up showing her feetsies
That is hilarious
And I will not be taking any statements
Because oh my god that's so funny
How are you
I'm good
A
A channel that inner ear girl
Arrah
Wait
Scottish VTuber that tries way too hard
To prove that they're like a Scottish VTuber
Arrah
We don't need to know
If your mum is single
We have the only mum in here
Anonymous
We don't need to know if your mum is single
We have the only mum
Oh that's so sweet
What the heck I thought you were going to say something bad
Thank you Anonymous
That was very sweet of you
Do you want to know a fun fact
A little behind the scenes fact
At violor headquarters
You guys have yet again supported the girls
So much that some money is on hold
You guys have supported
The girls unanimously
So much that
Paypal emailed
And we're like
Some of your funds are on hold
Not all of them
But yes thank you so much
For the out
Outcry no for the outgoing
Insane support
Of me darlin
You have literally
You support so much at the start
You broke the account
And now some funds are on hold
Because there's so much money coming in
It was actually a snowberry
That did it so shout out to the snowberries
You broke
A little bit of the Paypal
Holy shit did you hear my cat
Fucking I was playing with Gimli
Before I started
Extreme
I wish he was going mental again
And I think I warmed her up too much
Get supported, get supported, get supported
Nero
Imagine thinking that listening
That would be crazy
And mommy and daddy and I think
Accent isn't hot that would drive
That would be crazy
Well I get real close to you
I'm looking you in your eye
Is that what you should be saying
Oh my god do you know those convention
Signs
Those VTuber conventions where they like hold a sign
And it's like five dollars to get stood on
Bro
50 cent for me to smash my
Arse on your face how about that
One cent for me
A whisper daddy
In your ear how about that
Okay
We're going to do a thing at this VTuber convention
Called undercutting the market
You offer your goods
At an unbelievably discounted price
Now I know undercutting
Normally implies there's going to be
A raise later on
We ain't raising none of the prices
The prices you see are the prices you get
Pills out 20 bucks
Take all my change that's a steal
Strongly really undercutting the market now
I'm like 99% sure
I saw a cosplayer meme
And she genuinely had a sign
That said like five dollars
To be stepped on and she was like
I made like four hundred dollars
In a day type thing
So I guess
For that much we are getting married
With 50 children
Thank you for the
Is that Poland
I don't know what that is
Pozka
So I guess for that much
We're getting married with 50 children
Nah no children
Did you see Azura's alternative artwork
She did break all
What Azura did what
I didn't know she was down like that
I didn't know she was
Down like that
She drew that of her
She drew that
Yes Azura is an artist if you didn't know
Literally all the girls have some sort of
Drawing
History
Background
KFP Spidey again with the five gifted
Congrats to those who caught it with your
Face
In your face
Oh my god we need to play Kung Fu Chaos again
Tornado
Your doodles are so cute
Oh no
I don't know how to draw
Actually I could
I should have shown it on the hand cam stream
I tried to
Learn to draw
And I was consistent for like five days
Before work just got far too much
I couldn't keep up with work naturally
And the only thing
I was wanting to draw
Was the girls
So I have like terrible pictures
Of me drawing the girls like way back
A couple of months ago now
Sadly life got in the way but
I actually do genuinely think if I ever hit
The Jenga with the five gifted
Memberships thank you
Congrats to those who caught it with your face
In your face
Sorry I'm really
If you didn't know there's a character called
Candy Roll in Kung Fu Chaos
Her and sweet and sour
Were my favourite characters
And when my voice gets squeaky
Internally, not externally
But internally because of the
You hear yourself differently
From out loud
I sound like Candy Roll
When I get really high pitched
And I
Know all her voice lines
Was it ekololalia
When you repeat what you've heard
And she's like
It's my candy ass
And I just love her so much
She's just like 10 out of 10 characters
Oh my god
Gen 2 roller skates confirmed
Sorry some sort of girl on roller skates
I don't care
Bimbo! Oh my god we don't have a bimbo
Wait
What would the bimbo be
Maybe like a bimbo that lowers your expectations
And then does something
Xenowarrier thank you for coming
Remember
Roller skates
A bimbo maid
I would need something a bit more than a maid
I feel like maid is very default
I don't know maid a bimbo maid
That is quite nice though
Bimbo maid is cute
Because then she can spell stuff
On you all the time
And then before you know
Bimbo
Possum
A possum mod
Remove this man's testicles
Possum
As in the thing in them that goes
Anonymous
I'm so conflicted about
Who is my favourite in VLR
Please hypnotise me to stay loyal
To you mummy
Keep that thought in mind
Not for what you think
Because next week
We may or may not be rating
A very unique audio roleplay
Paul Lott
That involves me and
The girls
Maybe that kind of script
Perhaps sea queen
Script
Might solidify
Who your choice is at VLR
Jealous mother
I assure you
I wish to share all
All the goodness
All the spice
I have clear ideas
A possum are kind of cute
A masochistic maid
Is meta
But it never goes out of meta
I was debating on when to get membership
And then I decided if it's not on the day
Strongly offers 50
Cent butt smashes
What day will it be?
Honestly do you think conventions would let us get away with that?
Like obviously I'll be wearing a mask
And I'll have a little wig
So my hair is the same
But I feel like no one can stop
You're like
Oh what are you going to do
A reefling lies down on the floor
And I quickly butt bash him and then get back up again
Is that kickable to get out of the corner
I feel like that's such a baby thing
Oops I tripped and landed on my reeflings face
No
It depends I guess
Because it would be really weird messaging
The convention and being like
Hey
Am I allowed to fall on the
Faces of reeflings
Question mark
Am I allowed... well if they allowed
Stepping because then you can start to argue
Like oh but you allow other
VTubers to step on them
Did you know that is also vexally
Besifying
When I trip and fall on a reeflings face
With my
Arse
That's unacceptable
But if I step on them that's acceptable
Oh my god
Convention
Talk about having double sided
Is it because I'm Scottish
Convention
You can't do that
You can't show that you
Believe in the British Isles
Sorry
You need Kingdom over
Scotland
Oh my god convention
You don't believe in the independence of
Scotland
Convention
You can't say that stuff out loud
Yeah
Albuphobia
Sounds like asking for trouble
Well good thing my name is
Johnny because we're making it double
That's right me out
Sorry I was kind of going on
Team rockets
Blasting off again
Oh wait that's not what they sound like
That sounded like cream
Please be careful not to fall
What
As
Team rockets
Blasting off again
It's kind of there
Yeah
Convention what do you mean
So there's a possibility
In a certain timeline
Um
I may or may not be able to
Make it to our convention
Um
I would love to do that
But the only problem is
We have a bomb
And I'd actually need to hire
A bodyguard two bodyguards
Or one bodyguard
Bro I'm going to be so embarrassed
Messaging security is like
A private security comment being like
Hey I basically need
Security persons to follow me
Around a convention is that fine
Like for bodyguard
Well I feel like the reeflings
Would bodyguard me pretty much
So like any shitters would like you know
Get eaten up
I thought this thumbnail said
Backshot bro you've been on the
Patreon a lot too much
Okay that bodyguard on me
Three four four is quite a lot
Four is because you're Scottish
Nearly
Nearly even
United with the UK
Five might be a good number
Five little reeflings
And a paycheck's a paycheck
Literally
The bodyguards
Just watching me like sit on everyone's
face
Being like what have I been hired for
I thought it was a convention for like
Weaves or something
Like not understanding this like for Retubers
We probably
Get weirder requests
plausible
True blood reeflings would be natural
Bodyguards
I think I would have to hire professional
Security
Yeah no that's not the plan
A sniper too steady
I'm not trying to take anyone's heats off
Okay and what is this
France when Star Wars got released
Did you know
That in France when Star Wars got released
Was the last public beheading
Hmm
What if they are also reeflings
The bodyguards I don't think bodyguards
With a full time job have enough time
To listen to me Japanese
About anything and everything
That comes to my head
What yeah it's true
The year that Star Wars came out
Which is
Nineteen
Seven
What year did first
Star Wars come
I don't know
Was the last year there was a public execution
In France and also just happens to be
The year that Star Wars first came out
Leaving yeah
I've been at hold
I have a full time job
I can hear you yapping and so why not
How though aren't you getting distracted at work
Can I give you a bone bone at work
When we do the ASMR stream please
The thought I have that kind of power
It's too much power
Unlimited power
Speaking of Star Wars
I was freaked me out that scene
You have done that to me at work
Yeah stop you're gonna give me an ego
It's like one of my favourite freaking concepts
Oh my god should I write
A joystick
About doing it at work
And being subtle
No I don't want you to get fired
I don't want to encourage such behaviours
I'd rather you didn't get fired
As much as you may despise
Work as a whole
It's good for routine for the brain
It's good for socialisation
It's good for keeping you active
And the neurons firing
Maybe capitalism won a little bit there
But maybe reduce it to a four day work week
A four day work week
And not putting it up to ten hours
Because that's outrageous
And then for those
Who choose to not
Those who work on Friday, Saturday, Sunday
Get a cheeky bit of overtime as well
Because that's not common in all countries
Anyway before the tinfoil hat goes back on
What it's been 44 minutes already
Guys why didn't you tell me to start the game
Are you squidding me right now
You and the rest of the girls
Sheepy goes live in T-Main
And we're in five
Showing her thighs and feet
I have taken so long and been so
Distracted
Let's turn on this desktop audio
So you guys can hear what I hear
And let me turn off my
Background theme
This is what I hear in buckshot
Okay we're just going to jump into it
Hopefully that's not too loud
Testing
Let's get my schedule off stream
We know what schedule is
We're very thankful
It's been 45 minutes, start the game
Oh now you tell me
I might have to
Put brightness up
I noticed that in my Crash Bandicoot stream
The brightness was so not bright
But on my screens it was bright
Hold on, hydration
V-B-N-Y
V-N-N-Four
Hold the scape tag
Oh
Oh my god
We're Germans
Germans like to rave
Abandoned buildings for some reason
Can I get a light mate?
Are you got anything on you?
Are you got a wee baggie on you?
No right, we'll just keep going then
Please sign the waiver
What's my name?
Oh my god my name is
Ah
Ne
That's me
That's you
Dealer
Anon
One live round, two blanks
I insert the shells
In an unknown order
Oh my god this back
Like the faded out background music
Shotgun, shooting yourself with a blank
Skips the dealer's turn
If there's two blanks
I shoot myself
Okay, okay, okay, statistically
We're now at 50-50
We're at 50-50
I'd rather give it to him
Shooting yourself
No, I want to shoot him, how do I do that?
I shoot the dealer, 50-50
I'm sorry mate
Oh no
Oh no, he's gonna
A defibrillator
Careful now
Defit
Alive
Three rounds, two blanks
Odds are what?
They enter the chamber in a hidden sequence
Free live
I want to shoot, sorry
Three live, two blank
Okay, now it's 50-50
Two live, two blank
Mmm
Okay, okay, that's good, that's good
Cause now it's two live, one blank
Okay
I am shit at this game
You're lucky
I left you with a charge
Get up and on
The knight is young
Do you want this?
Okay
Do I need to turn the brightness up on stream?
So
The game
Is it bright enough for you guys?
Sorry, I'm gonna read chat
No, it's good, it's good, okay, thank you
I don't know why, but Crash Bandicoot was so dark
Wait, is he the one that raised me then?
Oh
Welcome back
Hi
I thought this game took like 20 minutes to
One live round, two blanks
Okay, the odds are in my favor
For a blank, so I'm gonna
Myself
Oh, okay
Okay, safe, safe, and then again
The 50, surely I wouldn't lose
The 50-50 the second time around
BLEET! BLEET!
Are you serious?
What the heck? I thought this was an easy game
Careful now
Oh goodness me
Right, three live, two blank
I
Used up all my luck on my daughters
That's what's happened
Three live, shoot the dealer
Okay, the game is feeling kind
Because there's now two live
And one blank
The game is trying to let me win now
I'm just gonna keep shooting
Okay, okay, we did it
We did it, we did it
See, I do not gamble
I have absolutely no
Interesting gamble
And on which you won, replaying
You did it!
Let's go
Let's make this a little more
Interesting
Sorry, I'm getting comfy on my chair
I'm sitting on my toes
Two items each
More items before every load
This is my kind of game
Oh, sheebie!
You didn't tell me you were a part of this game
Sheebie!
You do not, sheebie
Four
One live, one blank
Yeah
So what do you do?
Dealer
Skips the next
turn
Does that mean if I sheebie him up?
So I can just
Shoot both of them and win
Yeah
And then I get to shoot again
Okay, yeah, yeah
I'm getting it, I'm getting it
I'm getting it, so we win
Take that
Okay
Okay, now what?
Oh, I get more items every round
Okay, you should come front
Be your
Meh!
What was that? No, no, no, come back out
What was that? It said God
A magnifying glass
Two
Oh, it's a 50-50 again
What does beer do?
Racks the shotgun
Ejects current shell
Check the current
Round in the chamber
Whoa!
It's a blank
So I'll shoot me
Rack equals pump
I'll pump you in a minute
Don't worry
I don't know if that means the same
But in Scots that means I'm gonna do you
Okay
Well, I did a blank
So two to one
Okay, okay
Oh, poor dealer
He's going down, but I don't wish
him any ill will
He just looks creepy, but I don't
He's taking a cigarette
You know, a cigarette
What? Cigarettes are bad for your health
To health?
Bro
He heals up
and does double damage to me
You wet fart
Release me
Oh, I've lost this
I don't know what kind of
stuff be going on
Sure, I'll take that and that
Why not?
Two blanks
Three live
I'll win in this one
Oh
This is such a creative game though
I'll give it though, I like this
It's live
Well, you'll never guess who I'm shooting
That's so satisfying
I like how it's not too loud either
Do I need to lower in-game volume or it's all good to go
Again
Okay
It's fine, all good
Okay, okay
Oh, can I do multiple items per round?
Wow
I got two blanks, the game's feeling nice to me
Right, I think I can just shoot him
because there's only one left and it's live
Yeah, take that
You wet fart
Okay, we're back on an even
plain field
Okay, what items
What items
What a curious game
God
Okay, all I'm getting is handcuffs and beer
50-50, right
Right, I'll handcuff him
Um, please take these
handcuffs
Oh, it's a harem
Eject the current shell
It's 50-50, this will change the odds
out of 50-50
Shit!
The odds are more likely it's a live round
Oh, we're doing it
We're doing it, we have probability
Okay
Now it's likely to be blank
because the odds are now
one live to two blank
or three blank
Oh, I don't like this part
Okay, okay, it's fine
It's fine
Right, and now
it's again back to being live
Unless
put the gun down
I can't change my mind
Live
No!
I'm not going to make every blanks
Oh, he knows what's inside
Very interesting
Yeah, I'm not surprised
I'm not surprised
It's a 1v1
Careful now
Oh no
I don't know what, I don't even
I genuinely
do not know what's in this
There's no point in racking the shell
Is there?
Cuff him, everyone says cuff him
Right, I'll listen to the replays because you guys are smart
Right, I've cuffed him
And then I'm gonna
Okay
Oh, I just ended the round
Yes, I'll absolutely take that
Oh, and the Sugi
Giyazawi
Whoa, the odds are
very high for a live round
Sorry
Look, I'm not this smart, it's right
Regain a charge, I'll have a wee puff puff
Puff puff puff
Yes, nicotine
No, it's not good, don't ever
actually do it
A blank, right, okay
Okay, okay, me
Okay, that's good to go
Okay, so now it's like 5 to 1
We're just gonna shoot
What a curious game
I'm very intrigued by this
I'm intrigued by the dev team
I'm intrigued by the graph
You won, Refling!
And on one
Yeah
Long last, we arrive at the final showdown
No more defibrillators
No more blood transfusions
Now me and you, we are dancing
on the edge of life and death
Eh
Four items each
Handcuff
Magnifying glass, handcuff
I'm starting to forget about the feet
Eh, you know the drill
Is he gonna handcuff me?
If I handcuff him
I can double
I can double shoot
and the odds are he's gonna get shot
Okay, there you go
Okay, we're doing it, we're doing it
Doesn't tell you what his health actually is
So he's
So we can just double
Oh no, they're both blank, aren't they?
Ah, yeah
Wait, no
Oh no
I messed up, hold on
Yeah, okay, right
Fresh start and two new items
What we get, what we get
Show me the money, we got beer
More handcuffs
Oh, a beer
Four live, four blank
50-50
Handcuff
That gives me two in a row
Eject one to make
seven on the board
Odds are live
Blank
Two blank remaining
Four live, odds are
Shoot, shoot, shoot
One
Blank
Four live
Wow
Can't give him that
Can eject again
Wait, no, wait
What did I just do, sorry, eject
Live, three live, one blank
Shoot
Yeah
Cuff him, oh could I have cuffed there?
No, he's still cuffed
Okay, now he's uncuffed
He's gonna eject
Two live, one blank
Oh, handcuff though
Health revivals
Eject to live
Two live remaining
Son of double for two health
No
Three health total taken
Out of two live
This game is good
Oh, I like this game
Hold on
Okay, we got health
We got a peak, we got two peaks
A health and a cuff
Three live, two blank
Okay
We're gonna cuff
We're gonna heal
Because we do need a cheeky bit health
Because it is
Three live, two blank
Do we take a peak or do we
Wait, no, just taking a peak
Matter if he's cuffed
Well, because yeah
Doesn't matter
No, it doesn't
That's what
Two blank
Oh, dear
Doesn't matter if he's cuffed
Doesn't matter what the results are
I've already forgotten what we're at
Is it one live, two blank
Or two live, one blank
He's got two heals on the board
And he's got double son off
Now it's two live, one blank
Sugar didoo
Yeah, he's gonna shoot me
No, for two health
He's gonna shoot me for the son off
Oh, this is
My odds
Gosh
Wow, hopefully
I can get some cigarettes
Right
Cuff
Wait, why cuff?
It's two blank now
Yeah, so why
Shouldn't have cuffed
Remaining ammo
Zero, they're both blank
What
I'm not right, I need to focus up
I'm getting, I need a piece of paper or something
Maybe there won't be one
Right, items, cuffs
Peak, peak
And oh, we've got a double son off
If we peak, we could get a double
We could get a double
Four to two
Four
To two
Cuff him
Let me know what's going on under the hood
Let me double up the damage under the hood
Beautiful
Let us acquire two HP damage
Oh
That's fine
So now we are three live
Two blank
Now it is a two in three
Oh dear
Oh dear, oh dear, oh dear
Oh, he just released the blank
Oh no
Oh no, this can't be
This can't be
Oh dear
I am on life support
I believe there's
Unless that's it, I don't know
There's two on
Okay
Well, I'm handcuffed
He's won
I've lost the odds game
Oh no
Strummer bad, I'm handcuffed
Are you ready?
Yeah
Well, I can
Hopefully there's a heal
Double damage
Aww, what are these?
Oh, live, live, live, live
Five live, three
Goodness
Me, heals don't work anymore
Oh, you can't even heal anymore
Oh, that's why the game's giving me
Triple damage, right? Let's see what I'm working with
Blank
What was it?
Five to three, so now it's five to two
And then
We'll just check again
Okay, live
And then we'll do double damage
Unfortunately, the odds
Are not in our favor
But hey ho, so that's four
To two
You're not gonna make it
Unless he throws
We ain't gonna make it
Oh wait, what?
Oh
Oh, wait
Are you saying there's a chance?
If it's in the chamber
Against all odds?
I
What'd I do with it?
Oh my gosh
From the brink
What a fantastic game
Oh my goodness
Press any button to exit
Wow
Double or nothing unlocked
Are these the developers?
The symbol?
By computer game by
Mike Kaluub
Nika
Congrats!
What a fantastic game
The visuals, the direction
Do we go again?
Double or nothing? How did I do double or nothing?
Is it just start?
Just start
Start then click the pill bowl
Wow
It's changed
Because of our progress
I'll click the pill bowl
Consume pills
May impair your ability to drive
But reeflings, I don't want you to go
Consume the double or nothing
Oh no the guy's gone
Bye strongy, no reefling no more
Please sign the waiver
Yes
I am blown away by this game
Sorry, wait I know how to spell your name
Sorry, sorry
Sorry I didn't mean to misspell it
It was a genuine mistake
Double damage
Handcuff
Mobile phone
What are you?
One live to blank
I
A mysterious voice gives you insight
From the future
Swap the polarity
I think we'll just cuff and double shoot
If the both of the blanks happen to be in there
Wow I have rubbish luck
Okay that's fine
Now it's a 50-50
If I shoot a blank at him I'm going to be
Should I go all
Oh I'll tell you
Okay rough start
Double or nothing, rough start
Oh he's double starting
Now it's a rough start
Jeez I've got
Two health already
He's got a health upload
Smokes as well
Hydration check
Okay we can pump one out of the chamber
We can heal and we can swap
Oh another polarity
Wow okay interesting curious
Again
With a blank
I am going to pump one out of the chamber
To see what the odds are
Okay now it's 50-50
So I'm going to heal up
Because we already know what's going to happen
And then we're going to
Sol it off
And we're going all in on
Double damage against him
Dealer
Use the phone
Right I'll use the phone
The phone about the current round or the next round
Oh my god he's doing double damage
Against me
That's so bad
Right I'll do the phone, my apologies
I thought the phone was like for the next round
Careful now
Careful refling
Wouldn't want to be dancing
Death row
Let's see you
What is you
Okay
Let's ring ring
Hello
Three lie four blank
The game is trying its best to help me right now
A mysterious voice
How smart do you think
I am reflings
To be able to retain
Information that on the sixth
Shell it's blank
How smart do you think I am
What is this a pipe bomb
Steal an item
And use it
Well
Oh no
Oh that's exactly what happens
They put adrenaline directly into
Your bloodstream
What was that medicine box
I wonder what this is
I don't have it yet
There's nothing I can do
Are those in coffin and double shoot
That also means the fifth isn't going to be blank
Are those going to be blank
I just need to send it
Sorry I can't
No okay
So it means these next few are alive
Gotta go straight to coffin
Meet
Okay
Okay I've definitely messed up this one
What is that
A medicine packet
He takes a pill
Aw healed
Okay that's fine cigarette or pills healed
Oh no
I've lost
Who is he calling
Literally I get
Aw that's such a shame
Wait
He put the polarising effect on
Oh no I'm gone
Sorry
Sorry sorry
I didn't know how the phone worked
Not that it probably would have helped
Oh by the way the sixth one's a blank
Aw thanks for that mate
Let me just add it into my fucking calculator
Have the largest IQ
My brain goes three sides
You know the average person who can only retain
Like freaking what
Four bits of information at a time
Like come on give me a chance game
Let me write it down
Give me a wee piece of paper and I'll write it down
Just like this
He kicked the hell out this cuttlefish
Literally I'm
Calamari right now
By all accounts right let's try that again
Pump one out the chamber
Adrenaline burst health and
Double damage okay
Okay we can work with this
Four report
Two live three blank
What do I do with that
Information
I don't know
If three blank should I shoot
Myself
Or should I make
The odds known if it's 50-50
Three blank two
50-50 double damage
Let's go
Two blanks in a row
Possibly
Oh yes
Okay
He's gonna pump it out
Now it's back to 50-50
I'm being cuffed but I do have a blank
Yep and then one health
Damage on me
Unless he wants to use the polarizing effect
And let me win
But that's slightly different
Okay that's good
Let him get up
Good shot
Are you squinting me right now
Cooper
Brian Blasterman
Thank you for the five Cooper
And yes I will blast the man
Okay two blank one live
I have nothing
What's that medicine
Steelers medicine
I think I'm gonna steal his health
Prevent him from healing up
Give me that
Give me that what does it do
Why did my head just
Two blank one live
Medicine is 50% chance
One damage and two heal
Oh wait is that
You got the good pill if it's a bad pill you'll lose health
Oops
Okay we are classic 50-50
If we get this we have won the first round
Of double or nothing
Dealer
Oh that was a clean round
That was a clean
Round of odds
Very clean
And on win
Okay I'm not taking medicine again
Cause I didn't realise I could hurt myself
With it
Okay
Oh great fucking tiddlywink spawn
No I'm not taking that
Okay what are the rounds let me know
One two three four
Full eight 50-50
Full eight
Remove one from the chamber let me know my odds
Four four
Three four
Hmm
Hmm hmm
Three three
Six total
Fourth shell
Live
Ray
Can I just take his fucking heal then
Six
Four is live
Six total four is live
So I have to
It's most likely a blank
You know that
If four is live in that sequence
There are most likely two blanks
Before it
Wait
Did I not take a heal
Did I not take a cigarette
I'm not being dumb
Did I not
Two is your max
You can't over heal
Oh
Fuck
Fucking just show
This is not gonna work well
No
Why is he didn't polarizing
I
I suck at this game
Get let me go again
Let me go again we've got time for another
Why is this game
Ah okay soak it this shite
The only thing I'm good for sucking is willy
Not this game
Get me in that room
Right you
Again
Please sign the waiver I consent
Your gacha look is not great
I've actually never played a gacha game
Calling a friend
Polarizing in the seat
Right I'm glad we can get a peek
Let's try this again
It's okay
I'm gonna take a peek
What do we got
Alive
I am gonna steal
His son off and give him two damage
Now I'm aware he has a heal there
No I'm not I'm gonna steal his heal
Your cigarettes are mine
Oh you can't over heal
The reeflings just told you
That mere moments ago
That you can't over heal in this game mode
And what do you do
Reade it over heal you could have had him down to two
You could have had him on the ropes
But no no
Okay 50-50 odds
He's getting insider knowledge
Did you know
The celebrities calling the paparazzi
To tell them ahead of time
Where they're gonna
Right
Three lives
Two
Blank
And he's gonna hurt me
Real good
Three lives two blank
We won blank three lives
That's right take that
You stinky stinker
No two lives one blank
Yeah I'm not surprised
I'm not surprised
That's okay that's okay let him get up
Let him get up
So now there is no blank
Where
What
How can that not count
Now it's even again
We're back
Right now
There's no blank
Yeah there's nothing now
Not gonna take that
Might use that
Double or nothing
Double that dammit
Okay 50-50
It's 50-50
What you can do is call in a pow
Let's give him the damage
Let's go let's re-inhale
When I said re-inhale
I didn't mean like
Wind, literally all he
Felt was low
Oh man
Alright so that's blank
Very interesting
What are you stealing
Give it back
Oh you can have that please hurt yourself with it
Oh
I'm gonna make it
I'm so bad at this game
Careful now
I'm trying to be careful
But I suck
Okay if I eject this one
This one's blank so I'm gonna shoot myself
I'm removing this one
The next one is blank
So I'm just gonna play it safe
And do that
He is using developer luck
Remaining ammo oh my god you guys
You're trying to help me so much I'm so bad
I'm so sorry
Right we can now double spawn off at least
Why did I get two turns in a room there
Well it's now even Steven
No it's not
He has two health and not one
What is he doing
Polarize him
What are you gonna do
No I'm so bad
Oh my goodness
This is so hard
Yes please
Let me try again
Let me get up let me get up let me
Be very afraid
The fourth was the blank
Yeah that's why I shot myself with it
Wow sorry this must be painful
I'm so sorry
Look I'm not very smart
You guys didn't figure out I wasn't smart
By playing connect 4 with me
Hang on
You know what
Yeah that's right
Call me big willy
Cause I got a big massive willy
One
Right
Let's try hard
It's time to try
I only got two items
Oh he only got two as well
Big willy
It's a 50-50 the game
Let's try again
If it's a 50-50 I could just win
By doing this
But he can do the save
To shoot me
But he can still hurt me
Cause the first one wasn't
Oh if you shoot yourself
You get to play a second turn
It's finally starting
To make a little bit of sense
But I can't over heal
So don't get jealous
Whoa why so many items
Oh he got loads of items too
Two life three blank
No
Three blank
No it's 50-50
No
It's
Oh god
I can't use my brain and talk at the same time
Just let me see what it is
Please
Okay
So if I shoot myself
I get to go again
And then I get to double shotgun
Barrel
You
Am I doing it?
Am I doing it? I think I'm doing it
I think I'm doing it
No
Why is my luck so poor
There's all life now
What does polarised do
You could have inverted
And then sawn for the win
Wait that works backwards as well
If I know it's blank
I need to polarise it to change it
This must be the most painful place
Or you've ever seen
I even think we're going to be able to do it
In time for Shibi's monetisation stream
Okay I didn't realise
Polarising swapped
Oh shit I did not pay attention
To how many live in
If I know it's a blank
Use polarising
Got it
If I know it's a blank use polarising
Okay it's alive
It's alive
So
I am going to
Steal your double damage
Steal his salt
Yes I'm stealing his double damage
If I know it's a blank
Polarise
You've already finished the game
This is infinite mode
Wait it's the same
Right he's on one health
He's going to sawn a friend
Which is fine
He's going to cuff me
Oh I'm zadding
Oh yeah you want to
cuff me up
Right he's healed
Which is fine we're no one even Steven
What was that
Adrenaline
He's healing again
Oh you greedy
Hello
Why would you do that
Question mark
Did you mean to do that
Okay please
Take a xp
I hear a health down
Oh yeah
Oh no he's didn't polarise
Oh no
Ow
I don't know what it is
I don't know what's left
Oh I do know what's left
So if I blank myself
Oh polarise
Polarise you stupid women
Polarise
Polarise to blank
Oh my god I was so
I freaking clicked it and my brain was like
Wait a minute you were supposed to do something
Freaking polarise
Ah
Okay give me give me give me
Give me give me yeah give me yeah
Give me yeah blank
Right 50-50
Okay 50-50
Inspect element
Inspect element blank
Blank found
Polarise effect
Added
Polarising
And then what shoot myself or shoot him
With polarise on
Shoot him with polarise on
Man she sure is pretty
Yeah that's all I got going for me
This feature of model is adorable
Okay shoot him
We did it I was so sorry
Shoot um right we did it
Willy wins fake Willy wins
Imagine if this is the run I went on
And it's the one I call myself Willy on
Right
Okay let's see what we're working with baby
Rejection calling
And focus right
For health on big Willy
50-50 odds okay
He can see he can cuff
And he can double damage
Maybe the phone
Can tell me if
What's first
If not I'll just use the magnifying glass
That's absolutely nothing
Can you not pick like
The second bullet so I'll actually remember
Right I don't have
Polarising so I can shoot myself for free
That's
One
So odds are
Shoot him
No
Are you f**king
Kidding me
High odds of
Being live
Literally the seventh shell is blank
So and two bullets
Have been utilised
This is the third bullet being utilised
Right
So
So the odds of this one being
Live are high
Again
Oh no
Okay
Is that four
Shots now
So then
Five and six are live
Five is live
So
Does this game want from me
What does this game want from me
My odds
I know you can't rely on odds
That's just how odds work
My odds are
Astronomically
Right Willy's definitely
We can't do it as Willy
We have to go back to our roots
We have to go back to Anon okay
Cause this clearly isn't working
It wants you to suffer
My poor Willy
My poor Willy got blown off
Right
I'm actually can
Pay for it
These are good items
What are the odds
Give me a 50-50
Okay
We've got a 50-50
I can't overheal past two which is fine
If it's
Let me see
What's
Or eject
I might be able to
Eject 50-50
and tell me what's up
Right taking it out alive
So if we're gonna get a blank we're gonna steal the polarizing
No it's live
We actually don't have a double
Oh sugar but he has
the polarizing
Well the next to her blank
So if he uses polarizing
Then he's one
I think
No he can only do one damage to me
This round
Okay okay
Steal the cuffs
I don't think that would have
Oh Andy's healing
Bro
Bro this is not looking good
Why is this game so hard
I just need you guys to like
Send me your gaming fridge
Cause this is getting so bad
Careful now
All I've been told this game is careful now
Yeah yeah yeah they're both blank
We know
We know they're blank
Well at least I have a cigarette
Right
Two live three blank
But he doesn't have a polarizing
So blank actually means blank in this game
I'm gonna steal his cigarette
No
Can I get a vase
Three blank two live
So the three blank are up ahead
So odds are this is blank
Can I steal his health
I don't want him to heal
Yeah this is blank
It's my guess
Right this is blank sorry I'm guessing
But yeah okay odds are
Yeah
Right I'm happy with that
Right we're gonna take a peek
Blank again
Wow
And then the rest are
Live two live in a room
Well unfortunately he's gonna get
A lick in on me
How do I suck so badly
I'm not being funny
I'm getting absolutely
I'm getting
Just
They're making a mockery out of me
They're making an absolute mockery out of me
Does this guy even have a name
Okay phone a friend
Adrenaline
Oh he got a heal I'm gonna steal his heal
Right it's a 50-50
Let me start comboing the items
Oh I'm too dumb for that though
That actually feels like
Injection into
That puts adrenaline into your heart
Which basically forces it to go
Like I'm just shooting
So anyway I start blasting
Cause I'm unable to
Keep up with them
Oh wait I actually won out of
Just pure frustration
We won that round anyway
Starts blasting
We did it we made it to round two
Of double or nothing
I've still yet to make it
To round three
Okay let's see what we get
Cuff
Double damage
Not medicine
Medicine that's not really medicine
Too blind
Does he have a polarizer he does
Phone in a friend
Wow
Steel
Polarizer
Shoot him
Steel Polarizer shoot him
Yes
Steel Polarizer
Shoot him
And then shoot
Okay then he'll shoot
Blank on me
Cause we know it doesn't have
Anything in it
And then double sawing off
Oh he's healing
So let him shoot
It's just fine cause it's blank
Oh for god he can get an extra turn
Efficient himself
I keep forgetting the mechanics
Of this dumb game
Why is it he is allowed to heal
And he's allowed to do this
And he's allowed to do that
Don't you know the video game rules
Only I'm supposed to be able
To do all the things that help me
Win the game
Wow
I never thought that far ahead
I never thought in the first place
That should be my sentence
I don't think
Right what was that 50-50
Right at least we can heal first
Watch your enemies hand close
Bro
Hordeshell library
That gives me nothing thank you
Let me again
What's in the chamber
Blank
I don't have a polarizer
So I can officially shoot myself
Bunk
Right and then
And then what
I mean that means odds are
It's a double
Cuff him
Okay and then what
And then
What I can do is just guess
I'll say it from this one
So what's this the third
Wow
This is why I don't gamble
I have no interest in gambling
I have no interest in playing Genshin Impact
Because it's a gamba game or something like that
I actually don't know if Genshin Impact is a gamba game
But yeah
Remaining ammo inside
You're trying to help me and it doesn't help
Because I'm so dumb it doesn't help
I'm too dumb to be helped
You guys are just
Gonna have to send in your gameplay and I'll commentate over
And pretend that I'm playing
That seems like a plan
Surely
I'm not I'm losing it
Right
New round
Let's see what we're working with
Two lives three blank
A burner
Just show me if it's good or bad
It's good
I don't have a polarizer though
Clink
And there's four in the chamber left
So let's talk to the phone
Because they say, listen
Okay
That means the odds have increased
That this is a live round
So we're gonna say funk it
And
We start splasting
Yes
Okay we know next is blank
He doesn't
He doesn't have a polarizer either
Oh
Good or bad
We know this is blank
But we know that this is live
And now he knows it's live
And he's got a double
It's ogre
He's cuffing me bro
Wait what
Now it's live
Oh my goodness golly
This game if you are
Like me in small brain
This game ain't for you
I got one more in the tank
Because she be getting ready to go live
We got one more
Come on
That's it you know what
I'm writing down
This freaking piece of paper
What the heck is going on in this game
I'm gonna call in
This freaking
I'm gonna call in the big guns
Which is me writing on a piece of paper
To write down the odds
To write down what there is
To write down what to do
If we do not win this one
This settles it
That you guys are just far too smart for me
And you have picked the most
Are worded oh she
There possibly could be in all the lines
Right pull out items
Magnifying glass
Health
No don't want meds
I'm not taking my meds
You can't convince me
Right what's in the chamber
Two live
Three
Lang
And then I'm gonna do it like hangman
On my piece of paper
So the odds
Are already
Not the best
I am going to
Seal
His phone
I'm gonna steal his phone
No
Yes
Yes I'm going to
To steal his phone to get the intel
Fifth shell blank
Okay so for hangman there's now a B
On the fifth one
For blank
We are going to see what's inside
Cause either way we're doing damage to this round
It's a blank so we're going to
Apply the polarizing effect
We're gonna put B on the first hangman
Section as well
So we're polarizing
To make it hurt
The dealer is being shot
With the polarizing effect
Resulting damage to the dealer
Okay
So first one's blank, last one's blank
We now know this, that's perfectly fine
We're lint
All it took was writing it down on a piece of paper
And playing hangman
Neither am I, that's why we're playing hangman
He is now inspecting
He claims the contents
Are very interesting
He shoots me with a live
Round so the second position
Is live
We are now on a 50-50
On the contents of the gun
Being live or blank, we cannot ascertain
We can heal up
But we cannot ascertain
What is inside
This truly is a 50-50
He drank a beer
What did I miss it?
Two and three were live
The blank, wait
But none of us have a polarizer
So this round can't be complete
So we need to start a new
Freaking round in hangman game
Goodness gravy
All blanks
Okay, okay, okay
A BBL
No I didn't get a BBL but thanks for asking baby
Right
Let's play hangman over again
Let me, what is the ratio
Three live, four blank
Three live, four
Blank
For a total of seven on hangman
One, two, three, four, five
Seven
I have adrenaline to call in
For information
Which we're going to do
Right, you can yoink the yoink
Right, position
Second shell, blank
Hangman, second is B, blank
Oh sugar, I just dropped my pencil
If we handcuff
And we are going to act like
The first one is live
Okay
We are going to treat it as live
We do not know and we cannot ascertain
If that information is true or not
However, we can shoot ourselves for
Okay, that was a blank
So first two are filled out B's
That leaves
Two blank and three live on the board
We are going to shoot ourselves
To give ourselves another round
Sadly
There are now five
Pieces remaining
And we cannot ascertain
The knowledge, so we're going to treat it
As alive, this truly is a 50-50
We're going to treat it as alive
Because odds are it's alive
You know what, I'm just going to go fuck myself then
You know what, because that's the thing with odds
That is the thing with odds
That is the thing
With odds
Yeah
It could literally, you can flip a coin
10 times in a row and statistically
Never get hits 10 times in a row
But that's the thing with odds
They are not reality
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah
That's, right, another
Sorry, I'm addicted
I'm addicted, I like this approach
Sorry, the hangman approach is quite fun
I'm addicted, I can't stop
She beats up in 10 minutes
We've got 10 minutes to speak on this
Come on
10 minutes
Oh my god, come on, come on
Please save the waiver
I will, anything for you dealer
Again, again, again, again
Okay
Who goes there?
Identify yourself
3 life, 4 blank
7 hangman
Okay
We have adrenaline
We are going to get intel
from this adrenaline
I assume you can only use adrenaline once per round
Right, the intel is
The intel is third shell life route
Okay
Can we do double adrenaline?
Hello
Double adrenaline
That's cheating
Blank, shit, we need, oh we have a polarizer
Okay, that's perfect
If we handcuff
Or does that leave
That's 2 life on the board
We don't know about 3 life on the board
We don't know about
Tell you what we could do
Handcuff
Polarize
Shoot
Discard
The current unknown
Because we don't know what it is
We don't know what it is
And I don't trust it
So we're just going to discard it
Okay, we're just going to discard it
It doesn't really matter
Okay, so we can write down blank in second
So now there's 2 blank and 2 life
The odds are straight back to 50-50 again
We are going to shoot
Okay, okay
So now there's 1 blank remaining
And 2 live on the board
Hmm
I'm going to eject a blank
So all remaining are now live
Shit
And he's going to do 3 health damage
In the sequence
Wait
Yeah, no, yeah, sorry, sorry, sorry
Then blank was the 5th there
And then it's 2 live remaining now
Sorry, my apologies
2 live remaining
Okay
Unfortunately, he will get a lick in on us
But that's fine, that's fine
Do you feel so big brain now?
No, I'm cheating by playing Hangman
And writing it down, that's how hard this game is
For me to conceptualize it in my head
I cannot do this
In an abstract
Concept
I don't have the ability to do this
I have to write everything down, it has to be physical
In front of me
We've got 2 insights
Fantastic
Oh
I'm not going to do it for this round
Umm
He's got a polarizer?
No he doesn't
I might as well shoot then
Shouldn't I?
There's no point in using this stuff
It's a 50-50, I might as well just shoot
There's no point
I've got 2 phones
1 for the velar, no use the phone
No get info
Wait, wait, wait, hold on, hold on
What's the point in me using the phone
Right now, because it's 50-50
If it's a blank
Oh wait, yeah
Idiot, if it's a blank then he can't get a licking on me
Sorry
Sorry, I'm a bit slow
I'm a bit slow
I'm so sorry
I'm so slow
It takes me a moment to remember
The way this game plays
I'm so sorry
Okay
We are on to the second round
Yay
Okay, okay, okay, okay
Big brain time
Can you feel the wrinkles
becoming more wrinkly in your brain?
Your smooth piece of
chicken breast brain is now
magnifying
3 live, 3 blank
Okay
Insider knowledge, yes please
Third shell, blank
Okay
Adrenaline
Yonkers
I would like insider knowledge from the adrenaline
burst
Okay
What are you going to tell me?
Fourth shell, blank
Okay
Now
That leaves one blank
Unknown
The odds
is now one in four of the current
shell in the chamber being a blank
I think I want to shoot
So anyway
I start blasting
The odds of one in four
Yep, okay
That's what I like to see
Live one in four
We are going
Okay, he's going to heal up
That's perfectly fine
He is going to be able to see what's inside
And he does have a polarizer
So I'm going to have to be cautious of that
He's going to check it out
What do you see?
Very interesting
Okay
Oh he's shooting, it's alive
So the next two we know are blank
So we can
Blank it up to high heavens, okay
Blank
Bonk
And then blank again
Thanks to our insider knowledge
I can't believe it, hangman works
And blank again
Then we are going to drink the beer
To inject the second last bullet
Because we will be able to
If this is blank
Or if it's live
So that was live
So that means the remaining one
Is blank
So we can just shoot ourselves
Bonk, okay
All good, all good in the hood
New round
We do
Insider
The game knows we are playing hangman
The game knows
What we got, 4 live
4 blank
4 live
Hangman, 1, 2, 3
Okay I don't have enough room on the paper
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8
Sorry I need to re-write that
That really awkward bit
Right
Give me the
What's the update
Let us know what's going on here
3rd shell
Live, perfect
Let me know what else is going down
Obliet
I didn't realise he could do that
I didn't know he could do that
Like thanks
Right I'm going to
Judgement, I'm still going to take this
Because it's so much better and more valuable
To know what's coming up
5th shell, live, okay
Okay, okay, okay
We only don't know where 2 are
That leads me to believe
So the odds are now
What
1 in 3
That this is blank
No, that's not
That's not correct
I want to shoot myself
Against my better judgement
I'm going to claim this as a blank
Because statistically it should be
We did it
Okay we have a second round now
There are
Blank
What does this mean
Cigarettes
I can't heal up I don't think
In Minecraft
Unknown
2nd live
I don't know
Shit or not, your max is HP
4, oh is it sorry
Let's have a wee quick siggy break
We'll start all over this
Thank you, sorry, my apologies
I thought this was like you couldn't heal it
A 4, 4, 4
Should we get a cigarette, smoker and gen 2
Apparently that's a really big
Kink
That I didn't know about
You know a wham and smokes a siggy
No, I don't know what it's going to be
You know what
If I shoot myself
It's actually going to not be that bad
Okay, we know this one is live
So we can shoot
Oh no a double shot
Shit
I get so excited to like
Utilize
We would have gone on to the next round
If I wasn't so freaking quick
Shorty
Okay, he just ejected a live
So it's live, live, live actually
Wait what
Oh
Thanks for letting me go to the other round
Even though I messed up
I appreciate you dealer
The game must know I'm like sweating so hard
We finally made it
To round 3
Okay
Hangman ain't got nothing on us
Medicine
Polarize
That's very
That's fine
2 blank
3 blank sorry
Sorry number
We have no insider
Information at all
We have odds which is blank
The odds stipulate
This is a blank so I shouldn't theory
Put the polarizing on
And shoot myself
We have to go with odds
We have no choice
The dealer with polarizer on
So that was a blank
So now it's 2-2
50-50 perfect and he can see what's inside
Very interesting
Live
Okay
The odds are now 1 live, 2 blank
Wow
If I take the medicine I expire
Because my odds are not good enough
This is it
I either win this game mode
Or I lose it on whatever we pick
Refling's
Now the odds are this is blank
Swallow the medicine
I'll swallow it because you asked
Me to refling
Ah
Refling
Forever time because she be live
With celebration
It was worth it though
I died doing what I love the most
Guzzling refling's ink
I perished doing what I love the most
Okay
So I don't feel that bad
So good that was fantastic
I can 100% see us
Revisiting this game in a membership stream
I don't like replaying games
I may have already done before
But thank you so so much
For that fantastic
Experience on this game
Another 10 out of 10 game
Shout out to the developer
That is like such a fun little odds game
So goofy, incredibly entertaining
And the graphics
As well as the design
Visual design
Is absolutely beautiful
Some people might not enjoy
The poly
Looking art
I can't remember what the art style
Art style is the word I'm looking for
The art style
Right, we are going to
Redirect into none other
Than she be
Cotton bum for her
Saikam
Membership monetization
Celebration, wherever the
Frick diddle-a-dack
I am going to
Make sure I am redirecting into her
But that was fantastic
Thank you so much for playing that game with me
That was so good
We will definitely hangman this game
At a later date
Because gosh golly gee
That was just amazing
We finally started
It started to click at the end
I need to redirect into Sheepsters
Because that didn't work properly
Thank god I checked
Right, all good in the hood
I think
Yes, thank you so so much Reeflings
I will see you
You, yes you
For an ASMR stream
At the regular time
And then 15 minutes later
I will swap all my equipment back
To my regular streaming equipment
And we will have a membership watch
Along of Transformers
And don't be greedy, see that
Don't be a naughty Reefling
And see that, okay? Thank you so so much
For hanging out, that was absolutely amazing game
And I will see you
Giffy Gibbers
Pardon me as I burp my cola up
Tomorrow, my little Reeflings
We'll do it all over again
Okay, say hi to Sheeby for me
Bye Reeflings, I love you
Say hi Sheeby, right now