Mummy, the mummy hasn't abandoned no thing.
Mummy is in a foolish, foolish streamer.
When I did the footstream, I put my ring light.
I had to move my ring light so I could elimp the shit and put it down to the wall.
As it eliminate that mummy started streaming on her hands and knees, it's not what she did.
I need the ring light.
The thing that is flashing is the goofy and it's jumping about everywhere.
It went on and on.
So that is going to be the light.
Please, it's the only light.
Okay.
Alright, my face is eliminated.
I'm also on reactive mode so I'm actually going to react to the game.
Everyone knows I have an NVIDIA GeForce RTX 3080 with 10,067 megabits.
Hello, good morning.
Let me put it on.
Live chat.
Any live chatter?
Good morning, good evening, good afternoon.
I apologize if I sound tired.
I passed out after that RuneScape stream and I woke up 45 minutes ago.
I hope Icy's monetization stream went fantastic.
I believe Emmys is also today.
So if there's any pin pals or snowberries, they're down the hall.
Into the lift.
I apologize if I sound tired.
I am exhausted.
I don't know how.
I slept for so long.
I don't know what is going on with me.
But I've got cup of tea.
I've got two waters.
I've got a wee muffin.
And then we can jump into Crash Bandicoot.
As for any updates, since I slept, I have absolutely nothing.
A refling sent me a three page story, which I really liked.
But for legal reasons, I cannot speak any of it here.
I've also put together a little folder of BibBits.
Which I don't know why I didn't think to do it earlier.
But now I'm putting it all together.
Oh and a refling sent me a five minute audio.
And he was like, talk!
I was like, oh my god, reflings are getting so brave, honestly.
And before I die a lot, probably, probably, I'm not even going to put it behind me.
I don't know what level the desktop, how loud the game is going to be compared to me.
But give me a three page story.
It was about me, obviously.
But yes, you guys have been doing fantastic.
I believe AC has done well.
I don't really have any updates about anything else at the moment.
Other than my freaking ASMR meme video, I've got 30k views.
And I'm like, right, this has definitely left the target audience.
Because I had 5,000 subscribers when I posted that.
And now we're at 6,000.
I'm like, bruv, that like propelled my channel.
So I'm waiting, Mercy's is going to go up after this stream.
Or, or it's going to go up after she finishes her stream today.
And then AC's is ready to go up.
I may actually, I'm going to message her right now so she can reply to me.
And see, when you finished stream, do you want me to upload your meme ASMR on your behalf question mark?
And before you're like, wait, why are you asking the girls permission to do stuff that you made for them?
Because it's their channels.
I don't want them to be unhappy.
I want them to be happy little ducklings with me.
Who up?
Bandy their cooter.
Whoa.
Okay.
I'm getting a bit too close to that one.
Any Bandy cooters?
It's only such a sweetheart.
Yes, I don't want to do anything that upsets the girls.
And if they're like, no, now's not the time to upload the meme ASMR.
That's fine.
So I'll get permission from them and then possibly after the stream.
Apparently it takes eight hours to do this game.
Now, I'ma just say, I was a atom when I played this game.
I have barely any recollection.
My dad didn't buy it for me.
He bought it for himself.
Johnny, congrats on 6.5k.
No, I owe so many ASMR videos.
I was going to try and get my first thank you video out.
Oh.
Well, maybe after buckshot roulette after the doc.
Because I've got buckshot roulette.
Then I've got a couple hours.
Then I go to the doctor.
Is this a rhythm game?
It is not.
It's Crash Bandicoot.
It is an adventure platformer.
I know you can't hear the background of the game right now.
So it's just my voice in this room.
Do forgive.
Strongly winning a game.
Any ganky desks?
Hold on, let me hydrate with my tea.
I owe so much ASMR.
I do have it all recorded.
I just need to sit and edit it.
And I can't upload the clapping without using my hands ASMR.
Yet, I need to have some things in between it.
Strongly winning much and everything right.
It's a never ending move.
Every time she releases an ASMR, she gains 1k and she gets to go back to square one.
Honestly, I'm like, I hope not.
I think it will definitely calm down a bit.
It's going to have to calm down.
Because as much as our capitalist overlords love infinite growth,
that's just not plausible here.
Nor is it something that is healthy or thingy.
Because if you start measuring yourself by numbers and that kind of thing,
that's when, I think that's when VJubers probably get it in their head.
They're like, oh, I'm not doing well enough.
I'm not performing well enough.
And it's like, Brev, you haven't even given yourself a chance.
Just have fun.
People can tell you're sweating on trends if you're trying to sweat on trends, you know?
And then people can tell when you're just meaming around,
when you're just meaming around, you know?
And guess what?
You know, some streamers, sorry, this has just turned into a philosophical,
let's digest and get to the roots of why streamers are streamers.
Some people are just, what's the word,
optimized to have a nice, cosy, tight-knit community.
Okay?
Some people, some of your personalities, other streamers,
you're just supposed to have a nice little tight-knit community.
You're not supposed to be for the masses, you know?
So don't always be reaching for the fricking stratosphere, the stars.
Don't always be reaching for the stars when you do just fine in the stratosphere, you know?
Every time you gain 1k, you release an ASMR that gains you 1k.
So it's an infinite feedback loop you'll be at.
Infinity subs by the end of the week.
Not quite.
Especially those looking to extract numbers from TikTok that only have 100 subs,
but say they deserve a million views on every post.
Yes.
I can actually get into the psychology on why people feel they deserve subscribers,
versus others who feel unworthy of what they get because of what they've done.
I could definitely go on an algorithm stream that in, not tinfoil time,
no it's not tinfoil, it's not tinfoil, it's not tinfoil.
It's like human psychology as well as the damage that the internet does to the mind.
Cos if you didn't know, you're actually not supposed to be exposed to,
I think you're not supposed to actually know more than 100 faces at once,
and your brain is just not wired for any other way.
After that, your brain can only be wired to recognise tribes, which sounds terrible,
but that's just how it is, so it's like, ah, I am approaching the AC clan, you know?
Or the tribe.
Are you studying psychology?
Absolutely not, I have had enough of education.
I say that, I might be going back to beauty school,
but that's for, I'm talking like five years down the line beauty school type thing,
because I might want to run an ASMR room studio type thing,
but that's just me, that's just me.
Need a tinfoil hat or more?
For the reflins?
Honestly, I'm so down for that.
I need the meds to moat back, I need the thigh gripper moat back,
all other emotes that I need back.
I was actually going to ask if a refling has any batch to emotes,
so wink wink, if you could send me a cat box file of the batch itself,
so I know what to reorder, because I picked what I wanted.
Just so you know, just so we're all on the same, I picked what I wanted.
Oh yeah, Crash Bandicoot 3.
Yes, so I was but an atom and my dad bought this game for himself,
and the only thing I remember doing on this game is playing Coco on China
and using the horse all the time.
The horse, the tiger all the time.
I'll have to catch stream later as I'm working on eight slides of insurance termed out.
Even the thought of that is terrible.
I don't know what's going on with my teas, I've not been enjoying them as of late.
I'm getting a bit nervous, I'm getting a bit shaky why I'm not enjoying my teas,
because normally I'm all over them.
Although I have been enjoying this fruit juice company thing,
and they put loads of fruit in the juice, and then they juice it,
and then I drink the juice, and then I get all the goodness in me.
Yeah.
I've had too many teas, this is a very plausible and realistic sense.
Although I've only had one tea the day, I'll literally only, I woke up like,
well I woke up an hour ago now,
woke up, spammed the PC on, started spamming pre-chat for a few moments,
checked out AC to see what's going on with her, she's fine,
checked out the Discord to see if the girls are fine, they're fine,
refueling, slacking flavour lately.
You're not enjoying the tea because it's all just special, aren't you?
Oh my god, it sounds terrible, but should I just get a cola?
I don't think drinking a cola first thing in the morning is a good idea though.
It's a terrible idea.
Okay, let's get into Crash Bandicoot.
Any Crash Bandicooters?
Is that too loud? Or is that fine?
Oh my god.
How do I leave? Oh, my controller isn't even awake, hold on.
Yeah, plug my controller in.
So there's three games in it, I've only ever played Warped,
I don't know what the other two are about.
Hey, I guess the game.
Override save.
Is it too loud?
Guys, groovy as anything, maybe turn it down a little.
Okay, I'll do it in the start menu after the cutscene.
Oh, we're crashing?
Oh, I guess we are called Crash Bandicoot.
Thank you.
Oh my god, that's so beautiful.
Oh, it kinda looks like a Snow Berry.
Snow Berry.
Oh my god, this is so beautiful, this game.
It was that Infernal Bandicoot.
Bandicoot.
Oh, wait, it's a Tiki Mask, like Earth Tiki Mask guy.
Okay.
Oh.
What?
Insane.
Oh, I don't remember any of this.
Whoa, fuck it.
Oh, that was a flashbang first thing in the morning.
Did you see that?
I can't see anymore.
Oh my god, this game is so beautiful and cool.
For real, I think I just got a virus.
Oh, wait, wait, wait, I remember something like that.
Oh my gosh, that was so beautiful.
Wait, hold on.
I need to turn down the volume a little bit.
My apologies.
Game options, music, 8.
Wait.
Oh, I could do this all day.
We'll do 8s.
Oh my god.
Oh, wait, you can't control the camera angle.
What does Y do?
Y shows me my light, what does B do?
No.
Oh my god, POV, I'm coming for AC.
I'm a snowberry going for AC.
Oh my god, on the prowl, on the prowl.
I'm an Oji-san.
Come to me, AC, my princess.
Daddy wants...
Oh my god, this is so precious.
This is so cool.
Oh my god, wait, I remember these symbols a little bit.
No.
I mean, it's more powerful because I'm the goodie.
You're the baddie.
Oh my god, right.
Where does this work?
Oh my god.
Oh my god, this is like, you can...
Oh my god, we flints, we're already on the farm.
10 out of 10 game, we're already on the farm.
Wait, how do I do that?
To jump to spin to crutch for inventory.
Why would I need to see my inventory?
I guess if you're going for like 100%, but...
Oh my god, we can bomb.
This game is beautiful.
Don't remember that.
Does that need to hurt it?
Oh no, we spanked it.
Right, we spanked it.
We didn't kill it.
We spanked it away.
Okay, it's fine.
Oh god.
Oh my god.
Oh no, thank you for the 5.
Okay, I can definitely take fall damage.
Oh my...
Checkpoint.
I'm remembering.
Wait, go back on the farm.
Go back on the farm.
What does this do?
Okay, if you hit it at a certain time.
Oh my god, we're on the farm.
Right, frogs.
Frogs can hurt us.
Go back on the farm, where you belong.
Oh my god, I can spank everyone.
Oh, I love this game.
Wait, how about if I get two of the good bookers?
Oh, he's glowing.
Oh, you are glowing.
What the heck is it?
What did I do?
Where am I going?
Oh no.
What's this?
Oh, it's bone.
I got an achievement for doing this.
It's a bonus level.
Wow.
Is this just like free apples?
Oh my apples.
I never picked them up.
Oh my god, that's so cool.
Fa la la la la la la.
Who's farm the dream?
The bleeding hearts are getting spanked.
For real, for real.
A wimper fruit.
One puff, one puff fruit.
Go back to the farm.
Oh, we trick shot it with the bleeding heart.
We trick shot it.
Go back to the farm.
No frog for gen two.
Oh my god, Shibi really wants a slim girl for gen two.
I don't know how to break it to her.
She really wants a gen two.
I'm just like, maybe I'll give Shibi a Halloween outfit.
Wait, have we already been here before?
Or is this just kind of the same layout?
Okay, and spank.
What?
It's pink.
Why is there a gap in this bridge?
We need someone who works with stone to fix the bridge.
No slim girl?
No, maybe I'll give Shibi a slim Halloween outfit.
How about that?
Slim girls.
I get it.
What?
Oh, wait, so if you miss it, you'll...
Okay.
I missed a box.
Stinky, I don't know where it was.
Slim girls are my favorite monster girl.
Oh, but slimes are hot.
I'm not sure.
I don't know.
Oh, they came out of my ear hole.
Oops.
And then we just go back in Indra too.
Oh my god, that's cool.
This game is easy.
I like how fun and easy it is here.
Lamia's are my favorite.
I would entertain a Lamia.
Oh, the fisher thing.
To kick fast.
Whoa!
Okay, wait, that was very dumb.
Sorry, that was incredibly dumb.
Whoa, this game's so pretty.
Sorry, I've not got much accuracy under the war,
even though I'm a cuttlefish.
I know.
I don't want to...
Did I just like go past them?
Wait, that's a checkpoint.
Oh my gosh!
I remember something like this.
I used to be so scared of it as a child.
I thought I only remembered Coco.
I can hear a box back there.
Wait, what does that shark do?
Please email him.
Oh, there's a sand dollar.
On the ground.
Whoa, there's...
Jeez, this game is so cute.
I can't believe I didn't play this before.
Well, I mean...
Sorry, I got scared.
I don't know if I can hurt those pufferfish.
Checkpoint.
Why checkpoint?
What's here that shouldn't be here?
Is there something below that's going to kill me?
Because why did I get a checkpoint?
You can switch to play Coco.
Oh!
Oh my gosh.
What?
No wonder this game did so good.
It's like so creative.
Bomb, bomb, bomb.
Oh, there's hidden boxes under the coral rays.
That's okay.
We're not going for 100%
because I don't know how to 100% this game.
But we can go for lots of fruit.
Probably yummy yummy fruit.
Oh, I can beat shark up in this.
And I can explode things in this.
Let's go.
Oh no, I broke it.
I'm sorry.
I'm a bit of a klutz.
I accidentally broke it.
Bomb, bomb, bomb.
Oh wait, that's not the song anymore.
It's whatever the underwater.
Oh!
Sure, we'll get these boxes.
I think it's safe enough.
Oh my god.
What do you mean I'm so in love with a game
that's got the difficulty for literal children?
I can't believe it.
The accusations are unfounded.
I play Skyrim on Legendary mode
just because you can.
It doesn't mean you need to be...
Wait, can I hurt this?
Oh no, I can beat up the little puffer fish.
Oh, the purple puffers.
Okay, there we go.
Whoa, there's the prank crystal.
Okay, let's get it.
Wait, is that going to explode?
Oh wow!
Oh, if you don't do it in time,
it becomes a solid.
Okay, that's curious.
Is it hard to get 100%?
Oh, I missed a lot of boxes this time.
Didn't do that good this time.
But it's okay.
I'm happy just loving everything.
The scene reminds me so much of Jack and Dax, though.
Jack and Dax.
Oh, I threw that one up this time,
so it doesn't always come out your ear.
Wee!
The Orient Express.
Coco!
Oh, this is the mission!
Oh my god, this is the mission.
Ah!
Coco!
And we're for the Tigers.
They missed!
Oh my god!
I know it's like first thing in the morning,
but I'm so happy!
Oh my god!
This is the mission that I always remember
from childhood.
Oh my god!
Go, Coco!
You're doing it!
Oh, you're so beautiful!
Oh my god!
It's the music!
Get it, get it, get it, get it!
Get it, get it!
Oh my god!
Get it, get it, get it!
Yes!
Oh no, I hurt myself.
Oh, I didn't know what I was supposed to do there.
I forgot.
I forgot, but I got a checkpoint, so it's okay.
Oh, I jumped into it!
Coco, no!
No!
Oh, but it's okay.
The Tiger forgives me for being a terrible driver.
Oh, I did it again!
Oh shit!
Stop jumping!
What happens?
Oh, okay.
No more jumping.
No jumpies.
Jumpies, no.
But no jumpies.
And then big boy jumpies.
Oh, I missed.
What the heck?
I was so close.
Oh, if I run ahead, I can attack.
Run!
Tiger!
Oh, how can you?
Oh no!
It's so bad!
Oh my god!
Wait, what happens if I run out of lives?
Is it over?
Is it over for me?
This is over for me?
Wait, can I just run ahead and hurt them?
Whee!
Whoa, that was a freaking leap and a half!
Call me Joe Leeper,
because one Tiger run is all it takes.
Whee!
Oh my god!
That's such a good mission!
Oh, my little Tizer!
Soft, giddy, warm, giddy, little ball of fluff.
Oh, that's the best mission in the entire game.
Okay, we can end stream now.
That's all we needed to do.
I don't know what the diamond is.
Right, what we got next.
The Boneyard!
There are like three more of that?
Oh my god!
What?
Oh no!
Neurons activated from childhood.
I think I get chased this entire mission!
Oh no!
Oh no, there's lava everywhere!
It's jumping faster!
Oh, I don't know, I'm jumping faster!
Oh my god!
Wait, why did you do that?
Crash, crash!
Crash, why did you do that?
Crash, jump, crash!
Crash, you need to jump like double jump!
Whoa, wait, I can't do it!
Wait, can I just stay here forever in the tower?
Is that a Tyrannosaurus talk or something like that?
Wait, why can I not jump that?
Can you double jump it again?
Oh, is it that?
Jump, spin?
Whoa, I could hardly get over that!
Oh no!
I can't believe it, childhood me strikes again!
Can I not double jump?
Hold the jump!
Hold the jump?
What the heck?
I'm not going to make it!
I'm going to run out of life!
Oh no!
Wait!
Wait, it's not doing anything!
Hold on, let's practice.
Jump, jump, jump, jump, jump!
Jump?
I don't know how to double jump.
It's not letting me double jump.
Oh, it is letting me double jump.
Wait, but I jumped right into it!
Oh my god, it's so over and the stream hasn't even freaking started!
I can't figure it double jump.
Is my input wrong?
I'm holding A on my controller.
There is no double jump.
He is...
I'm getting so confused.
Is this a child's game or not?
Answer me!
Is this game for kids to complete or not?
It's not looking good.
Can't even get through the first freaking jump!
Dash jump is one way.
It's for kids.
I'm getting filtered by level 3 actually.
I don't know how to do it.
I'm like trying to extend the jump.
But there's nothing to extend it.
It's just a street magma jump!
You unlock double jump after beating a boss.
Wait, so leave and then go to beat a boss and come back?
Are you holding your jump button down instead of tapping?
If I tap, hold, tap.
Holding, tapping.
Right, hold A.
Holding A.
Fuck!
This is me holding A!
Okay, it just seems to be like so tiny and slate.
Like minuscule.
Right, this is the furthest I've ever got.
Don't mess up now.
Okay, I need a breather honestly.
Alright, I'm just going to keep going.
Oh my god!
Why was that so hot?
Oh, that's TNT!
That's more TNT!
They explode!
Okay, we did it.
Oh gee, willikers, I sure hope we don't have to do that segment again,
because what the heck, why was that so hard?
I literally have no double jump open.
You should try jumping over them.
Timing matters.
What's this?
Oh, a platform?
I don't have access to it.
Go away, you scared me.
Oh my god, it's discord nature!
Did this...
What does that do?
Okay, well, I remember what it does now.
Wait, can I do this?
Go away, you're so creepy!
Where are you?
Oh, bonus time, bonus time!
That's what it does.
Don't touch the nature.
No discord daddies.
No discord groomers in the velar.
Good luck.
Bounce?
Oh my god, free life!
Well, I definitely needed that after how...
Why is he so slow when he crouches?
Okay, I like the bonus distance.
Where's the key?
I tried to tap crouch when walking to get faster.
Tap crouch while walking.
Oh, every hundred apples, I get a life.
Ah, those things are so scary.
Exclamation mark.
What the heck did I just do?
Oh no, I was supposed to jump.
I missed the jump.
I was supposed to jump on top of the moku.
I don't like this camera angle.
No, this is why I didn't like the camera angle.
It felt like I was going to get chased again.
Okay, give me the checkpoint at least.
Oh, there's...
Gate the way up.
No, no, no!
Wait, what was that?
Crash? Crash?
Did you just stand on lava and let me win?
Oh my God, the game feels so bad for me.
That is letting me win.
It feels so bad for me.
Please don't slow me down.
Oh my God, get me out of here.
Oh, get me out of here.
I'm not playing this level again.
Wampa roots, they're wampas.
Sorry.
Oh my God, the game felt so bad it let me walk on lava.
Oh, that came up more.
Honestly, me right now.
Did I do four there?
Yes, I did.
Right, we're not playing that one again.
That one was stinky.
We're doing five.
We're doing...
Oh, Coco!
What's this one?
Making waves.
Course...
Huh?
To accelerate, right trigger.
There's no backwards.
Oh my God, it's so wobbly, wobbly!
Whee!
Jump shot!
Oh my God, this is...
Oh, there's a bomba.
Wait, wait, let me get the bomba.
Trick shot, trick shot, trick shot, trick shot.
Oh, 360.
I missed fast, okay.
360!
She's actually doing spins.
I'm not doing any input for her to do those spins, by the way.
I'm just jumping on it.
Oh, there's bombas!
Bomba!
Oh no, I've only got seven lives.
Oh well, I just regained a new one.
Okay.
This is a child's game.
Children can play this, so I can play this.
For I too, I'm wise enough to play a child's game.
Surely.
Surely I won't have to run out of lives.
If I play the same game,
like same level over and over,
did I just get infinite lives?
Because we might have to farm lives
unironically.
Right, hold on, what's going on here?
No, yes, yes.
Okay, we made it, and we're going to get this checkpoint.
Excuse me?
I said we're going to get this checkpoint.
Coco!
Oh my god.
Edging me right now.
Wow!
Oh, that was close, that was close.
I was a bit too close for comfort.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Timon's going to be fine.
Oh, there's a seagull!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Slow it down, slow it down.
Slow and steady, when's the race?
Do I need to go 100 miles per minute?
Wah!
Honestly?
Good game.
I am going to drop it to the bomb!
But I didn't, because I'm so
emotional at this child's game.
Wah!
Oh, there's two bombs, that's cheeky.
The devs did that for a reason.
They knew I was going to be greedy
and go for the bomba.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Hello?
Okay.
Holy crap, I was like, can I even
go near that at all?
Steady, easy, easy.
Take it easy.
Steady.
I'd say someone steady wins the race, but sometimes
sometimes you're going to just send it
and get out of here.
Oh my god.
Oh, this is so good.
Who suggested this game?
Congrats on you if you suggested it.
Just kidding, I picked it, because it's a child's
game.
Okay.
The boss fight!
Oh no!
Tiny Tiger.
Oh no.
Am I going to get perished by a boss?
Crash.
Stole the pretty crystals.
Tiny, take them back.
Excalibur Arena.
Sometimes here.
Oh no.
All the music is banging though.
MonkaS.
MonkaS, what'd I do?
MonkaS, MonkaS, MonkaS, MonkaS.
Ah!
Please leave me alone.
Oh my god, he's got J's on like me.
Spank!
Okay, okay, it's fine, it's fine.
One and three, one and three, we follow.
What does that mean?
There's Tigers!
I'm to avoid
everything.
Uh,
what?
I'm to avoid all those Tigers?
Right, Spank
and then Tigers. Right, we can do this.
We can do this.
Okay, take your time.
Uh-huh.
Oh yeah, uh-huh.
Okay, okay, I just got a little call
up in the last one.
Okay, just keep running.
Just keep running, just keep running.
Spank!
And then we do it all over again.
Okay.
Okay, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go!
This is so much faster than the second phase.
But that's okay!
Okay.
Okay, okay, just keep running.
Just keep running around. He'll come to me.
We did it, we're doing it, we're doing it,
we're doing it, we're doing it.
Spank!
Oh, we did it! Oh, what did we get?
What is this?
Oh, that's a boo!
Tomato, tomato, boo!
Beat him while he's down, beat him while he's down!
Ah!
Take this.
Oh, okay, what is this?
Supercharged Body Slam.
For a more professional belly flop, press A
and B
to the top of the jump.
Please!
I love this so much!
Oh, that's so good, I love it!
Momay Domination.
Dang straight.
Dang straight!
Well done, children.
By defeating Tiny,
you have unlocked the gate to the next time travel area.
Go back to the center
of this time, Trister,
and save your progress if you wish.
From there, you will see
that the gate to the second time travel area
is now open.
Okay!
Thank you!
Okay.
Okay, so I've unlocked everything in this one.
In the castle segment.
How do I save the game?
Left trigger, save.
Uh, sure.
Oh, auto-save is already active.
That's fine.
Yeah, just save that though.
Yeah, okay.
Just in case.
Um, um, um, um, um.
What is this?
So we've got Arabia,
China,
Egypt,
the future,
South Korea then,
for the future.
Tiny Spiny!
I would just like to formally say that I,
Tiny Spiny,
am not associated with Tiny Tiny in any way,
and do not endorse his actions.
No.
It's going so good!
I love it!
Wow, Bejinga!
Thank you for the five gifted memberships.
Congrats to those who caught it with your face.
It means you get access to the emotes.
I'm going to very quickly grab
a can of cola.
I'll be literally in those seconds,
because I couldn't finish my tea, so
I'll just get cola.
Surely the caffeine will wake me up.
Sure.
My question
is,
surely not all commissions are that short,
because there's only five locations,
and if there's only five locations,
I don't,
I think they were going to be finished with
gaming two hours and,
and redirect him into Sheevy,
because there's no way.
Thank you for the gifted membership,
Bejinga, and thank you for
the tip,
TinySpainE.
They're short, but you'll die a lot.
What happens if I get zero lives?
Like, I genuinely lose?
This is called
G-Wiz
and
Why? Why must you continue to be
a thorn in our sight?
Who? What?
Where was I?
Oh, Tiny was a good
fellow.
He hated everyone and everything,
but a good heart,
nonetheless.
Please be more reasonable with my minions
next time.
It deletes your save file?
Am I being trolled right now,
or do I genuinely lose all progress?
Because this is an old game,
and that's exactly what old games did.
They make you lose your, well,
go back to the farm!
Go back to the farm!
Back to the farm!
Oh!
Belly Float!
Okay.
Wow!
Oh!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
We know...
the way I absolutely decimated that
poor man.
It's not that old. You just lose your score
and start from your latest level.
Oh!
A game over. The player is given the option
to either restart the game from the beginning of the level,
checkpoint not counted,
with the standard number of lives, four,
or to quit to the title screen.
Okay.
So I don't lose all my Puegue.
That's good, because if I lost all my progress,
we're actually going to play
a game called Conquer's Bad Fur Day,
but Conquer's Bad Fur Day
is so old that
you... Oh my god, I like got a trickshot there.
It's so old that you lose your progress
if you
mess up.
So I'm going to try and win Conquer's Bad Fur Day,
but I actually have terrible news.
I don't know if I can win it.
Go back on the farm! Both of you!
You've been getting so distracted playing...
Oh.
Go away.
Ah, not me!
I don't like meages, go away.
Chicken!
Go! Checkpoint!
Ah, this game is so good.
It doesn't even... How do you not blow up that nature?
As if it's not right next to you.
Oh my god, Crash!
Oh my shoes!
No!
I got too excited.
I need to unlock double jump right now.
I'm so bad.
Let's go.
Literally, it has like infinite health.
Enemies can't touch me.
What defeats me? A gap in the ground.
Okay, I see how it is.
Ah!
Bleeding heart was coming right at me.
What?
Oh no, not me! Oh, I don't like meages.
Big jump! Great, checkpoint.
Is there going to be like an enemy behind this?
I feel like this is too...
No, there isn't. Okay, I'm surprised.
Wow!
Oh, I missed.
Bonus time!
Oh, that frog just...
did it's self in.
I don't know if you saw that.
He's that I've had enough.
Only Stronik is doing well.
Actually Crash and Conquer are both
Ginger.
What do you have for that?
Thank you anonymous for the tip.
I appreciate it.
Yeah, Conquer is Bad Friday.
I have no idea why my dad let me play that game.
I know that I think about it because it's absolutely outrageous.
Oh wait, I can't really fucking know.
Oh my god, I like the jumpy ones.
Conquer is Bad Friday was far too inappropriate.
Oh, it's a timer!
It's a timer!
It's a timer.
I don't like timer stuff, sorry.
Oh wait, no!
I missed the box back there!
Let me go down, go down!
I missed the box!
Let me go back!
I missed that!
Farm, no.
Oh, there's two of them now.
Farm!
To the farm!
You will be a slave on it.
And you will do all the bidding.
And then the refling is going to have a day off because you're the bad guy.
Farm, no.
Eh?
What did that do?
No, it was on the bonus level!
I'm a stinky stinkerton!
I asked the game to put me go back,
but it never put me back.
I'm eating my blueberry muffin
because I need to eat.
What's in the box?
Disappointment!
Because I can't go back.
I want to go back!
Okay, let me eat my muffin.
Classic 5am
Physicers, honestly.
This OST is bangin'.
I didn't realise how good Crash Bandicoot was.
For the OST, I didn't remember any of it.
Have you talked to Coco in the hub?
I don't really search for that stuff when I'm on the hub.
I'm more of an overwatch searcher.
That was terrible.
Interact, Ray Bumper.
Hi!
Do you want her to join your adventure?
I can go be Coco?
Oh, that's going to confuse me.
Sorry, Coco, you're going to have to go away.
Ah! Wait, I get to play as a girl?
Ooh!
A girl gamer.
She's just like me.
I want to be Coco because I'm a girl.
Let me finish my muffin.
It's like a little baby blueberry muffin.
Ah!
I cannot wait to get 3D models
because you will see how much I move around
and articulate with my hands
and all of that.
Boy! Thank you for the gifted member.
And E-boss.
Thank you for becoming on the membership tier.
Membership streams start next week.
So after buckshot roulette
or probably at the start of buckshot roulette stream
I will reveal to you my humble schedule
for a stream that week.
Oh yeah, you successfully avoided
the membership again.
Can't wait for Strony to flip us off in 3.
I saw someone
3D model have physics
around their buttocks area
and I'm like, I need that ASAP.
Sorry, I've almost finished my muffin.
Oh my god.
These games have such charm.
Like when your character is AFK
they do like a little idle thing.
Like it's... oh!
Oh, we've got a phone call. Hold on, who's this?
I see, what's going on?
Alright, bye.
She hardly even spoke to him.
Right, are we on 7?
Hang them high.
Literally, there's like so much detail.
Whoa, what's this?
Oh my god.
Who knows that Aladdin soundtrack?
Prince Ali
Whoa, what am I supposed to do with that?
Am I supposed to spank him when he looks away?
That's what you get.
Thank you again, boy.
Boy for the 5 gifted members.
Big congrats to those who caught it.
Whoa, what is that?
What is that?
What the fuck is that?
What the fuck? What is he doing?
Does he just block the wave?
Okay, oh my god.
I'm sorry, but that's so menacing.
When something follows your movement pattern
that is so menacing.
I did not enjoy that.
Don't do that again.
Don't ever spawn in an enemy like that again game
because it's so like scary.
Hold on, I'm having a cola hydration check.
What the fuck?
No, no, Coco, stop getting phone calls.
God, you're one busy girl.
Oh, wait, hold on.
Wait, jump and then hit.
Yeah.
And then...
Whoa, oh my god.
I feel like games like this
used to be so creative, honestly.
Right, jump down, check point.
What was that?
Dab.
Oh, that was so mean.
He had the delivery to do,
and I just ruined his delivery.
Go away. You scare me.
Menacing man on a carpet.
Wow.
Oh my god, there's so much.
Whoa, oh, there's a monkey again.
That's okay.
Oh, I hurt myself.
But when you hurt yourself,
you'll also hurt the enemy.
Okay, I'm learning, I'm learning, I'm learning.
Wow, I can't see.
Check point, I can't see now.
I am a monkey.
Oh, wait, I didn't realize I could do that.
Go away, go away, man on the carpet.
Go away.
You scare me.
I don't really want scorpions on the fan,
so I don't think we'll send them.
Oh, there's a bonus level down here.
Look, I see it, I see it, I see it.
Take us to the bonus level.
You missed some boxes.
I didn't realize I could attack while I was hanging up.
Oh, I missed completely.
Oh no, I got drabated.
I'm supposed to go up here.
Wait, I'd rather go for a life.
I was speeding up.
Oh, wait, I can't get them.
Whoa, that was lucky.
Wait, what?
How am I supposed to get that one down there?
Oh, butt bouncing adventures!
Pre-DLC.
How am I supposed to get down there?
Was that supposed to do something?
I don't know, chief.
I didn't get it.
TNT, am I supposed to blow it up?
I don't know.
Literally, we're doing butt bouncing adventures
for Elden Ring even now.
So, for the Elden Ring DLC.
Wow.
Those are so good.
Oh, we're at 14 lives as well.
That's fantastic.
I can't wait to make 14 mistakes.
Oh!
He bumped me away!
Checkpoint!
What am I supposed to do here?
That?
Ow!
I couldn't get over it.
See you lanky tall bastards!
Honestly.
How do I do the bottom one?
Right, right, right, right, right, right, right.
How do I do the bottom ones?
Okay.
That makes sense.
Oh!
You know what?
Give me double jump already.
Just give me double jump.
This is getting outrageous.
Right, you look ready.
Parish to the Fires of Gondor.
Wait, no, that's not it.
Cast it into the Fires of Gondor.
No, that's not right.
See you and your wee weaving baskets!
He almost pushed me off the map!
Don't bump me!
What did that do?
Oh!
Wait, what did that do?
Something just happened.
I don't know what.
Well, get me out of this level.
I got too confused.
I'm not well enough for that.
The Fires of Gondor.
I don't know why I said that.
I'm doing too many things at once.
This is really hard on my brain.
I didn't like that one.
That mission was scary.
The wee...
Hog Raid?
How creative!
I'm sore!
Oh my god, it really said no women are allowed to drive.
Wow, this game did not age well.
That's terrible.
I shouldn't have said that.
Oh, wait.
What?
Okay.
Right.
Am I just to get through the level
without getting hurt?
I think I can do that.
Whee!
Oopsies.
Oh no, the pole!
It's a polis, lads.
It's a polis. Pause.
Right, who's got a bag on them?
I don't want to touch them.
Right, we're doing a jump kick.
Whee!
Oh wait, I'm fourth place.
I'm to beat these people?
Oh, oh no.
Oh no, this can't be.
I didn't realize I was actually racing.
I was just having fun driving, to be honest.
I just think this is a cool map.
Oh no.
I'm supposed to win.
Ah!
Okay, hold on.
Oh no, I lost!
No, wait.
Oh no, why did I just break
to let that guy go third?
Wait, I won though.
Oh no, I didn't win!
Oh no!
I have to actually win.
I was just having fun driving, not going to lie.
I was like, oh, this is actually a really
fun wee game.
Oops.
Is there like a boost button?
Or is it literally just send it?
Okay, I'm just going for it.
I don't know if there's a sender.
I think I maybe have to hit all the green boost.
And it like guarantees you to go ahead
of, whoa!
Crash, what are you doing?
The steering crash!
Oh my god, there is like, no steering!
Ah!
Oh wait, I don't die if I hit them?
Okay.
Right, I'm third place.
I just need to hit all the green that comes up.
Uh...
Right.
All right, hold on.
I'm looking for the green to get me ahead.
Crash, please stop skittin',
skittin' a boot.
Okay, there's a green there.
Oh!
Get in my way!
Your ball back!
No!
Right, again, again, again, again, again.
He was in my way!
Right, try again. Go again, Crash.
Try again.
He was in my way on the greenery.
The green pads are the boost, yeah.
Right, let's freakin' try that again.
I feel like when I played this as a child,
if I even got this far,
I probably would be crying right now.
You know how like kids cry in frustration
when they can't win?
I feel like...
I'd be greeting right now.
Because I'm so bad at the game.
Would you laugh at
a young, strongy crying right now?
Crying are we eyes out.
Right, I'm third place.
There should be like
three green speed-ups ahead.
I'm not going to break the boxes.
I'm wondering if that slows me down a bit.
Go ahead.
So that's me second place.
Okay.
Crash, you're going to have to put... Crash!
No, wait, what must the...
It's Bioball here!
Ladies and gentlemen, I got first place!
Oh my god!
We did it!
We are the champions.
There's no time
for loses
because we
are the champions
of the world.
It's Tim Tame.
Forget Tim Reader.
Oh no, not the Aussies.
Anything but the Australians.
No, save us!
Oh.
Are you squidding me right now?
Jack, thank you for the tip. Well done, strongy.
Purple burglar alert.
I don't know, maybe not the farm.
Maybe go with the animal sanctuary rescue.
Thank you for the tip, Jack.
Oh my god, we're in Tim Tame's tomb.
Oh, look at the detail on the walls.
I'm sorry, but
they don't
make games like they used to.
Look at, wow, what is that?
A Crocodonkey.
Right, go away.
It got my butthole!
I didn't even get a checkpoint.
That's how
not far into the game I was.
It got my butthole.
I'm so bad.
Right, big jump.
And then up the stairs.
And then jump.
Okay, let's find that thing.
That was just bad timing.
Whoa!
It's oil!
I'm really scared. Oh my god, it's made from Overwatch.
I can't believe they based this game on made from Overwatch.
Whoa!
Oh my god!
She's so cute when she skates.
I love Coco.
Boom, boom, boom.
Look at the detail on the walls.
Uh...
Yeah, I saw that. I saw that.
I had video game knowledge to know something wasn't right there.
Brian!
Brian, but no message.
Thank you for the tip.
Brian!
Don't tell America there's oil there.
We're getting invaded.
Wait, there's TNT everywhere.
Oh, this is not going to go well for me.
Get me the heck out of here.
I'm not even just...
Does it blow off?
Okay, it just blows up TNT in the vicinity.
Okay, that's fine.
Oh no, I'm scared.
I'm hiding.
Something just went flying.
I don't know what, but...
Thank you for the tip, Brian.
Okay.
Yeah, I knew there was something up there,
but I didn't want to jump on it
because I got scared.
Oh wait, I could have barely flopped on the other side of the map.
Oops.
I can't believe it.
I'm not an MLG gamer.
What's this?
Oh, it's a time.
Oh my god, it's the Anka symbol.
Is that a Gen 2 reference?
Eh? I need to jump over this?
Okay, I can do that.
See you, yo, bam.
Great.
Oh no.
Oh, I got...
I heard the...
What did you hear?
Am I a vampire?
Are you squiddling here?
Ah!
Ah.
That's a trick.
The Dinger, thank you for the five.
You know what?
I actually was in trade.
I can't do it this month or maybe next month.
However, I am so down to do...
like...
what?
I am so down to do
showing off game dev type.
How the heck did I get over there?
I cannot make that jump. I know that for a fact.
I'm so down to do that
to give game devs that are smaller
a bigger chance type thing.
And we write a little review.
We write a little review at the end.
Oh no.
Oh no, this can't be.
Look at all the paint.
Look at the detail.
They're implying that they're painting the murals right now.
Look!
It's so fun and cute.
Thank you again for the five by Dinger.
How do I do this?
Is it a timer?
I don't know.
Okay, it's a timer.
Do not be distracted from the fact that it's a timer.
As beautiful as the game's...
The game's
background
storytelling is the thingy.
It is a timer, so do not be fooled.
Wait until it gets close to you, okay?
Wait until it gets close to you.
Oh!
Right, hold on, hold on, hold on.
Child's game absolutely
decimating me.
Oh my god.
Growing women beaten to pulp
via child's game.
Once it opens, then just go straight for it.
Right.
I'll wait until that comes back.
Because, yeah.
Unless Coco can just stand on this.
Okay, yeah.
Okay, we're safe, we're safe.
We're safe.
Wait!
Wait, how am I supposed to get around that?
Oh wait, no!
There's a life back there!
Okay, that's what I need.
Yes.
That sounded terrible.
I said I need a lifter.
Right, we've got a checkpoint.
Right, go!
Uh-huh.
Oh no!
Coco!
Right, no wonder there's a freaking checkpoint there.
Coco, what was that abysmal attempt?
You know exactly what you were doing, hen.
You, Karrish.
Whoa.
Flamethrower's a bit dramatic.
This is a child's game.
Wow!
I'm scared!
Oh Coco!
I'm scared.
Oh, get me off this level.
I hate platforming like that.
Oh, get me off, get me off, get me off.
Oh, another portal we go.
Safety, safety.
Only time's strong to get smashed.
Reflens, are you not coming to the convention?
Hold on a minute.
Hold on, this is news to me.
Right, no, I played that one.
And I just did that one, didn't I?
Okay.
So we're gonna play
Midnight Run.
Okay, Midnight Run.
What's my tiger called?
I'm sure my tiger has a name.
Oh my God!
He's so cute!
I can't handle it.
Tiger confirmed for Jin too.
Oh my God!
You're so cute!
Oh my God, jump, jump high.
Oh, there's a lot of enemies up here.
Oh, jump!
Oh, check mark.
And jump.
Jump food.
Oh, I love this freaking tiger so much.
Oh my God, why am I doing so much better on later levels
than I am on the early level?
Oh my God!
You're cheatsy doodle!
Did you see that?
Oh my God, I cheatsy doodle!
Uh, uh, uh, uh.
Right, checkpoint, checkpoint.
Jump.
I saw that.
I saw what the game was trying to do.
I'm tryharding on this level.
I don't care.
I love it.
And I love me tiger.
Love me cocoa.
Love me China wall.
Simplest.
Oh my God!
This freaking best level ever!
I know.
Jump, jump, sled, sled.
I love the tiger.
Jin won, you won for now.
It's 100k.
What, steady on, steady on.
No, I think I'll hold him for a while.
Trying to be gaming like a pro?
I freaking love!
Oh no, we're doing a boss fight.
Cola check.
Everyone hydrate.
We're about to do a boss fight.
The tiger's called Pura?
Oh my God, Jin to confirm tiger girl called Pura.
I'm not even care.
Oh, I've just tabbed out.
That was a terrible idea.
Sorry, I just tabbed out of the game.
I got a DM.
Okay, I have, I have good news for everyone.
I don't, I have good news for everyone.
Mercy and Aisy's meme ASMR are going up today.
I just got confirmation from the squadron.
Dingo Dale.
A Dingo Dale.
Oh my God, that's such an Aussie name.
Oh my God, they said no whammin' fights.
Yay!
A tiger girl called Pura.
Pura, Pura, Pura, Pura, Pura, Pura, Pura.
Them crystals are mine.
Call me Pura.
Oh, it's a...
Break out the butter.
Uh, uh, what?
What is this?
Um...
Hmm?
I don't...
I don't understand how he auto-locked me.
Oh, he did it again!
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Hold on, sorry, sorry.
I'm looking, I'm looking where his gun is pointing.
Sorry, give me, give me a second.
It takes me a second to figure things out for myself.
Hold on, hold on.
My brain isn't hot wires like the way it's hot wired for you.
Right, he's aiming there.
Ah!
He keeps aiming!
Now what?
Oh, he keeps going.
Oh!
Please don't do that.
Please don't do that!
I'm trying to hurt him.
Okay.
Oh.
Okay, I just need to do that three times.
Okay, okay.
I just needed a second to digest what the game is asking me to do.
That's all.
I just needed a tricky second.
Right, if he just keeps all locking,
I could probably just keep going like this.
Oh, no.
Okay.
Twat him?
Okay, okay.
We're doing it, we're doing it, we're doing it, we're doing it.
Okay, okay, okay.
Last one, boys.
I just need to look on the ground.
No.
Oh no, does he do a variation attack?
Oh.
Okay, nice and easy.
We did it, we did it, we did it.
Unless we need to do anything special, I think that's good.
Oh my God, he let you win.
With a Higgy or then?
Yeah, get him, Penguin!
Beat his ass, Penguin.
We'll do it together.
No one will do it.
Yeah, beat him up, beat him up.
We love penguins in here.
Gen 2 penguin confirmed.
Double jump.
Yes, a jump twice as high.
Okay, I can probably replay those other missions if I so desired.
No.
Oh my God, look at that vertical leap.
Look at that vertical leap.
Get me in the NBAs right now, NBAs.
NBA?
NBA.
Get me in the NBAs right now.
Coco, show us that double jump.
Wow, look at that.
She's a cheerleader.
Oh my God, she's such a cheerleader.
Right, we're going to change the turn.
Let's go.
Right, what are we eating first?
Baggies from Dim Sum's.
We're doing the Dano Mate.
Oh my God, that's such a good name for a TNT dinosaur.
Oh my God, Gen 2 confirmed.
Sorry, I'm just stealing all my Gen 2 ideas from Crash Bandicoot.
I don't mind if I do.
A pair of Pate Marsupials.
I am Dr. Nefarious Trope.
Master of Time and the creator of the very time twister machine you see before you.
Uka Uka and Dr. Cortex have sent me to end this little shroud.
So you won't be leaving my area with the crystals?
I swear it.
Wow, this game is so fun.
Thank you for watching.
No, no, no.
Is that what I think it is?
Is this going to be a chase sequence?
I take it all back.
Is this a chase sequence?
Oh my God, I can like clear those with ease.
What the heck is that?
Honestly, honestly.
Oh, that's lava.
That's not a path.
Oh my goodness.
My brain literally registered that last second.
Oh my God, this looks like a chase sequence map.
See it ain't so.
I will not go turn the lights off.
Carry me home.
Oh my God, that fish is so freaky.
It's supposed to look like crash, isn't it?
I'm not just making that up.
Oh, go away.
You're so creepy.
Oh, I'm scared.
I don't like it.
Wait, why are you not possible?
That's the second one that's not possible.
I wonder why that's not possible.
Wow, the grass slowed me down.
No.
Oh, I stood on its head.
Oh, it's like Mario.
If you stand on its head, it's gone.
It's dead if you stand on it.
Wait, what does the egg do?
Hello.
We kissed the egg and let it germinate.
Am I supposed to break it?
I really don't want to break it.
I feel like I was really mean.
I don't want to break the egg.
I'm sorry.
There's something germinating inside it.
We want it to wish it success.
Great success in your life.
Break the egg.
I don't want it.
There's something living inside it.
If you...
Although saying that, you can actually grow chickens
without their shell or being cracked open.
I don't actually recommend you doing it, but...
What?
Did you see that?
How big that thing was?
Go away.
No egg breakie.
We are nice to nature.
Okay, okay, okay.
Oh, the music is so good.
I love children's games.
I love them being relatively easy.
Yeah, that's right.
I'm smart at that segment.
I knew exactly what you were going to ask me.
Bonus mission.
You got a break here.
Break egg.
Help it hatch.
Oh, I'm to help it hatch?
Oh, that's different then.
Okay, I'll break the eggs when I see them.
Wow.
Butt smash.
Oh, I missed that one back there.
That's okay.
Butt smash.
Wow.
Oh, that's like so many wumper fruit.
And a life, which I definitely mean how much I'm...
Oh, I can't reach it.
I couldn't reach it anyway.
Oh, well.
Wee.
Let's go.
We're strong and we weave.
You don't get excited.
No, I saw it.
I saw it.
Did you see it too?
I saw the Terran and Zoran ring.
I have double jump.
Okay.
Trust in the double jump.
Wow, you're going so fast.
I have double jump and I still feel that jump.
Wow.
Oh, cool, cool.
This camera angle isn't helping, darling.
Yes, a bear camera angle, please.
Oh, please give us a bear camera angle.
Oh, get me out of here.
Oh, my God.
How are you supposed to know what's coming up?
How are you supposed to know?
No more dino missions, please.
My heart can't take it.
I'm getting so stressed out.
Deep trouble.
Okay, my time.
We still call that a skill issue.
Okay.
Okay, you're done.
Back to the...
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You need reaction time.
I don't have reaction time, though.
What?
Can I go up?
No, sorry.
The game almost looked like I could go up.
Okay, let's hope I don't mess this up.
Too much.
I'm just going to spam.
Oh, my God.
Yes, spamming.
Why did you not get hit?
Well, I'll leave you alive.
But tell your family.
I almost got electric shock.
Oh, my God.
Actually, I'm so sorry if you get sick of that meme.
It's probably the funniest thing I enjoy right now.
It's just full going, oh, my God.
This character confirmed.
I don't know.
I just find it really funny.
Okay, I can beat up sharks underwater.
Oh, my God.
I'm stuck in a vortex.
Okay, it's fine.
We made it.
Wow.
I like the tissues are just hanging out in this one winter thing.
Oh, God, that was two for one.
Oh, my God.
Crash Bandicoot really said inflation.
Inflation confirmed for gender.
I'm so sorry.
Oh, I did it twice.
Oh, my God.
I'm so sorry.
Please excuse me by all means.
Right.
Let's not do that again.
Spin.
Right.
There.
Jeez.
Why was that so hard?
Crystal does, but does it like a locker bonus thing for me later?
I'm just using my damage to get out.
Whoa.
I didn't even see that.
Literally spinning damage helps you move so much faster.
Inflation.
Wow.
I don't have a mask right now, so this is extra scary.
Right.
I didn't know you died in the vortex.
Oh, no.
How far back am I?
I lost me boat a wee bit ago.
I'm just spamming.
Am I going crazy?
No.
Oh, my God.
We're going to the rapture bio shot confirmed.
Oh, wait.
I can just destroy the natural boxes when I'm like this.
That's fine.
Oh, no.
Why am I so bad at timing?
I made it.
Oh, right.
Okay.
I literally perished right before the end of that level.
You need the purple crystals to unlock the boss.
Okay.
Bioshock.
I know.
Literally.
I'm sorry.
It's my favorite joke right now because I have had messages like that that have been
like, you said this in one stream.
Does that mean?
Is this the?
Oh, my God.
Wait.
Can the girl drive?
Girl can't drive.
Wow.
You mean a big sister?
Oh, we don't have a big sister, do we?
We do have a mama.
Maybe we should do like a cousin third removed for Gentoo.
Oh, no.
I'm terrible at the different people.
Okay.
Let's get to it.
Everybody.
To it.
Let's get them 40s popping.
Right.
Wait.
They can use the ramps.
I thought they can use the ramps.
I thought only I could.
That's how I was like predicting where they were going to go.
Go away.
No.
Get out my way.
This is my road.
Oh, my God.
Sorry.
It's like, wait.
I don't even know where the controls are.
I'm sliding if I do a.
I'm definitely lost this one.
That's all I'm going to say.
We are going to play.
We are replaying this for as long.
I don't know what the controls are.
Can someone tell me what the controls are?
Because I'm holding like, oh, I'm a, but I'm like, well, no.
I'm holding right trigger, but it keeps making me slide everywhere.
And that just instantly stopped my speed.
What is going on?
I'm confusion.
I'm, I'm a philosopher because I'm Confucius.
What the heck?
Bro.
Stop sliding.
Crash.
What is going on?
Yeah.
I've definitely haven't won this one.
Get out of my way.
I'll rearrange you and make it look like an accident.
Wait.
I don't know what.
Sorry.
I'm going to have to look up the controls for this game mode because I'm definitely doing
something wrong.
Like crash speeds up and then he slows down.
Wait.
I'm not.
I don't have any turning power when he does that.
Crash.
Our insurance bill is going to be.
Oh, wait.
Whoa.
They really said Mario Kart out here.
Yeah.
They said if you fall off the map, it's fine.
Whoa.
Controls just accelerate.
I just accelerated and got sixth place.
So something tells me I'm doing something wrong.
Strongly confirmed for Gen 2.
I need first to progress to the next mission.
Guys, I have a terrible feeling we're going to be here.
She's got ran over.
Did you see that?
Insurance fraud simulator on a flu.
She's got ran over.
Oh my God.
Child's game.
It's okay.
You're sixth place, but we still love you.
Literally green.
Is it?
Is there?
Accelerate just before a green light to boost.
One, two, boost.
That.
Okay.
Hold on a minute.
We're getting strats.
I managed to read the help screen.
Okay.
Let him get up.
Get out my way.
Right.
Everyone's doing that, but I actually don't know if you're slower on ramps or not.
Okay.
Hold up.
We're getting there.
If you cross the road right now, you're such a vampire.
You're actually such a freaking idiot.
He purposely, can I reset?
Because there's no way I'm going to win.
Resume.
Oh, you can't reset.
He's such a liar.
Literally swerving into me.
I'm faster.
I really don't feel it.
Why are all these cops on the road?
I know.
Literally.
Meet her springs out here with the cop hiding behind the billboard to catch Lightning McQueen.
What's that?
I know the lore of freaking cars.
Yeah.
What are you going to do about it?
Wait.
Oh my God.
Car girl confirmed for Gen 2, but you get to stick it in her exhaust pipe.
Did you guys see that thing on YouTube where the guy's in love with his car?
It was like my weird obsession and he makes love to his car and it's red.
I just remember the car being red and me being like, huh?
Huh?
Okay.
We're actually somehow doing better even though I've played considerably worse.
Yeah.
Like he keeps going off the map.
I don't know why.
The A.
Ah!
Okay.
Well, I'm still, excuse me, insurance fraud people on the phone right now.
Oh my God.
Why did they make this so hard?
I just got ran over again.
Right.
Hold on.
Let me look up the controls because I don't think anyone...
It said two things to me when I played the game mode for the first time.
Hold on.
Crash.
Bandicoot warped.
What is this?
Motorcycle controls.
Xbox.
I'll put Xbox because I'm using Xbox controller.
Hold down the X button to accelerate and square to break.
I said Xbox controls.
We don't have a square.
So it's literally breaking go.
It's literally just breaking go and that's it.
What is accelerate?
Is A accelerate?
I guess A is accelerate.
Right.
And then I just need to focus on not...
Oh my!
Oh!
And we don't even have an option to reset.
I don't know if I'd be faster to reset and then go again.
Bra.
Literally.
Get out my way, honestly.
Can the game tell that I'm a struggling child and then the AI will lower?
You know how some of those games have like reflective AI and they're like,
oh my God, you're struggling.
We're just going to lower the game difficulty for you.
Can I have that please?
I'm literally struggling so hard.
Right.
Stop drifting crash.
It's causing a lot of issues.
I'm not even going to pretend otherwise.
Can you stop?
Oh!
Right.
I get it.
Crash!
Crash.
Oh!
Well, I'm actually going to have a word with you once the stream is over.
Oh my God.
Can I really not progress?
Wait, I'm going to back out and see if I can just skip to the next level
because oh my God.
And there's so many police on the road and they're not even doing their job.
You're not even a civil servant.
You're not even serving the public at all just hanging about on Route 66 for any reason.
Honestly.
Nay wonder, like folk call themselves a sovereign citizen.
You ain't doing shit.
No again, please.
Oh my God.
Please.
Okay.
I'm going to back out and I'm going to see if we can progress to the next thing
because this is impossible.
Nay wonder, Coco.
Right.
No.
Don't restart level.
Give me a break.
Let me come back to it.
Let me come back to it because I don't know what I'm supposed to do.
I don't know how I'm supposed to do it.
Right.
We're not doing road crash more like right.
Hang time.
So what did I just do?
12.
No.
What?
Okay.
We're doing 15.
Oh wow.
It does let you skip ahead.
Thank God.
You need that crystal.
No.
Eh?
Go away.
Wait.
Oh.
Okay.
You can't even do anything against these guys at all.
How did I...
I didn't want to break it but hey ho.
Oh.
You don't get anything out of them?
Right.
I can definitely do this.
Whee.
What?
Who put all this poison to turn the fricking frogs game?
There's...
Wait.
How am I supposed to get past?
Oh my gosh.
That was like so close.
I'm sorry.
I don't know what the hitbox is like in this game.
But I'm feeling it Mr. Krabs.
Oh okay.
I was just going to belly flop.
Well that wasn't worth it.
Swing.
And then get past.
Okay.
We're doing it.
It's fine.
So if I do this...
No that's not...
I don't really want to set it all.
Wah.
Oh shit.
I thought I had enough distance to do that.
Okay.
I won't do that again.
I'll leave the TNT as is.
I don't need anything from the TNT.
Two.
One.
Jump.
Swing.
Wah.
It almost perished.
Right.
We're leaving TNT alone because I don't know how to deal with it.
I ain't smart enough for this.
Swing.
Bouncy bouncy down.
Right.
I don't need that.
I don't really know what to do with it either but I don't need it.
Go to the farm.
Right now.
No.
There's a mage.
Come on away.
Bouncy bouncy down.
Farm!
We need lots of floats so they can help with
the pests in the garden.
Okay.
We can do special missions.
How to stay ininal for mages.
it's because they have an auto lock and I don't like auto locking just so you know
AC is live with a watch along all that the movie that you guys are all featured
and you guys didn't tell me that you were in a movie oh no this can't be what
how are you supposed to get back yeah how are you supposed to and someone said
there's no sheepster stream there's no sheepster stream today I don't know what
the plan is for a zero I've got another life I've got 18 literally me yes she's
doing the karaoke now okay is there AC is doing karaoke
Emi I believe is also doing her feet today any any 10 toenail enjoyers please
feel free to enjoy Emi's 10 toenail
I don't know someone said it may grow back I mean it could
to the farm wow no no no no I hate all that's a lot of well I'm okay wow wait
huh can I not I thought I couldn't hurt these guys okay I can just bump over them
I guess no that doesn't perish all the enemies I thought it I don't know what
that is Emi streams too late for me hook for a board long as she doesn't go out
control wait so I can't progress oh no I can't progress until I do the driving
mission look refland I'm gonna be honest I think we're in here for the long
haul mmm oh this isn't gonna go well reflings yeah this is gonna turn into an
endurance stream at this rate okay okay on the green one two now we've got a
boost good to go get out my way and then just take it easy as long as crash
doesn't start like violently sliding on the tracks it's yeah see when you do
that crash when you do that crash it becomes very hard to control what I'm
trying to do so don't do that again crash and maybe just maybe yeah okay that's
fine haven't really done anything that's messed us up too dramatically we can share
we can share the ramp that's fine we can share the ramp right crash all the
sliding crash is exactly what I'm talking about stop sliding right now stop
it stop it young man okay okay don't frickin don't frickin do anything
different because I'm third place in crash then the cut crash oh my god I'm
so sorry if anyone's name is crash right now your like heart rate must be
accelerating I'm second please I'm second please I'm second please I'm second
please I'm second please I'm second please I'm second please I'm second please
crash crash crash oh oh I can't see it I can see it stop stop stop oh my god I
I think we did it.
Crash, I am going to lose it.
I am going to lose it.
Oh my God, we did it.
Oh, we can do the boss.
Thank God.
Oh my God.
Right.
Holy crap.
I am so sorry if anyone's name is Crash.
You're adrenaline must be pumping right now.
Holy crap.
First try.
Yes, that was my first attempt on that map.
Thank you for admitting how amazing.
Wait, did I forget to do a mission?
Did I forget to do a mission?
Oh, I forgot to do a mission completely.
OK, sorry, we need to do hang time.
I completely forgot to just do an entire mission.
My apologies.
Well, you've crashed a few parties before,
but I never expected you to make it this far.
If you don't turn back.
Yeah, I've lived the thousand years
as the flag of you, and the entire universe.
OK.
OK, I can do this.
I can do it.
And these kind of maps are.
Molotov cocktails.
I'm sorry, but there's something
about the Geneva Convention with that.
What's going on here?
Oh my God.
A magic carpet ride.
Oh.
Did I just get put in a jar?
Oh, wait, I forgot these guys.
So Molotovs already.
And a magic carpet ride.
Oh, I can hardly see that as it comes over.
All right, give me a checkpoint because it's not looking good.
OK, wow.
Isn't this not?
No, I'm going to put back here.
This is so far away.
I better get a checkpoint right now.
Give me a checkpoint right now.
And me figure when?
Go away.
And me a figurine.
You'll have to like and subscribe a bit more for a figurine.
The thing when right.
OK, sorry, I'm getting distracted.
And if you guys are like serious,
but like, oh, when can we get this particular merch?
That particular merch.
The sad thing is I have to message these companies
and then I basically have to go, here's the statistics.
Here's.
Oh, I almost perished there.
And it's like I can't go to a company to produce like merchandise.
It's like a lot of money.
And and sorry, let me try hard.
So OK, that's fine.
We got the checkpoint.
And and I basically I can't ask for like this merchandise
that costs like thousands to be produced.
If it's like, yeah, we've got 4,000 subscribers,
like it's just not happening.
And so, you know, if you ever want to support your girls,
just make some clips of them go viral or something.
I don't know.
OK, holy crap.
Wow, this is a risky map.
I'm not going to lie.
Oh, bonus map.
Bonus time.
They need a minimum guaranteed return on investment.
Yes, like Uber market and we're absolutely fantastic
because to get to get.
I completely forgot I can double jump half the time.
Wait, I don't know.
Oh, there we go.
And I'm not.
I don't want to accidentally fall off the map, to be honest.
I'm quite happy just to move on.
And yeah, like you need to go to the company
and be like, this is what we do.
And this is why we're a good fit for you here
as a statistic to back up, like, you know, such and.
And oh, right.
Give me that.
You go away.
I didn't realize there's flamethrowers here.
What's that death?
Do I want to go on that one?
I did just hit a checkpoint.
Oh, no.
Oh, no, I just said luck to an achievement for that.
OK, get viral, get viral, get viral.
Yes.
And like, as I said, Uber market
were fantastic because they gave three designs.
Like, they made three designs for the girls.
And it was like, the girls aren't even out.
We had absolutely no idea what the estimations
were looking like or the success or whatever.
And we were much.
No wonder they call it the death route.
Right, I'm not doing that again.
I don't think it's imperative to the clock.
Oh, yeah, no, I'm not fussing for the death route.
Wee.
Why has it got random TNT?
You got an A. But, yeah, they were like, yeah,
you can have three designs, which was fantastic.
And if all, oh, wait, I don't want to touch that
because it's TNT.
The guys just throwing swords over there.
Oh, checkpoint.
All right, hold on.
Jump.
Belly float.
Oh, wait, that's TNT there.
So it doesn't blow.
Oh, go away.
You're so creepy.
Oh, yeah.
Is this?
Are you going to?
Sugar, that hurt me.
That's OK.
Um.
Oh, I don't like the look of that.
Oh, I'm not even in range of it.
Oh, my God, his mouth like being wide open.
While he's climbing.
Oh, thank God, get me off this map.
You have to complete them to get the best ending.
Isn't there not only one ending where you win this crash
pancake game was like that.
But I've all met up with this enemy doctor entropy.
Isn't entropy when you're like skinny?
I'm not thinking of something.
Ah, you little vermin are way too stupid to understand
what you're getting yourself into.
This time, you've done it.
Wahaa.
Entrophy.
There's usually a special 100% completion ending.
Uh, jump.
What does that mean?
What does it mean?
I don't know.
Woo.
Oh.
Take that, you scallywag.
Ah, OK, OK, OK, OK.
Whoa.
Oh, my God, the music.
Oh.
I actually really like that the boss fights aren't that hard.
Like, I said it.
I'm sorry, I said it.
Sorry if this is going to age terribly,
and I'm going to struggle with the next boss fight.
But I think this is lovely.
Like, this is a lovely experience.
I spoke far too soon.
I apologize for my ignorance.
I do.
I spoke far too soon.
I admit it.
I confess to my sins.
All right, let's try that again.
OK, let's try that again.
I never made it this far into the game as a child.
I don't think I did either, because I am,
I don't recall anything past Coco.
I just think that only remember Coco.
OK.
OK, OK.
Right, this time, don't let the missile go to my head.
So that'd be great.
OK.
Wow, I almost jumped into that.
Honestly, him laughing is so mean.
Like, if I was an evil person.
Take this!
To spin longer and faster,
or to glide while in the air, press X repeatedly.
Wow, I love that move.
First try, yeah, yeah, first try.
First try.
Shhh.
Is he trying to...
Is he trying to guilt-trap us into losing?
Who knows what it'll do?
Oh, no.
Right, let's go back to being a lady,
because we did the dread one, isn't she?
OK, we're going to Egypt to Arabia.
The Sphinxinator.
I want to explore your Sphinxinator.
Oh my God, is this just going to the left side of the map now?
From that previous map?
No, it's not.
It's just me making stuff up.
I'm sorry.
Second gen Sphinxinator.
Confirmed, honestly.
I'm sorry, it's not...
Wow!
A sarcophagus!
Ah!
A mummy!
And not the good kind like Azura.
Wow.
Wow, wow, wow, wow, wow.
Who?
OK, that was terrible, Taibin.
Can we get like a crossbow, maybe?
OK, let's try that again.
I don't know when I was supposed to jump for him.
I ain't gonna lie.
Maybe I was supposed to double jump over the flames, right?
You?
And then a mummy?
OK, that's fine.
Return the slime.
Watching you play this makes me want to get...
Spiral.
I've never played Spiral, but people were recommending it.
And I was like, I might give it a shot.
Give me checkpoint, please.
But let the doors close first,
because I was 100% gonna fall for that.
Hold on, I want the spikes to go up.
OK.
All right, I'm safe to go on it for this section, which is fine.
That sarcophagus is making some...
You're scaring me!
I like how it pings off onto some of the items to break them for you.
Oh god, I'm so bad at this one.
Double jump!
OK, we need to wait.
Spiral is also fun.
Yeah, Spiral and Crash Bandicoot can I get...
Are they by like the same developers,
or was it just they happened to come out
kind of close to the same time?
What did I do wrong here again?
I had nothing to protect me.
I'm wondering if I have more time if I do that.
Oh, wow, I do.
Right.
And let me guess, that doesn't explode the T.
Oh, no, it does.
I was gonna be like,
oh, let me guess, it doesn't do anything.
Again?
Oh, no.
Oh, we're struggling with this one.
Goodness gravy.
Am I making this look easy?
No, sorry, am I making this look hard?
Right, and then wait for it to come back,
and then jump on it,
and then defeat the mummy twice.
Or the sarcophagi, jeez.
Let's try this again.
Right, and then I can just double jump here
because I'm out of range.
And then he's gonna drop that, which explodes that one first.
Just fine with me.
Right, don't send it.
Don't send it, Reflings.
If you ever replay this game, don't send it at that section
because that's what I thought I had to do there,
and it did not pay off.
I need to wait until he spawns the second block.
We'll get there.
It just takes me a few moments.
Can't believe it, they made me flat.
Lollipop model confirmed for Strony.
Right, again, just jump over this, which is fine.
Oh, there's not even TNT this time.
The game said, yeah, you're struggling.
Right, send it, send it, send it, send it.
I knew it would work if I sent it.
Oh, I've got a checkpoint, goodness.
That'll be very welcomed, I assure you.
There's really enemies behind this.
Yeah, there's freaking TNT.
Oh.
Take your time.
That will be a mummy.
Okay, we're good, we're good, we're doing it, we're doing it.
We are doing it, oh.
Why would they randomly have a natural, they are.
They are.
Oh.
Oh, send it, send it, send it, send it.
I like how he just looks at me, as if I'm not about to coblame him.
Uh, this seems suspiciously easy.
Rather, this is, this is, this is suspiciously.
Ooh, wait, hold on.
Two crystals, let's go on the bonus map.
Don't send it, no idea.
I'm literally giving you the strikes alive, because I'm struggling.
Okay, there's lots of TNT.
I'll just let it pop and then run away again.
Whoa, oh, there's too many.
Oh, dear.
There's lots of fricking.
Oh well, that's the best I can do.
The best I can do is what I got.
Cocodes, don't look at the explosion, because she's so cool.
I start off a guy.
Oh, that was a bit rude of me, but I did the job.
Oh, there's like monkeys in these pots.
Sling your shit elsewhere.
Oh my god, he's quaking, his little ankles are gone, he's quaking in his boots.
Bam, bam, bam, bam.
Oh god, another life, thank you.
Okay, ugh, perish, perish.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Start quaking more, boom.
I don't know what that does, I think you're supposed to like go back when you do that, but I don't go back.
There's a message in the discord, I need to be worried.
Okay.
17.
Bye bye blimp, I'm in the sky.
Oh my god, we're playing Crimson Skies.
Good game, good game, bye bye blimp.
If you ever played Crimson Skies in an old old game.
Shoot down the blimps, I have 100% health, okay.
Oh, how do I shoot?
Okay, machine gun.
A to do a barrel roll.
Wait, I'm already down 10% health?
The heck, I only just got started.
Oh, man.
I'm going, wait that didn't break it.
I'm barrel rolling, oh that gives me health.
Oh my god, I like this game mode, this is so creative, I like it.
Wow, we're getting absolutely obliterated, not gonna lie.
We're about to get survivor's bias going on here.
Okay, wow, I like that, that was nice and simple.
More missions like this please.
Wait, not all of us have a high IQ.
You're supposed to destroy every box,
the green boxes at the end get rid of the natures.
Oh my god, that was such a quick and easy one, I like that.
Give me more of that, give me more of that.
Give me more, give me more, tell no tales.
Oh, dead men tell no tales.
Oh, someone said do a watch along of...
Well, I made a few more vacations to my mechanics since our last encounter.
So back on, or be deleted.
Or be deleted.
Oh my god, yeah.
Okay, we did it, we did the ramp.
I was like, oh, I missed the timing on the ramp.
We still did it.
Right, we're safe, we're safe.
Man, this freaking game is just like so unapologetically good.
Yeah, suck at the racing ones, but that's fine.
Sorry, Mr. Seagull, you...
I got picked to death?
Oh my gosh.
Anyway, as I was saying before I got picked to death by a freaking seagull,
this game is like so unapologetically good,
like it's such a chaotic, fun experience, it's so good.
I didn't know the seagulls could hurt me like that.
I mean, is he even there? He's not even here this time.
So he didn't really care that much about the boxes, did he?
That was just like the music.
It's so... whoa.
That one, that's rude, don't do that again.
You upset me.
That is just like such a freaking good game experience, honestly.
Am I gonna land on that bomb? No.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
I probably went like the longest way.
I don't know if I had to do that, but that was like the longest way.
You're a cuttlefish after all.
I'll... I'll cuttle your fish in a minute if you don't...
I don't know.
Please leave me alone, Mr. Shark.
I think I'll just do this checkpoint.
Yeah, let's do the checkpoint because I don't trust this.
This is... they're starting to really fill it out with enemies, though.
It was like bear the first time you played this map.
The bombs are moving, there's like enemies everywhere.
I mean, I know games are supposed to...
Please leave me alone, Mr. Seagull.
Nope, nope, that bomb is teasing.
That bomb is teasing and teasing me.
Right, let's get out of here.
Bum bum bum bum bum bum bum.
But this is like a perfect remaster.
Oh, there it is.
That's what we need.
Oh, I don't want to do...
I don't have a checkpoint!
Give me checkpoint!
Give me give me checkpoint, give me checkpoint, give me yeah.
Oh my God, I just like cheese that corner there.
Okay, we're getting there.
We're like... we're doing it.
Can I do it first time, though?
Oh, I'm getting nervous.
Oh, I don't know why I did that, but we'll do it.
Oh my God.
So good.
I'm so surprised how much I'm enjoying this.
But then at the same time, I'll always enjoy kids' games.
Like literally, Viva Faniata could like blast about for ages.
Okay, we just did that one.
We're doing 19, which is future frenzy.
Ooh, we're going to the city of Caloon.
Although they wrecked it.
Wow, there's laser beam timing.
I miss Viva Faniata.
Bro, everyone is waiting for Viva Faniata 3 to be announced.
Unfortunately, I didn't like Viva Faniata about trouble and paradise as much.
Which is a shame.
Oh my God, this is so cool.
I like all of this.
I'm loving it.
Every day.
Can I destroy that?
Okay, I can destroy it when it's like that.
Yeah.
There's like so much...
Wumper fruit.
Oh my God, that nature just jumped and it scared me.
Right, I can butt bounce this.
Wait, we're already done?
No, this can't be right.
It's going to take me to a new section because there's no way.
Yeah, I was going to say there's no way this thing is done.
Viva Faniata beats.
Yes, in July I am going to start hammering out gamer score.
Why is there a reflective stream?
Why?
She slides so well.
I don't like you.
I'll jump on your head though.
I'll take you.
Double jump.
Okay, double jump.
We're learning.
Woo!
Okay, just jump over it again.
Okay, we're learning.
We're learning.
We're observing.
We're using our brain mass against her wills.
Hold on, I can double jump over this.
Oh, okay.
And then we'll butt bounce that.
No, we won't.
We'll double jump over this.
Oh, I almost messed it up.
Oh my God, the first checkpoint was so long into this.
On the flyer and sorcerer guys, I hate them too.
People are waiting for reviews to be announced.
And I agree.
I would want some sort of remaster or get the same dev team in because they're so precious.
Go away.
Oh, sugar.
Let's try that again.
Go away.
Wow!
What?
Yeah, that's exactly what I thought was going to happen.
And I was forced to do that.
Think again.
That guy's red.
Go green.
Go away.
Oh!
Oh, I just missed it.
Oh, I'm to fly.
Oh!
All right.
Oh, sorry.
I thought that was going to explode.
Right.
We'll do the bonus level.
I thought that was going to explode the moment I came near it.
Okay.
We're safe.
Oh, no.
The game's telling me to like double triple quadruple jumps and stuff.
Wait.
Well, double jump and then.
Okay.
We're fine.
Kind of.
Okay.
And we got an extra life.
Double jump.
Right.
We're not doing bonus levels anymore if there's a chance that I can perish in them.
I will not stand for such slander.
Thank you, Virginia, for the five gives to the members.
Shit.
And congratulations.
We caught it.
Enjoy the emotes.
I have four 10 emotes up.
Wait.
Just cross.
I have 10 emotes.
The girls are getting their batch attend before me because the emotes artist is going to take
a month to do them.
And I'm crying internally when she told me that because, ouch, why a month?
It hurts.
And they increased the price as well.
It sucks even more.
Because I like when emotes all look the same.
Like where it's clearly.
What the heck am I supposed to do?
Ah!
Wait.
Was I not meant to spam X?
You're a capture.
Oh, okay.
Oh, no.
You don't lose lives in bonus levels, though?
No.
So what am I supposed to do?
Yeah, that's exactly what I just tried to do.
But it didn't like it.
Oh, sorry.
I'm like hanging all these away.
So go up and then.
Coco.
Coco Chanel.
I'm going to start.
I need to work with your manager because what's going on here?
Coco.
Double jump.
And then X, X, X.
And then that's exactly what.
Ah!
Of course there's a TNT there just to ruin my day.
Right.
We're not going to double jump.
Ah!
Coco.
Coco Chanel.
Number five is the top leading women's perfume in sales.
It's just a fun fact.
I think it is anyway.
Right, go away.
Double jump.
I don't know why this is getting so hard.
Right.
So you do it that way.
So go and do it that way then.
Coco!
Oh my God.
Why are you not doing it that way?
You did it the other way.
So why won't you do it that way?
Right.
Double jump.
Oh sorry.
I'm like throwing all these apples away.
Right.
Not apples.
So fly and then X.
No.
Right.
That didn't work.
So fly up and then.
No.
Why?
Sorry.
I need to practice doing it this way.
But it's actually not doing it that way.
It's not.
Right.
I'm just going to spam A and X.
Oh, it worked.
It worked.
I literally just spammed A and X.
I'm so smart.
I don't know what the input controls are supposed to be.
Ah!
You know what?
See this game?
I have to go do that section all over again.
Because they put a freaking spike over that jump.
Oh!
And I've just lost my wheat oogabogamask.
Bruv.
I'm getting ruled.
I'll blame it.
My room is actually getting pretty warm right now.
Right.
Just spam A and X.
Okay.
We'll try again.
Wait.
Does the game know I'm struggling so it gives me a free mask?
I was like, oh, again with the tea.
The Nitro.
My goodness.
Alright, hold on.
I don't...
I'm trying to observe what I'm doing wrong.
No.
Is that it?
No!
Okay.
I know not to go now.
Right.
Spikes.
And jump on his doodle hair.
And then jump on that.
And then destroy everything and we did it.
Okay.
Jeez.
That was terrible.
That was a rough one.
The game giving me a free mask because I'm so bad.
You get the petty mask?
No.
That's terrible.
But I got the crystal.
That's the main thing.
18.
I did that one.
19.
I just did.
So, 20.
Oh my god, we're getting there.
Tomb wader.
More like, womb raider.
Am I right?
Thank you.
How many lives lost now?
Far too many.
Oh, there's scarabs.
Whoa, what are you?
Oh.
Okay.
There's water.
I guess I drowned in this game.
Right.
I guess I can't.
What are you?
No.
You're freaky.
Okay.
That actually worked.
I don't know how.
Wah, wah, wah.
Coco can't swim.
I'm gonna.
Let's get another one.
We'll stand on this box and let the water rise.
Please keep me trying a better one.
Oh, I don't like you.
Oh, go away.
Oh, what are you?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's what I thought.
Right.
If bonus levels cause me to perish,
I'm not really that fast for them.
Okay, hold on up.
Coco, up before you drown.
Oh, go, go, go.
Oh.
Wait, did that just go down?
I did.
Sorry, I'm trying to like,
peek ahead around the corner of the level
to be like, hmm, what comes up next?
Oh my God, no.
Not now, not now.
Wait, you don't drown?
Of course you don't drown.
Cause why would you?
But me?
I perish.
Oh wait, I'm gonna get this life
cause I'm doing so bad.
I need the lives.
Getting bonks back and forth.
Right, but 16 lives.
Right.
I'm trying to explode some contact.
Got another bonus level?
Oh no, that's a death level.
Oh my God, I don't like time missions.
They make me scared.
But we made it.
Oh, we got the gym.
Wait, hold on, hold on, hold on.
I'm so sorry.
I would like, commentate a bit more,
but I'm actually getting stressed
out playing this game.
Right, I need this platform.
The timing missions are like the worst.
Cool, cool.
Oh, checkpoint.
Right, that's all I needed.
Right, what are my recent saints?
Sorry, I'm like hardly reges at all.
Getting bonks back and forth.
A staring contest with a freaking game, honestly.
I believe the science assistants are robots.
Oh my God, we're getting secret hidden lore
that I don't know about.
Whoa, what was that up there?
I saw that.
I don't think I didn't see that.
Exactly.
What did I just do?
Whoa.
Is it this I just unlocked?
I think I probably just did that, yeah.
Ain't no way I'm jumping over those nitros.
They're going to explode.
I'm not even bothering to attack him.
Oh, can I make it in time?
Please don't crush me.
Okay, I made it, I made it.
Oh, there's TNT ahead.
Honestly, I thought this game was going to take eight hours,
but it must be eight hours if you're 100%
and like go back and do everything.
But yeah, I think we're probably going to be redirecting
to any of this.
If I'm blasting through the game like this,
it honestly would do me quite well
because I need to go up with the girls asmr.
Whoa, that per beetle just got absolutely annihilated.
Bonk.
Yes, Mercy and AC's meme asmr.
I'd be told I'm allowed to push,
I'm allowed to publish, so hopefully they do quite well.
Right.
Oh, let's go, Coco, you're doing amazing.
Right, we are going against Doctor...
Oh, engine.
Oh, I get it, I get it.
Let's hope I don't perish.
So, you want to go with your rhymes?
When this is over, we'll see who is obsolete.
Wah, my Tommy.
My Tommy.
Eh?
Ooh!
What am I to do?
I don't know what I'm to do, my shirt is willy.
Oh, my God.
I'm just spraying, I'm just spraying,
staying out of the way, holy crap.
The rockets are fricking locking onto me!
Why is he shooting from his winky, though?
I've not been funny.
I don't know what I'm supposed to shoot at,
and then I'm getting shot at really badly.
Eh?
No, nothing's happening to his health.
Maybe something's gonna happen after this attack sequence?
Oh, his winky single.
Oh, okay, I did it.
I destroyed his winky.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, you're hurting me, you're hurting me.
Okay, this one next.
Okay, okay, I see it's coming together, it's coming together.
I just need you to aim a bit better.
Am I to aim at his guns?
No, this cannot be right.
Although it kind of looks like I'm supposed to aim at his guns,
you know that.
Oh, but how am I supposed to do that without getting aimed at?
Oh, I'm not sure about that.
This?
Oh, it is, it is, this is guns, it's yellow, shoot the yellow.
Oh, my God, the yellow paint before yellow paint was a thing.
Oh, my God, Crash Bandicoot, you were before your time.
You were truly before your time.
Oh, I hardly got any licks in on that one.
I don't want to get in that way, but...
Okay, they're both sparking, so we're doing good.
I'll let him get as we spray out.
I'll go up so he can't get at me.
Oh, wow, his thing is really strong.
I can't really spray into him.
Okay, there we go, there we go, there we go, one more.
Oh, my God, we did it!
Oh, my God, we did it, we're so freaking good at this game.
Oh.
Uh...
Pura! Pura, Pura, Pura, Pura, Pura, Pura, Pura, Pura, Pura, Pura, Pura, Pura, Pura, Pura!
Pura's gonna help me!
We love Pura!
Okay, I'm literally just doing 360s to try and avoid any enemies and just do, like, tag damage.
Oh, my God, Pura is helping me so much.
Wait, that thing is getting closer to me, whatever that is, oh, it went behind me.
Uh, what the heck?
I don't know what's going on with that.
What?
Oh, Poodle, you're helping me so much, darling.
Poodle love.
We love Poodle out here.
Oh my god, yes!
We did it!
To fire fruit at a target, hold left mouse button to raise a gun and then aim with the direction and press B.
Wait, I actually do unlock a crossbow in Crash Bandicoot?
No way, that's so good.
I got nervous when I saw a face too, not gonna lie, I was like, eww, my confidence is making.
Uh huh.
Oh my aching head.
I'm not feeling myself these days.
So the end is in sight.
Gather another five crystals and again you will foil my plan.
Or will you?
He's got veneers.
Right, no, we're, wait, so we're falling for his trap if we keep progressing.
Wait, I've got my laptop and my laptop.
I have two laptops.
You're such an MLG gamer, Coco.
We're doing it!
Gone tomorrow.
News today, gone tomorrow.
That's the saying.
Are all the levels after a saying or like a pun?
Honestly, me.
Cortex is depressed for a throw.
What's going on here?
Double jump.
Oh, I don't like that.
Wait, double jump.
I guess you do even like.
Oh, I don't like that.
That's awfully menacing.
What do you do?
Oh wait, what was this?
I can unlock now.
I think I can throw food.
Oh, Coco!
Coco!
What on earth is that?
Coco, that's offensively large and hilarious.
Oh, I didn't mean to do that.
Sorry, I like jumped right into that.
Coco, that's not even a gun.
That's a rocket launcher.
Oh my gosh.
Wait, does this make the game like way easier though?
It does!
Oh my god, do you see that aim ball?
I could...
I will safely get past.
Bro, Coco, that was so violent.
Honestly, she's done asking nicely.
She's had enough.
She's like, bro, get me out of this game.
What, do this?
Oh no, I broke the box.
Oh my god, I didn't know you had a rocket launcher in Crash Bandicoot.
I definitely did not get this far into the game.
There's a child, there's a wean, there's a speckle, honestly.
I was probably a molecule when I was playing this.
I'm just the best in Bandicoot with a rocket launcher.
I thought of that meme, but there's like, nah, there's no way I can bring it up.
I'll have to let everyone bring it up.
Hold on, nah.
I can like aim to the sides like this.
Thank you, Lord of Strongs for the five gifted membership.
Congrats to those who caught it with your face.
You'll have to enable membership gifting.
You might get a prompt in chat if you don't have it enabled,
but congrats to those, you can use my emotes now.
Wait, oh my god.
I'm getting you.
Oh, it's out of bounds off, can't wait one.
Oh my god, I can destroy TNT from afar as well.
I don't know why I went up, I could have been blue.
Oh my god, this makes the game so easy.
I love it here.
I love fresh Bandicoot.
Or Coco can't Bandicoot because Coco Pog.
Wow, I almost got done.
Congrats on those who caught the member.
Wow, see it worked that time,
but every other time I try to do the fluffy effect and fly, it never works.
She didn't manage to do another two games.
I have never actually played the other two games,
so I don't know what the experience is like.
Oh, sorry, I didn't mean to get rid of all those asses.
Oh my god, the game is so kind.
It doesn't even go against your ammo.
Can I shoot you now?
No.
Okay, I have to do the dodge.
I'm freaking loving this game.
Oh my gosh, it's so well put together.
Other than the race in one's bus,
because I'm dumb and can't figure it out.
Ale vivas.
Thank you for coming on Membo.
And Lord of the Drums again.
For the gifted membership.
Me and the Reeflings.
Just as I was complaining about a race in the mission.
Ah.
It's the last one though.
It's the last race in mission.
Surely.
Two and then go.
Right, I got the boost.
The police are doing nothing.
Oh, I never even saw that.
Oh my god, I need my glasses on so badly.
Would you still love me as a streamer if I never put my...
I'm trying to hold it together.
I'm at the absurdity that is these maps.
For racing.
I'm literally seventh place.
There's no way.
There's no way I've got this.
I refuse.
Yeah, get in my way.
Okay, everyone's using the ramp which is fine.
I'll use it too.
Okay, you're going to have to use the ramp.
Because of the...
Bro.
These AI police cars!
Bro, you can't even reverse in this game.
Reeflings, I'm going to have to send my game file to one of you right now.
And then you send me it back complete and I'll go do the other missions while I'm at it.
Because this is ridiculous.
Why did they make the freaking driving one so hard?
And Crash, if you didn't stop skating everywhere across the map, we're actually going to have issues.
Out my road.
Okay, well that was terrible.
Please don't ever do that again.
I'm fifth place.
Oh, and I missed it!
Okay, the AI can actually go off road which is interesting.
I didn't know that.
The AI is adapting and I'm getting nervous.
Why are they...
Oh, and I missed it again.
I'm fourth place.
Honestly, that wasn't awful.
I'm wondering...
Right, we'll keep doing it.
We'll keep doing it.
That was the first time I played the map and the first thing I did was fall off it, okay?
Refillings are always thrilled to Princess Carrie and Mom, honestly.
I just wish...
I just...
I'm getting filtered by a child, okay?
Three, two, and then hold, boost.
Okay, and then on the left side there is already an issue.
So the AI is actually choosing to go off the map, which is curious.
I didn't think the AI did such a thing.
Very curious indeed.
Yeah, they're all avoiding the pull-offs.
So just take it easy.
These corners didn't do so...
Yeah, I didn't do so hot in these corners.
Wah!
I'll take that boost though.
I'll take that boost.
Thank you.
I have to take this ramp because there is a gap.
You will not make it.
Go Minasori.
You will not make it if you take that gap.
It's okay.
No!
Fenderbender!
That's illegal.
You have to stop and call the police!
Aw, fuck this.
Okay, hold on.
Can you Fenderbender?
Elsewhere, please!
Elsewhere.
Okay.
I'm trying.
I'm actually trying so hard right now.
I'm sweating my cheeks off.
I'm sweating my panties off, but you all know what's happening with that.
Oh, I might do it!
Oh my god, I might do it.
Oh my god, just don't...
No!
My mouth is a gap from how hard I'm trying right now.
Oh!
Oh my god, I did it in two!
Thank god.
Oh my god.
That was so freaking hard.
Literally maximum mouth breathing.
All wrinkly parts of my brain were locked in.
All the smooth parts of my brain were told to be quiet momentarily.
Oh my goodness, Gravy.
Thank god I never have to do a racing mission again.
Oh.
Victoire!
Victoire.
Oh lolol.
Oh, such a good game.
I'm sorry.
I'm absolutely loving this.
I highly recommend it, Revenge.
If you have got some money to spare right now
and you want to give a game-ish...
Hey!
I was on top of your heat.
I heavily recommend getting the V-Master Crash Bandicoot
because this is just fun.
I have to wait until the Knife Man goes away
and then I don't come this way.
Great.
Flamethrower?
I'm just fine.
Oh, the guy's gone now.
The game helps you if you're rubbish as well,
which is even better.
The game is holding my hand.
Oh my god, I can't believe a refling made this game just for me
because they knew how much I struggle.
Oh my god, reflins.
You're actually so selfless.
It's stunning.
You're so polite.
We've got a checkpoint.
What's going on here?
I made it anyway.
I don't know what's going on, but I made it anyway.
There's a little thing to the right.
I'm tempted to go explore,
but we'll go explore to the right.
What's over here?
Don't think I didn't see that.
I thought it was a hidden thing to the right.
And it's not.
You're telling me it's not a hidden area to the right?
Bro, I'm sorry, but reflins are pranking me.
I can't believe you got in the dev team just to prank me, bro.
Whoa, there's TNT there.
I want to interact with none of that.
I want none of this.
I want any problems.
I don't want peace.
I want to problem me giving myself more work is literally that mean.
I want problems.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, we ain't going.
We ain't going until you go.
Prince Ali, mighty is he.
Oh, blah, blah, blah.
Show some respect for you.
Oh, that's not a platform.
Okay.
Sorry, there's not a platform there.
Oops.
Oh, and I missed.
I think Coco just like constantly has her laptop on her.
She's like, yeah, I need this.
Honestly, it's safe.
I'm like, bro, but I need internet access to all things.
Okay.
Flamethrower, that's fine.
Do not go on the fake platform that isn't a real platform.
Okay.
You're going to be sorely disappointed that to find there's nothing.
Whoa, that was actually really lucky timing.
What's going on here?
I think the camera angles.
At first, I actually didn't like that.
I couldn't control that camera angle, but now I'm like, I get it now.
This is actually pretty, pretty nice.
This is pretty rewarding.
As much as we love a cheeky.
Oh, wow.
How often do you throw?
Right.
Okay.
I saw him peek and I was like, I'm about to get in trouble.
Right.
Jump and then jump again.
Okay.
We're getting there.
We're getting there refunds.
Oh my God.
An extra life.
Don't mind me.
The only thing I don't miss from the era is the time control.
Oh my God.
We're absolutely smoking.
We're smoking and no tobacco is needed.
Okay.
Wow.
So we only got two more levels and it's a boss fight.
Mad Bomba.
Bombadier.
Remember your bazooka.
Oh, I already forgot I had one.
Crash Coco.
Remember, it is not only Dr. Cortex that we battle.
Beware of Uka Uka, my children.
He is a far more dangerous enemy than anyone can imagine.
Oh no.
That's not good.
Shoot down the Bombadier.
Shoot down the bombers.
Like these planes that can shoot me.
Oh my God.
We're committing artillery warfare.
Get that plane done.
I'm going to just do this.
Are you a badie?
Yeah, you are.
Okay, so I can shoot the enemies as they appear and then I don't get hit by them.
Okay, that's pretty good to know.
Man, this one was so far away.
Okay, there we go.
Destroy this guy completely wholeheartedly.
I did see someone's one in there, but I think we're okay.
Okay, there we go.
I'll take the health now.
I don't know if that was a bit too preemptive, but we're doing it.
Oh, I see him.
I see him.
He was going to become a Kazian.
Jeez.
Okay, we're getting there.
We've got two more bombardiers.
What?
Sorry, the controls are inverted.
Sorry, I'm used to the controls being inverted for this.
Man, I'm absolutely smoking.
Sorry, I'm actually so good at this child game.
I need head pads for how good I am at destroying this child game.
I need accolades to forever recognize me as so good at beating up this game.
It's fantastic.
We did it.
Okay, we almost did it.
Wait, hold on.
Let me turn around.
Let me just get these guys first.
Turn around.
Every now and then I get to see you.
Oh my goodness.
Oh, I'm getting head pads.
You're in so good moment.
Good girl.
I was thinking of Sly Culver too.
You regularly get the petty mask.
No, don't point that out.
Don't tell them that.
No one needs to know that.
I don't get the petty mask that much, okay?
Okay, I just did that.
What's this?
A bug light, not to be confused with a bug's life.
Okay, you're doing great.
Thank you, Reflink.
This game is absolutely fantastic.
I cannot recommend this enough.
I may actually recommend the girls play it just because you don't really need any previous
knowledge other than that first dinosaur.
I was having a stroke trying to figure out how to get the dinosaur to not coblame on me.
I've got a little guide for the girls that has a list of the games that they can play
based on complexity, but I actually need to make it a much better list because I need
to add how long it takes to play or these temporary areas.
Oh, it's Navi.
Oh, wait.
Oh my God, I have my own light source.
It's beautiful.
All right, double jump, X, and we're safe.
Oh, this is beautiful.
Another light for me?
Oh, he got tired.
He needs to go to bed.
That's okay.
You don't have to do this for your entire life.
Oh, I keep throwing my apples away.
Oopsie.
Hmm, how far away did I just get put back?
Oh, I'll get masked right next to this one point.
Johnny's been fine, but most importantly, she's enjoying herself.
Everyone's happy.
Stream is bliss.
Oh, that's so precious.
I'm glad you guys are happy.
Oh, I keep throwing away me one for fruit.
Okay.
You can now go into retirement and then I'll take you.
And then what did I do wrong here?
I already forgot.
What's that?
No, Coco, you're spinning everywhere.
Okay.
Jump and then double jump.
See?
Nice and simple.
Biggest enemies are literally jumping in this game.
No other reason.
Okay.
Whoa.
No, it's dark.
Oh, hello.
I cannot see.
Please do not leave me alone.
Oh, okay.
Wow.
Okay.
Whoa.
Oh my God.
I'm sort MLG pro.
You literally can't stop me.
How long does this last for?
Oh, it literally ended just as I walloped that enemy.
Holy crap.
Okay.
Let's try that.
I'm gonna check mine. Thank you Zengo 999 for becoming a member. I appreciate it
And membership streams do start always it's so dark. I can't see
And membership streams start Nate how on earth am I supposed to deal with all of them?
Just to go for it
They start next week and I will show you the schedule the plan the dude. Oh wow actually well
Everything is showing on
Oh ouchie I hurt myself
Buckshot roulette my goodness. Sorry. I'm really trying to speak in I can't do two things at once
Oh my god, we did it bruv all these missions are so fantastic. Oh, I can't see for shit and there's a jump ahead of me
No, we're gonna say I couldn't see at all la Latina floor. Thank you for becoming a member
Oh
Boss fight
Okay, I can't believe you're playing crash Bandicoot. I'm playing childhood games
Although I only remember Coco and the tiger and the tiger's name dr. Neil Cortex
Boss fight already. Oh, they really said guys almost
Warped it's you know. Hi stranny
Can't believe you are playing one of my favorite childhood games
Been trying to do one childhood game
Oh
These missions are fantastic immediate criticism of the light in
Oh, no, oh
No, oh my god, they're battling it out the tiki masks are going for it
What I do
I do I need to jump over it. Oh, I need to jump over their laser beam if they get in the way
No tiki man's trying to help me out, but the baddie is all the way while you're putting yo C4
Why are you putting C4 on the ground? Oh?
Wait, oh, no, I was supposed to wall up him his shield was down. I'm sorry. I missed that cue
I don't I don't think I ever I highly doubt I actually got past the second stage
I
Cuz I didn't really remember anything right. He throws these and they explode and
His shield was there
What does it mean go in go in go in go in?
Okay, okay, okay, we've got it. We know what the mechanic is
Am I to go in? No, okay. I was actually about to go in that hole. I'm not gonna lie
Okay, they're gonna battle now
Oh, no, it's candy flosses ultimate from the hit game come through chaos
Okay
Right when he puts mines then that's when I can make a move. Okay now. I don't know if the AI locks onto me
I'm gonna get in and hole and hole and hole and hole and hole in the hole. All right. Oh
My god, we're doing and we're gonna do it reflames. I've never finished this game. I'm so excited. I
Get to finish it with you
Okay, they're doing oh
They're doing different moves. Oh, this is dangerous. This is very dangerous
Oh
No, no, no, no, don't do that. Okay. Okay, it's fine. We're safe
Okay, he's throwing the mines
Okay, okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Let me get up. Let me get up get all get all
Geez I hate you. She's human. Oh wait, why am I getting an ability?
You run faster holding down right trigger while running wait, this isn't the end of the game
Monkey is there's more
To the Bahamas
Wait a minute
I did it
He was talking about Tati bull jangles
We did it. Oh my god, that was such an amazing game. I'm clapping for myself. I'm pretty good
Wow
Oh my god
What fantastic game
It's so goofy it's so fun. It's so beautiful. I
What that was just an amazing game all around those are 10 out of 10 experience
I heavily recommend you to play that if you've never played it before. Oh
It's so good. I
Cut cut cut cut cut. Oh my god producers north. Thank you. Okay. Oh Martin for coming to the designers for crashing Coco
Thank you Justin Hessler. That was fantastic level designers
Andy, maybe not thank you to you because I know you did that dinosaur one
What was that that was not me burping for once for once the game burped that took me completely I was doing
Character artists. Thank you. Corey Turner lead animator Curtis or more like Curtis smashed it 10 out of 10
visual effects artists rich Megan
Fantastic you I artist Kara Zezas. We could not have done it without you engineers
My goodness your alchemy engineers Alan Abrams. Thank you
Alchemy senior producer Clive burgeon you earned that senior position role 10 out of 10. Thank you
Tim till lots in don't think I wouldn't forget you
Senior data analysts look you analyze that data far beyond expectations
Audio designers Matt Pirog. Oh your audio was 10 out of 10
The way the SFX was fantastic
Congratulations on beating the game
Pen penitent. Thank you for the tip and thank you for congratulating me on the game finish in the child's game
The VV backbone not to be confused with the
globally well-known VTuber VV
The ASMR ASMR the Australian VTuber. Let's go VV
But how could we have done it without you IT administrator Anthony?
Recycle to you. We're so thankful recruitment coordinator Blair. You recruited out the wazoo user testing
Johnny reach. Thank you for finding that bug on that one map and getting it written out fantastic VV babies
Oh my god development actual development teams children's names
Congrats at all being birthed from the loins of your parents that are on the development team of Crash Bandicoot warped remastered
Additional development support for toys for Bob. Oh
Mike Albert. We could not have done it without you and a very special. Thank you to Naughty Dog
Dan Erie
Fantastic truly truly
With an additional special thanks to none other than David Siller himself and a special thanks to shout out to all regional team members and
Activision you've run a few games into the ground, but this one you did 10 out of 10 on so I'll let it slide for once
Archivist Heather we love a good archiver shout out to archive and on Heather
And other archive annals that may be out there you worked the diligently in the dark to serve the light
Yes, that's an assassin's brother brotherhood just reference
Oh my goodness golly. Whoa
Wait, he didn't go whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa. I'm pretty sure crash bandicoot supposed to go whoa
Oh
Time for more children's games of Eva Pinata is coming up and so is cameo as I said in July
I'm gonna focus on nailing down some gamer score because I don't know what happened to Skyrim
I don't know why it wasn't popping we might return back to Skyrim actually wow
There's so many noises a bluey game win a bluey game. What's the bluey game? I'm so sorry. I don't know what a bluey game
Time yeah, strongy you set a perfect
I'm pretty sure he goes
Because there's loads of memes of them going
Bluey inside all the show bluey that's for Aussies
Activision publishing yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, okay
Well, let it slide Activision. Thank you to the market and team Josh to have
Your advertisement didn't come to me, but I just knew about this game from childhood
So shout out to you lysis and in partnerships. We love a good licensing out here
Thank you for lysis and crash bandicoot so I could enjoy it to its full extent
supply chain operations Tom Benny
We couldn't have done it without you enjoy that senior director position you earned it. Hopefully it was not
a
Nepotism hire, but you know what will let it slide for this game this
Experience the OST. I am gen 3
Background music is gonna be crash bandicoot OST. I'm not even I'm not even gonna tell any lies or any scoobies
I am blown away by this game. Obviously. I had a chance to play it in childhood
So there was a lot of nostalgia associated with the game
But this have always nothing but a short of fantastic a lovely experience
Truly the game didn't feel feel like it was going on too long if you enjoy it. You can also a hundred percent it and
Just ten out of ten all-round type of game
For me helps with a short attention span helps that was designed for kids to play helps that was beautiful
Colorful and everything is so interactive. Do you have any plans to play the newest crash game crash board?
It's about time. I've never played it
Um, but I would understand why not if it's anything if any of the other crash games are like this that they're quick
Wham-bam, they've got fun little interactive mini games inside like the different levels. Sure
I will a hundred percent play the rest of crash bandicoot
Oh
My god senior IT networked physician fergus
Beautiful voiceover production
Shout out to the VAs love that casting director Julia Bianco more like Julia
You absolutely blew it with the water. Thank you Julia. And then there's crash team racing. I ain't playing no
I ain't playing no driving games
This soundtrack to the old ST
Gods themselves. Thank you
Shout out to crash. Yeah
You need to play the spiral games. Oh easy child game friendly
short
optional one hundred percent
Count me in
Yeah, crash 4 is actually pretty hard. Okay, maybe not. Maybe we'll just pause on crash 4
Just for now
Yes, go pyro would be fun
Spyro is even easier than this. Spyro is super easy
When's the pizza tower stream? I don't even know what that is. I
Hope in the end of credits and it says and thank you the fans
I'm allowed to say a spoiler for the video game
The vealer video game
Sure say the spoiler, okay, this is for only people who are watching the stream at
The end of the vealer video game
You hear a voiceline from all of us and we say and thank you the player after you have just put one hand at our game
Because I love it so much in video games. I was like, I'm having it in this game
Trial wait, are these speedrunners? No trial testers one hour. Wait, why is it showing time? I
Don't know what the times are for
Okay, let's go. Yeah after we finish the game literally all of us come on and we all go. Thank you the player
and
Oh, these are the devs
Are these the speedrun times?
That's outrageous. Did they all know it can't be this is 12 minutes
No one has completed the game. Maybe speedrunners. 12 minutes would be broken the game
The other game is designed to play one-handed. Oh, it absolutely is we can't we can hardly even talk about it
I'm going to get the girls to record them playing it
And then they'll upload it to their alt-twitters so they can like play it for the first time and experience it
It's pair map the map names were on the left my apologies. Oh my gosh ten out of ten experience
What a magnificent game what a well-rounded no wonder they remastered it
So what does this do interacts swap hero save loads? That's it. We'll save
and
Yeah, wow just ten out of ten. Oh
Wait, what did I just do? Oh, did I accidentally just load over my save? Oops
It sees. Oh, it's fine. We finished the game. Anyway, I think I'm gonna mess stuff a little bit there, but it's okay. I
Think I undid all my progress. Oopsies. I did all my progress. That's too busy yapping
Don't worry though
We all make mistakes
Yeah, no, that's well, there's no point in saving because I'm already saved up. Oh, well, it's fine. It's fine. That was
Fantastic, right. I'm gonna check if there's any veal or girlies on and I understand that this is a shorter stream
I thought it was gonna be an eight hour stream, but I was wrong and
but in exchange
in exchange
For a shorter stream
My darling grieflings
Mercy and AC's meme ASMR is gonna be uploaded at a certain time
It might be timed after the stream because I think mercy asked for me to make sure it's after she finished streaming
She's gonna end up all savings over the 30% also. No, no, no, no, no
Emi is up in an hour. That's perfectly fine with me. Um, oh
Pardon me for being so rude. I just burped there. Don't mind me
Oh, no, I got kicked out of my YouTube account. Shit. Hold on. I need a fucking message management from my password
Hmm
Just need to message
What is my YouTube password, please? I'm locked out. I'm locked out. I don't know why I locked me out
Oh, do excuse me. Oh
But I hope that's not YouTube fucking doing something okay, okay with my account better. No be
Right, let me go to a chat and stream Dave. Have a what it's me
It's me. Oh my god. It's me
Right, I'll put some background music on
One one. I want one. That was such an amazing team
God, I can't go for that. Right. Emi is going to be up in T
minus
T minus what?
An hour. Oh my god, I have no hour to yeah, don't mind if I do
Oops, no, I definitely do not want to end stream from the dashboard
Please don't give me that option. That scared me. Don't do that again YouTube. Please don't do that again. You're stressing me out
Hey, I'm just gonna make sure I'm redirecting into any piezo because her monetization stream
Is monetization celebrate celebration
Monetization celebration
I give up. I give up. Um, Emi Emi Emi monetization celebration
And
Yes, okay, it says save so when I end my stream
God, I can't get over how fantastic that game was
Uh, what's going on?
Why have I got so many comments on that new ASMR video? Well, I'll show you the stats again
I'll show you the stats on that. I don't know. Uh, hopefully I'm praying that the girls's mean videos also get as popular as mine because
That that got really popular for like no reason. Oh my god. I don't want to brag or anything. Hold on
Let me let me screenshot so I can show you guys the dirty details
The dirty details the the oh, sorry. I just blurt flash behind myself trying to save this file save file
That one. Uh, actually, I can just take off the reactive model. That's probably a bit better of an idea. Don't you think?
Wait, so it's just a zero
Um, right hold on. How do I show?
How do I show this on desktop?
Um
What did I call the file? I've already forgotten the file name
Oh, there there
Okay, so this is what it said. Oh, it's there you on
Bit big bit big
This is what it says now on that video
So congrats. You have 34,000 views, bro. Yeah, I definitely got picked up in the algorithm because I only had 5000 subscribers
It says I earned 780 subscribers from it. She
My that video alone reached youtube's monetization watch time
Thingings it literally says 3000 watch hours. That's how much you need to get monetized
You need that one video alone. You need 500 subscribers and 3000 watch hours that one video alone
I could submit for monetization. That's insane
And also, of course, I'm breaking the bank at 20. Please don't be don't be surprised when the 3d models come out
Next week because my ASMR is raking in the money. Yes. No, no, there's no 3d
VTuber streams coming up just yet cost a pretty penny to get that stuff kind of dealt with
Yes, there will be signs. Yes, there will be signs
um
But yeah, that video definitely uh is getting about
That was fantastic. I can't believe it
It's not yacht soon. Absolutely not. I have no desire for a yacht
That is
I've I just never had an interest in that kind of thing at all
Right, I want to open up marshmallow, but last time I opened it up. It had a little bit of
Uh, right, let me I will link my marshmallow so you're free to
Penis chocolate ASMR surprisingly is popular
Brian, it's not that it was pentas dorkin
uh, it was
Uh, thank you. Oh marin something for the super chat. It was me asking to hold it while you tinkle
It's not pentas dorking
The next audio I upload is for now. I'm I'm I'm I'm teasing I'm breezing for a teasing
Dear mommy next time you go in a tinfoil. Yeah, can I join you on stream?
Wait, have you have you put a little tinfoil hat on a wiefling?
Oh, my little wieflings have a tinfoil hat. You're so cute. Let me put it on right now. Hold on
Next time I go for a wee rant. This is I'm gonna put you right next to me right here on my right here
Oh, wait, no, hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. I can do I can do you a step even better than that hold
Hold pause pause
Pause don't breathe
Oh
Okay, you can breathe you can breathe again. Wow
Wow
Look, it's me and the wieflings. We're gonna take them black ropes together
My little wiefling
You're so good
Oh my god wiefling you're actually so well placed. I can probably do this
That wiefling literally I know
Thank you for your helpful advice some events happen that would have hurt a lot more if I hadn't thought of you
What you told me you give me strength. Oh, I don't know what advice I gave but I'm glad it could help in the moment
You are
very strong
Your is
Some sometimes you could actually say you're as strong as your weakest days because on your weakest days
You just want to give up but you didn't so you're as strong as your weakest days
Does that make sense?
I don't know. Maybe it does
Keep your keep your chin up wiefling your headset's falling off king. Okay. Come on. We gamers out here. We memers
We're just memers
We memer low
away
No, it does not
Looks like a hair. She's kiss leave my hair. She kissed addicted wiefling alone
Hearts full balls empty should be a bit a vealers official catchphrase. That's amazing
Oh bucket tape. Thank you for becoming a member
Bye
Membership streams are revealed next tomorrow in the next 24 hours. You will know
You will know
and
But yeah
My mouse
See you it's because of not actually
Right, hold on. Let me I'll tell you some lore in a minute
The reason my mouse does that
Is because the light and is very low as well as I've actually not synced up my vtuber model
Nari rigged me so well like she made me so well
I actually haven't gone into the calibrations to make strongy like the
The mecca like reactive to the microphone or whatever
Um, so like Nari is just that good. I love your fangs. Oh, yeah, do you love them enough to you know?
Let me
In your Frankfurt
Hey, right, let me get my wee marshmallow link. Where did I even send the marshmallow link? I don't even think I did
Oh my god, I'm gatekeeping my own marshmallow
pay the bow
Can you see?
Wow, you guys can tell that I am not all there in the head from that message
I am not all there in the head, but that's okay
Oh
Yes, you strongy. No strongy. Yes
Why would you say no to me? I'm not supposed to say no to me. You know what happens when you say no
This
But that part comes later not yet soon
But yes, um, it is a smaller stream
But the smaller stream I actually thought it was going to be eight hours, but because it's not eight hours
I'm actually going to have the energy to go edit. So I might have my first
Thank you for 1000 audio uploaded on youtube on here for free all yours all yours
I will also upload the audio file to patreon as a archive to make sure nothing is lost to time itself
Um, and I will take it from there
my next patreon
audio
Should technically actually be uploaded on the 22nd, but I'm not gonna do that. I'm gonna let it be a bit funny
I'm gonna the first month on patreon is funny. You still get four audios on patreon, but they're just a bit funky
They're spaced out a bit weird. Uh g-man stew. Thank you for coming on
What happens when we say no you get hypnotized?
You don't have a choice
And I don't I don't care. I don't care if that sounds our wordy. You don't have a choice
But you you you'll come to learn to like that. You don't have a choice. That's terrible
I can't say that stuff out loud and yet I do what happens next
Hmm what happens next?
Outrageous streamer says some something outrageous. Oh, oh no, okay
Uh glad you enjoyed my three page story. It was so good. Maybe can I maybe read it? I'm gonna see if I can read it
okay
Stroney has just finished taking a shower and calls her wreathlings into her room
Hi there wreathlings. Stroney said oh in a sultry voice. Hi there wreathling
Stroney says in a sultry voice
Mummy is ovulating and it's time for a new gen
Can you all last long enough to satisfy me and get the job done?
She drops her towel and lies down on the bed
wreathlings approach
Slowly sliding a tentacle or two. I don't think I can read this. I don't think I can read this. I'm like
I don't think I could substitute
Slowly sliding a tentacle or two up Stroney's legs and arms
And across her stomach massaging her body so she can relax after a long stream. She just finished
Eventually some wrap their tent. Yeah, I can't read the rest of it. I guess really I guess really uh
But um, I wouldn't actually mind if you guys want to send me like little mini scripts like that
I honestly wouldn't mind just reading them and then putting them on the alt
Twitter just for fun just for a little
Uh something something
I can't be here then somewhere. Please. Yes
Um, it was a very cute story about how gen two is going to be produced with me in the replay
Um, I honestly don't mind. I find that stuff adorable and my voice isn't too fried right now
So I might be able to do it today. Um, do let me cook though. But yes, you guys are welcome
Um for me, I don't know the comfort level of the girls yet
So please don't apply what I am comfortable with to the girls. They are their own individuals
They are their own creatives
But if you guys ever want to send me a short script and just say please mummy
Um, or if you commission an artwork of me, um, you know a strong so you're welcome to say I
Or did you know I
Saw this fan art and I came up with the script if you want to combine the two together
Please do and put it on the alt twitter. I am happy to do that. I am very open to this. So, um
And it's completely free to access. I will not, you know, pay a wallet not not not my job
But I won't I won't pay wall. Um, like little short scripts and fun fans submitted
Stuff. I'm a fan. I don't like the word fan. You're not a fan. You're my reflet
Have the girls heard of the tinfoil right rants if so, what's the reaction? Oh, I'm too embarrassed to tell them
Um, I'm too embarrassed to like tell them how much I like despise debt and credit cards and how like the economies rigged against them, especially because like
um
They may or may not live in America, which makes it even like
Everything is against them
Like she'd be told a story about her crashing a car and then she jumped off a cliff or something
I'm like, yeah, I'm too embarrassed to tell the girls that part. I just say to them like, oh, you're doing great. Um
I just need this ASMR script from you. I'll edit the rest. You guys just have fun
It's too late for me. It's over two weeks and I hear your voice in my head all the time
Have I successfully mind broken you dear refling?
Why do you act like you don't want to?
Let it happen
Let me see into every part of you
Until it's all
Glad I could mind break you though. I've not even done that part of the hypnosis yet
I mean, we ain't even done the tear list yet where I explain in detail every scenario I want to do to you because of that tag
Hydration check
Stroni you make me fragile when you talk like that. That's why I do it
They're gonna be a little me mark and be all happy and stuff
But I do like the juxtaposition
As well as many other positions hold on a minute
Thank you
Here all week
Dear mommy. Oh, I did beat that one
Oh
Wow someone's analizing my ovulation cycle
So a normal ovulation cycle lasts about 24 hours each month. This is correct
Once an egg is released from an ovary it will dissolve within 12 to 24 hours
If it's not fertilized and the window is about a week before ovulation since seeds survive for almost a week
so basically
If I was to try and fertilize you I would need to do it the day before for optimum success chance
Which means the 13th of the month
All refling you went gen 2 already
You missed your window of opportunity. You're gonna have to try again next month with me, huh?
And we'll just keep trying and trying and trying
Uh
Okay
Hi, strongy. Hi replaying
Just wanted to say that I appreciate your content so far
Well, I absolutely continue support. Oh, thank you. I'm glad I'm glad
I'm a bit nervous sending you my first marshmallow. Oh, don't worry. I don't bite
hard
Uh
But I'll be sure to send you some more stuff in the future quick question any advice for aspiring script writers
Make sure to smash that like button and subscribe to my marshmallow account for more content. What?
What does that mean? Um
Any advice for aspiring script writers consume content and then do what you like
The easiest way for things to naturally occur and no then again. I am I have a raging
Uh tism over things which helps me like just absolutely work out the wazoo
Um, whenever I'm presented with a new
Special interest that I'm being educated about
I will consume multiple videos of that content. I will I'll put them in times too so I can
Understand the language that's being used the scenario or situation
Um, and then I just say I like this part, but I didn't like this part. I will do this
And I will do that and make it my own. That's basically how I tip scripts
It's not that it's not like saying honestly, the behind the scenes is rather boring
Hmm do risky things happen on membership stream. I don't know
Uh, we're doing a tag rating stream
Uh for my first stream ever doing a watch along. Um, I think we're actually watching transformers
The first transformers were sam wit wiki
Sam congrats if you're named sam by the way, but his name is sam wit wiki
His marshmallow cherry yonk my cherry now
Reflings have six tentacles you have eight you have eight arms
But you make a little love heart
With your front tentacles because we love each other and you got your little nicotine that
With
Actual cannibal shy and the buff
The o7 movie. Yeah, like it's like we're she a love off shy a love off. Sorry. She uh
She ain't love off. Um
Did you enjoy
The filian fanfic?
It'll be on fanfic or this local filian fanfic. Oh, I
Don't know where the location of that was
I
You know stroney my phone broke recently and all it did was glow green and start moving up and down
Kind of like when you start glowing it reminds me of you
Your phone broke. I'm I'm literally hacking into your technology right now. So you become even more obsessed
It's working
The nicotine patch subdues you for a little bit, but
Unfortunately, I get a bit too intense, which is why I need to subdue you
Editing a silly burp compilation of one of the girls. What do you think?
Uh
Yeah, I don't see why not. I'm not being funny. Someone said that a she be let out a to
I didn't I'm gonna freaking message she be after the stream and be like
Can I clip your to because whenever
A toot gets clipped. Um, all of a sudden
Um, it's like super funny and ha ha and all of that
um, so literally the start of the
Short is going to be like brian tts being like vtuber
accidentally farts on stream
And and play the clip and then oh, oh a hundred thousand views, please
Please give she be a cabillion subscribers. Yeah
Need to go ask the girls. I literally I need to go put in the discord
If any of you have farted, uh, please let me know so I can clip it if you're comfortable. Let's be clipping it
Oh my god edit my gen mates part. Oh
What a weird timeline we live in my ancestors were peasants working in the fields
If only they knew that the one who surpassed like the bloodline ends up editing a toot
Do you think my ancestors would laugh at that or they'd just be like what is going on over there? They're like, no, I can't handle this
Oh the archive of our own link. No, I didn't read it. Yeah, I got a bit nervous because I don't know what archive of our own is
I think it's just for text and stuff
um
I'm sorry mummy, but when you rage at games, I think of you are wording me with that passion
Or replaying. I don't think we're allowed to say that out loud
But that's hot
That's amazing. Have you ever played metal gear before I haven't
Um, is it easy if it's easy? I'll play it. Is there a story mode for gamers like me?
He's just the one that's saying it out loud wait post that meme where it's the guy like standing up
Hold on. Wait standing up meme guy. Uh, he's like standing up in a courtroom
Oh my god, I've got it. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on
Wait, let me make the meme. Let me make the meme. No one say a thing or I'm gonna forget how to make the meme
Okay, I've got the jpeg
And then I need to open it up in ms pain. Hold on. Let me open up the picture in ms pain
No one say a thing. Okay. Let me cook
Let me cook
Let me
Cook
Let me cook. This is so bad. This is terrible
Reflins, you're such a naughty influence on me
Said by one refling together
Okay, is that gonna work? I mean, I think it's gonna work. Yeah, okay, it's working
You can tell of me this is an ms pain. Oh my god. Hold on. Are you ready for this? Are you ready?
Oh, we are lost it. Oh no, it's like we're down here. This is literally
Oh
No
A thing thank you for the tip slice saver
Refling you're standing up against the masses. You're so brave for saying that part out loud
Oh
That's so terrible. I hope no other beach ever comes in stream and sees that
Oh my god, that's terrible
Why are we like this together? We bring out the worst side in each other like the the degenerate side in each other
honestly
Hmm
Moment are you gonna take the bit of some little test again? Yeah, I'll take it
Um
We can 100% do that stuff
I have no problem with that stuff. Where's the mean best? He speaks the truth
And they hated him for he spoke the truth. I can't I'm not gonna edit into that Jesus meme
I
Hi, Stony. I want you to bite me all over and leave marks all over me including on my tentacle. I
I wouldn't do it hard. Okay. I wouldn't do it hard
I would do it to a degree
Okay, I'm all caught up with marshmallows. So I'm just gonna be staring at you now chat. What are you gonna do about it, huh?
What are you gonna do? Sorry, I'm burping away over here
We're a match made in something probably not heaven because we can't make it into heaven
With this stuff that we go on about we can't make it into heaven. Oh, no
Stare back
I feel like I could uh, I'm terrible at blinking contests
I remember everyone in the playground was like, oh, I do do stare contest and I would always lose because I suck
I'm already in heaven. No need to go elsewhere
Will the member streams be archived? I may not be able to tune in. I'm not gonna try and get them banned. No, I think we'll be okay
We're gonna use our euphemisms
Where I go tentacle and ink
And I want to
Ink on the tentacle
Because we're cut off fish out here
We're cephalopods
But together we're a cephalopog because we're so cool like that. Yeah pogger
Um
Have I ever heard about the gates by ass rock? I'm so sorry. I've never heard of that in my life
We're all stuck in perigatory
Keep that in mind
Because there may or may not be a collab with a va and all viola members that is related to purgatory. So keep that in mind
Uh, funny you brought a funny you brought that up. Yeah
Um, imagine pieta, but it's the virgin mary given jesus. Whoa. We we can't be saying that stuff out loud
That's those are inside thoughts
Oh sense interesting. Yeah
You better be excited
I like when strony spoils. I try my best. I do
I the dust is definitely settling on my list of stuff to do
Like a lot of things are becoming a lot easier. Um
And it's getting to the point where I can fully be strummer. Yes, I can be strummer. Um
I
I wouldn't mind having a clip manager, but sadly, um
I don't have anyone. Um
I trust to be in that position
Um
Because clip manager needs access to the girls accounts to see what people have been clipping and it ain't gonna happen
so
Unfortunately, I am still clip manager at this point in time
But it's not too bad because literally I just take a clip and then I send it to editor and then editor comes back
And then I upload it on girls channel and it's all hunky dory. It's not a problem
Strummer I like when strony you didn't finish your sentence
Mummy protecting her doors. Yes. Um, I will be your shield. I know not a lot you play overwatch
I used to play it quite a lot. Sadly, I fell out of love with it. Um
When overwatch 2 came out, but there is a girl called
Brigitte Lenthal and her slogan is I will be your shield
And yes, I am Brigitte for my gen mates
Because I don't want anything happening to them
and
So I'm the I am both the owl and the shield
I love when strony does anything
Yes, uh tomorrow's stream. I'm gonna see if I can get my heart rate monitor working. Um
So
I should be able to do that
And then you can see my heart rate during buckshot roulette
I didn't manage to watch any more baltral content because I literally I finished stream
I did I see an emmy's memberships and then
Then what would I do? I don't know. Um, and then I went on twitter
I think I liked one thing and then passed out and then I woke up like
45 minutes before stream
I probably needed a big sleep like that. Like it was coming. It was coming that I needed a sleep like that
Strony that was the whole sentence. Wait, what was the sentence?
That's the whole sentence
I also like when strony I do like when strony
But why are clips private?
I don't know youtube doesn't let people see what people have clipped on
live stream or any content really
If it was public then I could get a clip master, but I can't get a clip master because they're not public
But hopefully youtube changes that in a couple of months because that would then negate me even needing to
Be a clip master. Um, and then I can spend even more time
We're briefly wait. They're not
Do you remember sending marshmallows to the girls? I remember completely crashing on yesterday's stream for anyone who wasn't watching the runescape stream
I hit the 11 hour mark and became
Delirious I spilled all my chips on the floor when I ended stream and I just left them until this morning to clean up
I was gone with the wind. I
I don't know what happened. I ate food and I was like, oh, this will wake me up. This will wake me up. No, it freaking didn't
day
One day we'll hit 12 hours for old school runescape. Honestly
um
No, I didn't have any issues with the
Playing it but I like completely crashed the ending of the stream was so funny
I just remember being like, oh, let me send the girl some marshmallows
And then I started typing and I don't really remember what the contents of it were but hopefully
All is good. Um
But yeah, I remember just
Freaking losing it basically
I crashed way before that part of stream
You used up all your energy trying to win connect for unironically. Oh my god
If you didn't see runescape stream quick recap in runescape, you can play connect for
I was getting
decimated
like
The reeflings were like ganging up on me just
Fucking one at a time one after the other like bro. I just accepted my fate. I could not win at connect for
One I won one because I tried so hard and burnt my brain
The second one I won by accident because a reefling couldn't see what I was doing
Um, I was gonna absolutely destroy
Yeah, I remember my sleep fading and then some strange noises coming up
Um
It sounds like a fun time bro. I was perishing
I don't know what happened because normally I can last 12 hours and I had an eight hour sleep before it
But my brain oh my stomach just made a noise if you heard that my brain just perished like it had enough
It was like, I'm sorry. I can't hold out anymore
Checkers. Oh, no, I'm not playing checkers again. That was the most confusing thing. I couldn't even bro
We were playing checkers and I couldn't even move on the board
Because I didn't know what was like going on
Um with the dang thing. It was a redonkula. Hold on
Uh, I'm just gonna pin the marshmallow. Oh my god. That's me. That sounds like that
Q and a
I say q and a is if we don't just like
That's not the q and a length. Hold on a minute. That's the that's what the reefling said
Wait a minute. Who are you? I need to draw any cuttles. There we go. That's one
Bit of q and a q
and
Boom
Uh, it's not really a q and a is it just you guys being lovely to me and then I go in a ramble and I see how lovely
um
It is to be here strong a leaks. Oh, yeah
Oh, no, I sent it to myself now
Oh, no, I've been discovered. I send myself all these marshmallows
I fell asleep to your stream and my brother was very much questioning what on earth you were watching when you woke up
Just me raging
I choked on my burrito rage and actually which was that makes it like 10 times funnier
so
And then I'm rage
Hi, mommy. I don't know what to ask, but I really love watching you. Oh, glad you're so funny, bro
You're giving me an ego. We all know the forbidden rule
Uh, just genuinely entertaining in more ways than when a yeah
Your streams always make me smile and giggle. Oh, you have any giggle mate. Please keep it up to te amo hemosa
Much love from
Te amo portarico come to brazil. No, we're not I'm not going to brazil, but thank you for inviting me. No
Thank you for the nice uh little message
How do you feel about the dragon age games? Particularly the upcoming veil guard game? Um
I've never played a dragon quest game properly. Sorry a dragon age game properly
Uh, I played the one where brother and sister and then brother like immediately. Well, I said for the brother or die
I think I played it for like 30 minutes and I was like, oh this ain't for me
Um, but there seems to be quite a lot of fans that are distraught at the reveal because they don't like it
but I thought it was just uh
I think why do we hate brazil? No, it's a meme
Where it's like, oh come to brazil do a concert in brazil, but brazil's really dangerous for foreigners
We don't actually hate brazil
Hi stronti, I agree with that one riff riefling when you rage. I always think of you
pinning me down and having your
your way with me
And then not stopping even when I finish. Oh my god, rieflings. This is good
I don't think we could say any of this out loud
What if I'm here because I was hypnotized by a moment. Maybe the hypnosis is listening up. We should hypnotize more
Not yet. You have to wait. You have to wait
soon
It's overtism
We're hitting overdrive
What was that stream song overdrive?
Burning machine
Oh brain power. That's it brain power
How did you decide which of the generation one models were going to be used?
Where are there other people auditioning for stronti? No, um, if you weren't there at the start development
All six models were laid out on the website under the auditions page
Uh, I was codename inks and it said I am a pre-selected talent, but please apply to be my gen mate
Uh, no one could apply for stronti because I'm stronti
There is only gonna be one stronti. You can't you can't get better than me. Okay
Uh, welcome to the danger zone
Ora ora
Um, as for who did I pick?
uh
The models for
I did take into account what the girls went for but when I heard the girls
Voices it pretty much instantly my brain went oh, okay. That's gonna be enemy. Oh, okay. That's definitely I say oh, okay
That's mercy. Oh, that's our genre. Oh, that's she be um
Because I got to hear them talk in general in the introduction introduce yourself video
And they gave me a good indication of personality type and all that so
If anyone wants to complain you you hired wrong you put someone on the wrong shot
shot
Don't want to hear it
Do you don't want to hear it?
Uh for a siren that can't sing you just need to ramble and yap and I'll follow you under the waves
I don't actually want you to perish
It was the concept artist that gave me that lore
I don't want anyone to perish
Hmm. Can you say shut one word to shut?
And you put the girl on the right shot
Don't want to hear it
Don't want to hear it give I'll give you gills. Yeah, you got a good voice to listen to I am I rambling you to sleep
Oh, dear
Listen to my voice as I ramble you to sleep
I
Don't he doesn't perish. He just beats on you
Like the water helps with where the things I need to do to you. Okay
I'm gonna put you
Seven days no ink help, please
How has it been so long?
I say that as if I'm not
Backed up but
How what do you mean help?
Help
This kind of help is that the help you need?
Is that what you need?
I don't know what help you need you didn't specify you got to specify or I'm not gonna come up with that one
Hi, strongy. Are there any talents of corpus you'd like you'd like or veal or to collab within the future
Hey, I'm humping you me plus and I'm humping v and you because they were lovely
Mythos tal hq were very receptive to us as well
Sadly due to timing couldn't do the watch longs
But mythos talents seem to be kind of already leaning on the alternative side
Which makes me quite comfortable with them as creators
As for actual corporation
tubers
Uh, I'm just if the person's happy with me. I'm happy with them. I never want to encroach myself on someone
That's not the word at all
I agree with those other two reef flings need mommy to take all that rage out of my tentacle until it's ink to dry. Oh my god
Um
Mom, if one were to eventually build up the courage for an audio debut
Oh my
Anything you would like to hear in specific
Uh, or should I just let the imagination go wild any time? No, have fun
I eagerly await your audio
Where did you we're all this time are you
Are you trolling me? Where did you we're all this time?
Where was I for all this time?
It took me a year to cook veiler. Give me. I needed to be in the kitchen. I'm not the best at it
I'm level 76 right now, but
It takes it takes a long time. Um
So I was working hard or hardly working, you know
We love to see a reefling piled up his couch
Uh, I could look he go for some water right now. Y'all should hydrate hydration check
I actually I'm going to finish my cola
Um
What what sort of settings would you say are the most appealing in audio booths? Uh
Grunting
I'm here that
I would have on your legs to be numb by the end of it
Oh are pleading. I'm gonna be like mommy. Mommy. Mommy. Mommy
I'm hydrating. Okay. I will hydrate with my beer
Is it the weekend? Oh, it is the weekend. You're allowed to have a beer
Right that time right that time
Are you squidding me right now?
I don't
Hello mommy
You were a very cute last night when you were sleeping. I hope you got enough rest
I did get enough my tentacles have been thoroughly inked ever since you came into my life
Oh, I'm glad you think so reefling. Thank you anonymous for the tip
Thanks for your tip anonymous
Thank you. I appreciate it. I'm glad you have been thoroughly de-inked
Ramura, Ramura. Thank you for becoming a member Ramura any Ramura remember
I can't remember member
I'm not really into this type of stuff, but for your birthday as a president you can
Use a figurine on me
For me you'd let me do that
Okay, October 10th is my birthday. So make sure you're all
Ready for what happens on October 10th
Are there any more indulge collabs planned in the future? Oh boy
Yeah, next week
You will be indulged out the wazoo if you mean six man indulge collabs
I am going to ask the girls if possible that we do one
Collab a month together of just hilarity and suing
Um, I do
Ah, what's that game?
It's hard because there's not a lot of six man games
So I think it might have to be stuff like among us or lethal company. I know
Residency for everyone plays it but the problem is there's six of us. There were many
I think there's a back rooms game that we can play together possibly
Um, I do want to do monthly six man collabs
Uh, but after that, um, it will be like two on two collabs. Maybe three three collabs
Angry scottish drunk karaoke wins soon. I was gonna do a drunk karaoke
On um, I don't know when yeah, I don't know when um
But I was gonna do it on a weekend
So like you guys can you know work work hard and then get all the relief on the weekend and we get steamboats and all that
When the talents are so
Jackbox would be great, but just with only one pop so you don't have to stream discord
Yes, I am open to doing that. Um she be
When we were first meeting for the first time
I got the girls to play a game together and we played jackbox and we all got addicted and we're like stuck
I was like because it was only supposed to be like a one hour icebreaker
So the girls could get used to like each other because like from my pov
I knew the girls like I had consumed their content. I knew kind of about them who they are
How they kind of are and all that jazz
Um, and then we ended up playing for like two hours and I'm like, oh, I'm so sorry
Like I didn't mean to steal all the time, but then like I went two hours and a half
um
In poor ac's tame zone. I picked a really bad tame zone. So she was so tired, but she was having so much fun
She didn't want to get off
Um, which was so cute
Then cute and good, which says cute. So if you put it dictionary
Oh, we we're gonna possibly do a dictionary
There's a new jackbox 18. That's really
Okay, I was gonna say I'm not sure we can hmm, but we had fun on jackbox
It was so mean against ac though because english isn't her first language
And one of the game modes was like asking all these really like hard questions
Like even english speakers can't get it. I felt so bad for her and she kept like dying in the game. I felt so bad
Um, I say not one to get off. That's definitely not true. Whoa. Did I say that sentence?
Deep rock galactica has a more players mod
Rock and stone
Hmm
Hi strongy
Would you be cool with us making not selling fan articles like daki?
Oh, you can do unofficial merch as long as you identify as unofficial merch
Fucking go wild bro. We ain't stepping on your toes and you aren't stepping on ours as long as it's unofficial merch
That's all you have to do unofficial merch. That's all you have to do. We don't we don't everything's good to go at that point
Um
Rock and stone
Deep rock galactica
Wholesome story time with strongy. Yes, that is uh how we all
It had a little ace breaker together. It's very kawaii me. Um
I can't say this on youtube, but I ain't twice to you today twice
Over the audio
Be honest refilling. Did you lose over the clapping with no hands audio is that why?
Any plans for
roleplays you'd like to do ASMR wise for alternative?
Oh, I've got four audios coming out every month on patreon and i'm fine with uh
You guys like submit scripts you want to hear? I don't mind
Shame
GTFO doesn't support six players. I don't even know what that is
Wow, don't be silly. You can't clap without hands
Can I do it right now? I might be able to do it right now. Hold on
Wait, let me stand up
I might be able to do it right now. I don't know
I know I know I know you can laugh. Hold on. I need to hold my my jibblies
Oh
Wait, was that it add my headset on so I never heard it if that if I that did it. Sorry my heads. It's banging on the mic
Okay, I can like do it all times by default
Yeah, you doubt it
That's ridiculous honestly
Nobody can stop her honestly. It's such a great clap
But you doubted me I can do it all times
I was wrong. I'd like to formally apologize. I accept your apology reefing and also the other reeflings
Thank you for letting me do that segment just to prove you wrong
Oh
Been a while since I heard that one stream. Yeah, I can do it at any moment. I don't even need like oil or anything
I could just do it
um
My suggestions for gen 2. Okay, I'll hear you
reefling would like to suggest
Uh, a japanese neon cyber punk hacker girl. Okay a middle eastern belly dancer curious
Fan to say alchemist girl nature loving flower girl. We do love a bit of nature out here. Um
disciplined ex military mercenary and a nerdy shy big worm. That's quite cute. Cute cute suggestion
um
Hi, strongy. Love you. Did you start v-tubing on your own or whether Schumer's that inspired you? Um
Inspired
I just I saw it and I was like, oh fuck it. I'll get it go. Um
And I I I've I've told this story before
I was very new and I could have easily been rejected for being an outsider type thing because I do a lot of things that you're not supposed to do
You're not supposed to
Acknowledge that you're pilot in America, but I'm pilot in America and I acknowledged it
You're supposed to know the terminology such such as zatsu or uh, tisker. Uh, well, it's not
Tisker, it's Tascaru
Uh, but I call it tisker. Um, and I could have easily have been um eaten
And chewed up and spat out
But the community was so loving towards me
that um
I kept going basically and I came back and I'm strongy
Hey, I've always been strongy. I've never been any other vtuber for legal reasons. Um
And yeah, now now it's going good. It's fantastic
Um, I did like iron mouse because she's sick as a dog. Um, but
Like keep streaming anyway. Uh, definitely
You can always kind of lend some energy when you hear stories about like people against all odds
Like you know, you got the energy to keep up and keep going type type thing. Um
Where's
my
Time in the robot mark
I keep saying it like tisker
Like a noise you make when dying
Noise that make when I die
Uh
Oh when's my time in the robot? Oh, no, I'm a mecca. I pilot a mecca like mecca salt
The hit video game from xbox original
Um
But yeah
That my that my mecca story. I do a lot of things. You're not supposed to do
Hey, I'm not supposed to say. Oh, I'm recalibrating my tracking. Uh, I'm putting on my my little face emotes
Yeah
Yeah, I'm not supposed to do that. Hold on a minute. Uh, but yeah, I do it anyway because I'm naughty
I'm getting the robot strongy
Getting the mecca. Oh, I'm gonna burp. I'm so sorry. Please open your mouth. Okay. There we go
Well, swallow it
good reefing
In regards to hypnosis audios, are you gonna make reinforcement audios for triggers and for audio loops for triggers and affirmations?
um
You're gonna have to let me start digesting producing it first before I can answer these kind of questions
I'm staying away from the permanent stuff because it makes me a bit nervous doing any permanent effects stuff
But I already have a public release audio
That will undo any effects. I may or may not do on you. What did you ask me in particular reinforcement loop for triggers?
for triggers
Mine's double finger snaps. Uh, I like it. Um, the most but I will train you in it. Okay
I
Embarrassed I'm embarrassed to admit by inked to your clapping with no hands and the party roleplay. Oh, yeah, you like that
It was really hot. I'm glad you like that. I put a little put a little bit of my heart into that
I like that. Okay. I'll enjoy how it came out
um
Hi, strongy. How do you feel about male?
Figurines being used in bibbute videos. Yeah, you can do that
um
but maybe
Maybe in the future you can use
official veiler merch association
Figurines
Ah
That's not something I need to fixation. Oh, I got five at 10. I got seven. I got nine at 10
I like the transparency though because you're just a normal person at the end of the day
Yeah, actually, can I say something that's really disrespectful and I mean no disrespect when I say it
You know those v-tubers that have those donations where like items get thrown at the v-tuber model when they get a donation
and then the v-tuber goes like
The the every time I consume any of that
I this is very disrespectful and I don't mean it this way
It makes me cringe to think that they're in a room
On their own with the iphone tracking them and going
I'm so sorry
I'm like actually so sorry
for me
It's a no
But people find it entertaining which is really cute. I like that people can get so entertained and so
Enveloped
That it's humorous. So I do apologize to anyone that I may have
Uh, thank you. Yeah, I've seen it too
Twitch integrated throwing system. Oh, okay. Is that what it's called?
And yeah, and here you are velour figures that well adjusted people can be normal
Don't think about it harder. It makes the cringe. Yeah, I remember seeing a clip about it and I was like
Don't get me wrong. I'm a cringe fest if you sit through one stream of mine
But I remember seeing it and I was like, oh, that's rough. That's rough even for me to digest
But I mean absolutely no disrespect when I say that like whatever works for you works for you
some people are
Balls to the wall in immersion and that's fantastic
For me, um, I am absolutely in love that reeflings are in love with pilot in America
It makes me incredibly comfortable
I'm
Like streaming and acknowledging like oh, I need to only go put my emotes on
Instead of like being like
I love you so much
Like
Bro, ain't no one here for that. Well, some people might be here for that but me. I'm not here for that, you know
Um
Yeah, it's basically just beautiful
But I don't mind like the roleplay like if I had a 3d model or I'll be roleplaying at the wazoo
So I'm probably gonna be hypocritical with that statement. It's not even a statement. It's just me blabbering
Any blabberers the heart eyes. Yeah, I love that my heart eyes are so different
Like, oh my god, my squiddles. Where'd my squiddly pupils go? Give me my squiddly pupils back
Oh
Wait, hold on you ready for this you ready for this. Oh wait, no wrong one
Me when there's no when there's no special honey tea
Oh
Wow
Me when me when there's actually a refractory period, I can't believe it
Any merch you'd like to have made in the future even if it ain't the the typical merch for me
or for the girls
Um a bash bite. Uh, I'm gonna try and get as a bash bite. Um, I'm not even pretending otherwise. Um
Hi, story any
Plans for age of empire 3 or age of mythology curious. I would have to look at it the current game
I'm investigating that I'm not familiar with right now is baltrol. Um, it looks pretty decent. It looks
Well, well rounded well adjusted game. Um
And I just need to kind of learn what the heck are flushes and all of that. We're brewing the tea. Give us a minute
Honestly refunds like oh, bro. Give us a minute woman. Jesus
um
But yes, I'm currently doing baltrol age of empires
I could look into
Is that that game where you can like have a king
But like a lineage of the region or something. I might have seen some gameplay of it
That's what I'm thinking
Strongly we love you no matter what make are you pilot? Oh, that's so sweet. Thank you
I said see you on my fifth persona in five years time. I wonder what I'll look like then. Well, I'll have double bunches
Let's let's find out
Any hints for a one-on-one collab and be alert. Yeah yesterday. Um
Me and mersey honk honk honk honk honk
Me and mersey
Uh, I love you very much and have for a very long time. Oh, let me tell you fling. Thank you for waiting on me
It took me a while, but sam wise the brave one didn't
One time the homies tried to play age of empires three with me
They made an asmr is off. Oh wait, you can make asmr is the age of empires. Huh?
Boutro is my current a obsession
Boutro is an occult that ballah paddle
The spirit is willing but the body is weary and sore
Not a third persona play. No, no, no, I don't worry. I can't be yours. I can't I'm done in after this
I'm strong in and I'm done
I'll happily
retire
Many and many years don't stop doing in many years. I'll happily retire and I'll just be like some sort of fucking
Vtuber runner advisor type thing
Uh, once all the viola girls are happy and doing their thing
but
Hi
strongy your patreon ASMR has been so good. I've been going back to them every night and inking
Yeah
You like the vanilla demo
Oh reef fling you're so cold
But I'm Scottish so I can warm you up
Don't you want to be warmed up? Hmm. Your protein equals getting cold too
Terrible don't retire. No, I can't be yours retiring. I've got too many plans. I'm sorry
But as we say to death not today, I have far too many plans to
Um
Execute before strongy gets executed
Uh, I have far too many plans. Sorry. I've put too much love and soul into
strongy and the viola girls that uh, yeah, I've got many a year in me
I assure you
Emmy is live and T-minus three minutes. Okay. Okay. Let's bash one out right now
That's terrible. I probably could if I tried hard enough
um
Yeah
As someone who's been into bit no kink for a while now, I
Particularly enjoy finger snapping too. Yes. I do double finger snap to get you under. It's my favorite
I love double finger snap your binaural. That's the word not your ear binaural finger snap
I know you can't hear it because I'm using a mono microphone right now, but I like binaural
I'm very much into a fraction nation fractionation obviously set the wrong
The practice has been put under and then brought up and
Uh, oh, that would be that would be a nice challenge. That would be a nice challenge
Your video of asking to hold it has been weirdly comforting while coding
Oh, do you like when I completely lose it at the end of the video and I'm just like, please
Like absolutely losing it at the end of the video
I'm glad it can be a comfort. I might have an official 1k celebration
ASMR coming out today because I got it halfway finished editing
But I need to finish edit in the other half and then I need to render it out
Um, and then we'll take it from there because I owe you guys five videos
And at the rate my channel is growing I can't keep up
And I have these ASMR collabs with all these lovely girls
Per Dempuz been waiting on me to record my lines
um
and I also have a
collab with uh
Freya and
Mimosa
The collab list gets pretty long
Actually, there's another yumi plus groba as a three-deal that I need to write our collab with
Wow suffering from success. Yeah, you do. Okay, Mimosa. Yeah, I was like Mimosa's waiting on me
I need to edit our one and you said it quite a few let her cook. Yeah
She calling you out. I know I know I need to get it edited and slapped up because Mimosa actually gave me her png for it already
um
So I just need to record my audio put it together
Um, and then put us both in our lovely little thumbnail and then I'll add Mimosa in the title
And then you guys can discover Mimosa. Um, she's been nothing but a delight. Uh, and she completely
I am like 100 completely comfortable with Mimosa and I've only known her for a week
Um, like she's just been so polite and kind and
That tells me tells me all the things
I I love it when someone information shares with me. I love getting you know, which I think I really yeah
Oh, I'm not uncomfortable around you
Um, winky winky babe
Oh my god, you're so cheeky Mimosa. I'm so cheeky
Oh my god, Emi's getting her dogs out. Okay, right
Speaking of letting the dogs out. Whoo. Whoo. Whoo. Whoo. I am going to read that was diva. Yes
Um, I am going to redirect into none other than Emi Bezu to celebrate her monetization
stream
Yes, please enjoy Emi and her dogs. I wonder how different her dogs look compared to my dogs
Um, but it's been fantastic. Please enjoy all 10 of her toenails while you're at it. Play extra attention
Uh, what redirect? Yes a redirect or a read is the terminology used. I had an absolute fantastic time on crash bandicoot with you
I cannot recommend playing warped
um
In your own time. It was magnificent 10 out of 10 game highly recommend. Please do enjoy Emi to her
To your full extent. Um, and hopefully you'll see some cheeky channel updates possibly an icy asmr
A mercy asmr
An astronzo asmr because I owe you so much asmr
But thank you so so much reeflings today was absolutely fantastic
You have put a smile on my face and I I love you very much for it and tomorrow
We're gonna play buckshot roulette and I will reveal to you what my evil dastardly plans are for next week of streams
Okay, so I'll see you tomorrow
Look after Emi for you and I give you one big kiss
One big kiss right one big wet slobbery. Okay, maybe two wet slobbery kisses
See you tomorrow reeflings, okay
Oh, my voice just cracked. Did you hear that?
I'm embarrassed. I'm embarrassing. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Bye. See you tomorrow reeflings. Bye
Bye-bye