Hold on.
I have a lot of chance.
My life.
I hope I'm on the right thing.
I'm done.
I don't know if I missed it.
Who's driving this boo?
Because my voice is so messed up.
Valor.
Am I streaming?
I don't see it.
There'll be a live for 40 seconds.
I can't even see myself.
Oh, there we go.
Hey, I can hear myself.
I totally lost my voice.
Testing.
Oh, freaking scary.
Broke my damn voice on that bloody stream.
Did you like it?
From here on out, it's nothing but scuffing memes.
If you're looking for professionals,
go elsewhere, buddy.
Go to Shibi's stream.
There's no happening here.
I promise you, mate.
My voice is so strange right now.
Oh, my goodness.
Just the way we're like,
oh, it's been a bloody while since we've been together.
Fuck me, man.
That took me a year to spawn this.
Oh, my God.
I did it, though.
Holy shit, we did it.
Feet sniffer.
I didn't mean to imply greed.
No, you didn't.
I know you didn't.
Please don't worry.
It's fine.
The only reason I say greed is because of the perspective thing.
Oh, fucking mischief, reflins.
My fucking god.
What a year it's been.
Holy crap.
I know I'm supposed to talk about my debut,
but let's be honest, we're all reflins here.
Oh, fucking mischiefs.
Of course, your names were going to be refling.
Oh, my God.
What do you mean you became a squid VTuber just so your name
may only reflect you in another life?
Oh, come on.
Refling.
Come on.
Get it?
Great barrier.
Reef.
Oh, I'm so excited to play Assassin's Creed Brotherhood with you.
When this stream ends, I'm going to unlist all my streams.
Any reefers on the track?
Are reefers cannabis?
I can't say that.
Does reeflings mean something different?
In another life, I had a fan base called Reeflings,
but it was spelled slightly different.
And I made it pronounced the same, but spelled differently.
Yeah.
Don't worry.
If you're not really familiar with me from the past,
don't worry about it.
Okay.
Don't worry about it.
I'm just strong at cuttles.
Let's keep it that way.
Thank you very much.
Okay.
Am I actually going through my 2.0,
or are we just meaming about it?
Are we just squidding around?
My bottle.
I have my reefing mail.
Skullfish.
Oh, Skullfish is so good.
Oh, that's actually really small.
Okay.
Thank you.
Right.
I'll actually go through my slides,
but I'm not really sure if there's much of a point,
because, well,
that's 2365 from Vsuck.
Bomet.
Product or Bomet.
Right.
Let me drink my cola.
Yeah.
I was supposed to say 53.
Also, someone doubted that Scots is a recognized language.
It is.
So, you know how it sounds like I'm speaking English here all the time?
I'm going to give you a sentence.
Okay.
I'm going to type it in chat so you can read it.
Hmm.
So, that is the sentence in Scots that I've just typed.
Okay.
And it says,
Are you coming to my bit tonight?
That means, are you coming to my house tonight?
That's Scots.
See how it's a bit different?
It's not in the best sense,
but it's what I can think of with the top on the head,
but yeah.
Are you coming to my bit tonight
means, are you coming to my house?
And I purposely don't really speak with a lot of slang
or mumbled the way I naturally do,
because I'm quite naturally monotone and mumbly
because the problem is
you guys don't understand me because I'm scottish
but if you are british or you're familiar with the scottish accent
then I probably actually don't sound from scottish indeed but
it is what it is and also I've been very like
when you're on the internet you're very americanized because of what you consume
does it take all your efforts to pronounce every syllable and not speak scott's
no I'm my mother dearest she actually taught me
she discouraged me from speaking in slang
so I doesn't always naturally come out but
um here's hoping it's the beginning of something
fucking cheers to that mate cheers to that
but yeah uh technically legally on paper
because I was born in scotland I could speak two languages thank you
neneath any help from jewel lingo let's go
uh but yeah so I'm a siren that can't sing
gee willikers I wonder why I just don't have a voice I'm also tone deaf by the
way so I hope you're ready for drunk karaoke streams
uh that stuff's gonna be uh intense let's see where these slides are
so both of your parents are scott's
um yeah the the band aids hold up
still top tier yep very top tier uh mongolian throats singing
the reason I don't like mongolian throats singing it's because cats don't
like mongolian throats singing because of the vibration it's an
unpleasant sound I have learned many traits of cats so I don't like it
drunk karaoke uh shebe's doing drunk ASMR this week uh if that's your
is that your heng to say is that your thing in scott's you go
is that your heng is that I is that your heng oh it is heng
and there you go um yeah I did some basic stuff
oh my lore's being retconned by the way thanks to you guys
uh apparently my weaknesses are mirrors which are really like
uh I'm I'm definitely gonna do something with that because I think it's
such a cool thing I should have done it like a
character reference like strengths weaknesses because that would be so much
cooler to do but hey hold I actually have started reading this year um I
had a really rough year last year gee wonders oh wow
um and I started uh I picked up reading I have never read in my life um
and turns out I really like the stopian novels like George Orwell was so good
like Animal Farm in 1984 I absolutely love 1984
Fahrenheit was good like they quit I've read the classics I'm not read that much
but uh um I see you're reading right yeah
um the women in the dunes as well is like the perfect
like book because it like encapsulates like human nature
and oh I just love like depressing books I love being depressed at the end and
being like no humanity didn't prevail no not humanity
what's the word uh human nature like didn't prevail against the odds
I've got the hobbit I've not read it yet but I have the physical
copy of the hobbit and I'm so excited um yeah I'm not much of the the girls by
far are more weebs than me I am by far the gamer
like I played the most games doesn't mean I'm good before anyone fucking
complains because every time you mention you play games
uh what do you mean you're not top 500 in this game
you suck like no I play video games fucking relax I bet you're
shit at them too like my god can you hear yourself
you're actually like so fucking negative anyway I'll help you get more
positive actually the reason why you're negative
is because your kd is negative because you're scrubbing the game
that's why you just project anyway that's just me
music I'm really generic with music I don't listen to music much
okay movies lord of the rings we're at hell yeah uh if you don't know uh I have
plans for on Christmas and Boxing Day uh to watch lord of the rings and the
hobbit film marathon absolutely adore it that would be
public stream no no gate keeping no membership none of that jazz
oh special thank you to everyone who watched the debut
I already meet the requirements for monetization on youtube
the problem is the stats don't update for like
48 hours so I can technically I already meet the requirements I just need to
submit myself to youtube and then I can do my monetization
stream and I'm so excited because my idea is so
cursed but I just want to say for anyone who's
watching me right now if you don't like vtubers doing
webcam streams showing their hands or their feet
I'm not a vtuber for you however veiler girls absolutely
check them out in the description you can hit subscribe
um but yes absolutely no hints to what my monetization stream is gonna be
you ain't ready I literally need to go to a nail parlor
I've been growing my nails for three weeks
for the monetization stream I am sick of having long nails I hate it I hate it
but I'm doing it for you enemies uh um
kaki goody still one of my top kaki goody kaga goody kaga goody
still one of my top and it's probably one of my top I don't I can't think of
actually fun fact do you want to know the very first anime I got tricked into
watching fucking boku no pico or whatever the
freaking dilla picadilla sauce whatever the freaking thing is
that is the first exposure to anime I ever had and I was
mortified mortified I had no concept a little innocent me
tick tacking on the keyboard oh this anime be recommended I should watch it
and then so I was really dumb do you know how it has a warning at the start
I didn't know what that word meant like and I watched it I was like where is this
ice cube going uh and like and actually I want to use my
notice my first ever exposure to uh uh like an anime that wasn't
boku no pico it related was a brother in oh my god oh sorry I thought there was
a spider on me holy crap it wasn't it was my cover
um my first anime exposure it was either it must have been an
anime based on a manga that got popular because that's the most anime's
turnout you know that um it was a brother and sister
hold on hold on hold the freaking phone for y'all circle
it was brother and sister and then it was um the sister is a flesh
eater and the guy's like oh it's fine and he has like
regenerative powers or something I I'm sure one of you guys
know what it was either a manga or a thingy
but she had to like eat him for some reason and she was like oh I'm so sorry
for eating you hum hum hum and I was like oh yeah that was the first of her
anime exposure that like I got into and I was like oh it's
it's crazy um and then I discovered what pururun is
many a day on pururun uh and then they shut down the website
ripping piss you will be missed actually sorry my voice is absolutely
short I promise this isn't my default voice it's because I'm so excited to
talk to you I've broken my voice already
and I came back
shut up pururun did not come hold on hold on we're doing research like
I have I may have a bikini toggle
I may have a bikini toggle for water asmr streams I am so sorry
I will unbind the keys for an x-stream I will take your word chat that pururun
is back I apologize for that
my deepest condolence
okay I know but okay I don't even know what to say to that right move it on
swiftly and we'll take another drink to me
Nikola
oh I don't even know what key did that was it you maybe
pururun oh I literally look over at my screen I'm like
hmm where's my yukata where did it go why is it through the window
absolutely anyway next next yes childhood games oh my god I am so happy
that xbox game passes a thing I need to create an account I don't know what to
call it yet like um I want to make it something like
meanie or funny
but yeah anyway I'm an xbox kid and if you were able to catch the group stream
it's actually true that I had to present games to my dad to buy for me
or he would just buy it for me because he was like oh that's good for responso
um inherit your dad's account
um but I so these are like the majority of the games I
remember I'm gonna do like tons of xbox games I'm an xbox kid I never had a
PlayStation at all um so I didn't have access
I had a PlayStation my dad got a PlayStation 1
I didn't know how to read like no
yeah so I I'm just trying to think like the timeline
a lot of these games I played I didn't even have the ability to read yet
like I used to watch my dad play the games because I was so small
um but yeah basically
sonic generation
is sonic generation someone that was made after sonic heroes
uh I've not played bio shock 2 no I played bio shock 1
where you had bees bees um
my sweet little bumblebee I know what you want from me
um hypnosis themed feature where I really like hypnosis I've never done it
before but I'm going to participate it and try and get it for you
uh I never played sonic generation then no I played sonic heroes and then there
was a bit of a skip I played sonic unleash where he's like that werewolf
but I got stuck on the game because I was like too young
not very smart I'm not a very smart gamer okay
which is why I am perfectly happy with
hand-holding through games uh some streamers really don't like backseat
gaming for me absolutely do not mind it I'm
daft okay I'm completely daft I have no clue what's going on
okay
we'd be hypnotized to vote for you as president oh my god
um but yes we're definitely going to replay a lot of xbox games as my
childhood dream was that 100k thingy um I only had the opportunity to play
fable 3 I can't wait let me see what's behind me hold on
what's behind me oh viva pinata trials evolution
yeah um right now my game of choice is the binding of the binding of isek
um it's absolutely fantastic game it becomes multiplayer in november
multiplayer in november just a warning for anyone who out there binding their
isek uh november games multiplayer games
are most likely going to be isek I apologize
I too um the best halo game in your opinion
I'm biased I'm going to say combat evolved because my dad used to play it
like over and over and I used to hide behind the couch
I was so scared from the grumpy oneies they were like so
scary you actually finished meat boy that looked like I
finished meat boy no I played it these games don't necessarily mean I'm
finished them but yeah hamsters live stream when
yeah you want to you want to play a hamster game together
yeah it's combat evolved the first one
yeah sorry uh halo combat evolved is the first one
uh you're like crash land and everyone dies but you
you're just scared
they're straight up what in the strip club straight up binding it and by it
let's just see my eyes like oh my god my favorite meme right now is like
replace the a with a f and then it says fart
relax snowflake it's called dark humor it's my favorite
uh I've also got um those old games uh from the xbox original days
definitely going to give them a shot again
uh I see actually mentioned that she played american magies
alice and I've played alice in one uh alice in madness returns
um and I thought she was going to say she played american magies alice but
um yeah uh god of war um
enjoyed that that was good I need to play
um shadow of mordor properly I actually want to play the golem game that got
like absolutely review bombed everyone hated it but I feel like I'm like
tizmo enough because it's lord of the rings lord of the rings
related to play it and the entire time I want to do golem's voice and I'm like
thank you I like absolutely wreck my voice to like
roleplay his golem I mean you know we started again
I'd love to do that my face when I didn't realize madness returns to the sequel
oh mercy I'm about to ruin your day uh there was a third installment called
uh alice uh asylum and EA rejected it the game has been fully
conceptualized EA rejected it and now it's gathering dust
so that's just to ruin your day there is to be a third installment of alice in
wonderland and EA yet again ruined it
yay do we hear yeah yeah we hear yeah so yeah it's
hard to ruin your day but that's true um what other games uh dishonored was
good um stealth was a bit funny at times but definitely happy to play that game
um I'm gonna burp I'm so sorry oh no I'm not I don't have to be professional
anymore
it's carambit oh my god what a terrible man
um I heard monster hunter uh hi dimpo again how's it going dimpo
um I've heard monster hunter has bagpipes in it
like as a weapon but it's the most like hardest thing to play instead of like a
sword um dishonored good yeah good I'm drawing
well watching you did you guys know that dimpo
created her own vtuber art model isn't that amazing
that's like literally so talented um talented as in terms of all her hard
work and effort and blood sweat and tears that she's put into
honing her craft and art so I read this thing ages ago about art as being like
um we don't really like it when you say it's like overnight talent because it's
not it's like you you honed your craft and like you should be proud of honing
your craft you didn't just spawn in as an artist you know
gifted that's it you're not gifted you honed your craft you spent years on it
you got your xp bar raised up anyway that's just my small rant about being
nice to artists they aren't gifted they have spent years specializing
into into a skill bar okay thank you
more vtuber babies you do concept art you do concept art dimpo
uh oh you know what game I really like I say this every time is
um what is it called college a ghost alien mode was so good I don't care
what anyone says it's super good I could for you any young
we in boys with dimpo with dimpa sorry I say
yeah notice there's no halo too because I never got a chance to play it
no there is is halo not there wait halo too should be there I played all the
halos hold on analyze analyze them in some in
analyzing oh wait I can't grab it where is it
place for debut there we go analyzing where halo two halo two halo two
unidentified okay I guess I have played all the halos
uh I wanted to I'm not playing the new red dead redemption
oh my god well it's not new it's been out for years now by this point but um
definitely do Assassin's Creed we're 100 doing
etio's storyline I'm going to be really controversial
couldn't be a shite once they killed it so off I mean he had three installments
it's not like he was killed off wait why I don't fit you
what you should be there okay I did it
alien isolation get to fuck I'm not playing that game
that's a terrible game wait why is that's chat
that's my background music
halo you need to be above yeah jeez wait no chat oh my god sorry I'm having a
stroke and not the good kind best Assassin's Creed
brotherhood Assassin's Creed brotherhood is the best
Assassin's Creed installment of all time I am not taking any questions
statements arguments or bomb threats to veiler
headquarters I'm sorry it's just a bit I will explain we're playing it tomorrow
I will explain to you chapter by chapter
step by step on why it's just the most perfect
thought out like um optimized game for like gameplay I just every I will
I will explain it all I'm actually making a video essay about Assassin's
Creed brotherhood um it's going to be one of my
donor-thon rewards I've already recorded the footage
to do it I just need to write the script and everything
but like I kid you not I'm doing like a video essay 40 minutes long I don't care
I'm like gonna fill Tezmo unless okay we've been on games for quite a while now
I'm like um you guys are probably sick of staring at these games
um I did that no I think I've done this wrong
hey hello
uh I think I said all the game stream said yeah oh we're playing old-school
Rinscape 8 hour Assassin's Creed brotherhood lore
coming in what have I done probably like
less than an hour but um
yes probably uh old-school Rinscape uh is our weekend game it's going to be
mostly a multiplayer game for this month until
June 19th when the Eldon wait why the fuck is there two
oh I must have missed one um you've never played Rinscape don't worry
we're doing questing my only problem with old-school Rinscape is
I think you have to pay the premium experience for premium
or we're all just going to get shafted playing that game like
not in a good way um but yes Eldon Ring
Eldon Ring DLC comes out on the 19th and then the multiplayer game for like
four days in a row I'm doing multiplayer games
you need to teach me old-school Rinscape literally I just go like fishing
the back of Lumbridge let me castle not the back
next to the main but south of the castle um
but I uh what was that single word of fun oh uh probably four days of multiplayer
Eldon Ring and then I have a very unique stream come in
with the first collab outside of Vealor at the end of the month
with a feature called Sin Sister and we may or may not have both purchased
shock collars which we will give each other control of the shock collars
and we are going to play multiplayer Eldon Ring and whoever causes us
to die whichever one causes us to die gets to shock them
basically yep we are we're doing that um I believe
Sheebie is also getting a shock collar so I might have some sort of stream with
her relating to that uh I use a shock collar for
DEMPA
but yeah my goals are pretty much I want to do 100 days smart clubs with the
trivers it's like a challenge for myself I like forcing
myself to like go talk to people like like I was scared of DEMPA
okay but at the end of her first because I'm a big girl and I was like hi I'm
20 would you like to say I was like oh yeah
would you like to collab with me should I fuck yeah I'm like oh my god that was so
good so yeah DEMPA based uh yes I'm gonna put
myself out there meet talk to VTubers mingle a bit more because
um I say is my voice is cracked as if literally you died zap true uh
everything else is explanatory uh I need to actually
purchase the Lord of the Ring book but we'll get there we'll get there
okay this I need help with um I actually genuinely need help I literally
have I don't know if you can hear that I have pen and paper to write down what
you guys think
I don't know what I'm doing that do I look like I look like I'm not smart
right hold on let me write down like general like sorry I'm gonna look down
every time I do click art old art mean and obviously
you
DEMPA's intimidating so you realize our tentacles can go
keeping keep them all as help okay
strong oh that's actually kind of cute strong yeah um
cuddle time yeah I'm DEMPA I'm with you like I just like straight forward
stuff Jen like strong Jen strong Jen strong live
strong clips strong art strong old art strong meme
strong notes strong notes would make them
snort snort snort snort something like what uh
something like what a swan would say small
uh general refers to um if you just want to say something like on twitter you
use that and then like I'll read it with my eyeballs
strilize strilize honestly my voice is cracking though
I'm not gonna make it I can't believe it if I can debut and already did
not even 24 hours later strong lure
ink time oh my god ink time sorry ink time
for art that has to be that's so good ink time
ink time I like ink time yeah like a reaction tag
strong sea oh strong seas like I see strong leaks
I think because ink myself is my my my other catchphrase
it's not catchphrase oh strong means strong
stronatized honestly that's wrong the inking
anything oh sorry I'm itching my eyeball
stronger oh god I'm so bad at this strong close I may just do what DEMPA said
and just like strong Jen strong live strong this strong that
ink time was used by a tattoo artist man tattoo artist out here ruining it for
all of us cuttle dafty we dafty
I inked myself strong Sina oh that's actually really good hold on
general text strong Sina I'll just do one and
that's so good I've seen you strong Sina strong suck it no
no V suck it I'll never beat the V sucky allegation
beef yourself I think straight forward make sense
mima rat mima rat sounds like memorize and I have the memory of a goldfish
incredible I'll turn out funny Jen can be strong you know what any mention
of my absolute horrific strut of fish strut of fish
uh god I'm so bad at this I'll think I'll need to freaking cook on it more I
don't want to be stopped small fish oh small fish is really good for all
art oh yeah small fish I'm putting that down
I hate when you have to like like TTL
E oh I did too many along what's that I can't read or write properly yet my
entire career is based on it
hell yeah
okay we'll move on I'll come back to I'll cook a little on my own
obviously this question you'll pretty much uh he did designs
lores there's actually full lores well I can't read it right now because my
voice is perishing um what else
mascots all the mascots were made um if you didn't know uh the reason I'll heal
your throat your tentacles please the reason why
reeflings have a patch on their head is a nicotine patch to help you with your
addiction because we have an addiction to one each one of you to each other
yeah so that's why you have a nicotine patch and you have lovely tentacles
I've already got lots of suspicious artwork of us together but it's for
November so I can't post it yeah to match it I've
absolutely cooked on the lores um background yeah I love my room uh odd
top was such a good sport I literally sent them a DM I'm like
hey can you base it off of sonic ost and you go
um waltz with me he did my little banner that's on twitter which is really good
absolutely do it
Azura could help you all with her healing properties um
uh oh really yeah small sushi she did great um small sushi actually she did
fantastic because she the girls weren't fully conceptualized when she created
them I basically just gave descriptions which was really rough I know you
haven't seen my stingers for my scene transitions I hate stingers I spent like
200 dollars and I don't even want to use them I like I bought it obviously I bought
it for everyone else but I'm like why did I spend that money on me no one feel
well I don't like using stingers I like just went straight into it and like my
loading screen was so expensive actually Yuri you may cooked with the loading
screen she's actually making another alternative version because I had to do
that cover-up thing but that was very expensive as well
I just like when I get into it and then obviously why I picked my gen
mate yeah that was so fun to do um like everyone's like oh this is my first
impressions no mother fucker I picked them
are so fun it was so fun being able to say that and being like yeah yeah absolutely
evil strongy be like I always use stingers I love stingers I love when v-tubers
have 10 minutes of stream starting soon at the start of their streams perish
absolutely perish nonsense I'm starting up on a brotherhood at the menu
tomorrow mark my words um but yes
uh I was just fantastic the girls
it's hard to judge people when they apply because
it just felt really um we're weird
hold on
hold on um yeah it felt weird trying to put put them on because some of them said
put me on any model some of them said I wanted a specific model I think Azura
got who she wanted
she'd be
um Mercy wanted AC AC wanted AC so AC got AC
Amy did you see anyone
anyway it's impossible to give people the outline that they wanted because they
couldn't even see it like it is they couldn't even see it it was just an
outline um did you have any awkward or weird
applications uh someone's intro video was
30 seconds uh for anyone watching if you're
serious about joining a vtuber agency uh what you're supposed to roughly do
in uh application introduction video is to say
your accolades whatever you achieved as a streamer prior to
what you're doing now so you mention how often you stream do you stream three
times a week consistently good thing to mention
um 30 seconds uh just it was like hi i'm
and i stream on and that was it and i was like bro what am i supposed to do with
that um but yeah you're supposed to say
your accolades what you want to achieve within the agency is a good thing
to mention um you're also supposed to pass the
test where you say hi vealer at the start because that means you read the
instructions properly if you didn't start with hi vealer
um i didn't close your application right away i gave you a chance but it's kind
of one of those tests where those who did it i know you read
those who didn't either you forgot although i say that i mean the girls
have given me permission to kind of talk about that the thing
azura's application was unprofessional
fuck i'm not even going to be around the bush with azura
she gave me permission to talk about it in her intro like her introduction
she's like hey i'm azura and she was like i really don't like pickles
and i don't like mustard and i was i'm like azura this is your
introduction video you're supposed to like tell me things you've achieved
she's like yeah i don't like the taste of these certain foods
and i was like you're perfect for the hag and you come
like you're perfect for the doting hag that we've got like no competition
um uh i say doesn't even english isn't even her first language
she had the most professional uh application she had these
massive paragraphs serious answers uh immi was a dafty she
freaking forgot to edit one part of her application
and in one of the answers she was like i want to diddle the other girls and i'm
like i knew it was an oversight because everything else was professional i'm
like any one earth have you put um
she be she failed the high vealour
mercy um must have watched her introduction video like
30 times over she was so like she went above and beyond
she actually created icy um like recreated her outline and named her and all
that pocha emmi left that on purpose
yeah um the introduction video gives me a very
good hint to what kind of each of her you are
no what kind of person you are because there's one thing to stream
but when you're talking directly to someone who's assessing you
you act a bit different um and yes it was very interesting
i got serenaded so much so i don't know why i'm
frol blinking and let me just give me one second
we're totally not recalibrating the old mech hold on
that's better calibration um
yeah i got serenaded so many people were singing i'm like you don't have to sing
to be in this agency you just need a one cover song that's it
i'm not gonna force you to sing um
probably
one of the most frustrating things was we asked to have streaming history
and people's evidence of like being a streamer was like a link to their twitter
and no other thing oh no content creator that was the
terminology used you had to be a content creator and it was like
are you okay why are you linking your twitter twitter isn't content
there weren't even a v-tweet or anything like that and it was just like
rub are the girls doing more songs yes
100% uh if the girls want to pursue more singing they just
come and me tell me what they want to do uh and i get that she don't
uh well other things obviously i'm not gonna say anything private um
i'm very flattered there were some very big names that applied
but they just weren't a good fit or they already had a pre-established brand and
it was like is this really what you want
i think you just wanted i think some people that were very
notoriet had high notoriety were interested more in the manager side
of things than actually being that velar we had like one person was
freaking massive and they were like can i keep my ip and join you and i'm like
sorry i need to own the rights to the models in order to do what we need to
okay it was a shame because i'm sure that person would have done just fine but
yeah it was it's not possible to not have the ip and utilize the gills
yes it was in the facts on the page um yeah the website got so many
fucking questions that were answered on the website
so they had to ignore the tab that had all the information
to go to the contact part of the website
to then ask the question that was already on the website
um literally i tried so hard to make that shit be as
comprehensible as possible
um
yes i think the applicants definitely read through it all
uh
brief time oh i can't see that sorry sorry i'm not uh that's the quote it's a
code name code name i did not say that word please don't get on me
um
um i'm just trying to think back if there's anything notable on the
applications oh my god there was one application
she was outrageous outrageous if you apply to an agency that agency
watches your content this girl my goodness
she applied i went on her twitter her twitch to listen to her live to check
her out and all that she admitted in the next
live stream oh i'd only do via lure for one year and then
bring the my audience over to this account
why would you admit that i'm very happy to say i never even considered her
but oh my god how could you be so like i don't even know what the word is
i was gobsmacked like i sent it to other members of the team
to make sure i heard what i heard was correct
but they outright said yeah i would just do it for one year and then bring my
audience over
dog thank god i didn't waste
waste a slot for you i'm very happy to say that all current talents
have given very high indications of staying at the agency
you know as long as income is all good and dandy so please do support them via
patreon or monetization streams when the girls get
monetized uh but yes i was absolutely gobsmacked
one to even apply to do it in the first place knowing you have no commitment
knowing that we're like 80-20 split everything's in your favor 100%
merch and saying that like you're not even gonna be
like dedicated oh my god and then to admit it to admit it knowing you
submit yourself and the agency is watching over you
oh my god absolutely gobsmacked
oh anyway i am very i will repeat again i am very
happy to say that all girls have given me indications of long term
commitment uh if you will and as well as uh if they sign on for one more
year like another year uh the split goes 15
85 85 to them 15 to the agency and they also get an alternative outfit on us
they do not pay for it we pay for it
i'm glad she was honest i didn't waste her time no
she was honest in her stream she was not honest on her application form to
fill all of that out and mislead and be like
i'm just gonna quit after a year just go
actually spat in real life and that landed on my phone
don't do that don't fuck with me okay i put a lot of love into this
women lie i can't believe it that's terrible you're you know you can't say
that that's the concept artist by the way fucking troll don't believe the thing
that comes out of his mouth i'm jealous of the phone
i didn't know she was gonna do that bit on her debut
where she was like i guess i was like oh my god
hey just so you guys know i didn't have anything to do with her debuts they all
did it themselves um i was like oh my god
expect that right anyway uh oh two point noes over right shows over folks
um but yes
right i'm gonna open up marshmallow because this time i can answer questions
please keep my yukata on i don't know what later did it but i can actually
answer marshmallows that are um
why are you so cute stop it my voice is so freaking broken
me
have you considered streaming elsewhere yes the girls are allowed to stream on
an alternative website at a later date please understand we are trying to
establish yourself on youtube at first and we have monetization on youtube and
the girls income is all sorted but yes there are plans i will make it free
access um
i do not believe in charging any further than
um youtube membership and patreon so all together is
999 for your oh shi desu to support because it
is it is 199 for emotes to make sure no one gets gifted membership
and then is it 499 or is it 399
my voice is
is it 4999 for membership usually
is 499 yeah 4999 seen agreeable okay 199 for tier 1 499 yeah that sounds
right that sounds right um as long as you guys don't think it's outrageous
like in the state each um as i've said in the vealer
smoothstream we are undercutting the market
um i'm not even going to pretend otherwise uh on the vea side of things
most vea's start at $10 for two exclusive audios
we are undercutting the market by doing four audios for $5
and no price increase at all is planned and if you
fell ever so inclined you can donate more via
donate you can support more via patreon there is a secondary
tier that uh it's $20 i believe um i haven't put anything else
um yes what's your history with hypnosis i'm learning i'm a new baby
um but i'm going to give it my best shot i have a very
uh deep interest in it i've just never actually made content about it like
straight up uh it's not expensive yes i
oh i really i've heard some stories around that it was going to be
five for standard and 20 oh no no we're undercutting the market five
dollars and you get four four audios per month
um are you concerned undercutting could cause a scene
wide price shift downwards uh no because prices are going up
everywhere um following the voice actress trends
um on the ASMR side of things and the the roleplay side of things
prices are only going up uh and i believe in the opposite i believe in
delivering both quality and quantity um without
overworking the girls please understand that management uh have
dictated the scripts for a couple of months however
um there's few girls interested in writing their scripts i'm also very
open to writing scripts live unfortunately will be a membership
stream uh for me content wise to give you guys exactly
what you're looking for um but please understand i cannot pigeon
hold the girls into doing the same thing over and over again
just rehashed that's not that's not um
that is no way for them to be set up for success that is
they will be set up for failure sadly if i did that and i really hope
yeah have you written any scripts yet yeah you listen to them
everything you look that's out right now on patreon is done by me
the two other script writers kicking i want to say roughly in three months
and then the manager for the scripts is about to kick in
i don't know quite what's happening yet if they'll write the majority
um this is just my humble opinion but because
i don't have my scripts do not come out as best
as if a man had written it that's just my opinion
um the emi has shown interest in a script shibi has shown interest in
writing i think azura prefers the help
azura um i think she needs reassurance ac
ac is good at improv i think she may do some improv scripts in the
future uh yeah
what is the adult aspect to the agency uh the alternate alt twitters and uh
patreon yeah azura did you just did
i eventually want to be a member for the girls you girls they're they're fine
uh yeah i'll kind of repeat this if you like are in a position where you can
support like a like one girl please think about supporting
the other girls over me um i am living a very good life um
and things are going very well please don't worry about me okay
how do you find the alternate of twitters
check who they're following yeah check it check who they're following
question about your design how did you come up with the twin tails and the
candy pee is seashells i'm a cuttlefish i'm i'm a cbtuber
uh these are cuttlefish uh sorry these are seashells
uh and then i got double bunches um i love symmetrical hair and i love bunches
so i've got double bunches
um would you be open to accepting script submissions
absolutely i don't know how to set it up i don't know how to do it and i don't
know i need i would need to like give a guide because
it's quite hard to get it all efficient and good to go
definitely open to it please do let us cook though like literally the dust is
settling the girls are about to start doing game streams after these two
point ohs um the first week i did request the girls to
stream as much as they're physically able to without cancelling streams i have
emphasised to them that cancelling streams
try your best to not over promise it's better to
take a day off than it is to um plan a stream that you think you can do and
then you get too tired and cancel it because cancelling streams is very
people plan people plan their time and their days and their energy
around a stream if they know what time it's coming on and it's very valuable
to respect people's time so like for reeflands for example you guys know
that i don't stop streaming like at all and i'm always there and i literally
have never cancelled the stream so and that's true i haven't cancelled the
stream
um sorry to tell you just to bring the topic back gifted membership is the one
that's closest to five dollars yeah you may have to go higher
eh it's all i thought gifted membership went to the lowest tier tier one was
going to be emotes only and then tier two is going to be four ninety nine
i really don't want to overcharge so there is gonna
well wait more streams uh yeah i stream all day every eight
maybe just make it an extra dollar it's expensive though
who goes there by the pope identify yourself
um how do you prevent any mischief from the talents
uh i know they're responsible adults but from a legal span
standpoint how do you prevent any possible uh repercussions of the
talents actions does the company not take responsibility
or do they do create freedom um i literally said in the interview you're
not going to get in trouble i'm not your mum i couldn't give less of two shits
what you do um i basically said the only thing i
ask you not to do is release any nda content and um
you know don't say the n word you know basic adult
stuff it's pretty much it i mean i don't know what else to tell you
when you treat adults like adults they act like adults
it's crazy
did you hypnotize the girls to become the characters
eh i hope you're drinking a lot soda i'm i'm going cola it's fizzy juice
actually sorry you're turning scots it's not cold it's not uh
soda it's fizzy juice um yes
um as for repercussions like as i said we don't do
um suspensions however i did warn them i said
does it mean you're allowed free reign like we can cut we can terminate
obviously we don't want to do that and no girl has given any indication of any
of that shit thank god yeah i have full faith in these
girls i've known them for two months now like no issues not one issue has
popped up um
oh yeah fizzy juice is how you say it in scotland fizzy
are you a hire up in the agency nah i said don't call me boss
um i basically
got their script started but it's going to script manager
and i don't have to do any work i get to stream all day long
um
yeah so i'm kind of asked about gentle uh year away bro
year away do you plan on doing movie watch alongs absolutely
will you ever do a deep sea creature list oh my god yeah that's so good that's a
good idea i like that i was gonna uh so this is a failed
stream idea i was actually gonna um order a like a cuttlefish
it wouldn't be alive but i wanted to explore the biology of it because
i think they're pretty cool like cephalopods are pretty cool
and i wanted to like show you guys like if i was a cuttle
it's a little looks good but i think people would find it a bit more bit
than like essentially playing with a dead body so yeah probably can do that
i've not played subnautica i don't have a memory of playing it
um uh could give it a good shot
could recommend it but it's for science
cephalopog for memes for memes cephalopog sorry
my tag now as long as no one's yoinked it hold on hold on let me scroll up so i
can see the spell in
a little pog thank you yoinkers my tag now
which tags are missing i've got strong sena for general
i've got smuttlefish for all and cephalopog for me
so i need live clips in art
cracked which i didn't even have to come up with it myself what a genius
hey
as long as i respect them actually use it for educational content
yeah i like biology but i think people find it quite morbid sometimes
and i don't want to upset anyone
can't believe you're already taking advantage of it
you like it really i've mistaken advantage of yeah
what a refund
tentacles i don't have any tentacles
i may get tentacles another time but i don't have tentacles
i feel like if i had tentacles they would come out with my
i'm gonna be honest i don't think they would be tail tailbone attached
i think they would come out my other end
out of all the girls who do you think is gonna overwork themselves for sheebie
and sheebie's already done so much work in advance
um so she can focus on streams
the tentacles not be around you
oh my god someone put the scottish coffee pasta
what do you think of that mr pajama weird and basket face
slipper wielding i hate the only thing i don't like about
marshmallow is that it cuts words in the middle
tentacles do any of the girls have any talents which surprised you
emi please piano for real for real um
mersey has acting
um
is there a draws sheebie actually draws as well and mersey and emi
and ac doodle um i think they all draw and i'm like
what the hell is he's all talented what would i do
i just sound like a bark pipe
absolutely um well the talents keep their silver playbots of course
jesus why would i keep that it's disgusting
absolute disgusting behavior all their hard work and i keep the play button
absolutely not
oh my god someone said an hour ago when will additions be open for gen two
i am hot and ready like a little caesar's pizza
come and scoop me up before a rich man does
i've spotted an american femenon
um me me on reflex oh my god i need to make a reflex post
on my alternate and my voice is so loud
mummy thank you for giving me a little sister you talked prior during the
selection process about keeping a list uh a list of possible candidates so
um i got my first choice for everyone i don't know how
but everyone was like first choice pick i wanted them in the agency they came in
the agency there were i would say like eight people
that were like fall back obviously azura didn't have one that was a problem
emi i was actually really worried she wouldn't accept her lore
she likes it
i was worried that she wouldn't accept the lore
and it's like yeah that's fine i don't care i'm like okay and then jeez she's
i was worried she wouldn't accept that but that's okay um
have any japanese corpos influenced your decision making
why do you believe there was no lid one before
uh no idea probably because you need someone who's done it
before to even understand like what to do and a lot of
guy owned corporations like in the nicest way most likely haven't been
streamers before and don't comprehend what you're asking people to do
like uh i kind of spoke about this a wee bit in the last
stream like that 80 20 split in order to motivate people you have to let them
earn what they're worth if you turn around and say to them
for every 100 dollars uh you're getting you know 20 bucks out of it you're
getting 50 bucks out of it like all that girl is going to be doing is
sitting there saying oh wow i could have made the full
hundred on my alt account oh wow i could have done this on my previous
life like that's all that they're going to sit there and think
okay like i'm we talking pure business baby i'm happy to talk pure
business if you want um
well the monthly audio releases be revealed before the month starts yes
and we need to get on top of that sadly there was a few issues
production wise with a few things i'm so surprised
turns out uh takes a lot of time to make these things happen
love artists but my fucking god can you not go over deadlines that'd be great
um but yes we will be posting monthly like what the tags are what the title
is um we just need to catch up like you need to give us time to breathe i'm
so sorry all i can ask is your patience and
unironically like bow emoji because uh we need time like it was
absolutely hectic on debut we were exhausted in that group
collab and like like i don't know if you
recognized like how fast we ended i was like right say bye to chat bye like
we all disappeared out that voice call so quickly i was like thank you guys so
much i'm gonna wait to pass out and then i ended up being really sick after it
um but yes we just need things to calm down
we're we're gonna ease into the first week everyone's got their games you get
to see their personalities more enjoy them more which is fantastic
um octopus i'm not an octopus i'm a codonfish
no call me octopus no call me squid i'm a cephalopod or a kurofish
better take your yourselves and now the things have calmed down like
the lead-up to debut is very nerve-racking like very very nerve-racking
i have finished my kola i will never start on
fame my warble
oh i strongly you're super good
hey you like my teeth is that what's doing it for you
um but i think i've called for for the question
oh no i lied is there a reason you went with youtube over
twitch yes i can manage the girls accounts from youtube i cannot manage
the girls accounts from twitch can't do a thing on twitch
management-wise um and twitch uh unfortunately are very sparse and
arbitrary when they uh throw the old band hammer down or
suspension hammer down uh really not a fan of twitch doing that
it's every week you see a girl being like twitch with a heck
i'm literally doing everything that everyone i'm doing stuff that everyone
else does um like it just at least with youtube you
can like beg them on twitter for help or whatever
and twitch is inconsistent yeah let's see
uh would you dominate inkling
i've never played splatoon isn't actually good it's probably like the most
war-friendly game for me to play
um
how does managing account yeah so i have it sounds really bad but i don't do
anything on their accounts but um i can basically go on their
accounts and set up streams for them or approve of comments for them
um anything they want to help out really like um now that
debuts have happened the girls are like gonna be controlling all that stuff
like they'll be doing their live streams and stuff but in order to reduce
as much stress as possible and the girls i pretty much tried to do every single
little thing but now that we're past the debut
stage like they're they're gonna have to be big girls now and
you know put up their put up their little games
put up their streams and all that and update their description
like i was the one doing all that behind the scenes
um have you played pokemon yeah pokemon ruby
my childhood game um mudkip was my starter
they have to spread their big girl wings yes i like putting a message in the
discord i'm like i'm so sorry girls but the hand
holding kind of slows down now
um yeah say hello
it was torsik blaziken is so strong and so is mudkip mudkip's really strong as
well um mudkip's always used in speed runs for pokemon
ruby or emerald she doesn't know i want to collect
her ink oh my god inks on you strongy is mama bird but it's time for them to
flee the nest honestly like um i hope overall they
feel like less stressed like um they didn't have to think about the
lores or what they wanted to say everything was edited on their behalf
like they had to give the audios over but everything was done on their behalf
and because like i've heard stories of like other agencies like go to the
tablet right make up your lore we've ordered all the art but you make up the
lore by the way and it's like what you literally are handing me the model what
do you mean you've not thought this stuff and it was like quick come up with
a description of your character really quickly quick quick
uh and it's like what you you're giving me the model what do you mean i come
up with the stuff like that's the whole point of the model unless it would be
customized like it's like um
how did you end up managing them or are you new to the agency well i'm new to
being a manager i'm not even their manager i'm just a streamer that does it
alongside them i just picked them but but me me now i want to
screen i'm fucking being a boss i ain't doing shit
um
yeah
um i know this isn't it someone said it someone said say purple burglar alarm
got it i knew someone was gonna say it i'll always guess this
right so in my like clear accent i say purple burglar alarm but if i say it
in a harsh scottish accent purple burglar alarm
like my tongue gets caught on the top of the roof of my mouth wait i'll mute
my background music so you can really hear it my my tongue gets caught
purple burglar alarm like ooh purple burglar alarm
you can hear my tongue getting caught say that
uh
what did you miss nothing it's just me meamin about
are you all trying to keep non conflicting schedules sadly it's not
possible when someone like me is on the team
um so whenever uh gen mate of mine goes live i will highly recommend you go
watch them because right now for example she'd be caught in bum is live
dinner 2.0 uh azura is coming on in roughly three hours
um but sadly i am an endurance streamer and the best time slot that i have
selected means i can go to doctor's appointments even if i do
um no i'm not dying before anyone freaking types that
i'm fine my health is good um uh it's all good don't worry
um but the time slot i have chosen means i can still go out to do
things like go shopping or to a doctor's appointment
or um you know go feed gammy you know how it is
i'm not dying stop my health is so much better
although i do have a sad story i mean i won't say it in 2.0
even though it's just all right well no i'll keep it to myself because it's a
bit sad and i don't i don't want to make you guys sad
like this is such a good happy time like holy fuck we're back
um after a year god damn that took so long to cook
but we're strongy cut with me that's just my name
admit it that's just my name um but yeah sadly i am an endurance
streamer which means weekly i will most likely have very long streams that are
not friendly to the majority of viewers please understand do not feel bad
um if you are unable to watch me live
um the other girls uh might be much more accessible to you time zone wise or
stream wise um i can still hear her
um but i play i absolutely do not feel insulted
at all if you cannot um you know keep up with me i'm not very friendly my
time zone isn't friendly i am aware of that and because i'm an
endurance streamer like tomorrow's stream is
literally eight hours long i'm not even kidding
we're doing the full playthrough of assassin's creed brotherhood
and then we're going back to 100% it because i've never 100%
in the dna sequence since assassin's creed brotherhood before
like that's what we're doing the next day what do you mean
i thought you just debuted
um so yeah that's uh why um whenever a gen mate goes live please you are more
than welcome to tell me i will direct you guys to the gen mate because i can't
redirect because my stream my gate if my stream isn't over
um so full point through first day is planned yes and then 100%
the next day i don't know how long it's gonna take but yeah
um eight hours isn't going to be the norm every single stream so like for
example oh for example
uh um for example needy streamer overload
um is two hours long i think i've never played the game before
i think it's just a click simulator type thing i'm not sure
um i've also got uh however actually um
james cameron's avatars an eight hour stream
sorry uh old school runescape is like 12 hours oh god
these are all so long like i've got to i need to make up for lost time
okay i need make up for lost time um not to mention uh once i get membership
once i get monetized i'm also doing membership streams
on top of all of this um it's a more stream on saturday um
and then i'm trying foreign sweets it is gonna be
like a uh hand like a desk cam oh yeah oh you get to see my desk man
um when do you rest i will rest until i'm dead i've waited a year to be here
i have lost time to make up for um people have waited in cryo freeze for me
for a very long time and the way i say thank you is
rather than saying thank you is like doing it through content through ASMR
through collabs through everything so yeah
i'm making up for it oh no uh someone says don't burn out please
i have a secret for you i have this thing your honor
it's called rotism and it means i actually don't experience burnout
i don't experience it i basically go to sleep
and wake up the next day i'm ready to take on the world again
uh i've never really felt what burnout is the way people describe it
nope nope i think uh my autism has given me a buff um
and means i don't get burnout and i'm very excited to stream every single day
it's a superpower um yes for the foreign sweet stream again that's
hand cam you'll see my hands so if you don't like v-tubers that kind of
show a wee bit of the flesh uh do apologize i might not be for you
however do have gen mates that are a little shy
and i don't think they'll show themselves so please be patient i'm just
like oh someone send me a picture of my face with the hat right now
so i can make it my twitter profile picture right
um i need to make it my twitter profile picture
strontism oh strontism is oh should that be my life tag
because i don't get burnt out strontism oh that's really bad though
i feel like you're making fun of autism i'm like
one shut the fuck up i literally have sweaty hands and feet
all day long like fuck you
um you gotta throw a swirl at swirl at them
mm i like that hypnosis swirls it's like this thing you swirl on a desk and
then you're like strontism life tag strontism
okay okay okay like i can blame you guys if someone's like oh my god you're
making fun of me
anyway i don't think anyone's gonna watch me that's like that anyway so
never seen a workhorse oh i guess uh it's even better than this when the
memberships come out
stront is shit in dodge
ain't no way ain't no way i named myself
kaka in netherlands netherlands praten
nee jung ike schnappet neat ike schnappet neat ike
namin my name wait i forgot all the dutch in the world my
my name is merda that's terrible i have autism
do oh my god autism gang gang gang gang gang
got the patreon oh yeah yeah you enjoy my patreon audio did you like the demo
it was so weird like hearing hearing the uh the scots if you know what i'm
saying
the demo audio was good oh thank you
hey you didn't tell us you could speak dutch
nee ike schnappet neat uh ike leer netherlands of my
xbox on that ike heb i had uh netherlands uh
mensen vrenden vroiden that's german i basically used to play college where
he was some dutch folk and then yeah learn some dutch
spoke with some french as well like if you want to say uh justice reigns from
above in french don't worry i've got you okay
plasso de luge de la justice
dutch is so funny azura was like i'm learning dutch i'm like azura oh my god
azura i'll teach you i'll teach you how to say turtle okay
you say oh no my phone's on 20 percent battery
no sorry my phone is what i i've piloted my neck on i'm so
oh my arms they're what did you hear
hello wake up wake up okay there we go i just put my my charger in
it's fine it's fine everything's fine
stop please please hold still no i'm sorry please hold still
ah please everything that can't go wrong go around
oh my god my pc is like screaming at me right now you guys don't see me you
guys are like horizontal on my desk right now
i'm sorry also i'm really sorry if you like immersive feature verse
i'm really bad at this i'm piloting a make-on i'm doing a terrible job
you're literally horizontal on my desk right now i'm like looking down at you
like hi
this is terrible okay let me let me have some more
oh
can you i mean it's working it's working i'm just looking a bit funny
oh my god okay okay okay okay okay okay right let me refocus let me let me
refocus get it because you're a reefling
reefling reefling i need to make an audio
of a certain nature where i just say reefling over and over
oh oh oh my god i oh my tracking stop it phone
who's piloting this meh who's driving this bus
who's piloting this meh please phone just stay still
stop wiggling okay i'm actually i'm gonna start i'm gonna start turning
scots in a minute i'm getting raging go and just actual sit still i've got like
what freaking give me like 30 minutes of you being
still see right wait hold on hold on hold on hold on
hold the phone no literally hold the phone get it
because the freaking phone won't try it right hold on
ah okay turns out you can put your iphone sideways and it still tracks you
i didn't know that i've just learned that right now
that's right ladies and gentlemen i was the one
who judged you if you're a beach over worthy enough to get in the agency
i've literally streamed for less than two months myself
that's terrible that's absolutely terrible i shouldn't talk about that
i'm sure there's some people are like really pissed that i didn't pick them
sorry i was your barrier but please understand we also took into
you know someone can have the perfect voice
okay i'm fine ah go away i get scared i get scared when management show up
i'm like leave me alone oh my voice is cracking
holy crap so much professionals big wow
right hold on let me refresh your questions okay
i want you to strong my cuttles until i ain't oh that's such a good sentence
oh my god
e what do you think of sunken gallery
i'm not convinced
such probation i know i know i know i know was that the melody of legend of
zelda
um will you get multiple endings there's multiple endings
i've never played i actually don't know much about the game i thought it was
like you click buttons that's all i know
that you click buttons you'll never get i'm really good at
clicking buttons you know what i'm saying they're all bad endings
oh no there's tons of endings i thought it was like one of them
quick games
how did you end up getting to pick the talents
when you're just new to the agency zelda
because i'm the creative director
i'm the creative director
good ending is when you get your mask no
oh okay maybe take your mask
and the voices go away no don't take your mask i don't want to play elton ring
and then take my mask because then you guys all disappear
oh my god do you remember that time we played elton ring
and we all like we're mimicking something
and then someone came in and went banzai and blew it all up
that was amazing how big is the viewer game
i mean it depends if you want to count contractors as well
i guess it's pretty juicy if you want to count contractors
like we've literally got like four more technical clippers coming in
no one person's about to be on trial
two are like we want them full-time basically
so that adds more people to the website
do you count the talents as well that's another six then
technically if we disappear who will stream site
oh yeah one of you guys have to come in as the baddie
wait what's happening with my arm
what's happening with my arm
oh no i'm gonna have to know you about that
it's a bit too aggressive
are there any big group projects yes oh my god
there's such big group projects i'm so tired
i planned ahead i planned every month there's going to be
some sort of event going on at the allure
um leave my noodle arm i don't know why my arm breaking
i'll annoying nari about it nari was absolutely fantastic when she came to
construct in me she's fantastic um you plan on getting 3d models yes but
you're gonna have to put your money where your mouth is if you want to see the
girls 3d put your money where your mouth is give them
memberships uh go on them patrons because
that's expensive expensive because uh we would have to buy them the trackers as
well i actually don't know much about 3d in yet but i'm
pretty sure like you can be our chat model and we can all like
touch each other and stuff in there
uh will there be group audios yes there will be group
audios um there's already one-on-one audios planned
with each other but i didn't know the comfortability level of the girls when
we were like at that stage of development so so far
is hasura and sheepsters me and mersey and emmers and
icers um i've not done anything further i think
donathan rewards uh will most likely be targeted at that stuff and it'll be
access free to access um because i think public
donathan rewards are much more satisfactory obviously we will have to
do the classic uh like first place second place third
place um because we do need to incentivize and um
azura um uh might be in the position to move out if all
goes well and she gets the support um like monetary like gets monetized and
all that jazz and if she can move out she can definitely increase her like
stream times for years and uh just find a easier
time uh that's why i'm kind of like support the others
because like they're in positions where like oh if i could move out i could
definitely make more content stream for longer do this do that be more like
you know so definitely support them okay
can i drill it in your head anymore to support them or
then you like hypnotize you
oh my picture's on twitter right okay i'll get that i'll update it
and
mm-hmm
oh no we did not have a vealer house a vealer house would be awesome actually
uh no the girls are like some of them are like still living with family or
and so they can't really be like oh like you know
all the time so yeah
we obey we support the girls but you kindly support the girl
so yeah um
that is why um so uh azure's up first for donathan rewards to kind of give you an
idea um i'm opening to you know farting about
and uh being open to like kind of the stuff you guys would like to see
perfectly fine with me no problem
um
are the audios on patreon already done do you mean like edit
um only one month it's been done so like june is done so the girl's
responsibilities like contract wise is three streams a week
if health permitted oh my god if health permitted i got asked by one of the
girls i just azure was like did i need to give you a
doctor's note if i'm sick i'm like no go rest my goodness
you're not well you're not well um so if they're in good health they are to
stream a minimum of three times a week and monthly four audios
that's it i definitely do not want to overwork
anyone i do not want them to feel stressed i want them to have good times
good vibes uh happy ending uh yeah and they've been like super
patient and like the behind the scenes stuff going on
uh do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do
do you talk often with one each other yeah we're in a we're in a discord we talk
every day for two months we've like literally
talked every day um you know some some girls like might
feel like awkward around each other uh we had like a couple of gaming sessions
leading up to that uh we had mock streams together
i like wholeheartedly feel a hundred percent comfortable around these girls
um like when it comes to collabing with other vtubers outside the agency
unfortunately for me personally i'm quite inappropriate and if i don't know the
person and i don't know their comfort level i'm not really interested in like
asking for like uh oh you want to do a vtuber club type thing
um so uh i'm probably not going to do too many
clubs out with the agency unless like the girls vouch for me
or something like i'm i'm happy to make friends with their friends
but um it's probably going to be solo content majority on
this channel uh such as content featuring the reeflings when we
play our multiplayer games um yeah i
um there is a notification discord if you go on the others twitter
uh it's notification only uh the talents are not inside it
uh the talents uh sorry my voice is like proper feeling it right now
um yeah management don't have access
uh sorry contractors don't have access to the talent
talents aren't in the notification discord there's no way you can groom
us we groom you
why am i freaking frog blanking it's me it's probably not set up my parameters
one thing get more stable with the group discord for
watchers to be joined on the table what are you saying
i have no idea what you just said to me
will you hang out say together outside of the collapse
i don't even know if we're gonna have time like collabs are probably just
going to be us memen and like catching up unironically
um emmy's very pumped for maincraft server in july is when that comes out
main uh group minecraft server um i the last time i like properly
proliferate minecraft uh this is gonna set a few of
you's back um the last update was the plant pots were
released and i think witches were released and i like never even play that
properly beyond that so that'll be interesting
um i don't really understand anything beyond it
um
i think i just stroke right in that don't worry i'm stroking right now baby
stop oh my god
that's for later okay i'm gonna look in this direction because i think maybe my
she's being armed isn't being that way um yeah emmy's like really excited for
main i don't really know what you're supposed to do in the maincraft games
because according to that cycle pdl oh wait should i be on uh chats on the
wrong side if i'm looking this way
fan i'm looking this way maybe a lord friendly
oh sorry i actually didn't mean that for once
sorry hold on i'm looking chat excuse me oh my hair is in the way right well
let me put chat when you hold on
i'm looking you what you can do about it
actually i'm burping all over you too
why are you rating my burps tisker oh my god remember tisker
remember that time you guys were so nice to me when you could be so mean to me
remember that time yeah i remember that time uh my ears are caught my ears those
are my ears i'm a boogie's cut off now there we go
fix it she be is having her burps rate too
yeah she be burps like me oh my gosh she's like so oh my god
she's just like me for real for real
moment how am i supposed to support the other girls when you keep filling me in
oh maybe you're just a reef one i don't know sometimes
like uh you don't pick the wait you don't pick the oh she the oh she picks you
is that the same because it's like you never you don't know like you you can
give so many v-tubers a try and then it's just like one you latch on to and you
can't get away from them
where the things they're not horns or seashells
is it not obvious they're seashells like they're transparent you can see my
little hair through them as well i feel like look really hard hold on me
why am i not feels hold on a minute cut talk this
girl like i'm still cut off stop i'm not being bullied i'm being
bullied by v-tube studio right now you know what i'm a victim
can you like kind of see the back of my hair through the
see like it's transparent they're shells they're
parallelism shells in my hair i still have bunches behind it like i have i have
hair bubbles
yeah well i'll put you behind me
that's made you uncomfortable i know some people are like uh i find it hard
looking at a woman in the eyes and i was like don't be
fat it's fine it's fine
don't mind me don't mind me baby oh my god i love this model
look at the i love when models do that neck
thing where they only like disappears it's like the best part like when
there is like so much that goes into like picking a modeler and stuff
i don't like vtuber models where like the art like the hair and the art like is
a billion different splits and stuff like i don't like that i like that big
chunky hair i think it looks the best
um and like yeah i like my pupils as well yeah my little
squiddles any squiddlers i'll squiddle you in a minute
who's my oh yeah the moment
that's actually hard to say um the thing is i've probably not got one right
now i watched like 300 people during those
applications there's a lot of people i could
actually test um i'm thinking you've made me use my
brain shame on you um at the moment i'm biased to fen
um i just think she's cute i really like her
mind so fen fen's got my oshi boat right now
a scoreboard for the burps honestly that would be well
i won't make you use your brain again down straight you won't
bait or not you better not
uh so did you get applications from other vtubers that you were surprised
yeah there was like pre-established people and i'm like what do you want
what what why would you want to join you've already got like an entire brand
and like thing going on there's literally nothing wrong like they already
got their own vtuber models though
oh my god my tongue has physics this is gnarly made sure my tongue wiggles are
you ready
let's go wiggle physics
hey i'll i'll do a proper hypnosis there but my
voice is through right
uh i can only emmy can okay so all the models got the same emotions
but everyone had like a custom toggle or thing going on for them
and main was as i move the phone out the way
main was this i can like layer the eyes together as well
what are you feeling you're feeling so sleepy i want to suck your
yeah means i'll hypnosis and i can layer the eyes if i want to
right let me take that stuff off i made my sleep bubble my anime sleep bubble
what do you think everyone's got a little idle thing like that super idle
um why am i asleep i'm the phone phone you're
you're trolling i'm getting trolled oh my god
right right enough enough i'm ending stream soon
is she be still streaming
my god this is a nightmare i'm like absolutely
fanny in a boot on this desk right now there we go she be still streaming she's
not going offline is she
but yeah i have like one default
that's just for like if you're really susceptible
and then i have my hair as well to really get you going
uh like it literally can layer like if you can or if that's like better
so those are my custom things and i can take off my yukata but i don't even know
what button does that i'm only going to do it for like a water ASMR stream
um i don't even know hold on no hold on if i go
right what layer was it that is it p
hi what layer was it
what layer was it come on man take my clothes off
what the layer was it
gnarly what one did you set up to i'm just like hitting all the buttons right
now just so you should know that
hey must be the money i'm wearing clothes
man
that part comes later okay that part comes later
uh bring it back bring it back hey bring it back hey
what are you talking about what are you talking about
right i am gonna make doubly quadruply
quadruple check your mouth um that i am reading into
shibu shibu shibu shibu
oh did you guys like my meme i'm just a meme
who means their life
away away
um let's see shibu yes um i'm reading into shibu
okay uh will you be playing video games
tomorrow i'm playing assassin queen this is my
this is my game that i'm playing these are my childhood games
so a shashin cute ballahooja is my favorite game of all time
uh game cameras average heart is another childhood game
old school runescape is another childhood game
um yeah that's for the first week so after the stream ends
i'm gonna very slowly start putting up the waiting rooms for those ones and
then we're gonna get back into it everybody get to
do it i'm starting to lose it by the way just so you know
just so you know uh right i am gonna read into the ever
ever-beliefed and uh sheepsters and and you guys
say hi to her and so uh azure comes on in t-minus two hours
mercy comes on and wait wait let me come on let me come on now
wait a minute there's this little hooligan coming on
where when does this hooligan come on
oh okay okay hold on hold oh come on come on sorry i was looking at youtube
i'm sorry i'm sorry i was looking at youtube
i'm sorry i'm sorry i need to unbind that like right now
okay i take it back she be you're getting rolled
uh we're reading into emmy because
i made it into she be in the last stream i can't believe i did that again
thank god it didn't happen on debut by the way oh my god could you imagine
i'd be like oh you did that on purpose oh that was so obviously bait
because i know some vtubers like do do it as bait but like i'm actually that
freaking daft that i've forgotten to unbind
sorry i apologize that was pretty scandalous
okay you got me for like 10 more minutes until emmy comes on
let me refresh marshmallow you got 10 minutes come on boy
you're too autistic to do it willingly literally i'm i can't plan ahead i'm
the last one okay we will now know the Hulk
key is either emmy beezer
uh she keeps fishing with bait no i should go back to the chat
so you guys can see yourself
10 minutes fly by what about infinite time
um i'm like can i leak my like other stream
plans for the rest of the week for the month and i'm like i'm trying to
remember what games i've put down and i've already forgotten them all
but they're good games so we're gonna do old-school runescape consistently
for a little bit because i want to get 99 fishing
do do do do no not fishing wrong one 99 cooking because i'm a woman
do do do do do do do do and that's actually real
um so we're trying my best horror games i have a bad heart
and don't do pause my heart is fine i got it checked
i have to go in if there's any issues um i i can play horror games
it's just ill advised i would probably do it as like a
reward uh without giving the game away oh i don't want
a game i'm playing next week are you guys ready
i'm playing skyrim fill achievements next week
because i know how to get full achievements in that game because i've
done it a few times before
um and obviously uh skyrim belongs to the north thank you very much
i'll be here all week storm cloaks yep don't care what they say
you know i'm all for talus praise be to talus
um
so that's my duration game for next week is skyrim first
i believe it takes me just over 24 hours to do full achievements
um we kind of you kind of cheat at the start because you do if you do the
companions questline first and then go back to the save
before so you're not a werewolf and then do the vampire quest
the problem i don't know if it's gonna be a problem if i use
um xbox pass for it because because um my xbox would break
so many times trying to play skyrim because the save file issues
um and i i if it's going to be the same way then
there's a strategical way to get full achievements via the xbox i already
know how to do it i've done it a few times so don't worry i'll lay it all out
for you baby i'll show you how to get full achievements in skyrim
in under 24 hours that'll be my challenge in under 24 hours
i'm sure you can do it under way less but i i don't know the strength i'm not a
speedrunner
he is i had a girl ghost me because i told her you picked the stormcloth
what why would anyone pick the legion sorry but the elves can perish you're
no coming into my home country being like no you're not allowed to
praise talos uh excuse me you can get
people a bit of casual fantasy or racism don't mind me
absolutely i'm stormcloth all the way don't care
don't care don't care i know i'm right
um
being team instinct in pokemon go
because if you always follow your instincts you'll get there in the end
unironically i'm i'm team instinct oops i don't know what you guys are in
pokemon go but i'm team instinct and then the moment was like if you always
if you follow your instincts you'll always win because it doesn't mean you
have to win or lose just follow how you feel
and life is good
because team mystic is for like wise people and then team red i've forgotten
their name uh is like for for like uh like i must win
people i'm like now i'm just here for the journey i'm just here for the good
time thank you
what instinct was the only one that seemed to lack a stick up their bum
uh excuse me where are we placing sticks
team ball of valor oh my god be alert in pokemon go collab let's go
i'm just wait did i read it wrong if i read it wrong
uh will there be any dead by daylight streams
oh possibly i've not played in eons i have no idea what the perks are and the
newest killers are and all that jazz but it would be
oh wait oh there's six of us
i don't want anyone to feel left out if we do like a big six man collab
i mean maybe not maybe someone can just beg to and then we all go running around
killing each other and dead by daylight
me running me chasing the girls listening to them scream
whilst i'm like chainsawing
black ops 2 did they fix the servers and black ops
oh we might be playing black ops 6 i think black ops 6 is coming out
the girl said they would be willing to play it as her was like yeah play black
ops before i'm like uh and then she'd be like yeah give it a go
black ops you want to play black ops with me
please
i'm so excited i'm pretty sure there's like a black ops six is it not or is it
black ops five i'm not much of a horror fan
sorry i'm very boring i don't watch much media
and if i do watch media i like fantasy like game of thrones or lord of the
rings or the hobbit uh i really like the old um
no technology type stuff uh i like the community stuff
guys we still do not have the shire lego set
all i'm saying is when the shire lego set finally comes out
we've got the freaking tower no one wants the tower
no one wants the freaking elven place either like
wouldn't just give me either bag end
that yeah give me the full of bag end or like give me the full of the shire
i don't care how much money it is i'll let you spend thousands i don't care
like lego get your get your shiz together
there's a new lord of the rings game coming out as well
um and it's like wet of workshops you're sitting on a gold mine
why does no one want anything of the shire the shire just like feels like
community and everyone's got flowers and everyone's got a little job and they all
go down to the wee pub um is it dragon or something
pub dragon uh not all the names are with me right now
um but like why why are you not investing in the shire people won the
shire i demand the shire
i don't want the tower i don't want the black gate i don't want any of that
stuff if it comes out we're building on
sure oh 100 no question the new wet of game
the game art looks curious to say the least it looks curious have i ever
eaten haggis yes i'm scots i've had haggis
um actually well i tell you a little secret
for future content uh st andrew's day is like national scottish day
um and it's in november and i'm going to be hosting
a game show for my gen mates because thank god none of them are british
um or else they'd be cheating in my game show but i'm going to do a scottish
game show but that's the secret for you and me baby
okay keep it a secret do i need to kiss you to keep the secret
there you have to keep the secret but yes i'm doing a scottish game show
i'm gonna make them spell scottish words i'm gonna make them guess scottish
memes i'm gonna make them um do a few things
um our japa cakes cookies biscuit or a cake
oh my god i'd say they're a cake honestly
uh but yes what's the best meal deal
honestly though that's the i'm wondering if i could get iron brew sent
to their houses to all try at the same time
oh that would actually be kind of a banging though not gonna lie be like
right everyone open your can of iron brew tell me if it tastes like ginger and
bubblegum oh what's it what's the go-to
greg's sauce uh greg's order i'm brewing buck fast
could i give them buck fat no i can't give them alcohol that's bad
man yeah because i mean it can be like strongy gave us alcohol
greg's tear list oh cheese and hamburger get sorry but
cheese and ham but if they don't put too much butter on the cheese and hamburger
then i and the best pie not pie pastry beans
cheese and sausage i'm like 90% sure my dad was a doll he used to go get it for me
so i um it's like i moved out um and i like i don't drive
and i didn't have access to a bike like i cycle
kind of why i got a big ass but um oh is emi alive oh have i missed emi
i might have to wrap up oh i think emi's live i'm so sorry i'm gonna have to
wrap up um um uh what i had i had to wrap up uh
actually no don't wrap up and pregnantion please um
who said that uh uh uh uh uh let me just like quadruple check i'm reading into
okay 2.0 yeah okay okay okay we did it we did it
we did it it was the unprofessional 2.0 let's go baby let's go right i'm going
to go rest my voice for tomorrow's absolute chaos uh shortly you will see
my streams for the week appear um i don't know if we're doing free chat or no
i don't know some people do free chat i just kind of talk in the free chat of
like the stream that i'm doing next um okay thank you so much my little
reeflings it has been nothing but a pleasure holy fuck i will make up for
lost time i promise you i will make up for so much lost time
let me kick uh and cook i did hopefully
hopefully you like the girls but thank you so so much i will stream to use
tomorrow and yep your hero thank you so much for waiting on me and thank you
for coming out of cryo freeze it's been a nothing but a pleasure
nothing but a pleasure i love you so much i will talk to you so so soon
eight hours tomorrow be there be square don't worry if you actually can't be
there for the full time i'm just teasing you i'm teasing you with my little
non-existent tentacles right talk to you later okay see you tomorrow
bye