I was trying to speedrun up in the stream started and the game.
This game crashes so heckin' easily and it literally just crashed there.
Praying it works.
But good morning, good evening, and good afternoon.
Oui, today my screen has gone black so hopefully I'm still streaming.
Oh my god.
Right, this game breaks.
Oh, I think it's about to break again.
No way.
Oh, this game breaks so easily.
Oh, don't break, don't break.
Oh, my screen's black again.
What?
This game breaks so easily.
I think this is like 2007 maybe?
But goodness me.
Good morning, good evening, good afternoon.
Oui, we are playing yet again, surprise surprise, another childhood game.
Wait, what?
Oh, it's 2009.
It says James Cameron's Avatar game 2009.
So I played this game as a little sheriff and is there a girl that's white with black hair?
Well, I'm not blonde.
I'm not.
Well, we just did that.
Right, we're blonde with green eyes today.
Yippee.
So this game.
Okay, now let's enter first name.
Squiddles.
Squiddly.
I'm feeling a bit squiddly-diddly the day about.
I bet you'd like that, wouldn't you?
I had no idea they even released the game back then.
Oh, this game is, I wrote.
I'll shush until the campaign part, but they much to the campaign.
Let me, it got slapped together.
Let me tell you that much.
I got slapped together.
So I am a big enthusiast of Avatar.
I absolutely enjoy the movies to the highest of heavens.
Cut.
Oh my God, I've not played this in years.
Oh, look, it's us.
Sigourney Weaver.
Big Sigourney Weaver, where you been?
We've missed you, Sigourney.
Don't screw up.
Got it.
This has not stood up to the test of time, graphics-wise.
My neck be bending.
My armpit textures are warped.
Oh, AC and Snow Berries.
Hi.
How was your puzzle game, AC?
I watched you in the bath.
Oh, this is really weird.
I was in the bath and I was like, I'm sure AC should be on right now.
And I opened up the game and you were like, this is a child's game.
How can I do this?
I thought I could do this because I think someone said,
why did you pick this game first?
Snow Berry Raid.
Yeah, there was like a big whale with loads of ropes all over it.
And I was like, I've never seen this game in my life.
I'm too dumb.
Did you not finish it?
Was it like a finished game or was it like one of those ones where it's like,
you just play for fun?
Is Sheevee's fault?
Sheevee, what did you do?
She put the ropes in.
Oh, that's very good.
Oh, you finished it.
Let's go.
AC Smart.
Hell's Gate.
Kendra.
Congrats if your name's Kendra.
Okay, so we are playing an RDA soldier.
Boots on the ground.
We are a signal specialist, okay?
We've just arrived at Hell's Gate,
which is where the humans have landed on the Navi's home planet, basically.
And the way that we humans survive is by sectioning off areas of Pandora,
because Pandora is so aggressive and dangerous.
Wendy, yes.
The big blue ladies.
Soon, soon.
Hold on, hold on.
You've never seen the movie before?
Okay.
How do you even summarize Avatar?
Just watch yourself around, Dr. Monroe.
He treats the avatars like his own personal guinea pigs.
This is a very old game,
and it is not a fair, like, assessment of what this game's about.
However.
However, however, however.
Too long didn't read.
Blue people good?
Humans bad?
Capitalism bad?
Being nice to the environment?
Good!
That's it.
That's all you have to know.
You have completely caught up to the Avatar franchise,
as we know right now.
Bojinga, I think.
Brian?
Not me getting Brian back on the HUD.
Thank you so much, Bojinga, for the 13, I appreciate it.
I'm looking forward to this stream of this game that literally no one has played.
I wish I could do a poll right now,
but if I back out of this game,
it crashes super easily,
so basically,
I don't even know if I'm going for a toilet break today.
I looked it up and it said apparently the campaign mode is...
8 hours, but I don't believe it.
Yes.
We're at signal specialist.
I didn't even know there was an avatar.
Well, there's a new avatar game now, but we're playing the old-
Let me take a sip of my honey tea today.
Aloha.
Did you guys watch Mercy's ASMR?
Congrats to Mercy!
Mojie's been the only member of Euler to not get her VOD taken down
and leave a warning on her channel for sexual misconduct.
Give it up for Mercy!
Oh my God.
Let's go, Mercy!
I am so nervous for my ASMR stream
because I had planned something a bit special for it.
And...
YouTube are dancing with all of us right now.
Sorry, I'll get over the cutscenes first.
We get to experience being in a navi body for the first time.
If you haven't played, or don't know,
you enter a booth which neural links you to an actual navi body.
Don't look too much into it.
It's pretty fantasy-based and all that jazz, but yeah.
We are now in navi, we have access to a navi body,
but we are still RDA.
RDA's the bad guys.
Boo! Boo! RDA!
Navi! Yay! Navi! Yay!
But RDA, boo!
Go.
Oh my God, that neck!
That's killing me.
She looks like a giraffe.
Let me get over this bed real quick.
So we have just been introduced to our avatar body.
Navi body.
RDA mission complete.
So yes, this is a much older game.
We're just...
So we are about to...
Anyway.
She's pampering us.
It looks good for its age.
Honestly!
So the newest avatar, I haven't had an...
Oh!
Brian!
Bero, thank you for the 20.
Would you guys neural link with me?
Like, if you could go to bed, like, you see everything from APOV?
Would that...
Would I still be in control at that point?
Or would you want to control me?
Or would you want me to control you?
Do you really need to ask?
I don't know if you want to see my POV.
You just, like, dine and be really disappointed that I don't have big boobs.
Does the nicotine patch interfere with the process?
Nah, you can leave it on.
If anything, it makes it better when you're in.
So this is the reason we are in Pandora, the world.
You see those purple things underneath?
Those are the resources we mine from this planet for capitalism back on Earth.
It is crazy.
Honestly, I get to pray.
Hard to believe you're finally here.
A-turn!
Oop!
They're purple.
The resources are purple.
A big butt better than Big Boa.
We're here to get the blue oil.
Did someone say oil?
By the dawn, sparely.
Did I tell you?
In a voice chat,
I sung that, but I only know the first two lines.
And then freakin' Sheevie and Azura burst out into singing like the actual thing.
And I was like, oh my god, this is really...
I was getting serenaded by the dawn,
sparely.
I once prayed.
I don't know the words at all.
And I don't know why it's so hard.
Like, why does it go high?
Did you guys see my Twitter post about how much I got scammed on American sweets?
Hello!
So these are just basic transporters,
but as you can see, this is the whole map of Pandora.
We will unlock a few more locations soon,
but there's not really much detail to it.
We're currently at Hell's Gate.
We are going to get flown to Blue Lagoon,
but as you can see, this Earth is healthy.
There's lots of blues and greens and all that.
It's a nice, healthy Earth.
Blue Lagoon.
Open the game...
Oh, that's just the information thing.
I thought I was going to explain what Blue Lagoon is.
Blue Lagoon is where a lot of the navi
that are controlled by the RDA-side hangout
and a few of the tribes are tolerant to our behaviors.
Our human activities.
So this is Tutorial Island, essentially.
I thought this game was a fever dream.
It's real!
Hi, Stony. I remember playing this game as a kid.
Congrats, you're one of the two people
who have played this game that's watching right now.
A very, very underground game.
I'll tell you a very fun factoid about this game.
So obviously, I was an Xbox kid.
If you were able to obtain a copy of the special...
Oh, I loved that little animation.
This was probably before motion capture was even a thing
because what the heck was that?
Our encounter with Pandora's wildlife.
These are Viperwills.
They're terrifying.
But their designs are so good.
The animal designs are freaking amazing.
I am needing to remember.
That's to analyze.
Okay, so we have freaking special abilities.
For some reason, I can go and visit and shit.
But you can level up and progress
and make these abilities way stronger.
But literally, it's pretty insane.
The game's got loads of things going for it.
So right now, we're just defending the perimeter
from what way the game isn't too loud.
I cannot adjust the volume without breaking it.
We're just defending the perimeter from...
Oh, I almost just shot our own guy there.
Is it working?
Okay, there we go.
You do get XP.
There is a level-up system in this game as well.
I am so bad at aiming.
Holy crap, I don't remember it being this hard as a child.
Child Me is like so much better gamer
when it comes to this stuff, honestly.
Lollipop model confirmed
we're doing some reward.
Because, actually, why am I so much better at this game?
I know they spawn over there a lot.
Okay, objective complete.
Love to see you play the game,
but I will be very happy for every Navi I see die.
For the RDA for humanity.
You're joking.
You picked the RDA?
Who are you?
Iron Reaper?
You picked the freaking...
Why would you prick?
Oh, I literally just had a Freudian slip
and called you a prick there.
Why would you pick?
This is not the Navi.
Thank you for the 50.
That's insane.
Grab a buggy and help him out.
But you're wrong.
RDA Supremacy.
Reef Flames?
We're here for nature
and to be nice to wildlife.
I'm literally a cuttlefish.
Are you saying...
Oh, is this Halo Controls?
No, kind of.
You can be attacked when you go out,
but I will say one thing.
The motion sickness.
Merci.
If you're lurking, do not watch this.
This motion sickness on the vehicles is insane.
Oh, we're doing hit and runs.
We're doing hit and runs.
Get wrecked.
Oh, right.
I missed that, but whatever.
Oh, I can't remember much.
There is going to be...
This guy should...
There is like aim assist in this game.
So if you're bad at video games,
please don't worry.
If you ever think you might want to
get this game a shot.
You're a lifesaver.
This game is giving commands for keyboard,
but that's because...
Wait, wait, wait.
Butt bounce.
Wait, where the heck did it go?
I'm fighting.
Oh, we're going to stick them out to go down.
Oh, come on.
You can tell Kale as well,
which is really good in this game.
This game is definitely for people
who are not very...
I would say if you're new to gaming,
the game is very friendly to you.
I say that as I literally am forgetting
all the spawn locations of the enemies right now.
These are Viper Wolves.
Literally waiting until this game gets so beautiful.
I wish...
I don't know what the new avatar game is like genuinely about.
I heard those growls.
I heard that.
I have gamer sense, okay?
Oh, there's another one.
Jeez.
Whoa.
My trigger just got stuck there.
Are you squidding me right now?
Glory to humanity and cuttlefish.
Down with the navi.
No, the navi are the good guys.
Slice Saber?
How dare you?
Thank you for the tip.
But the navi are the good guys.
We're supposed to protect humanity, okay?
Right, so we're currently saving
the current signal thing or something.
I don't know.
Tutorial.
We are doing tutorial, but I'm just spamming through it
because I want to be navi.
Just to be those dogs.
Everyone's literally so beefed up in this game for no reason.
Wait, you say navi's good guys.
Protect humanity.
The navi are the big blue ones.
The big blue ones protect nature.
We protect nature, okay?
We...
Wait, hold on, hold on, hold on.
You ready for this?
We...
You want to protect nature, little reform.
You want to be a good boy for humanity.
You want to recycle where physically possible.
But we understand...
Oh, wait.
If the RDA are the bad guys, then why are their mechs so cool?
Checkmate, tree huggers.
Uh...
The rea...
Well, I'm gonna show you me absolutely wrecking
and fricking decking those mechs.
There's no way you guys are genuinely picking the human side.
Doomsday, Dan, you're getting a spank,
but thanks for the tip.
And Beijing got again.
No, you're wrong.
You have to be nice.
If I have to hit me...
Tree huggers!
If that makes me a tree hugger,
then guess what?
I'll proudly identify myself as a tree humper.
Oh, I just got...
Oh, I'm getting...
I'm getting...
I'm getting ganged up on.
Literally, the bark is peeling off from how hard
I'm humping the wildlife right now, okay?
Because...
I'm not...
Oh, um...
This is so much easier as a child.
Hello, child, me.
Can you just, like...
I don't know, possess my body right now?
Because why am I getting wrecked and decked?
There's...
Uh...
Oh, for goodness sake, wait, wait, wait, wait.
I'm getting wrecked.
What'd you get?
Tim...
What the heck?
Tim Shuttle?
Your name is literally Cuttlefish.
A little Shuttlefish.
Glory to the hip, no toad.
Protect the Navi and the sea star.
See, Tim knows exactly what he's on about.
Thank you, Tim.
At least some of us have since...
Right.
You've got me there.
You've got me a wee bit there.
Hold on, hold on.
But give him a chance.
Give him a chance.
Thank you, Otter Von Biscuit.
Damn right you only sent for Cuttlefish.
We the best out here.
Wait, I just realized.
I think I'm supposed to drive the car in here.
Oh, I think I'm about to get attacked.
Or maybe those guys are protecting me.
I'm not sure.
There we go.
Run that, logist!
Oh!
See, you have level up system.
Um, I have terrible news for you.
If you want to do survival of the fittest, no weapons.
Absolutely.
Goodness.
Is this...?
Ah!
Take this!
Fart Bomb.
Thank you very much.
Sarge, IBW.
What a unique...
Thank you.
Thank you very much for the tip.
Sorry, Strony, but I'll never trust a species at...
Look.
All I'm seeing is give tentacles a chance.
I might be getting a little tentacle addition here and there, you know?
Am I going the wrong way?
It looks like I'm going the wrong way on the map.
I've not been here before.
Oh my goodness, the camera angle.
Look, the game aged all right.
I'm not going to say it aged well.
Wait, is there a little path back here?
No, there's not.
It's a lie.
It's up here.
Oh my goodness, this camera angle is horrific!
I'm getting sick of myself.
Let me in!
I'm human!
What are you doing?
Okay, I actually have to go backwards?
Jeez.
Thank you.
Not Alessandro as well.
Rules of nature, survival...
Yeah, no.
Oh my goodness!
Wait!
Oh my God!
Lady driver moment!
Please!
Camera angle!
Jeez!
Louise!
Let me work here!
My goodness!
This is awful!
Why is the camera...
Oh my God!
This is horrific!
Are you kidding me right now?
Oh, thank God.
I don't get emotions like in the video games.
Do you not expect the message to work this time long?
Anyways, have fun, stroney and dreams.
Brian's back!
So when you tip, you can actually, like, act in here and you can hear it.
Thank you again for the another tip, Alessandro!
Eh, bitches.
When you tip, you will never be read out.
Oh my God, that camera angle is horrific.
Please.
Do not ever make me drive one of those again.
Thank you.
Oh, goodness me.
Right.
What is the heck is this?
I've forgotten.
Oh, it's a teleport pod.
Okay.
You can teleport between the different regions.
So this is all the Blue Lagoon areas.
Oh my God!
This is awesome!
That camera angle is horrific.
Please.
This is all the Blue Lagoon area.
But as you can see, there's one, two, three, four, five.
Why are the teleport points all at the bottom and only one at the top?
Eh, I see how it is.
Make a mirror walk everywhere.
Okay, a little sip of my tea.
Have you played it?
Are you sure you've played this before?
The accusations?
I'm not beating the accusations.
Right, I'm going to finish my tea before it gets too cold.
Mmm.
I'm delicious.
I like the reverb effect on the verb.
I mean, I don't want to ruin anything, but that's definitely may or may not happen in
a certain ASMR stream.
I like freaking changed the title of the ASMR stream because I don't know what is going
on.
Everyone's getting warnings left, right and center.
Now don't get me wrong.
Any jumping up and doing on the bed is quite humorous, okay?
And I don't know, did she be actually doing anything that was that wrong?
Now the only reason I will say Azura had received that warning was on the pure basis.
Her voice is just like honey.
Her voice is the sun embracing you after a few days of rain.
Her voice is like that hug you have needed for years and you just let it all out and
you feel like her.
However, the other side of the coin for Azura's voice is it won't go down.
It can't stay down.
There's no such thing as a refractory period to her when you listen to her voice.
Maybe you'll get 10 minutes a piece at max.
You know what I'm saying?
So I kind of get why she got a warning.
I don't think she'd be got a warning because she was wise enough to private it.
I don't know.
I don't know if she did delete that.
Did she do ear licking?
Oh goodness me.
Can't even do a ear licking.
I don't know what's going on because people that show their face are still uploading all
fine and dandy.
So I think there might be a H-E-N update to the tie.
Possibly pop stealth policy.
Oh god, not the camera angle again.
I'm currently driving with one hand so this is going to go absolutely awful.
But look how big Pandora is.
It's fantastic.
One hand steering whilst I drink my tea.
I'm like a real contractor honestly.
Look, I'm just here to do the contract work.
I'm not here to do anything special.
I get paid on the day.
Okay, driving isn't actually that bad right?
Let's speed up.
Let's go.
Let's see if two handed.
I'm even worse probably.
Oh, I'm hitting the land.
I'm doing the Titanic.
Titanic momentum.
I am played this game when I was young and when I tell people about it, they never believe
it's real.
Also for the Navi, support nature.
Yes, thank you.
Thank you for the tip, Kitsune.
Gaming today.
Literally, I don't think I've really met anyone that's heard about this hecking game.
But I'm glad that a few of you actually have played it.
Okay, I'm just unlocking teleport stations when I do that.
Hi, hi everyone joining.
We're playing Avatar.
James Cameron's Avatar.
Some people thought it was Avatar, the last airbender related.
No, no, no, no, no.
Not at all.
Although, I think Amy might be doing a watch along that if you're into watch longs.
Please do think about supporting your local neighborhood little sister because she may
be doing a watch along that a little bit.
I'm going to take a little sipping tune of my cola.
I need to hydrate.
Now I get to ramble about all the work I did yesterday.
Okay, so the update is...
Are you squidding me right now?
Unless...
Brian!
Gaming in one hand while she stronts the cuddles in the other.
It's more difficult than you think.
Not that I'd know.
Honestly, thank you for the tip.
Tharja.
Tharja, I feel like that's not how you're supposed to pronounce it.
Are you Swedish and it's Tharja?
Tharja?
A little bit of a Swedish moment.
Look, it's that guy we saved in that cave only a few minutes ago.
What kind of cola?
Just cola cola.
Is it called Coke Zero when it's got the no sugar?
I finally went no sugar on the cola.
Aspartame.
I can finally tolerate aspartame.
It is that thing that is in the drinks to make it sugar-free.
But I was like, I don't mind having a big badonk-a-donk,
but I don't want it to get too big.
So I'm now drinking aspartame,
which apparently gives rats cancer.
So it's not looking good for us mammals.
But hey, oh, you got to die something.
And, you know, I'm not going out without enjoying myself.
That's all I'm saying on that much.
Right.
There are vapor wheels here, so please excuse the combat.
Boom.
Now you can just came to do this,
but it does bring you out of fricking invisibility.
Get in the boat, get in the boat, drive away, drive away.
Yeah, see, they get scared of my little fart bomb.
Actually, I think it's called a supersonic wave
and they don't like the noise, which makes sense.
You know, nature doesn't like loud noises.
Can relate on a physiological...
Physiological?
No, not physiological.
Oh, now you can just skip quite a bit of combat if you're cheeky,
but only if you're smart enough to do the things in the correct timing.
I'm going to heal up.
You can heal up naturally and it just means gentle for time.
As I said, this game is super forgiving to new gamers.
If you are into kind of that fantasy element, then...
Am I to walk from here?
I can't walk from here.
Nature doesn't like loud noises.
Literally the loudest of nature.
The sea bomb or a big badonka?
Those are the two choices.
I don't want to...
I don't mind getting too big.
No, sorry, I do mind getting too big.
You know, you got to keep that pear shape on.
You know, like when I do that hand cam stream,
everyone's going to know the real size of my chest.
Yes, I will teach you all the strats of this game.
For those who are wondering,
is this an adjourned stream?
This is roughly a seven hour stream.
So do feel free to stream yourself for the full seven hours.
If not, then the seven hour stream.
Roughly.
I believe we will actually successfully catch Mercy for a redirect
if my humble Mercy is streaming today, which I believe she is.
As always, if any of my gen mates come online,
please remind me and I will tell those who would much prefer to watch
a game that isn't archaic or whatever they're doing on stream.
We're supposed to for seven hours.
I feel like that would hurt.
But anyway, because I cannot tell you how strange it was
to go offline after two hours,
it literally felt like, what do we do now?
Oh, now we play the game.
Because I was like, wait, I have so much time and yeah.
So I've got three more ASMR collabs on the way.
I did a little bit of socializing.
We are now Navi.
We're about to do some Navi questlines.
But please remember, we are RDA Navi.
To use teleportations, we use the tree of vision.
It's very important to get those because my goodness,
it makes travel so much easier.
Look how tall we are and the camera angle has changed
and is much more favorable.
I prefer when video games have a really pooled out third perspective camera.
If the camera is two centimeters away from my face, I do not like it.
I find it very hard to look at.
I don't know if that's because I need glasses
and I still haven't trained myself to wear glasses.
Very bad girl, bad girl, very naughty.
But I think that my preference in video games is a zoom out angle.
It might be related to that because, yeah.
But hey, does anyone know the full name of the game and it's on Steam?
I don't even know if it's on Steam.
It is called James Cameron's Avatar.
Okay, the Navi can go through these doors.
Nope, only when they're green.
Okay, sure, sure.
We are about to encounter the wildlife.
They will still attack us even if we are Navi and RDA does not matter.
Where the heck am I going?
I'm going the wrong way.
That's why I'm getting turned around.
Now, again, we do have superpowers.
We have sprint.
We have invincibility.
We have health and we have ground smash, which is very good.
In order to get healing, if you look on when that health bar comes up again,
you'll notice the number zero at the bottom left on the right side of the health bar that appears bottom left.
The more cell samples we pick up, the more second chances we have.
Now, it's very common to run out of health in this game.
It's just the thing that happens.
It's not a big deal.
Again, the game's very forgiving.
You can literally do this all the way through the game and anything can hardly hit you.
But the later sections of the game, I don't know if there weren't many playtesters
because it was very rough in the later sections of the game.
I have to admit, it's getting pretty rough.
We are going to unlock this Tree of Vision, so now we can teleport to this region
when we come back to 100% the region.
You must be rider.
Let's get you up to speed.
How many games do you have lined up?
My apologies.
Do you mean to play in general?
If you mean games overall, like daily streaming games for a year?
Question mark.
Next week in endurance is Skyrim.
It's another childhood game of mine.
I used to do 100% achievements in Skyrim every year because I really appreciate the game and its vanilla form.
I do apologize if you like mods, but I don't know what to say.
Now we're among friends.
We aren't friends, so you need to learn quick.
We aren't friends?
Figure that out.
Would you guys, you know, would you guys really view?
What? 100?
You are one cool gal.
Fell in love when you started playing all my favorite games.
Also humans number one baby.
No!
I used to tactical strike every navi, every chance I got.
Anonymous!
No!
Bad boy!
Thank you for the 100.
That's a lot of money though.
Please make sure you're looking after yourself and treating yourself.
100 is a lot.
Jesus.
Bad and on.
Bad boy.
Come get spankens right now.
Bad.
Let me take a sipping tin.
Are you squiddin' me right now?
Goodness me.
Can't believe the reflings are betraying mama like this.
SMH.
Exactly, Nero.
Don't worry though, strongy.
I'll never betray nature.
Must protect the navi.
Exactly, we stand nature in this house.
We will look after nature.
As you see me, you can literally hear me dancing about in my chair right now.
So we are, what the heck is that zone?
And why is it so big?
Oh, we're plant sampling.
Okay, this is tutorial section.
When I explained, thank you for the tip again, Nero.
Anonymous, my goodness, that was a lot of money.
Play, is something attacking me?
No.
When you pick up cell samples, there's that little white bar on the left side.
I didn't, and you thought there was enemies because I was like, why am I getting, playing
as an avatar?
As an avatar, pondora's flora, which means flowers, and fauna means animals.
Yes.
As less aggressive towards you, therefore, killing and offensive creatures and plants
will not yield experience points.
All the reeflings siding with humans want to be the guy from strongy's lore video.
Oh, I'm so bad.
Hope a siren doesn't drown me in the ocean.
Thank you.
Thank you, Anonymous, for the tip.
Oh, you guys don't want me to, you know, take you down in the waters with me, that's not.
Honestly, my lore is so evil.
I promise, I don't want to, I don't want to hurt.
What?
Why do I suck so bad at this?
Wait, what was that?
No way, they have a slow motion kill cam.
I did not recall that whatsoever.
That's amazing.
Don't threaten us with a good time.
That sounds very yandere-esque.
But yeah, in terms of evilness in lore, why?
What was that?
I heard that.
I can hear it.
I actually got scared there.
I heard it, but I couldn't turn the analog stick in time.
So if I am human-
Why are there so many?
Oh no, I heard the plant.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, Mr. Plant.
I'm actually getting a bit scared.
Why is there so many?
Wait, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on.
Pause.
Pause, I hear more.
Oh my god, they're literally biting my ankles.
They're biting my ankles.
Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop.
Stop.
Okay, relax.
Relax or just collect and sell samples in this area.
I think I've hurt every...
All the enemies are gone.
Yeah, so these type animals don't attack.
They can't bite my ankles, man.
If you are human and come across this plant,
it is very poisonous.
It spits a bale at you, which is actually really cool.
But the design elements that went into this game
is just beautiful.
But yeah, the development, you can actually...
Yeah, you can scan...
Who goes there?
You can scan stuff and add it to a database and that.
I've never 100% of that.
Oh no, we can't because I would have to play the RDA side.
But I'm not playing the bad boy side.
But yeah, if you're into 100% completion,
absolutely you can do that kind of thing.
But it is a very beautiful game.
I am very much into alternative...
I saw that, it popped up my little thingies.
I knew it.
We can do this and just kind of try and bypass
all the enemies on the way.
Enemies.
Did you watch the second movie?
I absolutely did.
I thoroughly enjoyed the first movie with Jake Sully.
Absolutely.
I love your names, Jake, by the way.
Absolutely fantastic movies.
Completely captured me in that kind of fantasy,
different world, especially the night time scenes
when everything is lighting up.
Speaking of lighting up, hold on.
Reactive model, you ready?
Reactive model, do you want this?
Or do you want my normal model?
I can turn over in it.
The bioluminescence scenes.
Yes, bioluminescence scenes.
Pushing boots to destroyed Avatar 2 in the box office.
Nah.
Woo, our first meet with a navi.
Like an actual navi, not an RDA navi.
Are you ready?
Hello, Tanjala.
Oh, I'm stuck on this corpse of a theme of Ober.
Hello.
Hello, I'm on a kayak.
This is good.
Oh, Renee Harper is a corny weaver.
She's been poused with a navi.
She overslept them.
Tanjala wants you to kill the sick, strong beasts.
Anyone else identify themselves as a strong beast?
That's ridiculous.
We're really starting to dig hard for these words.
Avatar 2 had no story at all.
A perfect how not to make a sequel.
I disagree.
Brian!
Exactly!
Exactly, Grimble.
Thank you for the tip.
We do, Brian.
I have not seen fair and golly.
Bajinga!
Thank you for the tip.
What's fair and golly?
Have you guys seen fair and golly?
Are you doing what you eat?
You like Sigourney Weaver a lot.
So, Sigourney Weaver, the first thing I've seen her in.
Oh, we're just to destroy these, by the way.
Sigourney Weaver Avatar was the first thing I ever saw her in.
And I just adored her.
I adored her character.
Her voice is so lovely as well.
It's such a...
If you ever struggle at this point,
just jump up on this rock right here.
They can't...
Oh!
They can't hurt you if you go on the rock.
They can't do a thing.
If you're on the floor, these guys will knock you over
and take a big chunk of your health.
Is something else attacking me?
No.
But we're good to go.
Robin Williams plays a bat in this.
Fair and golly is basically the Barbie Pixie...
The Barbie Pixie movie in 2D, but human...
What?
And humans are bad guys.
It was a good movie.
The direct to VHS sequel was...
Okay.
Tim Curry sings.
Oh my god, Rocky Horror Picture Show.
You put your hands on your leg.
No, that's not right.
You put your hands on your hips.
That's it.
I find a dance inside.
We should watch that.
My mum really likes that movie.
So I've watched it from a young age.
Yeah, it's absolutely bizarre to conceptualise
what on earth happens in that movie at a young age.
But hey ho!
That's just life.
That's just how it is.
We're going to...
Oh!
I heard.
Butta dog.
Dog with a butta.
I heard that.
And mama.
Get your butt to the top of that.
I want that.
What are you doing here?
I'm so tainy.
Oh no, I'm so big.
POV, you're Azura?
You're talking to Azura right now.
This is the hate difference between you and Azura.
What's going on?
I'm shutting down the knob.
It's Emmy and Azura.
Oh, we Emmy.
A giant woman.
No, don't lie.
Don't lie right now.
And say to me, I didn't cook with making Azura a giantess.
I will not take...
Right, if that's not going to hurt me,
I'm actually just going to leg it.
I'm legging it, boys.
We're doing it.
Oh!
Wah!
Right, we're just going to stealth through this section.
There's a lot of dire wolves.
Eh, viper wolves.
However, we're no interested in fighting.
So, we're just going to zoom past
because this entire section is optional, honestly.
We're just going to zoom ahead again.
Cooked.
You did indeed cook.
No, I knew I wanted some sort of thick Vtuber model.
I'm sorry, I'm going to say it.
There's really not that much variety for the thick
and for the chocolate.
So, it was just absolutely no questions asked.
Probably going to do the same in Gen 2
where, you know, something's going to be lovely in Gen 2.
Brian!
Didn't expect Sigourney Weaver to side
with the Navi considering her history with aliens.
Is she the main...
Is she the main alien?
Because I remember reading a really...
Oh, we're on a horse, by the way.
Check it out.
Look at my horse.
My horse is amazing.
Oh my God, its face is all...
That's a really unfortunate face.
Everything else, yeah, that's all right.
Look, I'm riding a pony.
I'm such a girl.
Oh my God, this is the girls game as well.
Oh, no.
Oh, there's actually really...
This is really boring,
but when we come back to this section later,
an enemy always spawns on this rock
and he's infinite stuck and you can never, like, hurt him.
Okay.
It's time.
We need to make a decision.
Are we Navi?
Thank you very much, Iron Reaper, for the tip.
I think I actually forgot to say that, but thank you for the tip.
Are you squiddin' me right now?
Nero!
Speaking of, how tall is Stacy Milketon?
Thank you, Nero, for the tip.
So we are a signal specialist
and we've set those signals up,
but we were told that they weren't gonna...
It wasn't gonna be used for destroying Navi.
Nori, nori.
Ah!
So we're learning we just destroyed all the Navi's home.
It's work.
Are we the baddies?
Raider?
Hardly even nor.
Oh wait, sorry, sorry, hold on, do that again.
Raider?
Hardly even nor.
Come on, how goofy is that?
I wanted to see...
Raider, are you ready?
Are you ready?
We're gonna do it again.
Okay, hold on, let's do this bit
and then when we're mucking about I'll do it again, okay?
That was amazing.
Right, so this is where you decide.
Do you want to be Navi or do you want to be RDA?
If I shoot him, we become RDA.
If I shoot him, we become Navi
and defend this Pandora
in the name of being a foreigner.
We need to kill it.
We guys first go.
Destroy him.
Just...
Oh, I'm low health.
Oh my God, I'm farting about too much.
Oh, why is he so strong?
Right, go.
Wait, I'm actually gonna get...
I think I'm actually gonna perish.
He's like actually wrecking and decking me.
What's going on?
Why is his health not going down?
Why is my aim bought so bad?
Right, hold on, hold on.
Hold on, let me aim bought.
He healed up!
No, no!
Only I'm allowed to heal up.
The enemies shouldn't be allowed to heal up.
It should be illegal in video games.
Development team, you have failed.
It should be...
Why is he only shooting me as well?
Can you like shoot that other guy?
Right, hold on.
Let me readjust this aim bought.
No, he healed up!
Only I'm supposed to be healed up!
Right, that's it.
Grim pound!
It didn't even work.
Did it work?
I don't know.
I'm gonna be honest.
This is a few too many bullets are going through you.
I spoke too many bullets.
Sudden darts.
He survived all those bullets.
I gotta go now.
Grab your dire horse.
Dire horse?
Banshee!
Ik-nee-ma-ya.
Ik-nu-ee-ma-ya.
No idea who I'm supposed to see.
Ik-nee-ma-ya.
Sounds like I'm trying to say something in the dark.
The RDA doesn't do anything piecemeal.
Ik-kawanyo?
It's not Ik-kawanyu.
Got anything better than bows and arrows?
They defend their homeland.
Those are the only weapons they need.
Great.
Good choice, Ryder.
Ik-nee-ma-ya.
That's what I'm saying now.
Couldn't humans kill the main guys?
Human body in the machines?
Yes.
That's very true.
But it was arranged that the...
Look out!
Oh, look out!
We stunning on them.
Look at this.
Got a little outfit of the day moment check.
Come on.
Look at my jewel-wield blades.
That's so cool.
Oh, how did I hit?
Come on.
That's so cool.
I'm sorry, but look how cool that...
Oh, my God!
That's terrifying.
Imagine that running at you.
Oh, I just cracked myself right there.
Your avatar isn't blonde because blonde doesn't exist in Navi.
I don't think...
Maybe it does.
I don't know.
I don't think I've recall seen a blonde Navi.
Oh, no.
I do in the different regions of...
But we are jungle Navi.
This is jungle Navi.
There's different types of Navi.
Or jungle Navi.
Sadly, not closer to your level plus.
We need to win his approval.
Oh, my God.
She's so real for that.
That's...
Okay, we need to try and get the approval of this guy.
Why?
I've already forgotten the plot, but we're going to do it anyway.
But basically, we are full Navi right now,
and I'm going to tell you something.
Okay, this really is a girls game,
because every time we go to the next location,
we unlock new outfits as we level up,
and I get to like play a little wardrobe simulator.
Such a girls game.
That's such a girls game.
Yeah, he ain't happy at all to see me in.
Oh, I need to be able to raid a Banshee or an Ikran.
That's what they're called.
Oh, my God.
Blanky.
Hold on.
I need to get what's the link,
because I'm hurting my legs against the table.
Ooh.
Did I just skip dialogue down that?
Oopsie daisy.
New outfits.
Let's go to the next area.
Oh, my God.
Fashion Simulator.
We played Landlord Simulator on Brotherhood.
Now we're playing Fashion Simulator on Avatar.
Right.
We are about to learn a motherfucking bow and arrow.
Oh, did not mean to do that one.
Let's try that again.
Pardon me.
Excuse me.
That was very daft.
I just absolutely threw myself off the mat there.
How does zooming on the bow and arrow again?
Not that one.
Oh, wow.
It's just hold and release.
Okay.
Who would have thought?
It's just holding release.
The Navi's drip is indeed real true.
This game seems surprisingly competent, actually.
I was doubting.
I get game.
It is.
Honestly, I get game.
Wait.
What am I doing?
Oh, we're doing our first human kill.
Oh.
Yeah.
The aim is very forgiving.
If you want an easy game.
Definitely recommend this game.
The bow and arrow is very satisfactory.
But I'll tell you one thing though.
Oh, look at this camera.
Look how terrible this camera like pings off of different.
Like you can see the markers of where they put the tracking to do that.
Like it's not smooth.
Like.
Oh my God.
Who goes there?
Identify yourself.
I need to jump.
First human after killing two low level.
So actually true.
I just recalled that.
Really, really willy nilly killing over here.
Any willy killers?
No, don't.
This is another armor we kind of get to unlock about later on.
It's not quite the same.
But here we speak to bar a word for it.
I hear you betrayed your own kind to be here.
Yeah.
How soon will you betray us?
It will take more than this offering.
The scale of the arrows are massive they are.
Like Navi are so big.
So there wasn't a big tree in the game?
Oh, we aren't at the end of the game yet.
You just hold on to that thought.
You're a couple of missions ahead.
But I like doing this.
They don't disconnect us for treason, honestly.
She wants the braid tails?
What happens if we braid tails with each other?
Is that like a marriage proposal?
Is that Navi?
We braid each other's?
He will not show it.
Oh, that's his wife?
Come, we must destroy Sky Tower.
We find these.
How will you say?
Take care.
Will you help us?
These boxes are explosives.
TNT?
Yes.
We have word for this.
Kangangang.
Oh, that's so satisfying to say.
Is that a TNT?
Kangangang.
I messed with that.
You can flip into the waterfall to get down here a bit faster
than going all the way around the map.
I will heal.
I shouldn't have done that.
I thought you could slip down without too much.
Oh, you have 50 bow.
And every time you get a sample,
you replenish your bow and arrow ammunition.
So all those green is more bows.
Genghis Khan?
Okay.
You're done.
Excuse me.
Pardon me.
Coming through.
You guys can't aim.
Oh, I can't aim either.
It's fine.
Okay.
I think because my keyboard is registering.
Hello?
Okay.
I think because my keyboard is registering,
the aim assist isn't being as active as it is normally
on Xbox.
Because I could have sworn I didn't even have to aim.
Conta.
Jeez.
They just disappear.
Okay.
We seem to get either 5 or 10 arrows from samples,
which is pretty good.
I would say that's pretty good.
Kangangang.
Hans was simulator, actually.
I prefer the born hours myself,
but I'll tell you something that's really sad about this game.
As we level up,
our equipment also becomes stronger in nature.
Okay.
However,
if you did not purchase the special edition,
which they made about 1000 copies of for some unknown reason,
if they didn't do the special,
if you didn't buy it,
your bow does not one-shot the enemies as you level up.
It is complete nonsense.
They made only so few copies.
I was like,
oh, do you see how that flower attack is attacking them
and they're taking poison damage?
So unfortunately,
our bow and arrow,
I can't even see them through the...
Bra, why are you missing?
Bra.
You do heal over time naturally when there's no fight,
so you don't always have to spam heals.
What's this?
What's that?
Ammo.
I thought my ammo...
Whoa!
Wait, what do I have access to?
So dual wields,
one big ass swing,
a gun and a bow, right?
I normally just stick the bow.
Very good.
Very good, very nice.
But overall,
game is very forgiving.
If you're ever interested,
we should do that,
but that comes later.
We'll always come...
Oh!
The acran just said bye to that.
I'm pretty sure they would have got mowed over,
but like,
as long as they're happy,
I'm happy.
So right now,
we're picking up our boom boom Genghis Khan.
Do you mind?
Where did you come from?
You weren't even there.
You're such a liar.
You're lying.
Where are they?
I hear them.
Snipe,
and not snipe.
I am low health.
That's okay.
We're gonna heal up like that.
She can heal up.
And then we're just gonna move.
Oh, we're not gonna move on to the next section.
We're gonna go invisible.
Oh, no, we're not.
Can you still...
I don't know if you saw that.
Those flies were attacking him.
Like literally,
Pandora is so nice to you when you're napping.
I love it.
Oh, I hear them.
Oh, so these are bombs
that fly into you.
I'm pretty sure I heard a guy's voice though.
I'm like 99% sure.
I heard a guy saying they're out there,
but I didn't see it.
I love the way you say jaw wield.
Oh, no.
Wait, does it say differently?
Jew...
Jewel wield?
Jewel weel.
Jewel.
Pandora thinks humans are an infection.
They are.
They're terrible.
When you play RDF,
it's just as truly similar.
Oh, that's hilarious, honestly.
It's such a good game.
Such a good game.
I love this game so much.
The only complaint I have about this game,
it was made when games like to do...
Why?
It's like I have to aim a little to the right.
I do.
I've aimed a little to the right.
We can go down or up.
My memory says up, question mark.
Jewel wield.
Well, my memory was correct.
Oh!
He got a little ambitious
for trying to hurt me there.
Where is this?
It's up there?
Oh, it might be up there.
Whoa, I just spotted you in the corner of my eye.
Yeah, these are literally...
You know, I don't know what they're called.
Those bombs that are for submarines under the water.
I don't know what their name is,
but that's what those are, but in the air.
Oh, I missed.
Yeah, the aimball in this game,
working!
Aimball, please!
Wait, he didn't perish?
Jeez.
It looks like they're...
Oh, we need to shoot that.
Hold on.
Wait, do we actually?
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
Don't remember this part of the game, geez.
What's the rocks for?
Am I to destroy these?
No way.
Yeah, so I'm using bullets too.
Un-ball, un-mort.
More like, sent-ball, un-mort.
Why? The aim assist is not like me.
I'm not actually going to claim that tree of nature.
That's what...
The travel point, because...
Holy crap.
Oh, no, I don't have unlimited ammo!
Bruh! I thought I had unlimited ammo!
Jeez.
What did that do as a child that made...
It really must just be the aim assist.
Because I think if you all one-shot everything,
there's like no way this stuff is even hurting me half as much.
Oh, I missed.
I shot, and I missed again.
And then I shot, and then I missed again.
And again.
I don't know how to unshoot.
I can't pick up ammo from that.
I can only pick up ammo shells.
Honestly!
Let's see if we can get away with this.
Because we just need to pick up the package and then go.
Oh, wow.
Okay, cutscene time.
Cutscene time!
Whoa!
Gang, gang, gang!
Gang is gone!
Okay, let's get the heck out of here,
I don't want to get hurt anymore than we need to.
I heard that belief and I was going to go for it.
I think we're about to get on her screen.
Long story short, I missed.
Yeah, I missed again.
And then I shot.
And then I missed again.
Thumb arrived.
Alright.
Okay, we're about to climb.
Climb, climb, climb, climb!
Yeah, I think the campaign mode is roughly 7 hours.
We could probably come back in 100% the sectors.
And we can also play this mini-conquest game,
which actually I really enjoyed as a kid.
But you have to do it at the end of the game
for like 100% success rate.
There are Viper Wolves ahead,
but we're just going to be cheeky and do this.
And then we completely negate
even having to fight a lot of them.
Unfortunately, invisibility...
No, invincibility is when they can't hurt you.
Invisibility is when they can't sneeze.
It doesn't last forever,
but as we level up...
Like...
Oh, actually we're really close to leveling up.
I don't know if I should...
I don't want to hurt the wolves.
I don't want to hurt the wolves,
but I'll kill the humans, no problem.
Yeah, no, that's fine.
That's fine.
Yeah, that thing, that thing.
It's friendly fire on.
No, you cannot hurt other navi
now that you're a navi side.
I assume it's the same if you pick RDA.
Oh, good snipe.
Okay, if I can take my time to properly aim.
No, I think I was out of range.
There is a range to your attacks.
Like, you can't...
Oh, well, I just suck.
There we go.
There is a range distance to your attacks.
I cannot for the life of the human.
Am I to go this way?
No, classic dead end.
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
Mom, get the camera.
Play of the game, honestly.
Did you guys see that Marvel Superhero,
like 5v5?
I hear a bomb.
I see a bomb.
Um, um, um, um, um, um,
I really don't want the bomb to get me.
Oh, I'm already out of in this.
And the bomb is chasing me.
Okay, we're doing it.
We're just going for it.
We're committing.
Did anyone play it?
Marvel rivals.
Yeah.
It looks so good.
Everyone was, like, dogging on it,
but I'm like,
oh, I actually really enjoyed the look of it.
Uh,
I'm installing the game now
just to kill the Navi.
You know what?
You're done.
I'm definitely going to play
Marvel Overwatch when it comes out.
Yeah, and then wasn't there
not another company
that came out with another
Overwatch-style game?
I think it was Marvel.
It was a company that came out
with another Overwatch-style game.
I think development teams
literally watched, like,
the mess up in real time.
I don't know if that thing's still chasing me, but,
um,
there is another one.
Yeah, like Scarlet Witch
with Moira and all that.
Yeah.
I used to play a lot of Overwatch.
I actually really enjoyed the game,
but I just don't play it anymore.
Like, I don't find it rewarding,
or,
which is such a shame,
because I've poured
a lot of hours into that game.
Um,
but I would absolutely love
if we could do Marvel rivals together
as, like, a stream snag game.
Like, um,
I don't know how the accounts work,
but I'm, like, 99% sure
I can make a dummy account,
and then, like,
add users' friends,
and then make note of who's, like, played,
and then just rotate between,
like, kind of what we...
Oh, here we go.
Level up.
What did I unlock?
Let's see.
Uh, Bam Knee Pack.
We have a club weapon with frickin' spears on it,
or another type of RDA gun.
Oh.
And a shot.
And a missed.
Oh, and a missed again.
I can hear an enemy.
I don't see him.
Oh, there he is.
That wasn't him that said that.
Oh well.
Whatever.
Um...
Blizzard is horrible with their IPs yet.
Time to go back to Team Fortress 2.
Honestly?
But I'm sh...
I could have sworn I saw another development team
come out with something that was similar
out to the format as well.
So I think, literally, everyone watched,
uh, Overwatch 2 come out,
and as soon as Jeff Kaplan left the development team,
I think everyone behind the scenes
knew what on Earth was up
and knew it was, like,
essentially gonna flop
due to the, uh,
change in...
gameplay.
But when Marvel Rivals does come out,
uh,
because I think it's in beta right now,
or...
I may be wrong,
um,
I'm happy to make a dummy account.
We'll make it a multiplayer game,
and, uh,
we'll just kinda...
uh,
add in,
I think it's 5v5,
so it means four reeflings of myself
can play at the same time
against, uh,
just randomers.
Um,
we'll, like,
play actual public match games,
uh,
unless you guys
really wanted to go against each other.
I'm not sure having me and your team
will be a good idea though,
cause I'm not very strong at the game
cause I've yet to even play it.
Um...
But if that's something you guys
are down for,
I'm heking down for it as well,
uh,
obviously,
we'll
remove everyone
at the end of the gaming session
and restart fresh.
As I said,
it'll be
pow!
I saw that,
I don't know if I'm
gonna get ahaaa!
Right,
I'm backing off,
I'm backing off.
I don't think
down yet. No. That part comes later on. I didn't know. I'm gonna pick this up. Team
Landers, Johnny. Oh, should I tell everyone what to do? Protect me, heal me, heal me.
I used to play Zarya, which is an offensive tank. Over what? Oh my god, they're so beautiful.
The music's changed. Oh, they're so beautiful. The ikran. Look at them all judging me. Oh,
that's okay. You can judge me. Look at them. They're so pretty. Hello. Please don't attack
me. They're so beautiful. Oh, oh, oh, oh. Please understand. This game's a little old, which
is why they're all the same color. Please forgive. Please forgive. But I assume the new avatar is
like really beautiful. And my ikran literally almost made me perish and then said, yeah,
all right, I'll pick you up. I got pranked by it. I literally done a little pranky on me.
A little pranky-wanky. Oh. No. No. It's not a good look, honestly. I mean, you would really choose
match over Mecha over the big birdie. Exactly. Why would you pick? Oh, look at us. We're so
lying. There's no an RDA that will leave alive because the resource destroying the Pandora.
Oh, I love fly. Oh, ow, ow. Sorry, your wing, your wing. My apologies. Sorry.
I didn't mean to hurt your wing, little Banshee, but thank you for being so forgiving.
But we're just flying through the map now. Banshees have an insane HP. We will be shot at as we go
around. I don't know if you read that really quickly. It said lifting the fog 50%. Don't worry.
Oh, we really need to get some height. Oh, I'm going to do a little cheeky 360 to get that
height there. We are about to reach the ceiling in this game. Oh, all right. Climb. Climb. Jeez,
this map has a lot of verticality. Definitely did not remember that. But yes, there was a
sector challenge that says lifting the fog. There's a few sector challenges. Depending on how long
the campaign takes, we might actually just 100% all the sections. Oh, excuse me, game.
I know for a fact I flew over that. Would you like to register me flying through this?
No. Oh, okay. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Women moment. All right. Hold on. Hold on. Lady drive.
Okay, there we go. There we go. You got it in the end. I'm sure this is like really beautiful
cinematic if you do. Oh, we got it. Okay, but we're hitting that rock. Sorry. Sorry. Sorry. Look,
the camera angle isn't, it's not that easy to freaking dive, dive. All right, then go up,
go up, go up. Hey, there we go. But yes, Banshee are a really good way to get around these maps.
Whoa, easy, easy, easy. And we are back to the start where we started. Look at us going.
Isn't that beautiful? Okay, I am going to say before we start this next quest,
there is a voice line that repeats consistently through this mission. I will try to get through
it as fast as possible. It is so annoying. It is so annoying. Genuinely so annoying,
horrifically annoying. Unless this isn't the mission.
Don't say that.
Maybe this isn't the mission I thought it was.
And where are the turkeys? Audio bugs are the worst. Is that Ubisoft game? It has to be.
The, the animals slowly regretting letting you drive them, honestly. Okay, no, it's after this
mission. They're really annoying when pops up. What did we unlock? A crossbow and some sort of
ability. Hold on. How do I open that? Skills? Kinetic dash, Ewa's breath, Titan bash I don't
really use. We could maybe replace it with, Calls of Hyperwolf to your side. It'll fight for you
for a short time. That's pretty cool. Honestly, bees, death by bees. Right, here we go. What the
heck am I supposed to do? I completely forgot. Right, we're going to raid or a crane. Can I go on you?
Okay, look. Oh, he's going forward. I never really,
Hey, Ostrone, I'm off to work. But if the stream ends up being a bit longer,
then I should be back in time. See you after work. Hope to catch you there.
Thank you, tiny spiny. I appreciate the tip. And yes, um, I did look it up. I said the game
takes around seven hours to complete. If we come back and do section stuff that wait,
that where am I? That land? I think I'll land up here. Yeah. Okay. It looks like I'm definitely
to land to keep that crane safe up here. You stay there, buddy. You be nice and safe. But
yes, have a good day at work. Thanks for hanging. I appreciate it. And I appreciate the tip too.
I'm not to say donations because it's not a donation. It's a tip.
Actually, I don't know if I'm supposed to update the girls as things to be like,
you know how you're supposed to put like a disclaimer on like the freaking thing in case
someone does a charge back. Right. I'm 99% sure these guys just keep respawning. So I'm actually
not to fuss. Do you mind? Thank you. I'm not to fuss for completely clearing up the section.
Oh, it's a bomb. It's a bomb. Okay, there we go. Let's go up. Is that about to like blow up right
next to me? Oh, I didn't. Oh, no, we didn't kill guys don't look at explosions. You know the drill.
Okay. You know the drill. Kill guys don't look at explosion. Well, you mean stream,
elements is intact. I like some if someone does like a thing, a disclaimer for charge right would
be I'll probably edit the motor then or when I get off. I don't know. I get tired. I get tired
after screaming. Okay. Oh, I have a fantastic update for scripts. Oh my goodness. So the script
manager now has access and is taking over and look. So everyone has a four part series coming out
like a story that kind of progresses. Sheeby's four part series is currently being written right
now. I'm not trying to say anything, but good luck trying to hold it together when she performs that
script. Because wow, I was blown away. I'm like, there's definitely like something to be said about
like a guy writing a script versus like what I could write because I just like I like challenging
myself and in general like I know what overall you'd like us to say type thing. But I have to
admit I was like, oh my god, there's not going to be any anything left in the sack after that one.
And that was part one I read. I didn't even read the finalized series of it. And Azur's one is being
worked on next. Oh my god. Sorry. I didn't I wasn't paying attention to like how many bad guys are
there? Right, we're going to watch the explosion this time because we can. What's the explosion look like?
Okay, it was just kind of out of control. Oh no, the tower does go down. Okay, I like it.
I wonder if we can get some XP for destroying this. Ow. Okay, we can get XP for doing that.
I think, why didn't? Azur's story, I don't I don't know if I should ruin what the story is. Like,
I don't want to like tell stuff that's kind of like exciting for the girls.
But like, I like the four part series ideas, like Emmys one I really like. No, don't spoil it. Okay,
I won't spoil it. Um, oh, there's a home tree right there. Actually, I don't know if I should grab it
the now. Actually, no, I have access to the Ikaran to fly around the map. So it's not going to be that
a deal of us coming back. Newbie would begin a work is a lot. Yes, I like so now that like the
scripts are no longer my problem, I get to focus on making the girl short. So Mercy came out with
a short and she was like, do you do you think I should have been blonde Senpai and showed like
behind the scenes artwork? I'm going to get everyone to do that to show their concept art like me as
well. Actually, I need to write the scripts. And like, I get to work on that kind of fun stuff
instead of kind of like being stretched too far. Like, it's too easy. It's too easy. I'm not even
going to say it's that easy. Um, you can go as well because you were shooting my crime. You're
not supposed to shoot my crime. Um, literally, spoiler channel is always looking for literally,
uh, just I get so excited about everything that's planned behind the scenes that I'm like, oh,
I don't want to ruin it for the girls. Oh, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow,
here, here, here, here, sorry, sorry. I'm too busy rambling. I'm not even actually focusing on the
dang game play. Wait, oh no, we don't want shot them anymore. They've gotten too strong now. That's
the problem. If you don't like, um, farm XP, you will fall behind. Concept art was great to
see. Yeah, so I get to like kind of do that fun behind the scenes script stuff like the shorts
for the girls. Um, um, also super gracious thank you to everyone who is using YouTube clip feature
for the girls. Um, if you didn't know, if I go on their stream, I can see who and what has been
clipped. I just want to say, uh, there's actually quite a few people who are clipping my burps at
the moment. I might unironically make a 15 minute burp compilation just for the heck of it and call
it like scrawny burps for 14 minutes and 53 seconds. Uh, and just for the heck of it because
it seems to be something, uh, a few, uh, gentlemen seem to enjoy and you know, I'm not here to ruin
anyone's day. Uh, but yes, please do consider clipping. We have a really funny, uh, short of
icy coming soon. Um, our second clipper, we're kind of testing them out. I don't have a problem
because I've already actually got extensive clip history, but they're busy at the moment. So the
clips are a wee bit slow to be produced. We're getting there. We're getting there. So thank you
to anyone who uses a YouTube clip feature. Does help out any highlight moments? A short of icy
doing what? So it's already happened. So it's not a spoiler, but AC basically when,
in her adorable voice, like, I'm not very smart. And then she went, thank you so much, Mike, honey,
for donating to me and her adorable freaking accent. And I'm like, AC,
ACICAL. Should I have taught you that? Should I have said to you what that means?
So we're going to, we're going to get turned into a clip, not really sure on her thing.
But her accent is so freaking adorable. Okay, I'm going to bed. Rest well. See you in the morning
when you wake up, sweet dreams. I love seeing that. I love seeing that. Whenever you guys are like,
okay, I need to go to work or I need to go to sleep. I'm like, yeah, see you in the morning. See you
in the morning. Oh yeah, work or I'll see you after work. Yeah, yeah. Oh, you didn't go out
do some errands. I'll see you after that. I'll still be on. Right. This is the scene. The quote is,
Raider, you have got to get to higher ground. It will be repeated a ridiculous amount of times.
Yep. I remember the quote. I've not even played this game in many a year. Raider, you've got to
get to higher grounds. It will repeat. And I'm like, did no one play test this? Did no one see what
an issue this is? Because I've gone the wrong way. I've gone the wrong way. Oh, and I've hurt
myself. Let's hurry this up. Who's this section? Oh my God, imagine that coming at you. I would
actually be so terrified. Shawnee, you've got to get to higher ground. Honestly. Get that done.
Get that done. Right. We destroy one way.
Oh, I love it. Love it. Special. What's right? Oh, no. What's my special?
I don't know what button the special is, though. Yes, we spawn at checkpoint.
It's putting, it's giving me keyboard input, but I'm playing mouse and controller. Like,
I don't know if you can hear my analog stick. Right. Let's do that. Another try.
That was a bit daft. I do apologize for that MLG game. I'm going the wrong way again.
I can't all be good at video games. Literally, wherever nine year old me is inside my head right
now, can you like come and like help us out here? Because this is getting very good. It's getting
embarrassing. Right. I'm going to click the analog sticks this time to see if that's what the special
is instead. Right. Special analog. Nope. That's, uh, nope. That's scan.
What would R, what would R be? Am I literally, you know what? I'm just going to hit R and my
keyboard. Are you squinting me right now? Oh, Stronny, you've got to get to higher ground.
No, Anna, don't throw me. It's so, wait, why is this not breaking?
Is there a health bar? Oh, there is. Oh, is it glitched out? I can see that health bar,
that little green. What's going on? Thank you for the tip, Anna. Wait, I think it's glitched out.
This is an old game. Hold on. Let me do this. I'll do it with a bigger one.
Uh, game. Game, you're showing your time. I've never actually had it glitched out here before.
Right. I had to press F on the keyboard. I don't know what button I was supposed to press on the
freaking, I'm, I would, oh, I keep saying it. Literally, where do you've got to get to higher
ground? I literally F in the chat. That's, oh, oh, oh, you're getting whacked, mate. Oh, then you fall
now. Oh, he's hiding in the freaking bushes. Right, healing up, healing up, healing up. Don't
worry, don't worry. Uh, actually, I think these are much faster. Yeah, these are one shot. The
dual wield is one shot, but the long stick isn't one shot. Hmm, what does that mean?
Right, okay, we're just going to press the keyboard. We're literally just switching
between the keyboard and the ticket thing. I don't know what I'm supposed to press.
Get whacked for free, must be nice. Is that the honor you should be watching by any chance?
Hmm. Uh, right down we go. I don't know. Are you squiddin' me right now?
Virginia! Have you considered getting to higher ground?
Stop! No, I'm getting trolled! Thank you for the tip, for so. He repeats it so much,
but he's not doing it right now. I wonder, because I don't know why he's not repeating it,
but I kid you not, he constantly repeats, you have got to get to higher, you have got to get to
higher ground. Over and over and over and over. But, uh, I think we're actually being given,
oh, objective. The classic three and done in video games. If Aintbroke don't fix it,
do this thing three times and you win. Delicious. Delicious, delicious, delicious.
Love it. I love it when game devs get the memory. Oh my god, I'm inside that! I'm inside it! Leave
alone! No! Oh no, I'm a... Oh, that's not good. I'm having a seizure.
Home tree! Oh, wait a minute. I think I might have died and now I'm at home tree and I'm about to be
spiritually be a navi. Like, yeah, spiritually. I'm like physically about to be like 100%
navi if I remember correctly. Oh yeah, that's right. Oh, I can feel myself connecting with nature.
Oh, I should...
Are you with me right now?
Wah!
Heck yeah, speak for the trees. Thank you, Tim Shotol. For the tip. I can never say that
name right. Shotol. Ah!
Eh, AWA just resurrected me and AWA's word is truth, so I will not be taking any contesting
points that I'm no a navi anymore.
Actually, I really enjoyed the second Avatar movie because what's her name? The one that
is Sigourney Weaver as a child? I really like her plot line.
Eh, that she's like, can commune with AWA? I really like her.
Avatar Stoney has an arrow under her hair!
There's a second Avatar movie? Yeah, it's called Way of the Water.
Did you not get advertised on anything?
There's a second Avatar movie. It's out right now. I may have just spoiled it for you. I apologize.
If I was home tree, I would tell Stoney to...
If I was the home tree, I would tell Stoney to... I don't know what he want.
What are you on about? What are you on about?
This is a spiritual location. You can't loot the home tree.
Okay, I say that as if there isn't a Gen 2 concept right now that may or may not have
have some nun influence.
You cannot do any activated mission things. Oh, it's the guy!
Nothing but more than pure digging.
My new abandoned name.
Advertising for the second movie was a booze ball.
It still did really well, did it not, if I'm not mistaken?
Are you underestimating the power?
You acting like the tree? Well, it's the Holy Spirit of Navi.
Okay, we are going to Swatulu. Anyone else visited Swatulu?
Maybe on spring break you went to Swatulu?
Yeah, they are absolutely wrecking this place.
This is not... This area is definitely getting absolutely wrecked.
I just remembered what happens in this area. I'm like Nightmare Potenture.
Very good location because something very cool happens.
We aren't searching for the dormant site.
No, actually, I think it's a later level, you know that?
Anyway, it's cool.
The first movie itself was already advertised enough for the second.
That's probably what they said.
That was really outrageous writer, I'm going to be honest.
Saying no hablo to a Navi. I don't know, that felt a bit weird to me.
I don't think we should let that one slide.
That was... That was motivated. That was motivated.
That was bizarre.
And if you're literally fully Navi, you're not going to put effort into speaking Navi?
We're going to unlock the home vision tree. What the heck is that?
Oh, it's a tree of vision. Oh, it's a sector challenge.
Am I crazy or was there a horse I could ride back here?
Thank you, child, me for remembering. Oh my god, I'm actually so smart.
What are you? You're just menacingly guarding this horse.
Can I just take it? Thanks mate, appreciate it.
There are RDAs, but the beautiful thing about these parts of the map,
you can ignore it. You can just zoom ahead.
This is one of those games where if you want to take your time and explore it,
you most certainly can. But if you just want to be like,
right, I want to do the objective. I don't want to leave the horse in the middle of here.
What am I doing here? Oh no, I don't want my horse to...
Wait, investigate. Oh, I'm only to do a drive-by?
Oh, I can do a drive-by shooting all right. Don't mind me.
Oh, let's go.
Right, I don't think you can shoot well on horseback.
Sorry, dire horse. It's called dire horse.
But yes, I don't mind doing a drive-by.
Right, left or right? Both are terrible.
This one's a dead end, so do the dead end first and then come back for the open one
because it's likely that the open will be like the next progression.
Oh, my wee horse is getting injured.
Shattered village. Yeah, looks absolutely desolate.
Okay, I think the game's putting horses around the map in case we do end up losing.
Can you put like samples on horseback? You cannot.
Flex and then roll in arse. What do you mean you cannot roll your arse?
Can you not iterate what you wish to rock on?
I'll just start shoving ours and words that don't even have it.
Oh, my poor horse. Oh, it's a mech. It's a mech. It's a mech.
It's a mech. Oh, the horse is going to perish.
Oh, no, the horse is perishing this game. I don't like it here.
Let's get out of this place.
Is this the first game? It is. This is not the new game that came out.
This is the Archaic 2009 game.
Loongeree is not here. Where is Loongeree?
Loongeree, where are you, mate? I need to find Loongeree.
Any Loongeree fans? I'm a Loongeree fan. Oh, the horse is getting in.
Loongeree's gone to stop them.
With Unipee. That's right, Riflin.
Oh, Unipee's a person.
Oh, what did we unlock? Let's see. The Onatopak.
What is that? That looks like shards from the sky.
That looked cool. I've not actually summoned a horse.
What was that? Birds from the sky? Column Pandora to help strike.
Oh, my God. Hold on. What does it look like?
Oh, okay. Okay. Okay. Little baby. Little baby clangs.
Okay. Great. We can go through here.
Oh, I'm getting shot at. Or is he shooting at an NPC? I don't know.
Hello. Do you need assistance?
She just expired. I don't know. I don't even speak Navi.
I don't even know what her last words were. Oh, my God.
Her family's going to be like, what were her last words?
And I'm like, I'm so sorry, mate. I'm actually a skypey poll.
You're going to have to forgive me, but is there an enemy there?
No, that's a boss. Where's the enemy? That's actually really embarrassing.
Yeah, we don't know her last words because I'm a dumb dumb.
We're playing that. Hello. Are you okay? Are you squiddin' me right now?
Brian! I really like the second Avatar movie,
especially the scene where they destroy almost everything that was achieved in the first
True.
Okay, Iron Reaper, thank you for the tip. I'll admit, true. However, I present to you
Sigourney Weaver's second storyline, and that's fine with me.
I like that she's connected to Pandora, can control Pandora.
Okay, to Awa, and Awa grants her those abilities.
I don't think she's doing well. Are you going to expire after we finish talking?
Because I can't translate your last words to tell your to tell your family.
Oh, um, maybe you should expire because that's actually really great.
That's really rude. Please don't do that.
I need to claim. Please perish. Oh, my bow and arrow is not strong anymore whatsoever.
I used to one shot these guys. It's now costing two ammo.
Right, so what we have to do is just climb up these and then jump aboard when it comes
background, and then we destroy its receiving signal thing, which completely, um, okay, yeah.
Do you remember when we played Elden Ring and there is that chariot thing and you had to
drop down on top of it? Basically that. We just need to slowly wait for it to turn.
Yep, okay. And then when we get close enough, we just jump down.
Wait, can I not just, can I not shoot that with bow and arrow?
I feel like with their height difference, I could probably bow and arrow that.
Uh-huh.
Nope. Can't believe Elden Ring stole that idea literally.
Uh, right. I think that's just showing, I need to go up on this one.
What do you go up on this one? I can see it on the mini map that I'm covering up with my big
hair, but the mini map, I wish I could put the mini map in the other corner.
I'm always covering up the mini map when I play games.
Uh-huh. Hopefully doesn't bother you guys. I assume it's coming around this corner very slowly.
Something's trying to shoot up.
Are you coming? Hello?
Is it stuck? Am I out of its distance to move? Right, you, I can hear you shooting.
Knock it off. Stop moving. Oh look, the picture plant. Look, it's sending flies out to hurt him.
Death by flies. Death by flies. Oh, he's in. Did he come? I didn't know they could use,
no, come back. You need to perish by flies or by bow and arrow. Pick.
Fane. Okay, I'm out of the distance. Right, is this not, is it stuck? Why would it be stuck?
Oh, fane. I think we're maybe too early.
Watch it start moving when I come around this corner.
Yeah, I was kind of joking. I was actually joking, but I seriously did it. I knew that.
Where's the freaking bane? Where's the bane?
Moving again because I'm out of your render distance.
I am being pranked. I am being pranked. Wait, did it move?
Wait, that is it there. That's it right there. The render distance is broke.
Bro, it's going to start moving. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. Let me get up the dang thing.
Oh, that's literally the only song I know off by heart. It's actually really sad.
There is an anime called Avatar the Last Airbender and Uncle Iroh is an absolute beloved character
and he sang a really moving song. It's literally the only song I know off the top of my head.
But it's like beautiful sad, not like hopefully not too sad sad, you know?
I need to not bring that song up anywhere close to making here. We can not allow it to spoiler.
Has Emi not seen it? Please stop it. I'm going to cry. Okay, okay, okay. We pause. We pause.
I didn't realize there were bad guys here. Take this and this. Why am I taking so much damage?
I don't know. Have I unlocked a new outfit? No, I haven't.
Wait, do you see that stat increase though? So as we unlock new outfits, it's going to go up so much.
You mean you don't? I don't know Secret Tunnel off by heart. Secret Tunnel. What am I supposed to do?
I'm supposed to do something. Hold on. Ah, I see the blossoms.
Two lovers forbidden from one another. There's a mountain in the way.
And I kind of forget how this next part goes.
Secret Tunnel. Brian, I'm singing.
Emi's planning on doing it. So she's definitely support emu's when she does that. Definitely.
Thank you for the tip, Nero.
I kind of forgot how this next part goes. Can you guys put the lyrics in chat and then I'll like
sing it to you guys. Shawnee, why have all the Scottish people met? Also nice.
Why are Scottish people nice? Oh, we're just, we're just vibing.
Scotland, Glasgow's been rated one of the nicest. Oh, we've got level up. We've got level up in our
healing and our sprint. So are we like even faster? Oh, wow. Okay. Okay. That was a pretty
decent distance. Are you actually a blue guy in this game or are you a skin walker like the movie?
We have, our human body has died. It got annihilated via missiles. So yeah,
we're like, we're Navi now. We're just trying to get accepted by the Navi and to reverse the
horrific effects that I'm actually not very skilled at this bit. Oh, jeez, Louise. Oh my god,
they like ate my health up so quickly. So this is what I mean by you get a second chance.
I now have four second chances. Oh my goodness. Get right. He's perished. Oh my gosh, that was
right. He's off of it. I don't know if I need to like unironically XP grind or something.
I feel like I die. I think I'm okay. Where are we? Where are we? Oh my gosh.
I don't remember the game being so hard. Do you know that? I'm just getting over here like,
bro, I'm out. You don't need to worry about me. I'm gone. I'm in and out like a flash.
Call me you same boat. I'm gone. 10 seconds. No, not leaves from the vein. The other one,
the happier one, the two lovers one, not leaves from there. That's a sad one. Scots are nice until
you tear us off. Honestly. Oh my god. Yeah, I'm trying not me to. We don't want to be sad up in
here. Good times. Good vibes. Two lovers forbidden from one another and the moon ends in the way.
I have no idea what it is. Stroney, you just channeled some intense dark souls energy by spam
rolling away from the attackers. Honestly, though, I should probably pick up cell samples
because I ended up using two revives for that. I definitely need an armor upgrade,
because. Okay, ready to lovers forbidden from one another award their people
and a man and evades them apart. You must build a path to be together.
And I kind of forgotten how the rest of it goes, but secret tunnel, secret tunnel.
It's such a good song. There we go. A little sing song for you. A little karaoke before the
actual karaoke stream is planned. Have a look. I've got to stop. That will get stuck
in my head for months. Oh, do you want the Scottish version of it? So it's extra cursed.
Wait, someone refit the lyrics in again, and I'll do the Scottish version for you,
because I'm just so kind like that. Okay, so the one thing about close combat is the instant.
I said the instant die. Thank you. Right, Scottish version.
If someone puts the lyrics in chat for me, just so I can go. My brain's a little slow.
Two lovers forbidden from one another award evades their people and a man and Brian,
you're interrupting my singing, Brian. Well, I'm getting absolutely.
Award divides their people. All right. Oh, sugar. Thank you for the tip.
I'm getting too distracted. I forget the next couple of lines, but then it goes.
Thank you for tipping that. You didn't have to tip that. Thank you. I do appreciate anyway.
Right, right. Scottish version. Two. Wait, should I do really neasily, Scots?
Two lovers forbidden from one another award evades their people and a mountain divides them apart
and build a path a be together. Yeah, and I forget who the next couple of lines go,
but then it goes. Secret tunnel. Secret tunnel through the mountain. Secret, secret, secret,
secret tunnel. I think I need to go and visit for this next section.
Anyway, that's the Scots rendition. You're welcome for that on the house. Didn't even have to pick.
Why Bonaro? Why? I'll go invisible if I'm going to end up perishing, I think. Whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa. Okay. These turrets on the wall are my biggest enemies. Got a lot of enemies and it's
the turrets on the wall, not the actual thing. Strana, just had any idea for your outfit. What
about a version with all of your modesty plasters are replaced by nicotine patches, honestly?
What is going on? I don't, sorry, I really don't remember this section, so I don't know what I'm
up against, but I'm just going to take it slow. Not knowing we're taking it a bit slow. I'm just
a bit, I can see something over there. Oh, he's destroying the car. I see empty mechas.
What's that up there? Can I destroy these for XP? Hold on.
Oh, wow. Oh, I'm doing a task sector destroying empty mech. Oh, wow, they explode as well. That's
actually really good to know that they explode. Okay, there we go. I press X to do that, ultimate.
Strana, do I smoke? No, I just talk too long and my voice is fried. Do you need help with this?
You want to gang violence this car because you're like taking your sweet time. That's going to blow
up, bro. That's going to blow up. Oh, it didn't hurt him though. Oh, I get a lot of XP for doing
that. I don't know if we need to farm yet. If we get too weak, we'll farm, but at the moment we are
above the thingy. Watch out. I know what challenge to destroy something.
This looks very battle, don't ask, but I don't recall. I just heard an Ikram. I think that was an
Ikram. Is this the person we need to find? Because I don't think he's looking too good.
Are you okay? Yeah, you need, you need, oh, he needs some milk.
Right, I'm sorry. It was too obvious, right? That's how you get wrecked.
Don't want to get hit that much, but it's literally the best I can do. All things considered.
Okay, that special attack knocks them over. That's really good to know. Okay.
Heal, heal, heal, heal. Okay, that bought me time, that bought me time, that bought me time.
Okay, two out of three. Wait, that didn't damage me? That explosion didn't damage me.
Okay, let's go. Okay, okay, that wasn't that bad. I thought that was going to be like
insane battle door mask type stuff, but we're safe. Strony's inky milk. Strony's inks milky. Hold
on a minute. Someone, someone described my homemade yogurt as glippy. I have not forgiven
you for such descriptions since. Is there an enemy over here? Whoa.
The fricking, the, wait, how much do I have to redo? Because I was like deep in that. Okay,
I don't have to redo much. The plane took me away with it. I bumped away, man. I bumped away,
bro. As far as I'm aware, this game has infinite lives. I probably would never have finished it
if I didn't because, you know, I didn't make it. Glippy. Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
I didn't, that is so cheating. They have, they had pre-spawned in. Go away. You can shoot me through
that because I can't shoot you. I'm going to have to be in viz to claim up this. Oh my gosh.
Where did, where did they go? Right. I need to...
Oh, lovely. Okay, there we go. Yeah, I'm not one shot nothing.
Just so the screen isn't too red. There. Jeez, Louise. Oh, I almost didn't make that. Can I
destroy this? Oh, I can. Take that. I didn't get any XP for that. So
that's great. Something. Honestly. Oh, my Icaran's here. I thought my Icaran was going to come and
get me. Okay, it's because it's exploding. My Icaran is coming to get me.
Okay, let's see what we're working with. Whoa. I don't like that.
I messed up. I'm sorry. I even brought attention to my existence.
Please, please, please. I'm just a Navi. I'm just a, I'm just a sweet innocent Navi.
I'm sorry. I tried to pick on you, Mr. Car. I'm sorry. My goodness. That Warthog is powerful.
Oh my goodness. It was just a little arrow. My gosh. And let me up. Literally light them up. I
want that thing up. Blast it out of the sky. Oh my goodness. That was not good. Right. You're
standing up now. So you feel a bit better. Good. Oh, a great warrior. Oh, you were hating on me
about 20 minutes ago. Hmm. Don't think I, I didn't forget. You're, you're a little hatey.
Okay. Goodbye. Oh, I'm called Dreamwalker now. I'm no longer a sky people. I'm a dream.
So let me shoot an arrow at this armed vehicle. Look, I have some good ideas and I have some
bad ideas. That was a bad idea. Oh, oh, there's, what the heck is this? What did I do with that?
Oh, we got an unlock. What did we get?
I'll look up. Invis for longer. Oh, we've got a bow and arrow upgrade and a weapon upgrade. Oh,
look, her bow has changed. Look, it's a different design now. See, that literally
is such a cross game. Right. What am I supposed to do with these crystals? Excuse me.
I'm actually, here we go. I guess I'm to follow the crystals because it's doing the little light.
So, okay. It's to follow it. I was, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, okay. We're safe.
My goodness. I don't know what I need in order to survive other than an armor upgrade,
but those warthogs are so unforgiving. I was a mecha as I've unlocked now.
See, we're starting to get out of the tutorial where the game does not forgive.
Like the game will annihilate you if you don't like level up and stuff.
Oh, my horse is getting really shot out there. I didn't like that. I didn't enjoy that.
More enemies. It's impassable.
Oh, for God's sake. No, Mr. Horsey. Please do not. Wait. Gang violence. Gang violence. The horses.
Oh, no, my horse. Oh, my horse just perished, but I saw him attack on the leaf. That's two games
where the horse actually helps you. Okay. We're just going to have to take the rest on foot, sadly.
Oh, oh, do they attack me if I'm Navi? I feel like. Oh, oh, it's so beautiful.
Yeah, I really don't want them to attack me. I'm definitely picking up.
Rider, come in. I've only got a few seconds to talk.
Falco's gathering harmonics to find something called a well of souls. Well of souls.
You don't say. Falco's planning to use it to wipe out the Navi. I'll try to find out more.
I was hoping they didn't attack. I was hoping they didn't attack. Oh, I've gone the wrong way.
I'm getting too distracted. Oh, I don't want to hurt the whale blade. It just sucks.
Wait a minute. What did she call me? Raider? I hardly even know her.
Oh, you didn't. You didn't like that one? I guess. Yeah, I guess I repeated it. I'm sorry.
Yeah. Okay. I won't recycle jokes. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Is that? Oh, I can't see.
Okay, I'm sorry, but you guys are going to have to go.
I really wish they wouldn't attack. Oh, hello. Are you the person I need?
Man who is not man, a Navi who is not Navi. You are a puzzle, piece of Ewa's puzzle.
Oh, okay. I'm dreamwalking. Are we got an upgrade?
I thought no scrawny stream today. Are you sure about that?
She be a reminder. Okay. For those of you who are listening in are a part of the hair M.
She be cotton bum is going live in T minus.
Four minutes. She may actually be on the loading screen.
Eh, but yes. If there's any new YouTube mods lurking, you are welcome to speak,
but then I remove your speaking privileges instantly.
Class of 09. What is Class of 09? Have you guys played that?
scrawny streams never end. The return all hail the endurance cut off is.
As I play the Navi part, I did it later as a human.
Wrong. I've literally never done the RDA save. We will take. Oh, look how beautiful this is.
Literally glowing in the dark is just stunning.
Oh, could you imagine it with graphics that are updated?
Like, I have no idea what's in the new avatar game. Maybe we should play it for the first
time together, but I think it is as beautiful as this. Right. Why am I here? Oh, to get these crystals.
Okay, we're just going to ignore.
Because if we can just run in and out of these sections, if you hang around and kill anything,
yes, you will get faster XP. Oh, I don't want my horse to die. I'm so sorry. Oh, Mr. Horsey,
please don't die. Oh, no. Oh, no. Come on. We need to get out of here. Like right now,
I don't want you to pass away. I want you to have a happy life and retire at your old age.
Okay. And wait, this horse here is getting attacked as well. I was beating up that mech.
I was going to actually take it so this one can live its little retirement out. But
oh, I don't know if we're going to make it if they've got flipping flamethrowers and I've
got the wrong way because again, all turned around. Oh, please live, little horsey, please live. Oh,
no, the horsey is not going to. Right, that's it. We're clearing this. We're clearing this out.
Leave my horse alone. Everything is so strong.
Who? Who? Who? You, perish. Gosh. I don't have anyone to take out my special one.
Right, I'm healing because we're going to end this. Wait, I actually came out in your avatar.
Yeah, there's a new one. Didn't check it out. Yeah. I'm going to take more samples because
I've actually only got three. Wait, how far away? It's a wee bit away. It's a wee bit away.
All right, we are going to pick up cell samples just. No, my horse was still going to retirement.
You're so mean. Ow. Did that plant just smack me back?
Fine. My horse is already passed away. Man, he had a pension fund and everything.
Imagine working your whole life. Actually, I read a story about like that
where someone like worked their whole life and they got one week of retirement and passed away
and it was like, I would, I would be so mad. I would be so mad. I would explain to death himself
like, look, mate, I've kind of sweat my whole life. Dread Brian. By the way, I'm not sure if it was you
who asked, but it was someone invalid asked if the Black Ops two servers were fixed. Me. The answer
is yes, the servers were fixed, but bear in mind, it's still the Black Ops two servers. If you know
you know. I remember the game couldn't be played by streamers on the basis of like a super easy
to get like your IP going. But if they fixed it, honestly, Black Ops with the boys. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Have a little drink. Have a sipping tin. Thank you very much for the tip. Tarja, I appreciate that.
Yeah. Shawnee, the horse is only looking for three days anyway. Well, in Pandora, I'm going to hang
with sheep now. Yes, have fun with sheepsters. She's live with Class of O'Nane, which I actually
don't know what the good is about. Imagine had reals ifs that basically happened to. Oh, I'm sorry.
But yeah. Oh, we must draw harmonic from tree.
Oh, I think I know where this is going to go.
Oh, okay, that line delivery was a bit. No, long glory. No, we fling.
I will say one thing for the VAs of this game, especially for older games in the past,
odds are they had no idea what the scene actually had and they were just given a script and just said
like they don't know the depth of the script or what occurred. It was only until like recent
stuff like where actors can see live what they're performing. So follow the sound of vibrations
and find tuning points.
Okay, if there's three, it's probably going to be like identical. Yeah, okay.
Wait, hold on. Yeah, okay. And then the last one's going to be like right here
because of the way triangles work. Yeah, I love triangles. What's your yeah, yeah,
you know what? Favorite shape. I'm going to give it in our rectangle triangle or rectangle for favorite
shape. Oh, it's singing to me. Hold on. I feel like something mystical is about to happen.
I'm actually getting a bit scared. I just checked. Oh, no.
We must take this home back to home tree. It's a wooden delivery. Get it because of the trees.
It was a wooden delivery.
Oh, I came up with that myself came up with that comment myself. I'm so witty as a streamer,
aren't I? I'm just going to start stealing your guys's like witty comments and then doing that over
Oh, I have a new armor. New armor. Oh my god, girl game, girl game. Oh yeah, like the protection.
What is vitality? More health. I have more health overall because of the armor. Yeah,
well, you can see where they added more armor onto me. You have solved content creation.
Oh, that's proper harmonized. Yeah, good luck hitting them.
Armor barely covers anything. And honestly, like they are using right. We're going to home tree.
Wait, we're going back to home tree.
What? I'm about to report to them that. Oh, by the way, longer these dead.
I'm going to cry from that joke literally what cry of pain or just like just like how ridiculous
it was. Okay, we are going to be polite to Ewa and respect the home tree by not doing backflips
all the way up the trunk of the tree. Okay. Oh my god, it's tree balls. We love tree balls.
Let's just get very bright in here. I'm not going to lie.
Do I need to recalibrate? Hold on. I'm like a professional streamer. I think I need to recalibrate
my muscles. Okay, there we go. Recalibrating, meet your virtual, recalibrate it. Oh, yeah.
Sorry. Oh, we did actually report longer is passing. Okay.
You have the song. No, no, how but yeah, I scored the
not the thumbs up. That was so human of you. Please don't do that again.
A little tap on the shoulder. Sing.
What am I saying? Am I actually to say is this like a mini game where any like
what on earth is this freaky stuff going on here?
I don't even remember that at all. Thumbs up. Let's just try to come there.
It is the first step in our path. How many steps we got?
Find location is one step. Okay. Speaking to Ewa is another. Okay. This demands the need of a
the first voice. Only the first voice awakens well of souls. So this is campaign mode getting
explained to us. I totally know the plot inside out from this game. Yeah.
Assassin's Creed. I know the plot of this.
All I know is that we're doing good for the planet. Easy on the mumbo-jumbo stuff.
No, please, even if not directed at me, they hurt anyway.
What if the trees wanted to see a sick backflip?
Mission complete. Mission complete. Oh, not to jump around. Jump up. Can I put my weapons away?
I feel like having weapons out in this location isn't very pleasant. No, put the RDA gun on me.
Why is this so bright? I don't ever... Oh my god. I don't ever recall that issue.
Hmm. Oh, hello again. I would like to talk to you for my next mission.
We go to Toroknari. Toroknari.
I hear the human Thalco seeks your death. We will not let this happen.
You know, spending five years in cryo. Thank you, Tenjala.
War is new to this world. It must not happen again. Never on the enemy side.
But we're the goodies, so they're the enemy.
We're healing nature. We're healing nature. Mother nature always reclaims all. Mother,
mother, mother, mother nature. Oh, this looks like a dark room out. Beautiful.
Toph is the Marvel boy? I can't really do later voices like Toph.
Oh, Katana. Look, there's the castle. That's what I would say if I could see
something. If I wasn't blind. I can't really hear a voice at all.
Is it a castle? There's something in the sand or the library? There's the library.
Katana. Oh, sorry. It's not Katana. Sorry, sorry, sorry.
It's upside down, isn't it?
Katana? Close enough. I know. I know. Katana wins. Good luck, Tenjala. Good luck, Tenjala.
All right. Good luck, Tenjala. Hi. Oh, who's this? Hello. How do you do?
You come for shards. That must wait. Oh, I need a pause on the shards.
Post-trump on the shards.
A little cheeky hydration check. A little cheeky hydration.
There's the library. That's the way it would sound like the phone about the body.
Longer speak. Oh, okay. I'm going to say something controversial.
You know when maps are straight ahead like this? Yeah? I like that. I appreciate when games don't
make you go back and forth and you just keep going forward. When a game makes you turn around
to go do something on the map that you previously had that area.
However, when a game makes it nice and linear,
not going to lie, I almost fell off there. Oh, and I can't actually see where I'm supposed to go.
Thanks to this leaf. Oh, here we go. Backtrack. Hey, yeah, backtracking a bit.
Okay, let's see how it goes. Okay, so if you take the high ground,
wait, look, that's why they attack me. They've got backpacks on the wolves and that's why they
attack me. The RDA put like main control devices on the wolves and now they want to attack me even
though I'm Navi. I'm Navi and I'm navigating. What the heck am I doing here? Am I destroying stuff?
Don't have to ask me twice.
What am I doing? Challenge complete, right? I'm going to do it from up here. Oh, I see.
So I'm releasing the native Navi and destroying them. Jesus. Why? Yeah, we're like literally
so low level. We're not even one shotting. Can I break you? Oh, I can't.
I like how he just don't. Oh, he like dives over. I mean, honestly, if an arrow struck me,
probably. Oh, we did it. Like Ori in the blank forest.
I true. Wait, wait, wait. What am I supposed to do with that? Destroy it? I'm just going to pump.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa. Let me pump all the ammo into it. Where's my gun? I can't.
Yeah, your height, you're teasing me. I'm not even hitting you, bro. You're literally right under
the tree. I'm going to have to go. No, stop shooting me. I need to destroy this.
Hello. Oh, wait. Oh, wait. Oh, no. Game. Game.
Did I need to hit the other side of it, I guess? Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Okay, done. Jeez, Louise. They are killing us here. That was very strange, but we did it.
That's the main thing. Right here. We should not. Are you trying to shoot that guy and you're missing
like horribly? Oh, you are. Oh, and I'm missing horribly too. You know that both of us are as
bad as each other. He healed as I, bro, come on. Hello, would you like to talk to me?
Oh, I'll just keep talking.
Backtracking works if the map is good. Yes, I would argue yes. I did try and play Ori in the
blind forest, but I was just too paid to pay go. It's definitely not a stream game for me, but one
of the other girls most likely would play it. I feel like it's a, I definitely chill stream, chill
stream. Yeah. This is actually a really beautiful map because you get to run along the little tree
roots, which I really like. Yay, nature. Nature wins again.
Uh, right. I can see, and we're maybe fighting here or are we,
huh, are we just running through this? Oh, wow. We actually did pretty decent damage.
Yeah. Wow. I'll take that. I don't, I don't, I think that was just a payable drill haul.
Super. Are they cute? I can only, I'm okay. Hold on. I, it doesn't seem like an objective area
because of that reason. I'm just going to do this. I know I shouldn't. I know I should probably like
level up a bit, but I am very happy just to keep walking on the tree trunks.
You want a non chill stream? Place a list. I've seen a lot of streamers place a list. Like,
it's interesting to see what like, um, oh, I'm in trouble. Uh, oh, I'm in trouble. Oh, I'm in trouble.
Oh my goodness. I do not remember being in so much trouble playing this game.
What's the way? I think it's maybe I used to farm areas to level up and I was just so OP
because I think this map, we're actually supposed to be unlocking a green
armor right now, but I ain't doing it.
Apologize dude. Just doing some backflip, literally backflip dodge and bullets.
Right. We're getting ready to attack these guys, but I need to actually activate the quest by
talking to this guy before we attack and release more of Pandora's. Me?
How can I help? You would not like my answer. Listen, like it or not, you've got my help on this one.
String. The tattooed lord of sky machines with weapons.
Was it, I think for anyone who did actually watch the first Avatar movie,
I think scum means like idiot or something like that. Like scum. You have to go like scum.
Or else you're not saying it right.
Yeah, I feel like I replayed and leveled up a lot more as a child and right now we're just like
speedrunning through this. Although when you do complete a mission, you do get like a nice
chunk of XP. So speaking of leveling up, I have a six minute timer at the top of the screen.
That looks like a protection spell that I am putting on. I didn't realize I unlocked some
sort of protection thing. I definitely want to put whatever that is. Greatly reduces. Yeah,
okay. Yeah, we'll definitely be utilizing that right woman to do. Right, let's test this out.
I'm about to destroy the ship. Jump up here.
Hello. Oh wait, I can just, yeah. Is this what I'm supposed to destroy?
Oh yeah, okay, it is. Oh yeah, take that. You like that? Yeah, you're like a big adult. Oh,
am I going to get a blood raid because it's facing me now? I'm getting, I'm getting shaky,
I'm getting scared. Okay, we're fine, we're fine. Like honestly, smooth sailing. Okay,
the NPCs aren't really locking onto me too well because of the distance. But we're making it,
we're making it. They're getting a bit closer, so we might have to actually start shooting them
a wee bit, just a wee bit. Oh, that was a good shot there. One more, and then that's three of four.
You're telling me that quad aerial thing can stay up with three? I don't believe it.
One more, two more. I'm not hitting that at all. It's not registering. I'm just going to spam it
in. Am I supposed to go up?
Of course, the thing I want is like not facing me. Is this one in the corner?
Okay, there we go. Hey, wait, wait, I just, I'm looking at it.
Sound like a human iron birdie, I'm just saying. Literally. The steel a crann is no match for me.
I'm going to loot this stuff. I've got three revives. Oh my gosh.
Oh, the poor babies, they're not even attacking us. Out you come, baby. Wait, so, okay, it looks like
regular ones don't attack me anymore. Hello? Yes. I think we're going to raid him.
Oh, they're so cute. We're helping the little forest critters.
What do you need? I'm sorry, medications for the big guy.
Oh, just basic flowers. That's fine. I can get that. That's no problem. Hold on. Hold that thought,
little guy. I'm coming back. And then I think we get to ride him into battle like a horse,
but it's not a horse. I think it's called a Thanator. If I remember correctly. Oh my goodness.
I remember that time I said in this map, you don't have to backtrack.
Honestly, it's not that bad though, because it's to help an animal. And, you know, we
shadow wizard money gang. We love healing nature from these parts.
I'm going in. Oh, I'm getting sprayed and prayed, but they can't get me. I'm too good.
Gather plants from the banshee's nest. Oh, that's what that is. I suppose we'd be comfortable with
that. Pandora is Ohio, but more natural. You're not allowed to speak for the next 20 seconds.
Do you understand me? Don't say that again.
I'm so excited for your ace mushroom. I just want new earbuds for it. I hope it's not a
disappointment. I most likely will not do ear licking. I'm just going to say that now before
anyone gets thingied. I have no idea what an earth is going on with YouTube and ear licking at the
moment. Something, there's either a policy update being pushed or something, but for some reason anime
ear licks bad. In real life, human person ear licks fine. So I don't want you to be disciplined.
I have put a lot of thought and effort into it, so hopefully the Acemari is good. I don't know how
long I'm going to stream for. And the problem is I get really distracted when I constantly
read your guys' stuff because you guys make me laugh all the time. So I'm not really sure how
official an Acemari is going to be. I'll probably try hard for like 15 minutes and then it's just
going to... Oh, that's so cool. Has Ava gone mad? No, Ava has blisters.
Whiskers, honestly though. We whiskers. It's impossible because YouTube can't tell the difference.
That's my theory at the moment is that anime is getting... because YouTube are saying it's implied
else. Whereas we all know what actual ear licking sounds like because it's literally a 3D microphone.
So it's really put in a bit of a hindrance on my plans. Oh my gosh. Is this not the coolest ride
you've ever seen? Oh my god, it's so cool. Oh, he leaves. Can he go faster? Oh, he attacks.
Oh, that's so cool. Can he jump? Oh no, that's not jump. Oh wait, wait. Do I move as it moves?
Oh, oh man. Can you jump? Oh, I love him. He's so slick looking. Like genuinely so slick.
Not a hair on him. How do you keep warm? I'm fine. Like almost. Laughing was the highlight you'll be
fine. Come on, buddy. Come on, whiskers. Let's get him. Wait, am I going back? Oh, I'm just going back
to talk. It's just like, literally, it looks like he's been dropped in tar or the perv thing,
but it's just how he is. A little hairless thing. I don't like hearing this kind of stuff.
Okay. Why?
Do not speak like you understand. Why is she so informal when talking to this guy?
You have to pick your battles, B. This guy is speaking a second language. At least try and
speak clear English, you know? So it's easier for him. Danny, go back before it's forward. Okay.
There we go. You ready, whiskers? Oh, I did not mean to do that, but that was absolutely horrifying.
Right. Come on, whiskers. Let's get him.
Hopefully you have a lot of health, whiskers, because I'm not doing any combat at all.
Ah, whiskers. Can you go across this stuff? You can. Oh, you're actually such a smart kitty,
honestly. You're a smart kitty. Okay. I auto-jump if it's quite a... Oh, there's a
two, please don't attack, question mark. I don't think they attack me anymore.
Speaking of contact, the enemy's got a lot of enemies. Okay. We're all good.
Whiskers made it into a happy attack. There's another whiz... How many whiskers are there out
there? There's so many of them again. Bingoes. Some mate like the...
What is going on in the background?
Uh, cutscene moment? Cutscene moment, hello? Cutscene moment, hello?
Oh, I think I'm stuck in it.
Just absolutely chaos in the background, by the way.
Endgame... Oh, and we've got to level up as well. Right, we need to help out that whiskers.
Right, hold on. Leave whiskers alone. What's going on here?
Stop it. Wait, what's going on?
Right, I'm just going to do melee for the sticks. It's just so easy and quick.
Why no health? Why no health? I'm doing my spell. Am I supposed to be on whiskers?
I think I'm supposed to be on whiskers. Tear them up, whiskers! Tear them up!
That's right. Who's a good kitty? You're going to get some treaties after this.
I'm just going to do whiskers for the crazy in the background, honestly.
Just a reminder that Sheevee Cottonbump is alive if you care to watch classes all night.
Oh, this is so cool. Oh no, my kitty's losing health. I can't heal him.
Oh, baby. I don't want you to perish. I want you to have happy retirement.
Oh, there's no way kitty's going to deal with these mechs without being perished.
Unless I put him away. Right, you stay there.
Oh, my goodness. And I don't have my protection spell yet.
I don't have protection spell. I'm literally... Oh, kitty, I might need you back. Kitty, I might need
you back. Kitty, where are you? Kitty, you're saving me, kitty. Yes, knock them over. Yes! Yes,
oh, you're so smart. You're so smart. You're so smart. Oh, you're such a good party party.
Right, I do need to heal in a moment, but I think we're doing all right. What's going on here?
You're... You've glitched out and you're not even fighting alongside me, so that's fine.
Oh, the kitty... Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, heal, heal, heal, heal, heal, heal.
Oh, I've casted protection. I've casted protection. I did crash protection, but I was too late because
I healed first. I should have done it. Okay, okay, we can do that. This is super easy to get them.
Where are they? Where's all the ones? Where are they?
Two more? Oh, there you are. Okay, we're done. Oh, there's three more. I'm telling you, peppers.
Hopefully, the cat didn't die then. Okay. Actually, I'm gonna... Oh, wait, no, this is
okay. Right, okay. Yes, yes, yes, this turns to the corpus.
I cast skill issue, honestly.
Okay. Yes, we can do that. One more shard and then we do a song. A little song and dance.
Oh, I crammed. Oh, that is really rough. That was a rough landing with the animation on the
navi there. I have to admit, you're bending with the element there. Right, let's unlock the home
tree. No, not home tree. Tree of vision, which lets you teleport around the map. Yeah, it was
crunchy. That was crunchy. That was 2009 showing. I never know how long these bigger games take to
develop. I still think it's like three years development, two years development. This smallest
development game tank crunch I ever heard was Fallout New Vegas. That was like big like that.
I think they said it was 11 months development, which was crazy, all things considered.
Uh, I think we just walked the rest of the
Raider hardly even or anything else to brighten my day.
Okay, so I'll stop making that joke. I'm sorry.
It's a ticking time bomb. We can't let Fowler get anywhere near the well.
She's can't keep getting away with it.
Hey, am I supposed to find my Gornu? Are you feel health, kitty? Oh, you're not even
readable, actually. I'm not supposed to read them anymore. Yeah, I know. I know. Right. I won't do
it anymore. God, give it some bit. A 15 year old game. Look, look, look. They did actually come
some pretty decent games like back then. Are you squidding me right now? Oh, Brian. Last one for
today. I got to go night night. Good night. Thank you for the tip, Virginia. Good night,
and I'll see you in the morning. How long are you two hours in? So statistically we have like
four. Oh, no, no one's sleeping in four hours. I'm a nation must die. Do you wish to help us or
not? Yes, I'll help you, my goodness. Honestly, yeah, you actually do deserve a bit sass. Right,
we're okay. Yeah, just go ahead. Whoa. What am I supposed? What animal? Am I supposed to eliminate?
Oh, actual cutscene. Yeah, we do not get actual cutscenes like this often.
Oh. Oh, sorry, I'm petting my hair right now. My hair is up in a bun.
I'd rather that sounded rather old.
Two and a half. Stony, you get one more of those jokes for all your jokes become unfunny.
I don't have any more sound effects to do it with. I don't have any more sound effects.
That's them all. So I can't make the joke again. I've only got crickets now.
I really don't like hurting these guys, but if they're baddies, there's nothing I can really be.
I give you, I send you back to Awa. Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa. There's a lot more of
you in this plane, this pen than I thought. Jeez. What am I supposed to destroy in here? That.
Uh, I hope this works. Uh, I cast protection. I cast protect- I re-
I'm stuck in the corner. I cast protection.
Okay, thank God this game is so buggy. Oh, I didn't mean to do that. I didn't mean to heal. I wasted that heal.
Oh, this is making me nervous. Haha, you can't come on the rock. You can't come on the rock.
Most games for older games, elevation really bugs out the AIs that they have. So don't be afraid to
use elevation to your advantage because then you get moments like this where you can just have
a good time because they can't get on the elevation. Okay, for you. Glad that's over because that is
really not an easy enemy to defeat in the world. My gaspan bug rug. Shawnee, you seem to have upgraded
upgrades available top left. Wait, actually though. No, I don't, I don't, unless it's that.
Greatly improved damage for a short amount of time.
Hmm. Yeah, like for some reason, if you don't like tab over these, it'll constantly tell you you have like weapon upgrades and stuff.
What else have I got? Yeah, so like things get more like stronger as we progress.
I could do a club, honestly. Let's see the club. What does it look like?
Oh, that's a meaty swing. Oh, that's a load up though to get that. That's quite a load up.
Oh, yeah, that it doesn't. Okay. No, this is for these guys. It's the double. It's the double for me.
Oh, why would you guys even be in a broken facility? Be honest, right now.
Oh, why? How are you even getting me through a fence?
Well, I need to aim. You need to reload. So which one of us is going to go down first?
Yeah, the club's too slow. I'm just gonna go for it. Okay. Yeah, one shot with the things I'll take.
Is there anyone else here? I hear him. I hear him. I can't see him. Oh, he's so tiny.
Oh, you're so tiny. I can't even see it. Ha, ha, ha. You're welcome.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Gang up, on, gang up, on. That's what I get for making a joke.
Spank, spank, spank.
Hello, scrawny. There was no notification for your human discord.
Discord hates me. I can't believe it. I'm not discord's little kitten or whatever. I said anything
that thing. Shibi is live right now with Classable 9 if that game is more of an
interest to you because I'm literally playing the most like unknown game ever.
I don't know if this game out on PlayStation and that as well. I don't
remember it being... oh there's a Thanator in here. Where is it? Oh I hear it. Where is it?
Oh it's literally right there. We'll just spray it down.
Oh I'm already out of ammo. Oh I thought I thought I thought I thought I was going to be like
coded. Oh okay now he's not coded to go any further. I was going to say I'm like I didn't
think it was coded to go any further. This is another thing about older games. You can like
just absolutely smurf them because there's only so much game memory and game storage that they
can allocate for areas which means coding wise they will just stop enemies from doing stuff like
that. I just love it. I appreciate it so much. Like it just makes everything nice and easy.
Peasy lemon squeezy. What you got to complain about? Huh? What you got to complain about?
I know the game did come out on PlayStation 3. Okay okay so it wasn't... I didn't think it was an
Xbox exclusive but I don't think it ever got released on Steam. What? I don't know. Hi it's
done. It's done. Hydration check. Your own people would not have you so you come to us.
I'm gaming. I'm not doing this for me. There's a lot more to cheese. I'm cheeseing it. I'm not smurfing
it. Cheeseing it. Do you think I enjoy this? How much do I need to play for that? I've never
done it. I've genuinely never done it. I don't think so you don't need to pay anything at all. I've
gone to an RDA. I assume the RDA is just like congrats you've destroyed the planet thanks
and then the credits just roll. That's how I imagine the RDA side ends. Are you proud of yourself
for beating a helpless NPC? Hold on I'm getting rolled. Oh my armor! I just noticed that my armor.
Oh my god girl moment. Oh my god fashion show. Fashion. I've got a passion. Whoa look at that
protection walk. Are you squidding me right now? Today I learned that if you click on the hashtag
smuttlefish hashtag in the stream description one of the first videos shown is the pufferfish
gagging on a character video. Truly perfect. Actually thank you for the tip. Sorry y'all.
Oh that poor little guy. But yeah fashion show momento. So human basic armor. A little bit
of an upgrade and then we've got like location based armor. I knew it so hopefully we can take
a wall open now because are we faster as well? Oh who's here? Oh why are you here? This is Navi.
I'm destroying Pandora just trying to input these guys. Let me put my glycs on. Can I see none?
I'm invisible. You shouldn't be shitting me anymore. I'm literally invisible.
Am I going to heal naturally or do I need a pulp to heal? I need a pulp to heal.
Take this. Oh I see the TNT thing. I'm going to grab the crystal before it gets me as I don't
go to craft. Get me out here. Get me out here. Get me out here. Oh that sprint is so good. Oh my
I just came out of nowhere. He blinked and he was gone. Oh need to pick up more samples. Oh get me
out of here. There's too much. If they start having like knock back that's when it gets dangerous
like being in the middle of the enemies. So do forgive me if I literally just blow past all these
sections. Oh I can do that. That's fine. That's fine. That's fine. Okay okay we're we're getting
so mo. Oh that's such a good thing. Ah see when they do that they stall you. That's when you get
this. Oh no no no. It's literally TNT in the sky. Okay we made it. We made it. Let me just
unlock this little tree of vision. You can't see me no. The vitality and protection boost.
Yeah. What about the corp? Did you find out why they're pulling out? Why are you pulling out?
Hmm. You don't want to pull out there?
Okay we've got our second song so does that mean we need to do a third song and then we're
who? Am I to talk to? The Banshee?
Teleport?
Wait what am I supposed to do?
It's on to happen. It says yellow on the map. Am I supposed to read the ikran?
No. I'm sorry I wasn't paying attention. The willow tree? The willow tree?
Am I to use this to teleport to here to get to home tree?
What?
Wait was there a thing back? No not conquest. No not conquest. No no no no. We don't want to do
conquest. You must do it at the end of the game. No no no. I already know how to play. Thank you. No
conquest. Not now. Was there something I was supposed to pick up back there? I feel like I
don't know. Child support scary. Is there a crystal? Oh dumb. Dumb dumb dumb dumb. Gee I wonder
if it's supposed to go here on this conveniently place little island thing. Okay I was gonna
I need something. Now what was the third one here? Yeah okay okay don't make it too don't make it too
obvious video game devs don't even need yellow paint in this game.
Okay we have the song. My apologies. I was rather confused there.
I'm becoming na-vi na-vi na-vi na-vi. You bring hope for the future. Give our call. We bring this song
before ta-i. The battle moves swiftly. I fear humans are a step ahead of us. We must return song to
home. Mercy's just DM'd me. Strongly my alt twitter's growing really fast. I'm scared
but under the tweet I'm getting nervous. Should I post this?
Yeah you can post what you want. I'm gonna reply. Mercy you can you can post what you like my darling
whether whoever makes you happy. Yeah I have replied to Mercy.
Farah Yandere she sure does love being like on ironic this is gonna sound really weird when I
say this out loud. She sure does love being a good girl and getting permission for everything
Farah Yandere. Like literally all of the girls are so fantastic. And so we're slowly getting
past the stage of do I need permission to do this? Because the answer is always no you do not
need my permission you're in control. So I was the same. The best kind of Yandere.
Yeah damn need some sunglasses to get up this tree. But yes the girls are definitely easing into
the concept that because I assume you know they've consumed enough kind of like oh most
future agencies like have this long list of rules that you have to abide by and it's like my rules
are like literally you know be cool with lollipop stuff and no no male collabs and you know that's
it. It gets really simple you do everything yourself I'm not going to tell you what to do I'm
going to dictate your content. So Brian. Yes you can post whatever you want my dear mercy
leaks classified military documents war thunder style. I know about that if you didn't know
military documents keep getting leaked in a video game because people are like they're like so
like wanting everything to be correct which is hilarious thank you for the tip Farah.
But that's like true real and true because what I'm sure one of them was like they were arguing
over a helicopter detailed design either in the cockpit or something to do with a helicopter
and then someone was like so Tismo they were like no you're wrong and here's why and then they just
like flop down these like documents that shouldn't be publicly accessible um and it's happened
with the law. Okay we're singing a second song I'm going to assume by the third song we will progress
to the next story part element is good good let me try a rumble nun will soon be found
okay it's a little weird daily so many stuff challenger tank manlet armor but it
in a Eurocopter shells etc it's happened 15 to 17 times
bro bro was like slams on desk see I told you so
now this gen is blessed truly guide you to your next like it wasn't even one country leaking
the info it was all of them together just so that the the equipment and tanks and all that were
accurate in game the next song there's literally a joke zero days since last military leak
she sees what you may become they don't like to be wrong exactly great honor I'm just someone
who gave me a song back home we call that a DJ oh he she just stroked his chest
didn't you worry mate I just collect the songs look beyond the cup that's already full
og san says as he drinks it means
uh they are a Ramu a certain dominance honestly actually leaks really five and seven but other
times they were export uh restricted but it could be found online I'm really proud to belong to the
war thunder community for their dastardly arcs the forest burns our warriors flee before the humans
these are drinking what hmm the rda must be gunning me and me I say actually all of them
you know what well that's it all of them we can't escape the the p-corp jokes
is the time to counter their attack or must be risked in times of need
just all of them are at it honestly I mean if you think about it as there is milk heels
so what would the other liquids do I don't know I don't know we didn't lure that that wasn't
concepted but up to you what you think the other ones do uh what is this area I seem to have
forgotten this map I actually don't remember it the warriors here know the land uh the obligatory
okay please be the last song because no more song missions please see if they can find big b we could
use this big b all right just marry big b this much at this point I feel love them so much
he enjoys crushing skulls of many tortu tortu or humans when you have all I want to have squid
ink spaghetti is that because of me be honest time to find out hey oh strony you didn't have shebe
you didn't hear shebe's discussion about oh no actually this is one thing that I'm actually
genuinely a bit sad about because I stream so much I don't have time to watch everyone's streams
and it ups it like it genuinely upsets me like um I raided into mercy yesterday and she was playing
oh mario or whatever the name of the game is oh I've never seen it or played it before
and um she was like yeah I've been quite adorably but I just feel bad that like I don't have time
like just everything like when I popped into ac stream playing that puzzle game obviously
shebe's live right now I have terrible news but I don't have shebe uh in my ear right now
that you guys can't hear whilst I game and stream and talk at the same time it's just not possible
for me I do not remember this map at all I'm like um let's go for it let's see what this maps all about
then what is this is this a run through type of thing uh no this is a search what is going on
whoa this is pretty
what is going on I need to learn to do that protection spell more wait why did the area
just moved wait so am I supposed to kill those in the area let's go let's see yeah it's kind of
shame that all your streams are overlapping I will say one thing I did ask the girls to push
on the first week to stream as much as possible however um some of them are going to settle into
streaming um I literally said to them do not even dare stream every single day after this like you
will be taking breaks that like I was I've lit and they can all vouch that I told them straight to
their faces don't you dare stream every single day the only reason I can do it is because I don't
experience burnout the only reason I would not stream is if I am on death's door I'm not even
kidding um oh that horse is beating me up they're jumping me wait use the ultimate use the heal
heal heal heal my goodness you're so so what am I supposed to do here stop
oh
I'm gonna need to take these um getting hurt by something um
what am I getting hurt by I have no idea right wait why am I just to run around these sectors
or just stop it oh there's more of them here I need to heal are you forcing them to take breaks
I'm not gonna tell them not to stream because that's not my place to do that but I will be
worried if as time goes on like I've noticed one of them are like non-stop streaming
but I will always like take their like if they say they're fine I'm not gonna question it I'm not
I'm absolutely not gonna question it if they want to stream they can stream but I would be a bit
worried like hopefully you're not like overdone you're safe because when I do it it's fine but
when others do it hold on a minute I'm getting worried I'm I'm turning in a mother mode like are
you okay uh is there something I could help you with is there like a reason behind the scenes why
you want to stream everything you know I just want to make sure you're okay baby okay you're my you're
my wing you're my wing oh my goodness uh you literally just stopped me from doing that ultimate
okay objective perfectly right okay we did it we did it
take care of your daughters these uh unironically I've been getting nightmares about my daughters
um I had a nightmare that I didn't redirect into one of them and then they wanted to leave
violor because of that and I literally put in the message I was like am I real mummy now
without her because I'm like I'm literally having nightmares like of like oh no something's not
going right or like I've done something wrong are we babies here we go well like uh I managed to get
streaming did no streaming detachment anxiety that's not the word is it oh wait am I supposed to go
this way um separation anxiety from the reefing um that happened and I don't know if I'm gonna develop
it again for a little bit uh plausible but it's happened with the girls where when I go to sleep
I get so nervous for them and like I'm worried like something might happen to them and I'm not
there to like help them through it or something um but yeah yesterday was weird going after
the tulip remarks there was so much time in the day but the good news is I got a lot
behind the scenes work done wait follow me uh I may or may not blast into that dialogue and I don't
know I'm at his court her Mr. Horsey that was me twat wait what oh fucking spank you today what
are you playing at protection where's the other guy I literally just saw him or did I just get
them both in the goal I assume I'm gonna score in her too yeah okay this is like an escort mission
about everything does she attack or does she not attack no she just stands there and lets me do
everything all right and ask you have it and lazy bum lazy bum lazy bum that's right I'm calling
you'll be a lazy bum what you're gonna do better oh I love that one hit like fly by
I swear in those it wasn't thing in the movies no it definitely is not is she getting attacked
no she's fine
she is getting attacked
can you get
there
right we can progress to the next one she's on a very caring mama honestly
she's got worries I'm like I remember my mom telling me when she had me she used to be a deep
sleeper but when I was born she became a late sleeper and I'm like I feel that because I've
not had like a really good night's sleep since debut oh before debut I didn't even have a good
sleep either and the yap is the best part also in general a really cute thing for now is that
they are yapping a lot but not a bad way no I love when the girls yap honestly it's like so nice to
listen to like their stories and and the situations have been in they've been in like quite humorous
situations um and it's just like fun to hear different people talk from like different walks
of life like I know that sounds so freaking weird to say but like um it's just fascinating it just
I don't know I just I just find it fascinating I feel like you can also learn a lot from people's
stories as well even if it's a humorous story normally there's some sort of like thing or
element where they can look back and giggle and be like oh I wouldn't have done that no but like
oh wasn't it funny at the time and like you know just little good things I should maybe do a
reefling story time where we share stories and it'll be like sure like I would be have to be like a
google submission thing and it's like oh share your um share like a memory that makes you embarrassed
and like I'll read them out and then I'll share you an embarrassing story of mine um like that
kind of stuff I would absolutely love to do I feel like those kind of interactive streams are
quite funny and we can all like kind of have a wee giggle at each other also you guys must
remind me to brush my teeth at the end of the stream I keep forgetting to brush my teeth
for that guy and um we need to do it together for 21 days so we can establish uh our beautiful
training uh yes
hello rocks village behind village the shards are behind honestly me speaking french rocks behind
go got it I don't I've forgotten what behind is derriere
village derriereville and then rock is probably just like l rock
I think there's not a will stand below
or is this a fate is this a fate oh it's a fate it's on peer protection I'm literally a warlock
peer protection oh we don't like fire fire bad oh get raked get raked get raked I'm getting raked
I'm getting raked by the I leveled up though but I'm currently getting absolutely you can
literally see the ammo shot that is coming from me from that freaking thing oh unlock new armor
whoa I'm naked is that less protection oh no it's the exact same oh if it's the same as the green
one yeah we'll just use it um oh my god am I through your reload or something geez get me out
of here I'm just gonna run ahead oh I haven't in this as well right we'll do in this
try to speak as I say so it's not so
literally I was green a minute ago with my armor and then it all disappeared and I'm like excuse me
where's my uh protection via armor like you're telling me the navies still haven't figured out
that uh maybe we should literally have bullets or getting thrown and you're telling me the
navie haven't figured out that we should probably there is much they say you can do uh I can do
a shard nearby I'm going to drink a water you should think about hygiene near the east village
you must help we were attacked by humans many have died
you are not too late go find Alona when he can help and Mercy says uh I'm sorry I've accidentally
stumbled into the algorithm on Twitter and I'm like congrats because I don't know how the heck it
works either uh and a lot has been used to find all low new in in the village of to the east
the red feathers look pretty bad uh where are we going oh a bit of a bit of a walk oh no no
not a bit of a walk well because there's a horsey horsey easy bear would you let me read you and
say easy there like this dire horse from the hit video game James Cameron's avatar released in
2009 um
how many resurrections do I have I've actually not been collecting much samples does that attack me
are you friendly oh well that got answered real quick didn't it whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa
whoa whoa whoa whoa a bit too much action on these roads for me a bit too much not only I would
say my only complaint about this game is that you can never freely explore the land like things
constantly keep respawning which I'm not a fan of I quite like the idea of like clearing out an area
and then it's like safe every time you like want to come back we're gonna unlock the tree of vision
this game well this game did become PlayStation Platinum um uh apparently there's a multiplayer
mode in this game I don't ever recall playing that as a child so it's running when is the history
stream of yapping about the Irish potato family I was gonna do a teachers day where we have like
40 minute or well maybe 30 minute classes so we do like English study and then we do like a French
class and then we'll do like a PE class and we're like literally I'll just instruct you on what we're
supposed to do and you'll just hear me jump up and down in my room um um what other we'll do mass
as well I'll teach board mass is how we do it in the UK or maybe maybe just Scotland I don't know
uh board masses brackets of division multiplication addition subtraction is different what the heck
am I supposed to do I wasn't paying attention I think I'm supposed to collect things in this area
yes I am I am to collect things in this area if that's the case in viz right now
right we'll just do the outskirts of the area because I think that kind of highlights what the
daily was where the heck over oh there is right there's one I can hear lots of enemies but I'm
trying not to engage in any of them I am gonna get him to not attack me by doing this nope that
was not that wasn't it oopsies literally just aggro time on me for no reason oh there is we need one
more pink tentacle oh there is there is right we're safe safe safe safe safe we're gonna try and
avoid all the fights because you really do once you do like if you engage in all the fights you
really do get like tangled up and all this time strongy teaching man and it's not gonna go well
but like we would do all the most basic covers like we do biology we'll do physics we'll do
chemistry and like a full day and the way I was gonna do it is we're not allowed to progress
until you guys actually give me the correct answer so depending on how fast you do it we'll get through
the school day like really fast but like I'll put a little I don't know if I can get like a teacher
I don't know maybe put like a graduation cap oh wait hold on I just realized I'm not gonna light
on that's why my mouth tracking has been all funny hold on hold on professional streamer moment
I'm gonna recalibrate just because I keep seeing my mouth is wiggling away I assure you I'm not
about to cry you know when someone's about to cry then their mouth starts wiggling that's what I do
anyway but we will recalibrate a little tricky a recalibration nope and my
blanket is currently trapped around the microphone that's not fair Mr. Blanket
please please work with me here your math phobia I hope you have a math
phobia numbers oh so I was calibrating so I had to go in the dead silence
what you scared the numbers oh multiplication oh yeah that terrify
you that stuff made out of nightmares for you yeah where's these horses
you could give a history lesson on the battle of bannock born I absolutely will
we'll do we'll have a Scottish lessons stream a segment for it because if we're
gonna study English later at your name I'm gonna stay off the horse for this I
think I'm just picking these people up horse you're in my way thank you
reunite the hunters well we'll just I'll just let them fight in the
background whilst I'm in a cutscene don't worry guys you're doing fine keep up
you know you're fine you're fine you're doing what's your favorite protest what
does that mean what's a protest I don't know what I'll make sure alone a win
knows you're coming oh my god a veiler group calibration with the math cuz
apparently all of you struggle with math literally I like playing in the
criminal games but you know I don't actually like doing the thinking part
when it comes to numbers so yeah this is the way to victory to victory to
victory this is the way to victory and this is a way we'll go I'm actually so
fast on this is this faster than the Thanator actually might be you know oh
there's so many samples around here I'm just gonna check oh I'm actually max on
revives I've got five revives over getting ready to attack you have done
much for my class yeah we stand beside you even she be was struggling with a
puzzle puzzle games are mmm I asked Emmy and AC see if they would maybe
collab on we were here that puzzle game and they had to swap the game they gave
it a little shot like just as a five 15-minute practice and they were like
we're not playing that and I was that's fine that's fine you don't have to play
it's fine fine I wanted to see if I could do it with the refling but then I'd
have to like if I could do it yeah they wonder the rock killed me it's sort of
flipping entire boulder on my skull are you joking how is that supposed to know
that was about time that's outrageous oh map design change what's in here
enemies got a lot of oh can you guess really not see
okay I give up I give up that's really annoying what's going on here I've done
protection I've got knocked back I hate when they knock you back because that's
when you can just absolutely eat all of the damage that they're laying out which
is not good yeah like I'm literally getting so injured this your spawn point
is it behind here you suck give me that spawn point get that spawn point out
here oh we're just like literally going back
could you do a lesson on Mary Kunis cause honestly oh my god I have to make you
do force the force Pete are you religious education as well actually
maybe not I may not be that fun for people I'll make us sing a song though
a little don't carry anything down the dusty road something like that force choir
I'll have to get us all to sing at the same time but it has to be it has to be
like internet culture songs because why are we why did why did he just oh there's
a dog there but a dog dog with a book and I don't know what songs I could make
sing it would have to be related to meme culture what did you guys think about all
the songs that made the girls sing I freaking how am I supposed to avoid that
I'm sorry there's absolutely no way you can dodge that unless you went to attack
but if you am I am I going the wrong way
I've gone horrifically the wrong way sorry I had to like really think there I think I'm
actually about to lose my dire horse coming back here because of this car yeah wow literally
Brian what if the game show with the girls where every stream the questions are about a
different subject eyes hold on I'm getting absolutely right hold on protection in viz
let's go oh and viz sorry right hold on narrow thank you for the tip hey shroney what if
veal or game show with the girls where every stream the questions are about a different
I'm sorry I can't do two things at once hold on hold on what way did I go stick to this one
oh oh oh I'm no I'm no I'm no smart enough to do two things at once I'm gonna have to read
that all over again one more time take it from the top hey strong why is there more enemies
what if veal or game show with the girls where they stream the question there are different
there the great questions are every so we do have one game show coming up that I'm gonna make
I am going to reach out to a creator for possibly they already do a game show but I was gonna set
it up for them so literally they can just rack in all the money if you didn't know the easiest way
to collab with people is to do all the work but let them like take over type thing it's the most
likely way that a collab opportunities will be accepted so I've got possibly a game show
we're going to show up on someone else's channel and and then I'll get like a highlight reel made
and so I need to reach out to another creator but I'm letting this first week settle down like
it's been a bit hectic like trying to get a script manager in place and we're trying to
deal with this clipping issue that we've kind of right now things are a bit slow to be produced
but the girls are going to have shorts that come out consistently on their channels at some point
but like me and she be are literally lagging for shorts because I'm waiting to get us monetized
first before we start putting shorts out because this is just a fact but shorts do better if
there's something in them that's a bit humorous in that way and the one that I got a she be to do
that a fauna speedrun challenge like that did well and all and I actually really she got to show
off her mine like voice which is absolutely perfect but the other ones I actually got her to discuss
milk body type v-tubers which I thought was super interesting but I'm too scared to put it up
right now because I would be mortified if the girls didn't get accepted for monetization
and this recent ASMR stuff geez I'm literally getting grenade launched my goodness draw destroy
the amp soup well okay I'm gonna say where is it um but there will be a lot of shorts coming up
like one monetization is freaking dealt with uh because the stats updated but it only updated
halfway through debut so it says I still haven't reached watch hours even though I think I have
like a stupendous amount of watch hours now especially after that assassins creed my assassins
creed brother you'd stream almost has more views than my debut stream which is hilarious to think
about because I streamed for so long and I guess people just didn't expect it so like they came
back in the stream twice at some point you made 20 hours in two days literally like but after
debut we all successfully had enough watch time at that point it's just youtube has taken an entire
week to update and today I was supposed to be able to apply everyone's channel for monetization
but it only partially updated the thing I think it's faster if I jump no just jump down on this
bridge that comes up um but I only did it halfway through debut so I need to wait another 24 hours
for it to update and then I can submit all the girls channels um like I've got an ASMR short
of sheebie as well but Azura's short got denied for monetization for advertisement and I think it's
literally because her voice is just too strong like I don't know how but her her voice is too
strong it needs nerve oh I really don't want to go down if that's there can I destroy this
hold on did I just snipe him out of that car
did that car just disappear I'm just gonna invis through this section but that looks like
I sniked him out that car no I clearly didn't because he's right there you don't hear anything
that's called the AI cheating what's this a bomb ooh a bomb
ooh a bomb whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa there's far too many of you right now there's far too many
of you right now oh my gosh oh my gosh I've done it now I've done it now I've done it now I've done
now commit commit commit commit submit conceptguitar where's the one where's the one just one more in
here there is a siya siya siya siya we can do this we can do this as long as I do I do it
I'll hit checkpoint right get me that head out here ooh I don't have heal yet I don't have
I have heal, I have heal, I have heal, I have heal, I have heal, I have heal, I have heal.
What's going on?
Why?
Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, get on the horse, get on the horse, get on the horse,
get on the horse.
Am I on the wrong side?
If I go this way, I can teleport to that other one and then go from there.
Yes, we will do that.
Oh no, there's another one of these.
Oh my gosh, they're so pee.
Goodness gravy.
What does that even mean?
How, literally, I think it's because very sadly sheepsters in Azura might have a cover
up for their, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know what's going on, we're kind of,
we're at the question mark stage of what's the problem, what's the issue, but we'll
get there, okay.
Did I say thank you for the tip, Nero?
Sorry if I didn't.
But yes, there are game show type-esque things coming up, there's no horse games.
November is my Scottish game show, I don't know if one of the girls might be interested
in holding a type of VTuber collab game show, I'll need to see, mate, I was actually helping
you, do you mind?
Jeez, you're so rude and stinky.
Alright, I think I'm to go this way and then, I'm sorry, I'm getting really switched around
with this freaking map, but we'll just, we'll go for it, we'll send it.
Ooh, no thank you, no thank you, no thank you, hehehe, not interested, no thank you.
Your horses butt is soaking up all those bullets like a cha- honestly, stagger an amount of
endurance on that thing.
The Easter wheels, oh, are they finally giving me a path with no enemies?
You know what, I'm not speaking ever again, that's a ridiculous timing, you've embarrassed
me.
I would, I think that's my only complaint about this game, it would be so nice if there
was areas that you could just enjoy for the beauty, which I know this sounds like such
a weird thing to say, but like, I really, I like admiring the game, okay?
I'm a little, a little map design admirer and like look at how much nature there is.
I'm pretty sure there's actually a steam game that came out and it's all about identifying
plants in nature and I'm like, honestly, I wish I was like more entertaining so I could
play it, but I'm not that entertaining, B or B, I gotta go somewhere, okay let me just
pause the stream, we'll wait for you to come back, see you when you come back.
Oh, it's not Osha, is it Peeta, P-E-T-A, Peeta, that's that animal organisation, Peeta,
Peeta, that's not working in my head, I don't think it's Peeta.
Oh, new armour, oh, check that out, oh I like that, hold on, let's do a little wardrobe
check, wardrobe check, oh wait, whoa.
My mobility is way down, but my protection is so up from that, we might leave that up,
I'd rather like have more indefinite protection than having to deal with all these issues,
with constantly like getting barraged.
Ah, right, okay, crystal, crystal, crystal, crystal, let's beat them up, where's the crystal?
Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa, steady on, steady on, where's the crystal, I'm like literally
jump-scaring these guys, whoa, you were on the crystal, alright, where is it, am I staring
at it, oh it's up, oh wow, okay, I wouldn't have known that, it's like I was on that
crystal there, mission complete, wee, ow, my ankles, no again, protection is more important,
the mobility, I would say so yeah, that's a big old horse ride, um, can I, wait is that,
that is done, uh-huh, uh-huh, yeah, yeah, just reading them up, yeah, I don't know where
to go, I don't know where to go, I don't know, really turned around, I think it would be
faster if I took a teleport near this location, um, hello, uh, I have to redo the set, alright,
okay, no, I just fell through the map, okay, classic open, but there we go, I think we're
actually getting pretty close, I have never done that before, I guess this game, I mean
I did say that games have problems with vertical stuff, especially older games, when it comes
to mapping you just fall through the map so many times in older games, right, we're gonna
teleport where, it looks like that and then just take a weird straight ahead, what a strange
layout for a map, a skill issue honestly, childhood me would never do that, and yet here we are
being an even worse gamer, pardon me, I'm doing this with baby birds this time, I saw the
truck, I saw it, wait I need to claim this, I don't know, oh my, I don't know if I'm,
can I get away with this, oh my god I can get away with it, oh, oh that poor horse I've
just left it, I'm so sorry you get to meet Ewa now, hush hush, your plight is over, you
no longer have to, you can frolic in the fields in Ewa's heaven now, if I've just left you,
to perish to the RDA, ooh, I would make the joke but I don't have any more sound effects,
magic your way to the other side of the map honestly, a bit cheeky to claim when there's an
entire tank shooting at you, you're the best gamer I am especially when you rage, oh no, I
always feel bad when I rage because I feel like it's like, I like doing what I like to see and if
I see like a streamer rage I'm like, I'm not sure I'm finding this entertaining but if you guys
like it then sure I'll tap into my ancestors rage, I'm literally the, is it the orcs and
Skyrim, I think their special move is called Ancestral's Rage and it's like 10% more, or
Berserk type thing, it's like 10% more damage, what's going on here, the last song, right,
look for the thumping when bumping, nope, there's a fight, why is there a fight, I thought I just
had to interact with the tree, did I not have to interact with the tree, oh, okay, okay, okay,
we're doing it, we're doing it, we're doing it, we're doing it, come on, let's do it before
they destroy absolutely everything, is it not here, triangle, hello triangle, looking for a
triangle, triangle, this is a triangle, there we go, are they going to blow the tree up before
I get the phone, no the Ancestral stuff was done more, Berserkers rage is the one that works out,
ah, right, invisible because we're not out here trying to have a billion battles every two seconds,
yeah, probably feedback on the game, kind of calm down on how many enemies you put on the map
because they are constant, hello barrier, did this, did this game really say go around,
no way this game just said go around, oh no it's fine, it's fine, it's fine, it's fine,
yes, yes, let's get out of here, this place is gonna blow, oh, we must return to Kellotron,
take your ecran, we ride to home tree, okay, we go to home tree, home tree,
I think we're getting there, I can't really recall how much more to the campaign there is,
this would be three songs and if we're playing the classic video game rule,
I can't remember what comes after the third song, I swear if it's like go for another song on my
right, wrap it up, wrap it up, wrap it up, you're taking a bit too long now, take a bit too long,
we're gonna need to do something a bit more than home questing, but look how cool that armor looks
honestly, that's pretty thick, it would be so cool to see this game remastered,
but I do not think it sold well, I think it hardly did it, it's numeros, hello,
we love them, James Cameron you did it again, is it snowing, no,
let's hope we're getting close, we don't find it soon, this whole planet's gonna
fly, winter in Australia is just fake, it never goes below freezing,
yes yes the song, the song, ay was song, please be the last song, no more singing,
ah ah ah ah ah,
tells where it is, please, no more songs, surely we know what's up,
many of the people believe in you yet some fear the tattooed spirit inside you let me get
fedama he blames you for much there was just a whole missing voice line i think
it was so hard to come to our realization that christmas is summer final song it's not natural
but it's a pretty decided once i wrap up a business that i am going back to
yeah if you ever went to open up a business in the uk don't you better do it in australia
but then go back to the uk once you're done with all your business
yeah here for more entrepreneur tips
like and subscribe
tanjala wants you to fly to a new location i don't know what this
i'm afraid my memory is getting very easy now for the game
you'd kill for a warm christmas it is bizarre i did not enjoy it like i phoned my family
and i was like oh i wish it was cold i wish it was cold um because you do get snowy christmas
in scotland which is really pretty when it does happen when the stars align it's very nice
hello hello i haven't given up where is the shot
where sky machine has crushed you are so mean i've literally been helping you for ages
i'm sorry but i think enough time to pass where he should be all right with me
and you're giving me any nonsense you make it sound so mystical it's very beautiful
where the what the heck is this map i do not recall at all
memories getting a little bit easy i can't see where the map ends because of that very
top right corner very clearly that's where this map location ends but i don't know what happens here
i can't believe it right i think we're just gonna leg it as we always do
but yeah like these look the map details like the kind of the further you progress the more
damage the areas are and you know it was trying our hardest but like there's only only so much
awa can do and the navi can do against literal bullets i have to admit bows versus bullets
like i'd rather have the rather have the mp5 or the famine so my wait why did i get off i just
want to activate that oh well i needed to get off anyway because i need to cut up in this fence
i'm itching my little whoa is this elden ring oh you've got this right let's see
uh we'll just avoid thank you for spawning in but not really interested me wait am i going
the wrong way no i can go this way i just happened to walk right into an rda uh aligned and i need
to cut this fence as well goodness gravy i might make a cup of tea shortly and go for a peep because
we've actually not peeped in three and a half hours of uh unless some of you guys have a detached
headset and then you go for a peep whilst whilst still listening to oh the fact that there's a
very high chance that a reefling has dropped a loaf of bread while listening to me ramble on stream
that's right reefling i'm on air i know exactly what you're up to mm-hmm i know what's going on
a drop a loaf of bread honestly drop apparently the there's another same which is a drop the
kids off at the pool which is a guilty is charged oh no it's been confirmed you know when people
say like oh what did you what what did you think would happen like when you became a
vertebra etc uh apparently i didn't account for someone dropping a loaf of bread to my voice so
there's that yeah um yeah quite a few unique scenarios definitely definitely
how are you ever like he teleports around this map for fun i swear okay hello
no the shard was blown up not sure not sure the first voice is not sure oh i'm being called
the first voice i'm no longer dreamwalker oh my tummy rumbled if you heard that
listen into your patreon audio we'll see in a man about horse
i didn't want to miss the second of your beautiful voice though if it's any consolation
you make dropping and you make dropping a loaf of bread hell a lot more comfortable you're done
you're out out you're done
we would be not identifying as loaf of bread droppers oh that came out nowhere
oh my poor horse i should have picked up a new one
because he's so low health i want him to retire and live a happy life
but i don't think that's gonna is a left or right it's this way
she knows too much hey yeah
oh right i'm gonna pick up this horse here because i would like this one to literally
retire and have a happy life excuse me mr. horsey see you go enjoy yourself and heal up and then
i'm gonna have you
and then everyone lived happily ever after and the and everyone around me clapped yay
hey that's what we're supposed to listen to the first honestly though
um wow that's a lot of power about a lot of manpower behind that
they're destroying the crystals before we get them is someone telling them this
how do they know where the heck all these crystals are
right we'll finish this map and then we'll go for a tinkle and i will also go for a
tinkle and make a cup of honey tea to help soothe my curve voice it's really bizarre
my voice is so broken but the microphone makes it sound so like fine and not broke wait can i
just teleport no um so i sound like pretty normal on stream my voice has been broken since uh the
the violor exposed violor stream um i don't know thankfully i've managed to record a lot of
stuff in advance but don't be surprised if you get a patreon audio and i'm just sound like a frog
i'm like yeah you like that good boy and you're such a good wee boy and you like my toad boy like
it's getting it's getting curious it's getting curious and you are a demon how is it you live
honestly that's kind of a fair assumption there's something i gotta tell you we must have been
those who have fallen do some patreon videos in full pantomime you get 3d models and start like
mime in the axe yeah wouldn't be the first thing patreon looks and audio in me a little frog voice
moment you let a horse die oh it was a mistake i can't save them all but i can try my best
also i just want to say i am still getting marshmallows of people asking me to save
each oh that horse literally just perished right before me oh where am i supposed to go
uh that's quite far to go by foot but we don't really have a choice there's no more horsey
boysy um skull horse skull women sound really cute when their voice is cracked and squeak
from over use and they're giggling asking you to say what no they're they're asking me to save
certain v-tubers and i said it on that stream the other day and like we're all having a giggle
but i woke up and i got a few more and i'm like i don't i don't know if it's reef link sending it
or whatever but like i'm gonna be on it oh it's full health again um i'm gonna be honest uh i hope
it's understandable no i can't literally save all v-tubers you know i'll try my best to look
after those who have faith in me um you know i'm a big believer in reciprocation in terms of you
have faith in me i have faith in you type thing oh well i better not am i on a timer and i don't
know it i think i'm on a timer gotta go gotta go gotta go i know i know i know i know i'm trying
i can unlock this uh tree of vision you can leave from the front and try and change i think
the content creator owned agencies definitely have a place um definitely have a place um
because i think people are a bit it's not for me to say what the the overall feel is but i think
for me anyway it was very disappointing to learn how little creators that sign up for
these agencies get in exchange for all their hard work because did he just go ahead me powerful
then a river did he just go ahead me um hello hello human resources do you guys have human
resources on pandora because um what was that excuse me uh yeah because we have very specific
unlikely but um i did actually learn about another agency that did have a higher split
than the 5050 which i'm i'm quite happy to hear about um so i think hopefully over time that 5050
split uh gets raised because i will tell you right now for however hard the girls work on
stream it's absolutely nothing to do with me i don't tell them what to do they do it all themselves
um and i believe that they should take home the lion's share that's just me but not every
agency out there feels like that um but if you value um if you genuinely like as a special thank
you is what wait hold on i'm getting absolutely annihilated here do i need to take these down i
think so hold on i'm doing i cast protection what's going on here am i just to destroy
because i'll do it ow we're on the same team right i don't have protection anymore but
uh okay okay we're to just kill i can do that i can do that we but i'm a weapon
what's this is this and can i not know uh
whoa whoa whoa you're not agro to me hey hey yay yay yay yay we're helping a while we're
helping helping you know what helping is yeah these guys these are the best
are they spawning oh my game just froze there did you see that i don't know if that was calling
stream or not but that was for me and i thought i can hear bullets from over here so we check out
okay let's go oh one more one more mission oh here here spawned a navi resources
the world would be a beautiful place if you're more like me
the only the only problem is uh
you never know if someone wants to take like advantage of you but i i got very lucky in
all my pics of the girls and none of them have given any indication such things
we got the crimson yeah froze i saw that monk is monk is monk is please don't please don't crash
please don't crash please don't crash
and yes i've um i've always been described as naive like my entire life um and i like i'm
used to it and i i do have to agree i do have to agree um but the the good news is it can
lead to such such crazy experiences you know like i could have easily like have just never
bothered about any of it and just you know get the resources to myself all that kind of thing but um
i'm passionate about helping people achieve their dreams and you know i've already kind of
achieved everything that i kind of wanted to do in terms of like successful content creator and
to give people that experience that kind of thing just like that that's the new goal you know
that's the new goal like as but like yeah yeah you know life life's good life is beautiful um
and you know if you don't try out these things at least you know at the end of this at the end
of everything like well i mean wrap it up wrap it up wrap it up come on wrap it up at the end of
everything at least i can say yeah heck yeah i went for it i did it um and wow what an achievement
you know what uh what an experience as well like an insane life experience uh just to even be in
the position to make any of this happen and it's just lovely lovely job right i just saved you you
better be nice to me now only a demon should carry such luck you still don't like me gather your
soul let no more of my warriors you still don't like me you're joking you are joking me
it's funny how it'd be an inspiration right now on a thursday afternoon
you're doing great dumb dumb but try to also think of your health oh i've been good i have
my health has uh just been uh has been going up and up and up what the humans know what we're doing
they destroyed the show this you said us to die for nothing no i think i can still do this you will
die human i can do this what am i going to commune without the shards a while loves me sorry i'm a
was little teacher's pet right now i'm not even kidding i'm floating no i'm not sorry that was
the camera angle i thought that was levitation i was just the camera angle my apologies got a
little excited there uh got a little uh head of myself that was a cheeky little camera angle moment
you must return the song to tahi tsunami wait you spoke as the first voice all of a sudden he's
been nice to me i would not hear one day i will repay you for all is it because he saw me commune
with awa that he's nice to me now if we're still alive after today beers are on you if that is what
it takes he doesn't even know what beer is do they even know what fermentation is humans will soon
are you telling me the navi gets steaming every weekend i'd believe it honestly
i'd get a steaming with the navi not gonna lie i'd like ask them to carry me around on their backs
and stuff he was we discord kitten honestly he's not a hater anymore literally he was just a bit
stressed from all the war just a wee bit of war wee bit of war you know strong men more times you
know how it goes you know everyone needs a bit of release if you know and then it's just what
happens just what happens oh my god do you approve of me now you think the first thing the humans
gave to the navi we're making friends with beer honestly oh here's a bit diazepam you just get
hooked on that uh cause a little uh drug pandemic you know here we go
the humans gather do you have the final song oh wait are we at the end
i think so something happened are we at the end of the game already i don't know why
i'm like 19 percent sure if you look up how long does james Cameron's avatar take it said
literally eight hours to understand now quickly um sing the final song oh but that's like such a
short screen though i never thought this far ahead i thought it was gonna be like an eight hour day
i suppose the only good side if it was a short stream i can work on my asmr then
because i've got collapse with five other girls that i'm working on outside of yellow
yeah you can always yeah uh yeah we can do some marshmallows after the game
wait am i seriously i was going to make a cup of tea and peeping all of that
wait i think that's super about to do the last level
only first voice can awaken the well of source okay and how am i supposed to do that oh so many
questions trust himself now rda play through for more time no i refuse i refuse rda like
open your mouth rda players
that's what i think of your rda players
any percent speed run honestly i feel like we're about to play the last game
like the last level human you're so tiny oh you're so tiny human human human you are so
tiny
hello writer look at you you really look full naughty now what are you doing here it's falco
he's found the location of the dormant site i know you have to move fast falco sent a dragon
to the site he's gonna drop the emulator on the well of souls this is the last mission what the
heck you need the true first we're not even on the forever mark of gameplay yeah about that
looks like it's me the eight hours i must be four yeah i was gonna say it must be four
hours navi four hours rda i'll take care of this kendra i gotta find tangyala
wow i didn't know i expect that
at all
oh i was like strapped in for a good long
though i'll say one thing the only good thing if i do go offline earlier is i can read into
another viewer member and i can get to work on those asmr scripts because their girls uh
that i'm collabing with are waiting on me are you squidding me right now brian big big please
play the rda with money on top
you can't give me money and ask for it because then i feel like i do have to do it partner it's still
me if we play the rda sage you all have to call me a good girl okay what about tantis thank you for
the tip iron refer that's crazy to put that money behind that door oh i've never played it before
hmm right we'll finish the navi sides and then you are a good girl you're the best
i just got home from work no 12 hour stream today well we might do a lock in for another four hours
if we play the rda side but i get really scared because the rda side you're so small on the
camera so small and the navi are so big and scary i can't promise i'm not going to be scared
because i've never done it before i don't know what comes up but like with these ones like
my kind of remember what comes out it's a good girl it's a good girl yes you're astralia
best girl we got a work right right let's unlock the classic tree of vision momento thank you
hmm head pads and scritches um my freaking tags aren't working on my alternative twitter
i'm trying to retweet all the like things i get in for a fight here or what
we must attack the commanders put their forces in disarray grunts will not know what to do
you're such a good girl how the hell do you know something about me oh she girl
also all the plants and animals attack you and rda no i'm so scared i'm scared already
um we share this battle like i'm actually going to be scared i'm not even kidding
hopefully my abilities keep me alive when we do the rda side but
oh i'm like genuinely dreading that i don't know if you can tell
many boom
you're gonna hold my hand through it yeah you better i just know there's going to be a
hypnosis mark i actually know i didn't ask secret subject i'm very very busy maybe i
should just get the balls to do that enough what is this map i do not recall
hmm
right we'll go grab a horror horse let's go and then we'll see where that takes us
i said it was gonna be should we should we pause for a tinkle and a cup of tea then
possibly wait i need to go left or right and you follow the path clearly
burning the countryside literally be careful because that plant will accidentally uh team
oh my goodness i hope i've got good armor this is crazy thank god they're not looking onto the
horse wow this is getting quite a lot what we're supposed to hear
i'm to kill certain guys sure okay oh he's actually got health hold on let me get these
first so i'm not getting like crossfire damage they have special abilities he literally just
precision freaking pulsed me no the horse is horse horse let me take him
horse let me take him you're getting oh horse
breath perish perish i command thee to perish before me sky people
rename dreamwalker rename the first voice you will perish under by my command i'm actually
gonna have to walk through this freaking battlefield why is there an eight commission
line there's two oh well we'll go we'll go for it uh invisible let's go in this uh i'm pretty sure
they all all this location stuff responds genuinely not a point in clearing any of it
oh i've got calm crossfire there i suppose that's a good detail to have crossfire
level four on abilities is the highest like in most effect physical i've been literally i was
going to say i've been invisible for a very long time now so we'll get to it everybody let's get to
it to it help a while expect expel the humans and restore nature when i start drinking my
does all my thinking
blame on this whiskey shift and get me tipsy buy beer or pay the rent my signing bonus
was quickly spent something something and i'm gonna beat the meat like a bitch
brian you didn't say anything you forgot to put a message anon anon did you forget to put
the message in the message box thank you for the tip but anon you were you're you can put like a
little message and then brian will read it out and then i go brian and then we and we discuss
what you put and then i say thank you anon but next time that little box that says you can put a
message here you can put anything you want anything you can even ask me what i think about
pythagoras theory you can even ask me what i think about all um things we can even talk about the
ming dynasty if you really want it your wish was my command but thank you for the tip
are you squinting me right now you're telling me a shrimp fried this rice thank you snis snis
i appreciate it the tail squinting me right now anon anything you want anon don't waste your
money like that you goofy goober thank you for the support but don't waste your money like that
but thank you i appreciate it you're you're clearly a man of few words why say many words when few
do try clearly the ming dynasty i'll see what i can do this you must do i don't know if i would
listen to something of them now i would i would go with like a time bomb i just seem to remember
that one song i wanted to do a scottish cover of it brian no smile that's the long money to be
me man about with thank you again anon no smile you've been granted the nickname no smile anon
congrats oh i didn't mean to jump down i didn't realize there was a ledge i just sent that
poor horse off the ledge it listened to me though it like trusted me i learned this about horse riders
apparently it's really dangerous if your horse doesn't listen to you
brian work ahead i sure hope sir thank you can't quit me for the donals
good work ahead i sure hope it does that's a good thing oh my god there is so much
exploding i don't think i'm gonna make it out of here honestly thank you for all the support
guys i'll push you get that oh it's just gonna let me through open cumin my
um um um i have protection on i don't i don't know i'm trying would you stop doing that i need
to heal now i need to heal now okay hold no i lost my special i should have done my ultimate first
okay we did it we did it okay one next one next one next oh i love it i love when the game
makes me go all the way back i'm actually gonna go ahead and get this uh unlock we haven't been
using our bones i got jump scared in real life i did not see that whatsoever i don't know if you
heard that inhale there that was so dramatic oh my god my heart is pounding i jumped scared in real
life a blinked and then something was right in front of me oh my heart oh my goodness right
that is so much quicker we're gonna do that go back to the thing can't confirm a fellow for it do
you tell me a shrimp fry this are you telling me i cuddled this fish damn right i cuddled this fish
go go gadget jump scare honestly hello did i help you again i am amazed many believe
right i'll call a break when we finish the navi side because i i feel like we're about to do it
mount the banshee and report to the third leader
banshee banshee banshee
mount the banshee banshee i don't see a big ikran i see a horse where am i supposed to go
blink blink blink blink ikran
ikran
ikran oh okay yeah i was gonna say something's not adding up here something's not adding up here
well i wanted to do like meme song covers where i purposely like really put on the accent for it
um because i think that's funny like uh that song is funny i wanted to do an m and m one
the everywhere i go um always know the chanley scene he's got how he made that he loves to show
wake up grab rear grab rear put on some scene gear when you get drunk come on mom wait so
break up with my girlfriend's working i'm undead unfed been sleeping on bunk beds since 10 so if i
don't booze it i'm gonna lose it everybody get to it to it let's get this party started let's get
them 40s poppin hi mero sorry about that we're just enjoying the old scotch accent and singing
see what the combination is like and it's pretty cursed but it's like the good kind i am currently
absolutely destroying this pro banter you smack that against all the world how realistic are
uploading song covers do the rights cost a lot no you don't have to pay rights at all you just get
a copyright and you can't monetize it really um it's the biggest thing it just won't like monetize
it let me guess wait it's the strongy it was the strongies who made along the way strongy can i
send you a meme in dms and do it for me on stream someday thank you thank you what was your
have i got you on discord or have i only got you on twitter
i don't have you on discord
so i am you're not you're absolutely no i apologize for using that language
i'm not i can't look at my twitter this sounds terrible um but uh the game i'm playing right
now mero is so old that if i tab out the game crashes so i can't actually look at your twitter
communication uh so i apologize i will try and add you on discord shortly though um because i'm
wanting you i'm wanting you for a secret mission mero a mission so secret
now is that it's okay it's okay yeah maybe i'll make a short maybe if it's like a
quote thing i'll make a wee short of it i'll be like thanks for the oh my god thanks for the the
money idea money money money maybe oh i'm getting wrecked by that guy jeez lowease i'm doing for
more weights right what we're supposed to do in this area the classical right i'm gonna do protection
prayer i'm gonna warlock up in this okay you are definitely a good thing i don't like you at all
who are we going for next to you yeah okay
oh that auto lock onto me those rough i do like that you can knock him over i do appreciate that
detail what we're looking at oh just walked right into oh wait he comes out of the mech and he does
this oh i just unlocked my special as well
don't do it don't do it i know you're tempted don't know he healed i knew he was gonna
take that oh that ultimate was cool though i'll give him that did my horse survive i don't think so
at all oh look at the mech little megas is a little guy he's a wee a wee lad barely more than half
my fun oh right okay i should heal up once i'm out of range of that enemy so i don't need to
use my use my um my healing ability ragdolled honestly the mission even if secret is punching
humans punching me honestly if you if you try and dissect the gameplay a little too much you
might find yourself a little a little underwhelmed it may be a little lackluster but uh this one
oh don't wait wait wait then you worry about it right then you worry about it you're all destroyed
Savoy and his demons oh demon skin i like the description for America i'm currently in my demon
skin how do you do fellow demon skin enthusiasts take your banshee and ride it oh
have i done it awake well of souls i think this is a a gasped and my throat made a noise i'm sorry
if you heard that i don't mean it oh level up rathmore oh my god new armor i saw it i saw it
i have a skull on my head oh hey i almost forgot this game because congrats you're the second person
to play this game uh that even knows about this game because one person said they played it earlier
and then now you've said you played it so now all three of us who have ever played this game are now
here because literally no one has played this game does anyone i wonder if there's a public
record of how many copies were sold because i just feel like it's such a thing way too late for this
stream but i'm also one of the two people i played yeah uh everyone thinks i'm playing the new avatar
i think possibly i don't know actually i don't know what the new avatar games called because this
one's called james cameron's avatar the game well we've got to say oh my god mansion armor to winzies
go waits for me in the in the cavern okay to the cat to the cavern to the cavern or something's
waiting for me waiting waiting waiting cavern right i'm about to go around okay i'm to go around my
apologies this the game has an interest in story i like it basically you are human and then it turns
out a war planned on you kind of i don't know it's really bizarre oh a scalp the perimeter comb that
beach why is that phrase called comb a beach what's that you mean what does it mean what does it even
translate to am i going the wrong way i'm getting nervous i'm going to they can literally hear me
like jump a boot i hear them oh my going to make it is in this oh i almost made it past all those
rda soldiers i'll take it i'll take it a couple paths yeah i assume when we play the rda side
we're literally just playing the exact same maps but doing the opposite of the bad people
and destroying everything wow i need prediction on right now i'm getting
absolutely nailed them right now i don't want to use healing because i actually do a full health bar
when i heal let's uh let's speed on speed on through okay this looks more navvy oriented
four hours is it going to be another endurance stream i think so originally it wasn't but um
um i got paid money to play the rda side and you guys are holding my hand through it because
i am genuinely afraid of what happens hello how do you do i'll hope lies with you dreamwalkers excuse
me i'm actually called the first voice i'm no longer i didn't i don't respond to dreamwalker i'm the
first boy will not let them any first voicers has asked you to kill rda forces yeah so emmy is going
live youtube moderators i grant the permission to link a sheet stream it is mine it's unarchived
okay smart and mckels smart smart embers uh this looks like it's uh destroy everything mission
because there's a timer oh right there is actually a timer on the day i don't know if any protection
spell yet i'll wait until i'm getting whacked i don't i'm not experiencing the whacking yet
uh i'm gone right okay i think the game's actually getting mildly oh my god imagine
three navvy ganging up on you it's over it's over i wouldn't even bother just put the gun down and be
like uh actually i'm gonna be one of you oh wait hold it sorry i'm getting distracted protection
i've casted protection okay there we go gang violence gang violence we're literally
ganging up in the fur guy oh that's terrible absolutely a wipe in the night i guess
one for you one spank for you and one for you okay we just need to defend the village now
without perishing which i can definitely i can hear someone getting hurt over here oh yeah
one for the true warfare i think we're cheering each other on
we responsible i was just okay i'm gonna need that prayer to pop again because now there's mecha
getting involved demon skin parish
but yes uh emmy bezu uh the beloved hex maniacal dealer is live right now you are welcome to jump
into her stream and uh make sure you're you know make sure your little sister stays in check don't
want any issues wink wink uh
imagine assassin's speed but planer's attempt yeah that's what i'm kind of like why on earth
would anyone want to do the rda but like money talks dirty cash i want you dirty cash i want you
oh money talking money talking stupid oh um oh camera angle steady steady right we've got one more
minute isn't that a game already what game are you partly viewing about identify your topic of conversation
one two three four five ultimate yeah honestly that ultimate is actually pretty sad so i'm gonna
heal because it's not gonna all heal when we're not around it because the enemies keep coming back
so protection oh there's a mech over there i think oh it's out of bounds wow i just do this for now
oh no no i won't somebody's getting me oh maybe not maybe not the navi are actually helping hold on
ai that actually attacks the enemies that are around you hold on a minute this game's 2009 and
you're telling me they nailed it here and then games afterwards it's my biggest like great
with video game development if you have allies that can attack but they do not actually end the
enemies looking at you lego franchise looking at you and they actually don't help at all i don't
know if the newest lego star wars they actually do help her is she playing this because she genuinely
likes it or is she as a warning to the rest of us avoid this it's my childhood game i do like the
game i'm just rubbish at it i i like the navi side i've never played the rda say whoa
oh that's so cool looking i think we get to write it
that's like such a cool looking dragon such a badass looking dragon
and if you wanted to shorten it i guess you could see we're raiding that bad dragon
oh thank you thank you i'll be here all week try the veal
it's awful i'm so sorry
2009 my child i'm too old for this oh my god we are
that was fell it was i apologize that was a good one thanks came up with it on the
it probably is the game i completed the most that's much fun should be ashamed of yourself boom
dragon dies oh my god look how big its wingspan is oh gorgeous
oh beautiful beautiful i love that design that's so cool jen too can we get this color palette
or something because that is wicked that oh sorry sorry my bad it's first time riding you hold on
hold on there's a saddle on down excuse me thank you very much it'd be nothing
i'm not that lovely we're not i heard that that creepy noise oh uh no i'm not jealous
i'm ashamed of finding that joke funny eh what is that noise i think that's the
where the soul is calling on me first time raiding warning warning
raider hardly even nor oh oh wait i don't even get the bidimps for that oh okay sorry
i wouldn't i would entertain the idea of uh gen 2 dragon that hordes you like treasure and she
calls you like my treasure my value like that kind of angle i like that that's uh that's not bad
i would entertain that i'm gonna entertain that oh you have crickets too yeah
i would actually entertain that um
and for anyone asked fin dom no i don't like it i don't i don't think it's me
oh what the jelly what the land jellyfish gonna do huh
oh i've completely forgotten what happens in this cutscene if i'm gonna be honest uh
uh
is that an electricity sound are we about to lighten and bolt this thing out the sky
electricity oh
thunder and lighten and maybe
okay
okay question mark
okay question mark question mark
we're saved though that's the fantastic news first voice does not need a second
he really
we prepare a storm is in the sky
we did it na vi na vi na vi we're the best we're the best better than the rest better than the rda
let me take a little little drink too
congrats on getting second please for na vi any percent lemo let me submit this stream for it why not
another game down well uh we're gonna go for a tinkle winkle and i'm gonna make a honey tea
because my voice box is dying and then we're gonna do the rda side so don't uh emmy i believe
sheebie is playing class of 09 emmy bezu is doing an unlisted unarchived stream so please don't be
afraid to go check that out because i'll still be here actually i don't know how long she's gonna go
for that maybe i mean if it's four hours to do the rda side it is very rough on the voice to whisper
for four hours so hopefully i know boo rda rda hate emmy is making pin pals do math oh no way
i think to know if you play as a human you have multiple places where you can betray them
hmm what is that like all the way up to the very end
because wouldn't i wouldn't i just become a na vi at that point or am i still human
you wouldn't i have to do the evil side now unfortunately
i think i would ruin the run if i did it i beat the game already literally i think it's
four hours for each side yeah there's emmy rda hate but gun and flamethrower fun though
then every straight up ask you to switch like three four times oh do they
i would know i love gun shoot so i
right i'm gonna quickly go peep um and make a cup of tea i highly suggest everyone to stretch
your legs don't be afraid to open up any stream the now um i will be roughly three minutes it takes
me like three minutes to boil the kettle and tinkle and all of that so please do do fish pee
absolutely fish pee all over you right now um please don't be afraid to check out sheebie or
emmy um i will be a couple of minutes and then we will jump back into the naughty naughty human
side bad human bad human stinky human stinky stinky um but yes please do consider standing up
stretching your legs getting yourself a little snacky wacky um and then we'll jump in and you
guys have to hold my hands with the game because i am actually genuinely terrified to please swim
in all the way through because camera angle is so freaking low to the ground and if i've got big
navi running at me i'm actually gonna be scared so yes hopefully this doesn't work i really hope
the game doesn't break well i'm gonna wait for like literally three minutes but the game's so old
right please do stand up and get some rest okay i need to do this did it work did it work oh yeah
okay i go now
so
I don't know what's going on here, but I don't know what's going on here, but I don't know what's going on here, but I don't know what's going on here, but I don't know what's going on here, but I don't know what's going on here, but I don't know what's going on here, but I don't know what's going on here, but I don't know what's going on here, but I don't know what's going on here, but I don't know what's going on here, but I don't know what's going on here, but I don't know what's going on here, but I don't know what's going on here, but I don't know what's going on here, but I don't know what's going on here, but I don't know what's going on here, but I don't know what's going on here, but I don't know what's going on here, but I don't know what's going on here, but I don't
know what's going on here, but I don't know what's going on here, but I don't know what's going on here,
but I don't know what's going on here, but I don't know what's going on here, but I don't know what's going on here,
but I don't know what's going on here.
I don't know what's going on here.
.
Oh, I'm having a stroke and not the good kind.
Oh.
Okay, to my next card.
What do you call a man? No.
It's so goofy.
Turning the stream into a dad pun stream, honestly.
I love this bit.
Well, when you guys do witty comments that I can repeat on stream,
I'm literally stealing them and then doing that gag over and over again.
I should be straight up to working.
Okay, I have to go now. Bye-bye. Bye. Thank you for hanging.
I don't know why, but the crickets make me laugh.
What do you get when you cross a snowman and a vampire?
Why was that so delayed?
I don't know why the crickets were so delayed.
That was even more embarrassing.
That made it worse that the crickets were delayed.
All right, you ready for this we're skipping we're skipping
Even the crickets aren't having it literally even showing up
Eight hours built on the shorter side
I'll let you like I've kind of mentioned I weave it, but like going offline after two hours
I like sat and was just staring at the screen for a little bit. I was like
What do I do now like I've got like an entire day, and I'm not on stream like it felt so weird
Like I don't
But I reached them a smart collapse type thing, which is really good
Our little cheekies are definitely red
reporting for duty, sir
I think I'm too German for the jokes are the bad they are terrible the jokes are not funny and
That is why we we use the
Cuz no one's laughing at the joke
Honestly it felt weird like
I'll every week I do plan in a couple of injured streams
But the days that have shorter streams like the two are one like I really enjoyed needy streamer overload
I did not expect to enjoy that. I looked up the
Ending I would have gotten if I managed to not ignore her and
Like she was like ready to become a god and like take down 10% of the world's population and all that and I'm like whoa
I so wish I could have gotten that but I messed up too badly, but that's okay. I couldn't have known you know
played for the same
You know you get none of the squat you go you and none of the squad laughing with that one I giggle
You're still sitting on your feet. I am I'm sitting on my right one right now
And then the left one is just wiggling the back of the chair. Why do you want to go?
Don't abuse
What do you say?
Niko from undead and what I don't know
Think of criss-cross applesauce the way you sit like that, but I'm sitting on my foot like against my
Honestly good way to really enjoy streams of you because I constantly like wiggle and move my legs type thing
I
They're putting pressure on moving them like cuz cuz I'm sitting on my foot. There's pressure against it
So it's like keeping the station
You get a little ground out of us a little mouth curve
Oh, yeah, did I have the ability to make you put air out your nose a little just a little bit faster?
Yeah, I'm thinking
Crouched no, I'm not I'm not crouching. I'm like sitting on them this time
But I do go on crouch on the chair sometimes
Like I was having to send all I was talking to like eight people at once trying to organize something for the girls
And I was golem crouched on my chair
Because I was trying to like get it done so fast so I could go to bed because I was exhausted
I'm like trying to like send this to an editor and upload these files over here and send them off and get the link and make sure
It's a pretty like oh
so
Yeah
Although they attacked me when I'm Navi as well, so honestly just a wee bit deserve
Oh
These things are indestructible honestly
Should unplug my mouse and keyboard right now just looking
I'm not even paying attention honestly, I should but
I
Think you could probably xp farm here if you had the tolerance for it because you're getting 50 every time and my
It says I need
1600 xp to level up
So yeah, that's the pretty big xp form
Ow
my angst
You're like I got paid to side with the humans. Okay, I got this is
Not me. I'll put a little disclaimer at the top of the screen. Not me
You're not funny, but your accent is doing the heavy lifting
Fucking hell, you're not supposed to say that part out loud. That's supposed to be an inside thought
Absolutely just got annihilated. Oh my I don't even know if I can come back from that. Oh
That was brutal
I can't even come back from that. I
Got 10 xp from driving over that plan
Literally
Okay, the dogs don't get like perish from the bungee
Which is fine carried by the Scottish
Literally
We do have to be careful
for
We know
Do this do the slow mo for me so I can actually oh
Jeez the way aim ball
Are you trolling me right now? I'm sorry, but my bullets should have sprayed all over that goodness gravy
You just like oh I
Don't like that they win some pain either
Just feels so mean
Why are you being so mean?
You're a mean mean man
Cuz you're just jealous. Oh
My gosh, I don't like it. I don't like it
I'm sure they were probably win some when I was Navi, but it's everything feels so meaner
I
I'm going in biz so I can get around here without a tract in the other far away one
What did that do recovery gather tensile and pulls through our recovery okay my second chance I heard that I heard that I knew you
Right here we go. Hello
I
Just run out here spraying all over. I mean, I'm a cultfish. I don't make sure that it gets far, you know for protection
to
Disorientate is it to disorientate creditors and escape the threat and must be whoa whoa whoa
They have unlimited ammo I do not okay
Why do I not have unlimited ammo? That's a bit of a problem. I heard that
I don't see like cuz the camera angle is like way smaller cuz I am smaller as well makes Pandora like even scarier
Hmm
The accuracy of our drugs
Hey
That is unbelievable
But that no, it's comedically slow that reverse considering how fast and a
What's the word?
Motion sickness and just in the forward spring now
I've unlocked a grenade launcher. Okay. Maybe maybe mucking around with the weapons would be such a terrible idea
Trooper pack unlocked some sort of blaze
Excuse me, excuse me, excuse me. I'm just driving through here. Then you mean me. No, I'm not looking for any trouble. No
Just backing up here to my meme the dune buggy
What's that that music video from gorillas that had like a random buggy in the desert? Oh
I need a gun
To keep myself from harm the poor people
Are burning in the sun
Go a chance
Then the buggy out of nowhere
No way
Old military set of gearbox don't want to go backwards only forwards towards dying enemy
This is like a flashback right now. Oh, can you like see the music video in your head as I'm talking about it?
Can I put images in your head if I talk about things? Oh my god, I never even spoke about that
So I can't like see things in my head the way others can like the way it's just like I can't do that
So if I say things does it appear in your head?
Ah
Sometimes okay, okay, I'm totally not gonna use that
Against you at any point
Can I do a music videos I am now making you think of
The gorillas music video where noodles is dancing in that room and then the guy
Has a big head and it goes never did no harm never did no harm
Wait, it's all the wrong one, I don't know one of them the giant head literally it was just a man
I saw the comments and someone was like that a key Joe
Honestly his jaw. So, um, if you ever take the recreational
and also known as bebex to say and
That makes your jaw clench or something along that line and
so
In scott's you say like all his jaw was spinning
or like he's got an achy jaw and
And
Like the comments were all saying that and we'll watch it back and I was like, oh, wow
Oh, excuse me. Excuse me. I'm just a signal specialist. I'm looking for a fight. Excuse me. Excuse me
No, no, I didn't want to fight leave me alone. Get me in the boat. Get me in the boat
Jeez Titanic all over again. Get me in that boat. Oh
I forgot it's just a little more down here. It's dare
Do you know the song from grills kids with guns? Oh
No, sorry, I thought you're referencing that music video. I know the what's that other one? I really like humility
I don't want no
Isolation
You see say I'm in now
Unfortunately, I don't know the words very well like I never oh, I'm just jumping most of them except in all these
I've unlocked a nail gun veteran pack. I
Can call in a motor strike hold on a minute. Hold on a minute. This is actually maybe I admit
It's a little bit cool. I'll definitely keep zoom because it keeps me away significantly increased damage
Oh, but that one's
Calling an airstrike destroying every enemy and be aware it takes a few seconds for the strike to arrive
Maybe just defense I think defense speed and health to get me out of there and whatever the last one was
Invisibility and zoom get me out of whatever situation I'm in the video with Jack black
Yeah, yeah, so I'm about to go full fortune it's on the nappy. I don't know what fortune this one is but
Hot hot take coming in. Oh, I don't like the gorillas. Oh, yeah, that's okay. You don't have to like everything
Some things are for some people and some things aren't for some people that is how the world work
I don't think anyone should be punished. However, if you don't like Assassin's Creed brotherhood, then I will happily
Put you in either
Mercy's basement or she bees
Dungeon take your pick, you know up to you
Um
Right, we are just skipping through this for those of you have kind of just joined in you're not quite sure what's going on
Um, we have successfully finished the nappy side of this game
We are now purposely joining the RDA, which I have never actually played before but we are still in the tutorial section
So I know what comes up ahead like it's not a big deal or anything like that
and I
Prepare a paranoid myself
You're always a good girl. Whoa
Hold on a minute, why am I getting praised out nowhere?
What are they? Oh, what do I do? Oh, what do I do?
Not everything know everything but no humor
Remain just noisy. Whoa, where's the print? Whoa. Whoa. You can't be doing this one
That's not fair. You know like to take me when I'm not prepared. Okay. That's not fair
That's cheat see doodling don't cheat see doodle. Okay, Dr. Harper. I presume
You must be rider
Let's get you a day needs to do something to prepare it. Oh, I mean, I mean you got you got get the guy give good
Funny, I think people in there are prizes no punishments
I'm not here to make enemy
Then we'll get along just fine now, please go and assist
Oh
It's gonna be so weird doing the RDA side you listen noob. I need you to grab me some florist
Listen noob. You ain't afraid of a few carnivorous plants. Are you aren't afraid of a flower among friends?
We aren't friends. Oh, you need to learn quick. Okay. Jeez. Lois. Talk about being unfriendly around these part
Make her blush for every bad joke of today's stream. Honestly, it's been pretty rough
Right if I remember correctly, there's literally
Yeah, um, okay. I've just noticed that we have infinite ammo on this gun
One that's not how they work
to
Actually, it's a wee bit of a pet peeve the one all we should watch those Keanu Reeve movies because they have the ammo reload thing, correct
And how am I trying to say it like in movies where they just like
With a pistol and like pistol literally have seven max like if you're talking like the M7 or something like that
Why where the enemies I can hear them. Oh
Well, I did ask to see them and I can see them loud and clear
Jeez the camp. I'm stuck on something. Oh
Jesus, I need I need some space. I need some space in order to like actually shoot please game
If you're not gonna give me aim assist at least let me fricking shoot
They sound like buzzle gum from Viva Pinata, it's almost like they're based after flies
Why
Johnson the Baba Yaga
Wic. Yes, that one we should watch those because I like how they're actually accurate with the goons
It's very nice that they're accurate with the reading. I love the way John Wic uses reloads to set the case for gun face
I don't know you'll notice that that's true
Unlimited ammo and mass effect
Someone said I might like mass effect
I've actually never played the series before but some said I might like it. I
Know he's called Sheppard
That's about it. Oh, no, I don't need to do that at all. I'm getting confused
All the John Wick movies are good. Yeah, speaking of John Wick. Have you played cyberpunk? No, I haven't I watch
Shia cyberpunk
but I am
I am still absolutely heartbroken about Rebecca. I am so sorry. Is it
Her name is Rebecca. What's the name of the?
The cyber
You're over the rainbow here. Is it Lucy?
Is it Rebecca and Lucy like brotherhood? I'm getting brotherhood. That's awesome screw brother. Wait, it is Rebecca and Lucy
What are the odds that assassin creep brotherhood and
cyberpunk the anime I
Am I am heartbroken over Rebecca? I'm so sorry. I'm gonna see something so controversial
I have no comprehension no
Comprehension on how Rebecca just doesn't auto win like people like all this see this
Lucy
Lucy are you can you open your eyes and look at how perfect Rebecca is? I'll actually tell you some more development notes and
You don't have Rebecca's voice
And on the concept of I see obviously I see before I see you know applied and all of that
We actually were quite happy to give I see to
Someone like that may have had a deeper voice because of Rebecca from cyberpunk. So that's a fun
Behind-the-scenes and I am not over Rebecca my first
Trigger I
Actually, I'm interested in potentially cosplaying her for an ace more stream
And I think that would be a hoot and holler and I won't show my face
I'd not
I'm not for that and
But I'm happy to do like
a
Nick down
I'm good to sip of my honey tea to see if it's a sip but yeah, I don't know Lucy everyone arguing about Rebecca and Lucy
I'm like, how is anyone looking at Lucy Rebecca's just peak like design everything
You know, it's a really sad detail if you haven't seen the cyberpunk anime close your ears for about two minutes
And after no, no, I need to say this part out loud close your ears for two minutes
If you don't want spoilers about cyberpunk the anime the really sad fact is that Rebecca
Got an upgrade to her hands
after her brother died to the the crazy guy because of the blowback she got from the shotgun
She never gets any root ricochet from shotguns anymore after that fact after that scene and it's such a sad fact
But yeah, and
Anyway, sorry back to the camp back to the actual gameplay
I'm just really passionate
The cyber cycle. Yeah, so the cyber cycle takes out her brother
But in that scene she shoots a shotgun at him and she goes backwards and then after that moment her
Her hand upgrades come in like her fisty cuffs and she never experiences recoil when shooting weaponry
And it's all because of that incident
And it's so sad
But her design is just beautiful. Absolutely beautiful
Let me drink my tea
The recoil so a little background on Rebecca studio trigger was asked to change her because
Her design was too lollipop a trigger went now lollipops these
Rebecca definitely influenced I see
Creation with the hips area and the legs. I'm not even gonna pretend otherwise a peak design. Sorry I
Knew from the get-go. I wanted a troupe a tan, which is what Emy was and then I see
and
It's not true pattern
but and but I did want her to have like the thickness of Rebecca basically it is I mean
I'm happy to talk about development. I know it's and
Like a Zura. We knew we wanted a chocolate and thick. So we've got a goddess and
Yeah, we just took it from there. Obviously. Um, sorry, let me finish this to you. Oh
Yeah
Adam Sandler said you look like a cut of me. Are you wait in the game? I'm pretty sure that's from the game
I'm sure I've seen a clip of that game
Coming down with the
I'll actually tell you some other developmental notes, you know, if I had a lighter voice
a me
Amie's design and every in lore and everything if I had a lighter voice
I
Would death will be a
I would death will reflect if I had a lighter voice
But unfortunately I don't and so, you know, I take like the the big sister look approach
Yeah, don't be surprised if it an alternative outfits, so I look a bit more true to myself and I am
I suppose I'm a Rebecca. How tall is Rebecca?
No, I do it in centimeters. Don't give me freedom units. I can't do freedom units
But I guess Rebecca's really very reflective. I think that's probably why I'm gravitated towards her so much as well
Because I'm just like hey, like I just love her
I'm gonna leave for the night. So here's your bro teeth brushing. Yes. Thank you
So I'm gonna burp my tea up if I'm not careful hold on a minute
No, I'm just gonna check how far away my my delivery is of my Mac is my cheeky Mac is any any Mac
It's still on its way freaking driver at the restaurant always driver at the restaurant
It's never drivers picked it up and it's already on its way
It's always at the restaurant just hanging about waiting for a second freaking order. I
Know that shit's gonna get here cool
The version 2.0 update they did on smashers
He needed the update who's smash her she's a hundred and forty five one fifty. Oh, I'm too tall for Rebecca
Oh, I need to get at that to the same board
For now, I'll just use my
Adam's matter. Oh
The guy that says the quote she's around one five two wait. I'm out. No, I'm not I'm one six. Okay
Okay, take Rebecca and make her slightly taller. Oh my god me. She's so me for real for real
She's so me for real
Behold how tall she's streaming on out. Mm-hmm. True. Oh
No, it's time
We're the baddies
He said the B word wait, why the stuff that was put the B word together
Oh
I'm sad. I don't want to expect from here on out though. It's Johnny told Rebecca comes honestly
We can't see
The donations are broken again. Are they actually great work, right? I smell promotion in the air. Oh, yeah, pay
Better not. Please tell me you guys haven't given me so much money. It's broken again
Have you broken it again, be honest be honest. There's a page not load. I
Like the edits of John Wick and cyberpunk so funny of him see yes. Oh my god
I wanted to do that with the girls debuts, but I don't have time. I have the highlight
There are currently two out of six highlight debuts
Created so far and I'm so excited
It mercies and azures, but I'm gonna release them all at the same time
but mercies and azures have been made and
The rest are on the way. It's so exciting
It's loading but not going through it. Wow. I really is broke. Wow
Thanks again for breaking
Are you guys at all?
It's never never we're the baddies
Against these guys we can take them
Let's do it right now right now. I order you to shoot
Well, this is it
This is it
We're doing it we're the baddies
We'll just spam them down I guess
I
Missing because of the hit marker
Please don't heal don't make this harder than it has to be unironically because I'm not I feel bad
I picked the woman's
I
Didn't think that was possible. Have you broken it twice? Hold on
You feel
Wait, what happens? No, I can't be a Navi like I'm a fully human like I'll never be able to go back
Wait a word good girl. Oh, yeah, so it does work
Thank you for the tip no, I don't know what to respond to that
Maybe
Well, wait, so it does work and maybe just Tame and yo because it's
It works in fire folks
Anyway, you don't actually have to tip or donate or anything
But thank you very much
We just got annihilated by a Banshee cheese. Oh
Well, we all saw that move in the frame, but hey, oh
Okay, this is actually quite different. I thought he was just gonna
Wow, I didn't even know
We don't have to but we want to give her
Oh my gosh, okay
Well, we survived a helicopter crash and an attack from an akra
Are you all right? I think I'm okay, but the pilots banged up pretty bad
Radio's fried, too. You've got to go for help
Don't worry, I'll be fine. I've got a full clip any vultures
Have to go out on my own
No, I don't want to go out on my own. I'm scared
Oh
Have I got you oh wait, so is this my wardrobe change? Oh, I literally is it's just more
That's just follow the hood that says to go this way what she shouldn't she shouldn't what she is
Things can attack me from the sky as well
Hmm
Wait, these aren't recycled maps at all
No, the plan I'm scared wait, I can't have a limit on
Is it maybe the head is gonna take more damage
I
Flamethrowers are effective against all plants that have one
Don't have a flamethrower. Oh I have infinite pistol. Okay. Okay
I have to show my shooting skills
Literally, I thought they were just gonna recycle all of the maps, but this is like an entirely new side of the game
I know this sounds so silly, but I just assumed the recycle the maps and like oh
I'm claiming that all right
Okay, I can do it
Okay, I've got more ammo
Did he do the ikran?
Okay, I get points for this. Oh, I'm so tiny. I'm so small. I can't even I can't even see over the freaking grass to see the enemies
Oh my gosh, give me more ammo. Oh
Stop spawning in I need to heal
Right, we're doing a biz
There's one over
Oh
I can do it. I can do it. I can do it. I need a level up so quick so I can just keep spamming that run
There's so many plants in the way as well
I'm so tall. I'm so small. I'm not myself tall. Oh
I can't do it. I'm actually sweating right now
Can I make it through the poison without having to destroy them all the time? Oh
Please keep your ink to yourself
What are these? Are these bombs? Oh
I think the pretty I don't the purple have health. I think they're
Well, there's no secret behind this waterfall like in Legend of Zelda
Right, let's try that again. I didn't know me. Yeah, I didn't know me to the oh good as we
Using vehicles and amp suits will be your friend. Okay, so I'm gonna says oh
Moby heart, right, let's try that again without doing that
No running
Just shoot. Why are you not responding? Can I respond or my game already broke?
All right, hold on hold on. I think my delivery app just a just oh, oh my delivery
Hold on. We've got a food delivery. Is that gonna swipe for me as a health bar?
Hold on. Let me go at the front door
Oh
There
Oh, yeah, okay, I'm glad that thing doesn't slip down and like take my fricking eyeballs out must go
Rather terrifying my McDonald right. I've got chicken nuggies for everyone open your mouth go
Wow, I've got
Is the fricking how you call it this the thingy my Bulbas
Why the wicked it is so bad for me
But if it's bad for me
Well, it's a lamp in the Navy so brave. I'm sorry. I'm so bad at this like
Mmm, you're having a sip of my chocolate milkshake. Yes, I'm actually having a chocolate milk shake at 9 a.m
And then nothing you can do about it
Is it cold you bet your ass it's cold because that guy was sitting at a flipping restaurant for ages
Okay, um, I would tab out to read any
Marshmallows, however the game breaks when I do that. So I'm just gonna read chat and munch away
So, please if you don't like munching sounds and he's live. She's live, but me I'm a munching your ears
I'm having a beer at 7 a.m. I
Will enjoy my new they just spicy nuggies so I've got spicy
And mukbang time honestly
More headpats for the most adorable cutlery
Okay
Hopefully I don't mess up too many times actually doing the RDA campaign, but I have to admit
It's like terrifying. I had no I thought the maps were gonna be the same and I was like, okay
At least the maps are the same and I'm familiar with the past. Nope
Mmm
I don't they apparently sold 2.7 million copies of this game
Yeah, that seems really low for like any game. I feel like that. Does that mean it full-option?
Mm-hmm, I'm gonna inspire people to get a McDonald's breakfast at this rate
You it
A little hard in America they do 24 hour breakfast, so I'm jealous. I have to admit
You still think the tips are slightly broken or you're getting limited. Oh
Hmm
I'm not sure
That
Last tip did come through I wonder why that would be maybe reach every region locked
No, that seems silly, that's the answer I
Don't like break I don't like the breakfast menu of most fast food places rather try it for me menus on
I know it sounds weird, but I love to make some nuggies a salad and put them both together and
Wheatwrap and yogurt that just sounds like a
and
What's that Greek thing? Where's the chicken in a wrap?
I've completely not kebab, but like it's on different
We're back in 10 minutes
See you shortly
and a
Jiro
Fun fact gyro means to be on benefits in Scotland
Alarm gyro, okay gyro is great. Oh, but it's with pork. Okay. Okay. Oh
It's over
It's pronounced you know
Then why did the Fanny's put a G in front of it?
We've got them got them in 4k as I drop a chip on me. Oh
Oh
It's and it's gif
It's not a Jeff. It's a gif. I don't know why Jeff started and if your name is Jeff
Or should I be like, I can grasp your names Jeff because it sounds like Jeff I
Don't comprehend where Jeff came from unless it was from non native English speakers. That's the only like and
Thingy, I don't know why it is a thing. Obviously. It's funny in internet culture, but why is it Jeff?
I know Jeff literally
My name is Jeff I feels good man. I'm sorry
Literally G and gif it's also there's a second and
The UK it's a shop called pray mark. Okay. It's like a clothes shop. It's like and
It's called pray mark, but folks say it pre mark and the folk that say it pre mark
I'm talking to you right now directly
Do you say primary school or do you say primary school?
You say primary school. So the shop is called pray mark and I will not like let's oh
Congrats if you names mark by the way
I don't know why
It's a debate and the UK
Pray Murray
It's the same one pre mark noise. No, it's pray mark primary school pray mark
Hi to all marks. Yeah. Hi mark. Hi
Congrats if you names mark
Also, Jeff is a peanut butter company. Is it
Okay
our peanut butter and
And jelly sandwiches actually is tasty as
American movies make it out to be because all kids unanimously in TV shows have a PB and J
Is it actually that good or is it being hyped up as I choke on my food?
It's a comfort food. Yes, it's okay. She seems to think so. Okay. She be's word is law
Yes, it's overhyped. Yes. It's an acquired taste. It's good yet. PB and J is good
They can't be it's okay. Diabetes in a sandwich
I
Absolutely, they're a good tree. Okay. It's a tree kind of not like a everyday thing
Mmm, I skipped the jelly and only the peanut bar
I've tried the jar ones it's
Pretty okay, but just okay
It's a thing they are raised on so as a result. They love it. Mmm. I
Suppose like iron brews my example if you don't drink iron brews a kid, you'll never have a taste for it
It's so bizarre and flavor
It's like that and
Japanese natto
fermented soybeans is a breakfast thing
apparently if you are a back-of-guy gene and
You like it's really hard to enjoy natto unless you like force yourself to eat it over a while and then you get used to that
Yeah, like it's hard it's hard to get into it. Mmm
Remember the old commercial from it made from
Gerders
It's cheap as heck and that's why we eat it so much
I've had peanut butter toast and banana and it's delicious. It's very nice
What's iron brews supposed to taste like they advertise it as ginger and bubblegum and it tastes like battery acid that's only
explicable
Way that you can see what that orange liquid tastes like it's battery acid, but nice
Mmm
Literally mountain juice is the closest you'll ever get to it
That is just not positive. Sorry. I'm trying to eat and talk and I want to eat the food as fast as possible
So I'm not holding up the gameplay too much. Hmm. I
Take a drink from my chucky milkshake
Hmm, they forgot to give me a straw. So I'm literally just drinking out of it like some animal
Hmm, do you see mountain dew? Yes, I said mountain dew
Oh dude, no
Mountain dew, mountain dew, mountain dew. Whoa, that's so close
Mountain dew. Whoa, you can't tell the difference when I say that
Oh, that's crazy. Mountain dew
Whoa, it sounds like I'm saying Jay, but I'm no
I'm saying you
Oh, that's so cool
Did you drink my manju? Oh, that's weird
Mmm, okay, I didn't know I said I like that because I'm here now literally
Did you drink my manju?
Wow, why does it sound like that? I can hear it. No, do you
Did you drink my mountain dew?
Dew
Yeah, I've tried manju. I don't think it tastes like I'm brutal
No, but it's it's only the closest thing. It's a German. I feel not good here. Monka is bro
Love
To do a drop of dew and a dew gets all the same pronunciation
You now have a new earworm enjoy
All right, I've got two more nuggies left and then I've got this like uh burger mcgrittle thingy
I don't know what it's called. It's called mcmuffin. That's what we call it mcmuffin, but I think it's called mcgrittle
Mountain dew was originally made to be a mixer for whiskey
I don't know when I'm gonna do my first like drunk stream
I'm down for drunk karaoke, but I would have to rest my voice a day before
I was very nervous about it like the first time I ever did it, but now I know that
I'm not hitting them notes. So I'm gonna go for it. I'm gonna send it
Mmm
The original coca-cola had cocaine in it. Honestly, I just know that
It would just have been such a good time to be drinking that stuff, you know what I'm saying
I
I'm sure I learned as well that um, what did I learn that they used to prescribe like um
I was a heroine they used to prescribe that if you were feeling rough back in the day
The drunk stream would give a hundred percent a hundred out of hand barb, I'm sorry
Here in brazil come to brazil many restaurants serve nuggets with creamy cheese or green green sauce
What would green sauce consist of would be some sort of veggie blended up
I would do cheese sauce definitely
Sorry, I'm looking my fingers like an animal
Most of the nasty addictive drugs started as medicines honestly like they were just having a good time back then
I just choked. Um, I don't know if you've ever heard about this guy called Sigmund Freud
He was absolutely wild and with his theories, but he was also highly addicted to
and um
Like a lot of his stuff got discredited, but like as time progresses he gets proven right again and again
Um
Also, there is the oh my god, this looks fucking awesome. I'm gonna take a big juicy bite for you
Oh
I went out yesterday after stream to get those american sweets
um
The lady was so nice. She was like, oh, can I help you anything?
and I'm just like
Anything american you've got
That's like smaller packaging
I would love to take away with me because i'm just gonna taste it all
And she was like so nice and helpful
But she was so surprised with how much i'm buying and I didn't want to be like, oh i'm written them on a stream and all that
I was just like, I'm just really passionate about american sweets. Yeehaw
All right
Hmm it was like a
Ammonpaw independent shop that I supported
And I'm gonna inhale another bite. This is good. Yeehaw. Sorry, that is that's just what I imagined like am I at yeehaw at any moment yeehaw
They used to prescribe, they used to prescribe smoking at people we asked them off. That's terrible. Go on a brother
You got a pretty accurate spread of my, well like I put the picture in the discord for the girls to rate it
and I told them
I spent 53 dollars getting all of that stuff and they were like you got absolutely scammed
Like that's not even worth 12 dollars. I'm like, oh, okay
But um, I'm gonna make a little
Rate thing
um
Like where I rate them
So hopefully we'll do a fun little chart. I don't know if I'm gonna like anything
I think I'm interested in this was it spicy cheetos I call or spicy thingy or the or tackies or whatever
I always hear about tacky
um
And it was
Mmm
It was rough, but like I'm gonna support like a wee independent shop. So
Eat the chips last it's overpowering. Oh, okay. Okay. Okay. We're getting the strats. Thank you, mayor
See for the strats
Are you streaming the day? Well we T-minus well less than four hours for mercies. Use your start time
I
Don't know what don't I thought dr. Pepper was in the uk but
I think I'm confusing it with pepsi. I genuinely can't remember if I've ever tried dr. Pepper if it's an american thing
Oh, you're playing that climbing game. I remember the thumbnail
Because we had your skirt was open so we had to close your skirt
Honestly, maybe that should be a toggle for you. No, I'm not. Maybe we should toggle that so you don't have to worry
Dr. Pepper isn't the okay. I've just never tasted it before literally i'm brewing cola
I used to be a fan of fiend and a sprite fiend as well
But fan are like addicted to so much
I do have an american dr. Pepper so at least I can stay true to the the task at hand not my open skirt, honestly
Then you can accidentally toggle on and off and stream true
The only person who worries for receiving followers aim
Dr. Pepper taste dr. Pepper taste kind of cola with with mint mint mint fizzy juice
I'm not sure mint fizzy juice is gonna go down well with me. I do apologize
I just remembered i'm not sure another brazilian already took it first
So i'll do it myself come to brazil cutlass congrats. You're the first one to do it
Come to brazil
I don't think I know any
Plus so tell a bay
So so tell a bay is all I can say
I'm almost finished. I'm so sorry for those who are waiting on the gameplay
I think dr. Pepper tasted medicine
mint
Not like cinnamon. Sorry not ice cream soda just cream soda
Dr. Pepper's cherry cola
Hmm
The guys see the online discourse about the ingredients in like american food versus like any other country
And like so much stuff has been banned
Hmm
Hey, stroney, did you know that mint and spicy can be active at the same time in your mouth try it in your experience heck
Mint and spicy
I've never even thought of that. Yeah, that's never occurred. It's like spicy water
It'll be interesting to see what you actually enjoy
Hmm
I think that other drink was a and w
Root by air. I think I got like creamy. I think it was cream soda or creamy soda a root by air root by air
No, root by your root by air
McDonald's you can check for ingredients but don't you say 35 ingredients most of them are code numbers?
Oh, yeah, american drinks for instance. They often use high fructose corn syrup and
What happens if I ingest high fructose corn syrup die like explode? It's a dangerous
Hmm
No, kinder eggs
Actually, you know what's even sadder about the kinder egg ban the new realize
The only reason those children
Hmm past because of the kinder egg was because their parents weren't even paying attention to them
Which is such a wee shame like it's
Um
They have to ban it
Instead of being like hey here public announcement pay attention to your little ones because we didn't know
um
little ones explore
Using their mouth. That's why you can imagine literally licking any surface because you did it as a wee babby
It's an exploratory thing. You you learned so much from it
Like for example if I tell you
Uh to imagine what it's like licking a cold pole with rain
It's gonna sound i'm in danger. Why is it red? Why is it red? I saw that
I saw that I just entered combat there for a second
Monka is Monka is I saw that those like I'm not watching your game
um
My HUD went red. I I'm covering up the HUD like with my big hair
But it went red which meant I was under attack there. So I don't know what just happened
The kinder the American kinder egg man is real if I was a mean no I feel
Oh
Is that also why there's no toys in the cereal and everyone thought about that
I'll flew into my cross here. Mm-hmm
Okay, last bite
Last bite. I'm gonna go get a cola. Actually, I wouldn't mind a cola after that
Just to really really make sure my health was really bad. Uh, mcdonald's on a cola. Why not?
I won't make
I'm so true that's a oh my god my headset
My headset just moved in a flinch. I don't think I was getting attacked in real life
Yes, I was
I'm farming the dump it on this one
I ain't swallowed this before I choke. Hold on a minute
Oh
Okay, cola time have a little sip of cola with the edge. I'll try and have a little bit more of that milkshake
Yucky milkshake
Right, I've probably got a big burp generator eaten because I've just eaten so I do apologize unless you want me to get out of the way in there
Mm-hmm, so I can have a sip you absolutely can't have a sip of the cola
Oh, so how's the Nutella seen in your countries?
Uh as Nutella
Although I know in the Belgium they have these like adorable little self-serve size Nutella
I don't know where the burp is it's hiding in me, right? Right. I'm a big girl
I'm a big girl. I can just ignore literally everything
Nutella is on a cracker honestly. Oh, there we go. It's all coming up now
Make it stop make it stop right I think that's it
Okay, there we go. No, they're never in it right. I'm not running off the map this time
Whoa, that was a joke
I'll let oh I got 50 for that one is it because it was multiple in a row
Oh, there's another one for you. It's all coming up. No, it's all coming up this
Yeah, we're
Where are we going?
Where are we going? No one's no one
Kaka kaka combo breaker
Bonus one breathe in have a big whiff I go
Mmm delicious. Oh my goodness. What's this? What's this?
Can I fly it out and those helipads it looks like it?
Whoa, they swoop that actually have to be careful of them. No our guys are just tolerating their presence
Wow
So I can use the bikes to get a boot
Okay, okay. Boom. Okay
Oh
Thought some marmate. I've actually no had it. What is going on in here. Hello. Oh, this is like a proper facility as well
Who the hell are you?
Chopper went down over that ridge and my team's still back there. I need a new bird. How are you so perfect?
You've landed in a bloody hell all night
Banshee's been killed by men, but thanks for the company
I've not tried it. No our vigilmate. No
She's fueled up better firing circuits are fried because everyone's giving it such a terrible review
I'm like, I don't really want to spend money on it just to like have a wee dip
Look around they destroy my paper. You don't have to tell me
That's the weird. Oh, that's the weird thing because you are okay. You're timing the blush or something. Hmm
Um, actually, I should probably you know, I paid a lot. I'm not gonna lie. I paid a lot for all these emotes
Uh, yeah, man's not using them. Well, I'm just I'm just a bad
I'm just a bad streamer, but it's fine. It's fine. We work. We do a thing
But like I'm not being funny. How am I supposed to be mid game? And then like someone goes good girl and I'm like, all right
Hold on. Hold on. Hold on pause pause the game. Let me just uh, okay
Like I mean you can hear it in the flexion of my voice. Okay
God, it will send a ger a vegemite if you
We were discussing should we have p.o boxes
But I said to the girl like it's just far too dangerous on this day and age
Like with trackers and stuff and there's been so many streamers
That oh
Oh, that's how to go up. Oh, right. Okay. I'll go up like this. Whoa. Whoa
Uh, how do I move? Oh, this is awful. Oh
Hold on. Oh my god. This is how to go up. Go up
Oh, this is awful. This is even worse. This is even worse than writing. Oh, no. Oh, no, the flowers are mean
Oh, this is not gonna end well. I'm not gonna end alive in this. I can just tell
Hold on. Uh, right. Just bear with me. Bear with me
Icy's in the room because bear with me. Holy. No, don't get me out. Can I land like right now? How do I land? Okay
Okay, let's get out. That was awful. I was literally having to say blame that
That was terrible. Don't recommend
Oh, he perished the banshees are pretty hairy out there. You're gonna need the chopper missile online and fast
Grab new firing circuits from the samson ruckage
I'm sure regiment wouldn't be considered a bio weapon
And uh
Oh unlock new outfit or new perks upgrade them perks already. Okay
Okay, I'm starting to understand why that supersonic thing is the one because they gang up so quickly
Yeah, can you reload please? There's literally an invisible one. He's cheating. Oh my goodness
Oh
Oh, where is he? I hear him
You don't feel that
No, you don't feel that that didn't hurt. I know even a little bit
Jesus
Jeez Louise right what am I doing here?
What am I doing
Am I to search the craft or something? Oh, okay
Kendra save me Kendra
Kendra
Kendra, please start shooting Kendra
Kendra Kendra
I know you can see me spraying and praying for my life right now Kendra
Oh Kendra
The biggest pet peeve if you give an enemy that can shoot an ally that can shoot but they aren't doing nothing
Right, am I safe? No, please. Can I enter the cutscene or am I about to get like absolutely mugged in the cutscene?
Give me
No wonder only two people have played this
That should clear up the skies and help Kendra. Hey, you've got to help naga this. Where are you going?
She just stands there watching me
Check out
Oh, no people box. I'm just have to send money money instead. What a shame. Huh?
Whoa
What we doing?
Wait unlock again. Is this like super easy to level up as an rda?
Hmm
Right i'm to use
The helipad
I put it did I leave it? Whoa who parked it? Who driving this aircraft? This is terrible park
How to go up?
Oh my god, this is awful
Whoa
Hold on
Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Okay
Oh my god, this is awful. Oh, wow. Whoa there. I'm getting bombed
Pandora
Pandora like super strong and I whoa, whoa, whoa
Can I like shoot that one from here?
This is awful. I'm so sorry the controls are not like straightforward with this
I'm just trying to see it back in the spray. No, I'm not hitting. Oh, this is terrible
Close your eyes. Don't look mercy. Don't look you're gonna vomit
I don't really want to get hurt by that, but I think I'm gonna have to
Oh, I'm out of like the render distance for it, but there we go. Oh
Where's the next one?
Wait, there's one behind me apparently it's right behind me. Uh, no
We're oh, whoa. Whoa easy easy easy easy. Oh
Wait, so I can like actually die in these choppers
Oh my god
Oh, did I do it? No, I got you now
Where's the Dancino?
Get me out of this like right now. Seriously
Go up and then go forward a bit and up and forward and up and forward and up and forward right just up
And then we'll go just forward. Okay
Easy easy on the tilt. Why are you it's literally tilting me? I don't know why insist on tilting
Squishy human versus navi with their carbon fiber reinforced bones. Honestly. Oh my god. I just missed the helipad as well
Oh, let me sit then get get me out of that. I'm gonna vomit if I'm in that any longer
You guys can deal with the freaking bad guys because I'm just absolutely rubbish. Get me inside
You have rockets. Oh, I didn't know. Okay. That might be a bit easier
I'm holding on good girl. Wait. Why are we thinking?
Must be because everything wants to hurt you here
Wounded our inbound
How's the game so far we've completed the navi and we're doing the bad bad human side now
I'm going to keep this simple, but I don't know what to expect. I'm pretty scared of that because I've never played this side
This project starts with you our signal specialist
This is the sector you're currently in. We need you to go to these three ports
Once there you must collect small shards of unobtainment. Oh, right. So we're literally doing
Directly the opposite. I mean that makes sense
But right now just get those three unobtainium shards. Don't worry too much about the details, writer. We don't have a lot of time
Okay
Good Falco out. You heard the man
Oh
Okay. Yeah, I have a few questions. All right. I'm out
Uh, honestly, I'm like leveling up so much. I don't know I can call in I've got weapons up for it as well
It's trying to hate humans
We are not humans
And you make it a lot harder for yourself than it has to be
Hey
Look, I'm no very smart. Okay. All right. I think that one will have full health. Where am I? Am I flying? Oh, I'm it's a flying
That has to be flying. There's no way I can do that on foot. Sorry. There's no way right. Who's ready to get motion sick me?
Okay, let's first turn to the first wait woman's closest. Yeah, that one is closest
Okay, first let's get hate so we don't bump into the walls or anything
Is this the ceiling of the game is wow, we're already at the ceiling. Okay, uh
Sorry ceiling of the map. My apologies. Hold on
Whoa, this is like humongous. What? Um
Oh my god, this is so much harder than driving an ikaran
Am I looking for
We're dead plant we're dead part. You know, don't you guys don't have a helipad here?
Oh, there's navi down there. Oh, I'm gonna get rolled by them. Hold on wait
I can see transport over here, which makes me think it's safe to put down the chopper here
I don't know if that's true, but we'll try it. Oh my god. We're about to go against navi for the first
Oh my god, that's horrifying
Oh my god
That's horrifying
Oh, I don't like that. I don't like that. I don't like that. I don't like it. I don't like it. They're so big
They're genuinely so big
Oh my god, I don't know what to do. Is this a sniper shot?
No, this is a shotgun. Oh my god
Okay, it's a shotgun
Oh, he's using a billy
Oh, this is awful. This is
Okay, I'm a big girl. I'm a big girl. I can do it
Okay, it's fine
I can hear noises
I can see I'm getting shot at but it's okay. I've got oh, you're so big
Okay, okay, okay two two shorties and dead
I hear you I hear you
Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa. No, no, don't stop. Look you still lock me. I'll still lock you
Oh, not now
Okay, okay, okay, okay, it's okay. Okay. Let him get up. Let him get up. Let him get up
Let me reload
great
Whoa, whoa, whoa, they just keep coming
Oh my gosh, golly
What does the sales samples do? Do they not give me ammo? I'm gonna run out of ammo
I'm just gonna have to I think I'm just gonna have to go for it
If they come at me, I'm just gonna have to deal. I can hear them respawn in the corner of my ear. I'm no bothering. I'm no bothering. I'm sorry
Oh
Oh, oh, that's awful. That's horrendous. That is truly awful. I'm sorry that that height difference is freaking me out
They're like so long and elongated from this movie
Where'd I go? Where'd I go?
Oh, they never told me this was a freaking horror game
Oh
Oh, right. Okay. I'm going the completely wrong way, but
No, I need to go back
No, I don't know I don't because the cave's freaking collapsing
Oh
I don't like that. They're so tall and lanky
I don't like it. I don't like I don't like I don't like I don't like it. I'm so tall. I'm so tiny
I'm gonna have to pay
This is so freaking please. Please. Please. Please. Please one shot one shot
I can't do it. I can't do it. I can't do it. I just need a help from that guy. Is he the
only one I see the only one I'm just going for it oh where's my heel okay
that was heel oh my god like the creepy whisper it in my ears and help and
either no I want to be told I want to have third perspective we're gonna
actually see the enemies over the grass they need to be eradicated I can't
handle this I'm just gonna have to come back for I'm sorry I'm going to the
one oh okay okay okay it's relaxed here see like there's no baddies oh it's
getting so fun see okay yeah we're going the right way oh look how relaxed this is
see nothing's attacking me let's get fine I can I can handle the dogs I can't
handle the Navi they're too tall I don't mean that right okay excuse me just coming
through this holy site with a buggy I need a shard to keep myself from harm the
Navi are absolutely terrifying and the kills I need to farm
no go a chance okay wow it's actually quiet for once Christmas mark of course
they start in of course they spawn in of course they spawn in the moment I try
to achieve anything I'm not really stuck jump jump forward go I don't know
where to go I can't see anything and I'm getting barrage straight now okay leave
the buggy behind leave the buggy behind we don't need it we don't need it this
is gonna be a really rough four errors I'm gonna be honest I'm not oh please don't
unclog please don't unclog please don't unclog please do not unclog please don't
unclog I don't want to unclog for the Navi or lay I'm getting spanked and know
the good things oh my god oh my I'm getting gang violence come on right
right that's it that's it I'm trying I'm trying I'm trying they all have abilities
and they're all freaking ganging up on me and I don't even know what's behind me
how are you supposed to play this the RTA side honestly I'm just happy to see a
plant I don't mind if it wants to freaking do that to me I'm welcome over
these freaking Giants then there's like 12 of them behind me I'm making this
the most freaking stressful game experience of my life oh I can't handle this can I
get like knee surgery to elongate me so I can at least see a little bit or worse
like going no you know you're not even scary dogs it's the Navi that are
terrifying absolutely horrific hi pinbells height in me I'm currently
playing this horror game cause James Cameron avatar and absolutely more fine
wait there's a celliculture there don't want to take it no I go just take the
car how is your unlisted stream or I can archive stream with pinbells was she
being was she behaving hmm oh you guys have her oh she more I'm ignoring all
the Navi couldn't give less of a rat's arse what's going on oh there's dogs
everywhere as well what is bombing me no invisible oh I can't do this my we heart
can't say this where I'm supposed to go just got all the way back right I'm
gonna take that helicopter and we can get the heck out here and we've done one
of the four shard collection missions I assume it's just gonna copy the
previous tactics hi hi in me currently in a horror game right now awful it's
terrible oh we did homework and brushed teeth oh did you actually we're
brushing her teeth too is this gonna be another 12 hour stream no it's gonna be
eight hours if I don't die too much I have successfully completed the Navi
storyline in this game I'm having to go below because the map isn't letting me
go above is this a dead end
I'm not safe anywhere genuinely not safe anywhere how do I do my bombs I don't
know how to do bombs you say I have bombs but nothing oh whoa I do have bombs
okay well well I need to go up holy crap can you go up so we can get like a
bird's-eye view on these oh forget this day where can I land there's Navi
everywhere I can't believe it there's people everywhere that look here all
these controls are awful I missed the Falcon from Halo and literally I'm
getting wrecked and decked controls right I need to destroy that it crammed
I'm screen but I think I'm a render this is terrible oh my god this is awful
can I fly in here excuse me pardon me coming through excuse me right just land
just land this is awful land it won't let me land I can't believe it won't let
me land in the tiny freaking right a crayons get my face
right everything's getting annihilated I think there just won't right right I
think there's a landing spot over here this is my guess because of the map and
we can't see it my big heads covering up just just freaking get out of this
thing now get out how do you get out hello can I get out I'm stuck I'm stuck
in this freaking chopper get in my face honestly I need somewhere to park but
I'm about to park next to all these freaking Navi I ready to demolish my
boss okay there we go there we go we're actually out success I am playing the
lovely game of please ignore me and we're getting the heck out here and
we're just absolutely speedrunning these these are horrifying
Shawnee doesn't even know what she's doing only wait I'm probably really wrong
where the heck did you come from identify yourself she I killed all you's on
purpose and you've all respond
eat lead the archers are probably the worst because they can pin me at least
I know that other ones around the freaking corner yeah yeah no way that
still hit oh can you guys stop using your abilities I honestly do not remember
the soldiers even this amount of ability go all I'm getting again I grew no
and another one's just one follow the same vibrations I'm not the only one
that can use oh wait you're not the only one that can use freaking abilities
around here again aggressive oh here we go here we go here we go right
triangle time triangle time well this patch of dirt looks a bit different I
wonder if it was here where's the triangle somewhere over here oh this patch of
dirt looks slightly different okay we did it I played like two minutes this
game back and then dropped it yeah and you have to play the Navi side for it to
be and remotely rewarding if you want to play a horror game feel free to
report back to offer some adori I'll see you back at hell's gate oh
Midori how nice of you to show up when you could have done that like five
minutes ago and help them some firepower but why is on fire or is it just
dark becoming oiled I'm becoming the very thing I swore to destroy
right we've leveled up so we get more armor got yet more armor thank you well
my reward for it whoa whoa whoa you ain't taking me with you I got hurt by
that oh hey name's Trudy Chico hi Trudy Falco's assigned you to make sure you
don't go tango uniform on me T you means you're safe with me so let's get air
to you I ain't getting paid by the hour is that supposed to be the actual character
that was in the movie so fighting for humanity isn't easy no it's not oh okay
I don't even know that's good for that tee tee up any tee uppers freaking horror
game honestly who said play this hydration check no slipping tin of some
sort of liquid really matter what it is at the end of the day oh sorry I've just
why are you going to the side I don't know but I'm drinking all horrible she's
just really enthusiastic about the wall oh okay little cheeky camera I don't know
you're doing that but I hope that's not joy con drift oh that's what I should
name the gamer if we ever had a 2.0 model joy con drew with an eye with the joy
oh I need a like a wink sound like a whee every time I wink it goes wheezy
hello writer you brought actually don't know the let's get start the dialogue
still got some time before the emulators up and running the emulator you don't know
yet all in good time right now we need to upload that harmonic pop it into the
module and let's see what we've got okay sure here we go what's happening now what's
all this stuff for doc yes let me explain the knobby have a unique relationship with
the plan using a sacred site they're able to link directly with the ecosystem it's
how they communicate with the entire so we're searching for something different
our research there is another site that can help us sever the knobby community
con already has my joy stick place the knobby call the well if we can find this
old this is why they aren't letting you name any more car honestly I know as a
I'll never live down from the liberal but honestly best name this is where your harmonics
come in right we don't know where this dormant site is hi so the harmonic helps you find its
location I'm actually enjoying these cutscenes because I've never seen them before we can
triangulate the precise location of the dormant well of soul okay now let's see what your first
harmonic shows
excellent did you notice the red dots no those are supposed to be a cutscene with each harmonic
will reduce the number of red dots cutscene cutscene docu will be our well of soul red dots docu
you're up for this plan indeed now it's time to check in with commander falco for your next mission
okay I've got your next mission on deck
officer midori will meet you fever a new area they really didn't recycle any of the
map escort you ain't no plumber you'll be good with it and a score oh my god dug it help please
please dug it help of love uh we can partner in crime for those tree huggers are crying foul over
this emulator all worried about
Monroe mentioned that what is this emulator you stay focused on your mission writer you start
growing the conscience and you'll end up on the dead end of a knobby spear dismiss okay okay falcon
is your travel to fable hmm that's where they made different maps reach when I genuinely assumed
it was just gonna be recycled I can't believe it I'm surprised but we've picked up one song so we need
two more songs and then I assume the third we destroy it or the navi destroy it before we get
it so it's like literally a complete hundred I could flip yeah words and stuff um hello please
fly me to the flea ball let's hit the envelope just promise me no power she really said no
projectile woman the fever I feel like I'm gonna be even more scared
are you disappointed that they didn't reuse assets since you know the RDA
period now I'm just a surprise like I just assumed the opposite was going to be the same
maps but we're attacking from a different side but just watch yourself out there I'll drop you
at the load with midoring I'm being so fuel I'll catch you on the other side
well back into the free let's unlock this teleport first and then get assigned or
quest from Kendra welcome to the fever you need to link up with our forward units
they've got orders to secure your shards be careful these guys are in that's what it was
I was I was wondering why the voice sense so familiar
kind of sad they put so much effort into it didn't get much traction
I think in 2.7 million sales you made your money back though
so investors can't feel too bad I think I don't know if like avatar because when the
movie came out it was like this big unexpected hit like no one expected it how do I
motion sick buggy okay warning for motion sick people
oh right here we go first take a right far or maybe to the
well go talk to the person however we need to obtain this quest from okay no navi please
you guys freak me out to high heavens seriously oh in the plants even when I'm in the buggy
oh my okay okay okay it's like lamp posts in that one game
oh oh I didn't see it it just came out of nowhere because it's the same color
shade okay let's just accept the mission first
hello
oh I can hear a navi's bow and arrow behind me in this cutscene
uh kill the hammerhead before well I do seem to be a level I'm not real quick though
can I get more armor please courage pack you know what whoa I can hear that oh I knew it
oh I need like a long range gun
come on now let me reload before we do this oh our we're gonna cut some
I've heard really went nuts in here whoa wait we don't even get to meet these in the navi side I
didn't even think they were in game oh my god I'm just so surprised about everything
medic medic oh are you okay get back up man get back up are you joking me after that
is that me I hope that's not me and they're about to put me in the cutscene where it's right
like gameplay where it's right in front of me thank goodness I thought it was pranking me man
let's see what the deal here is
oh come on
what are you surprised I dashed to the side I need to get like vertical like right now holy
why is that only going for me
I need is there like a rock I can hate on I need cheese on a rock like right now I need cheese on
this rock I'm not even being funny I need to like breathe on this rock I need to cheddar on this rock
I need to do anything on the rock please jump on the rock it's all I ask I'm so small I can't
jump on basic rocks okay uh yeah see this is why I don't even want to bother
I don't know why I just changed its mind I am going to see if I can shoot from the spine over here
I can hear it get closer to me I'm vertical though what you're gonna do about it nothing
because you can't do anything when I'm vertical I maybe okay it seems like it can't come here
yes oh I'm out of ammo already
get ready whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa you got a lot closer that time
I am going to run out of ammo well before this thing perishes Azura's just gone live
okay if anyone is interested Azura Dulay is streaming whoa can it hurt me
it can just stun me
I just put my hand on my head I'm like uh
uh I feel it oh Azura is playing one shot okay
hey starting do you think the notification discord could also post the girl schedules it'd be helpful
um
maybe I don't know I'm like seriously have no ammo
maybe it's a shotgun kind of thing wait do I have more weapons
so that's my wee shotgun which does them up cool so that's my standard rifle that's my
maybe change this to what a nail hunter put back oh
what not is it going down
I don't know his health doesn't really look like it's going down now I'm absolutely spraying and
praying I'm not gonna lie a motor strike maybe yeah that probably seems much more likely because
this is like really uh whoa no I pressed get me on that leaf get me on it
okay hold on how long how do I summon the motor strike
uh B no what am I trying to achieve it won't let me put down the strike for some reason
uh wow I just completely destroyed nothing I'm so good at the game she be she be finished
how was class of oh nine schedules have been posted in the discord apparently
she I mean it's getting weaker but I'm probably doing something horrifically well let's be honest
a grenade launcher sure let's try that okay I missed I missed oh
oh no I missed what she be said and I can't I can't back out the game where it's gonna break
she be she be raid she's rassy okay well uh I'm not sure what on earth occurred in class
of oh nine but as long as you guys had fun that's the main thing uh she was partying like the 1900s
you weren't you went to grace
geez that was awful that fight I'm I'm
to say I'm confused about that fight is an understatement honestly I hope I don't have to do that
get flamed for next time I guess
don't listen to them is the here I'm telling fibbers are you telling fibbers about my wonderful daughters
what's that noise you guys don't want to deal with that that that navi right there no
hold on let me reload with some perish in here
okay we're both as bad at aiming as each other am I so small he actually can't hit me
I'm starting to think that's what's going on hey thanks I owe you and your boys
she be streamers funny as heck only came in at the end I don't even know what happened I'm just
this here and won't snitch oh okay well for those of you who are comfortably joining in
merci modis is going live in t-minus three hours at the moment we are playing a game known as
James Cameron's avatar which is childhood game of mine we have finished the navi quest line and now
we are playing as the bad guys I am absolutely terrified of genuinely fighting the um
the navi um so we are just trying our best to get through the quest line as fast as possible
with the least amount of spikes as possible and the game has aged a little bit in terms of like
I don't know what they were thinking these camera angles and stuff why does that look like it's
gonna wallop down on me as I go past it I saw that I can that is horrific I've not seen that
oh there's noises being made oh there's navi standing up okay that's why that's why
we're just gonna keep driving to objective and everything's gonna be all right and we're
totally not playing horror game simulator at all honestly this is terrifying as a human oh please
let me roll you over please don't get back up again oh please mr rocks don't ruin this I don't
want to fight the navi they are absolutely horrifying and terrifying to me I'm not
oh that car's gonna blow up so I'm probably gonna have to walk on my feet
where or what am I supposed to look nope you're friendly and I'm just shooting at you
sorry sorry I swapped teams my bad I swapped teams give me a second give me a second what am I
shooting at right let's get some oh no that's a granny let's talk about oh oh wow uh that actually
landed the grenade landed why why are you not registering the game's age should be a bit she
can do no wrong exactly the hair and have been trained well clearly are they is there supposed
to be a shard here I don't I think I'm maybe just to help them
uh I will destroy feeling I'm confident as soon as I have allies literally I'm having people
help me with these fights okay so it's a clear amount mission this car is gonna battle oh
oh I sure wish it came sooner oh balance mid-match blue senderman
oh that's probably I'm actually terrified of them good grenade honestly I don't even know how that
hit I didn't I was even aiming hey scrawny what's going on playing a game called James Cameron's avatar
complete the navi side we are now playing the rda which are the naughty naughty bad humans
and I am absolutely terrified every time I go against the navi because they are so tall and
lanky and scary and their arms are so long and whoa getting shivers just right we've got
we need one more crystal from this map and then we can already move on out here thanks for your
help you should know that your men didn't die for nothing I'm gonna make sure of that yeah well then
don't get killed that'll just piss me off more the man said he's here for the count
this game actually looks well made for a movie I don't want to really write that that's literally
gonna oh my god but to take all of that on foot with all the navi is terrifying
can I repair it you know get like a little bit oh is it stuck okay hold on I don't want to run
this guy over so I'm just gonna just need to edge it out excuse me mate excuse me right there we go
this thing is gonna explode the moment I encounter a navi I just don't know it okay I'm already
right hold on hold on hold on this is not gonna go well I can already see myself perishing and
like five seconds flat this is just the camera angle why did they find a light
I was not even like explode out just perish
well let's not do that again I guess so I have to do this on foot and be absolutely mortified
the entire time let me put on the protection spell that was the dumbest thing I've ever seen
don't ever do that again where is it protection right so I have speed protection health and blend
I can do it I'm big girl I'm already level three on the abilities so they're actually gonna last
quite a long time right that's okay that's okay I'm a big girl and this isn't scary to me at all
I'm not absolutely terrified and there's not a bit of pee ready to come flying out of me once I get
jump scared we're cutting it we're cutting it short we are cutting it short I have to admit
this thing's about to unclog okay that's fine it's just plants plants are allowed to expel that
thing I don't know what the heck it does I feel like it's gonna slam down on me and I just want to
confirm or deny
I get eggs pee for destroying plants
no way that's so silly I know how to farm now
eh right we just need to go in this uncharted territory I'm sure it'll be fine and there's
not tons of navi ahead I'll need these don't raid a flaming cart I think it's okay it's okay
okay this is gonna last a good cheeky 10 seconds five six seven eight nine 10 11 12 13 14 maybe 50
15 20 20 oh oh I've never been happier seeing a human how's it going oh my goodness yeah uh long
day yeah just want to okay there's a little fight going on over there uh I'm wondering if I should
farm the wildlife I don't know I don't know you're a lifesaver you're a lifesaver a face of maneuvers
can't even explode the car that the higher ups the vehicle license oh my god I can't we
don't run away from the same thing wait they still go for me even though I'm zoom in I am literally
looming please no navi I did say please but I understand
wait wait wait there's a tail look for survivors wait looking good
cleaning zenos for xp is always a perfect plan yeah I'm thinking maybe if I find a turret I might try
level up
if that hammerhead taught us anything is that you ain't got enough damage for bosses
monkey ass are you implying there's a boss ahead monkey ass because I I don't I don't know
stalker's valley oh my god this is where mercy lives
okay but it's mercy morning and t-minus less than three hours
whoa whoa whoa
all right I think so something came out of the jungle big I have to go against the tana or
thing hit me I'm gonna have to call for another chopper you rider oh yeah I think you were my ride
how can I help I'm fine but you'll have to know I don't know what the hell is out there
even navi had bosses like those dudes that took a lot of killing now imagine the reverse
what does monkey ass mean it's a twitch emote where you look really stressed out and like oh no
this doesn't look good I'm gonna get that I'm gonna go backwards and get this and
oh my god why is it such a horror ambience I'm not even being funny
like the leaves shaking about the leaves are like so violently shaking about whoa what what
what is going on
you're getting jumped by a pack of wolves you'll be okay
this I cannot wait to get through this and let it be over because this is just
this is too much for my little heart I can hardly take a desert guy they perish oh my yeah this is
so
how am I supposed to achieve anything
when oh I'm just standing in plant poison they're spitting bail at me
bro I'm sorry I'm gonna need to like literally get a co-op mode right now so you guys can carry
me through this you're not even shooting the plant what are you trying to achieve
oh forget it we hate nature literally what
it seems like there's more soldiers placed everywhere though maybe to help you through it
just because they know they made it a bit harder with the plant and the wildlife and the navi
ganging up on you at least like when you're navi only a little bit of the wildlife gang up on you
and that oh yeah I would definitely need the frickin oh my is that friendly bombs
none of those plants spying
oh okay okay it's fine kind of fine this is just a slaughterhouse
this is absolute chaos
chaos with the a ch whoa what got me it made me jump like the opposite way that you were
she's low right there's a sloppy a sloppy plant up ahead actually we need to play cameo because
these plants remind me of flecks from cameo I don't know either we're just I cannot wait until
I get level four um that's out that is outrageous how many plants there are
that's insane oh there's a buggy thank goodness there's a buggy oh my god is it going to have
better camera angles whatever this is
how do I go forward no how do I shoot oh no let's get out sorry wait wait hold on let me let me
learn how to shoot let me learn how to shoot
is there not like an alternate weapon okay there we go let's go let's get it I should get it okay
wait I need to go up or down doesn't matter okay I like this I like this I feel a bit better
feel a bit better things are going things are looking up things are looking up this
doesn't even have a bad camera angle with either oh maybe it does it's just because it's a bit
oh okay I'm sorry but you're gonna have to get out of the way literally
what on earth are things a freaking boulder I'm stuck oh okay it's good it's good it's
good guys why are you stressing so much like honestly oh it seems like you guys forget I'm
like MLG4 or something I'm just gonna bum rush it honestly no I'm not no I'm not
no I'm not I'm gonna go back for that mech that is the bravest no I'm getting out I'm getting out
it's gonna explode it's gonna explode it's gonna explode no no run away from the explosion
we're going for the mech
give me this thing what does it do what does it do let me in let me in
okay okay let's see let's see what we're working with
what we have how will PR we can compare some
okay okay okay let him get up let him get up all right all right not feeling scared anymore
have I blocked the way for this poor guy I think so sorry mate now have to figure it out on your own
okay okay hold on hold on we're cooking by gas because this isn't terrifying
this isn't terrifying I'm just kidding mech a time I can't believe we're playing mech assault
see this game's just mech assault simulator all right let them come at me what let them get up
okay let them yeah see they always seem to hide the navi behind the like corners and stuff
I'm just gonna let them attack and hope they don't keep respawning
and then it's safe to come out okay okay okay now hold on hold on all is not lost this might not
be the most painful gameplay of rda side you've ever seen it's called tools pa
the wildlife cannot
okay hold on hold on hold on
can you aim why does it never register like I really just not want to register
what's going on with this bomb it wouldn't even like hardly let me perish it okay I've always
loved the mechs it's here they're a bit it's starting starting throwing bombs at me I'm just
gonna move on I honestly think it's safer just to ignore everything and like only shoot for like
exp or something can I like crush them with a mech no I can't that's interesting oh no is that
just get me out of the mech no way they put this in the game because then you are come on jump
the mechs can jump oh my god that's so cool
oh
wait that looks like the mech can the mech crouch nope that's just reverse
they knew exactly what they were doing freaking putting that one log there I'll have to get out
the game knew that I wanted the mech I'm gonna get jump scared by like 10 things at once
and now we're gonna come flying out right go away no you're scaring me
you get me the game's just freaking jump scare simulator let me put that on
no this is a battle dorm stop it this is a battle dorm yeah it's literally called prayer
is then and you know who the prayer is me I'm being predicted upon
no
oh
okay
friendly friendly surely friendly surely friendly surely friendly surely friendly
um is there anything you already have perished me I'm literally one HP in a dream
can I like hide behind I can't I can't win
hello why I mean I know the game really wants to punish
you're gonna have to give me a better weapon than whatever this
is a assault rifle launcher
a gun machine gun a shotgun a hammer a flamethrower
brave brave I'm literally cornered I'm getting ragdolled this is it this is the best I can do
this is the best I can do
that thing you're literally turning into beef jerky please please please please please please please
I'm freaking please
please I am beef jerky right hold on let me let me take a break
well that was a terrible idea because you can just turn around and swipe me
he's not even half health and I don't even have full health yet please
okay heal heal because I only have one res
wait can I use these bones is this is this the trick is the bones
because the AI needs to pick a bone pick a side pick a side that's right that's right you thought
you thought you thought you thought didn't you
definitely don't want to destroy the bone structure however can you blow him up though
no this isn't working sorry I'm needing the the grenade isn't working
okay but don't give up on me because we're actually getting somewhere I just need anything
that freaking sprays honestly gone right these oh
this is what I need this is what I need this is it just frame free this is it this is it
this is it okay possible I've not accidentally so flocked myself and this is actually plausible
okay it's okay it's okay it's okay it's okay just let it happen just let it happen just let it
happen let it happen let it happen sorry this is must be so annoying watching oh well
hold on hold on hold on hold on let me get up let me heal let me go back there again
okay okay okay it's okay it's okay we're actually doing it I won I don't even I need to watch other
people's gameplay of this to see one earth they dead because this is so cheese this is so that was
awful don't ever don't ever free and I only got 100 XP for that that was awful other people
played this question mark honestly I don't know what I was supposed to do like unless I'm just let
it happen missed opportunity to the cut off fish color thing it's like go sleep go sleep go sleep
literally that was awful
oh Kendra hen you're gonna have to start pulling your weight
oh no you thought I'm using the old ways honestly can I get weapon upgrades stat because
okay I've got an armor what on earth are these armors we're just getting well I'm like out the
wazoo by that one I'm doing I'm getting in a plane all right get me the heck out here please
officer Midoriya oh it's Midoriya from the hit enemy show uh here eat this I don't know what it's
called off a lot nothing to the med that was skiing that was skiing but we're doing it okay
but you're running between the bones to shoot is what you're meant to actually do
you're paving the way for future avatar gamers congrats to James Cameron's avatar for me playing
your game you've now gone up two game seals because of my my influential influence
question was this destroyed it is hi Kendra I got all three shards that wasn't so hard was it
that was awful grab the harmonic from the willow tree I made contact with hq all's good
Trudy's meeting us at the evac and stay frosty word from intel is that badamo himself is gunning
no way badamo's on the no way listen to me if you run into him don't waste time
just kill him the guy's a monster now go get the harmonic and meet me at the evac no way
he's gonna beat the absolute he's gonna beat me to a pole
oh right I'm using the plane
ice it won't let me drive this I'm gonna have to go on foot no I'm not there's a buggy right next to
me okay I felt safer in the mix than I did the buggy why would you send one signal specialist on
their own why would you not send an infantry to sorry I'm trying to discover what's the
there seems to be two bridges ahead seems to be multiple bridges actually if I go straight
ahead and then take a right not if you beat him first this was the best part in the movie
they really paint the nda is the bad guys oh the navi is the bad guys I mean I guess it's like
justify
now they're just spraying
I don't know if I should go they're actually really hurting me I'm not gonna lie
I'm I've already lost maybe like 150% health
and I think I'm just gonna run through the best I can
and oh wow that I think that pinged them off the map there
I mean the navi share three letters with
ww winner okay no you are a plant
you are you are a plant there's no way you're doing that to titanium steel I refuse
call me hailey williams because I refuse I refuse why
I wish I could speed up in these but I assume
take a right at the next right not this right for the next right
are you have you cleared the planet for humanity yet no I'm not but I'm doing
it now slice saver I'm doing the RDA side I feel safe in the mecha tanks I do not feel safe when
I am outside of the tanks I am absolutely mortified because this is awful and scary can the tank even
fit on this oh thank goodness it can literally I this is awful and my tank is actually getting
low health I I don't know what happens if it explodes or no I'm getting out I'm I'm getting
out I'm getting out I'm sorry okay this isn't gonna go good I need to do the song
and they're all gonna come at me they're all gonna come at me they were already locked on
before I even came out of envis and oh no oh no oh no this is fine this is fine this is fine
this is fine everything is fine everything's cool when you're part of rda everything's all gone
um
is it safe
oh goodness to me jump scare sim where is it somewhere here oh get me off this planet
get me off pandora don't be scared we can hold hands on infly
uh
is that him is that him stop stop stop stop stop you're actually terrifying and I only have one revive
stop stop please question mark
no way you hit that distance
no he's distancing me no no no no no no
is this even hurting me I don't know what he's freaking fire resistant sorry but you need to patch
this I need to patch hot hot update pandora you're literally eyewa eyewa is cheating eyewa is
cheating eyewa is cheating eyewa is it cheating she's cheating we hold whoa whoa whoa why can't I
oh I'm out of ammo oh my god the shotgun blasts him back stay back
stay back oh my god the shotgun blast the shotgun he healed only I'm allowed to heal
only I'm allowed to heal please can I have infinite shotgun ammo that would be grand
don't spank me again I need up he keeps doing that freaking invis thing and I can't
seem to shoot him when he's down like that stop stop stop hold on I need to take my sweet time doing
this honestly don't heal again please don't don't make this harder than it has to be
please this is what you get for disrespecting me so much in the last run let me reload
let me okay I love the shotgun from from now and ever I love the shotgun did you see that dodge
that was actually pretty good dodge not gonna lie and that one oh come on oh oh we did it
oh my goodness oh my goodness I don't know how we did that shotgun love because oh my goodness
what on earth have I lost my mic oh it blew up didn't it where did I need to go
somewhere I've not discovered it okay I need to backtrack
oh is he shooting at me or is he shooting at
is the wildlife attacking the navi oh the it is
huh curious the the viper wolves are actually attacking the navi I thought it was an exclusive
I thought it was exclusive to us Malina let me tell you something let me tell you something
honestly honestly get much better um it was like pretty terrifying oh these things whip for quite
a distance can I make it past without getting whipped okay okay I think wolves just don't
like everyone in this game please don't knock me off the bridge that would actually ruin my day
I don't have invisibility
I'm gonna unlock the transport location unless unless unless that
have I made a mistake I maybe don't need this transport location I just thought it was important
to unlock but are there any games with hypno effect not that I can recall
maybe that whoa these whoa whoa whoa whoa these flies are stun locking me
sorry guys I'm gonna leave you behind to get absolutely annihilated because I don't want to
deal with that did I don't know if that card game encryption has hypno in it I don't I don't
know if I'm just making that up I I've not played it myself I think I've like paused for like two
milliseconds uh to see huh whoa whoa whoa skipping watching my usual streamers for Sony
does a new approach you I am an endurance streamer so if this is not your kind of game don't worry
Mercy is going live in T minus two and a half I have never been happier to see these these guys
wherever the heck they're what are they called let's see what they're called don't move a UT drone
I've never been so happy to see a UT drone oh depends if you go the other route okay yeah
the alternative stuff yet definitely there's not an inscription okay I misremember
oh I'm so stressed playing this yeah I'm not even pretending okay I really appreciate
that I already went to the ocarina time skull trainer we need to hurry tensions are starting to boil
over at hell's gate oh I'll be just puked up in the verge of declaring martial law he's starting
to invite scientists for questioning I'm not sure what he's nervous about we need to be careful
if the time comes we may need to make some tough choices so Kendra wants you to report to Monroe
at hell's gate if you're gonna give me 8000 xp for showing up sure I'll go to hell's gate pretty
sure there are lots of sections of everything in vampires the masquerade and destroy all humans
have hypnosis wait vampires masquerade do you get to play as a vampire that hypnotizes people that
would be kind of cool oh my god I'm here for that oh okay I feel like we level up so fast
this rda maybe the rda isn't as long I think so oh that's so cool maybe we'll take a look at that
I've never played it or seen any gameplay of it but uh is that like a highly rated game
dark souls 3 has rapport for anime potential I suppose I mean technically more door shadow
and more door you can take technically like imprint enemies so they're not mean to you all right
upload the harmonic I'm behind on my doomsday diagnostic this is the second song wrong with the
emulator we could have an ecological meltdown okay let's hold up a sec what the hell is this emulator
yes the emulator we're searching for a dormant well of souls right now once we find it we need to
communicate oh they're pretending being called a first voice he's the only person who can awake
in a well of souls they're pretending that the emulator isn't just a nuke once that's done
we can control the entire ecosystem so back to that first ecosystem you're going to do a diagnostic
well hey everything has its risk come now upload that harm they're lying to me not
but we're still going to nuke the planet anyway once they're closer depending on the location of
the dormant site you should check in with the man who doesn't in fact have the option to be a hypnotic
and highly rated as a question it's a cult classic oh my apology I did not know that
it's good might need to mess with it a little to make it work though it's an old game oh yeah
doesn't Baldur's Gate have a bunch of them I'm not playing Big Baldi's Gate yet
scenario don't start growing a brain it says it's corp is it like corp that can bring you get
you guys in and out or is it another kind of corp the human colony and avatar is pretty impressive
that emulators are one hope Baldur's Gate has tons of main controls especially because main
flyers are a big part of the plot hmm doesn't have main control of the game
it's quite a vtm vampire's masquerades old game it's not that kind of cool one we're going to
Graves Bog okay did you know that in scots the bog is slang for the toilet did you know that in
Australia the thunderbox is slang for the toilet I don't know what any slang for any other
this voice actor sounds like grandpa max from band tan
nice to watch band tan
new set new set
oh new scary location oh me oh my
I mean Baldur's Gate has twitch integration oh that's a shame there's no such thing
the bevel
I can't hear you
oh I keep not getting a good night's sleep before streams I don't know what to do
or how to stop it you know I'm saying I have nightmares about the girls I keep waking up
like way before I should I don't know how to have a good night's sleep
a sheba to drop me open I can literally see wolves like kendra wants you to collect a shard from a
navi village oh a village full of navi sure let me just go have fun freaking why not drive me to the
village kendra you suck wait I've already been here before oh no
wait so dad go the path I've not been all right go the way I've not been
use hypnosis to sleep duh honestly you know what oh wait I should not done that
all right get me up here
okay am I
do they they can
that's gonna take a lot just to get rid of them jeez there's other guys I can hear them
I think he's biting my ankle oh there's so many of them
oh not even giving me whoa whoa whoa I just hurt myself and made that so easy for them hold on
get my gun out oh
what was that animation that was just like x-wax x-axis 90 degrees animation for the rock destroy
lol
right hold on okay it's a big fight I'll ignore the fighting and I'll just go get the mission
objective and then I'll use the xp from achieving the mission objective uh whoa
oh am I burning my own guys or just him oh wait there's a thingy I'm going I'm not really sure
what how I feel about the flamethrower I don't know if it's as fast as I think it should be
I said I want it faster they're at least helping you this time honestly a Christmas miracle
I almost dive into the fire to sacrifice myself okay just grab it right uh now what now what now
what check them up uh just keep to keep going the path that hasn't been walked excuse me pardon me
coming through I'm literally watching all the humans get annihilated next to me and just be
I'm like yeah not my problem see you later alligator in a while crocodile oh level four
invisible please soon that's terrifying oh what you didn't even give me a warning
you did not even give me a freaking warning that was gonna go down oh I'm getting absolutely
roasted I'm gonna I'm not gonna make it I'm not gonna make it I'm gonna make it the gates are
right there come on oh oh oh come on help me out turn man help me out shoot them
hello oh thank goodness I thought they weren't gonna open the gate I was like I know you can
see me right now open this open let me in open the door oh flamethrower in video game only come
into flavors overpowered or a wargun on anything this fresh meat can do it's like a struck a match
and I'm like here take that one person versus the whole planet literally why not take me out with
squadron uh did I need this right oh okay okay well oh I'm burping I'm burping
spring pray people spring pray oh no don't don't spray the allies oh okay okay okay I'm gonna get up
okay I'm trying to get like two at once but it's not working oh my goodness
right I'm not that see I'm not scared when I've got allies but when I've know I'm absolutely
modified the vents are unfolding five we need six oh I'm getting wax whoa that was a big stick
okay I want to collect the samples where's the shotgun no that's pistol no that's empty that's why
oh whoa
okay
is that working I don't the flamethrower isn't like am I going crazy
I'm I'm losing it it's not doing anything
yeah the shotgun actually does something though
come on
there we go there we go
there we go that's much better hold on hold on I'm get I'm getting hang of it let me let
get up there one more goodness gravy
yeah the aim is to stone eggs folks just
can I finish a kill please that navi just completely ignored me though
I mean I'll take it a lair north gate is under attack oh we have more where what one
yeah north gate oh I just looked at north on the hut I'm like where would the north gate be
me hapsich would be facing north this shotgun
who is that we literally just did a synchronized dance there
are you crazy
yeah I wish that literally synchronized dance
little head on skull moment good oh jeez what a waste that's like never ending
and I can hardly see them because they're invisible half the time
oh I'm hardly getting the credit for killing them
is there
pirates I can climb up yet
there's no ladder climb on those turrets they're just for what oh there's one over here hold on
hold on hold on hold on this might make things a lot easier let's try it let's try it let's try it
oh my god can I look at these guys nope that's friendly oh my god this is so much easier are you
joking me I I've been struggling for how long
oh this is too simplistic no I'll miss that guy but it's still
oh
yeah and they keep stealing my kills oh get this great
okay three and done this is the last one there's no way get me off this
I have two razes I do need to try and yeah sorry I'm ignoring everything and
and well I would ignore everything if you get you weren't perfectly you're blocking the way
grunge learn your
okay okay let's let's go let's go let's go
we're making progress
oh this is so why on air said I don't think of this sooner
reeflings why didn't you suggest this you're supposed to be holding my hand
oh I'm gonna need catch up on chat honestly I feel like I'm gonna have a thing to reach her
oh
oh right oh done jeez louise so if I'm not part of the 20 players on this game
r.i.p. I can't believe it it's such a legendary game I can't even say I recommend like I'll go out and
buy it it's the experiences for me is more nostalgia although this part is like actually
like I'm actually like having a challenge playing this part
I'm still in disbelief the game even exists your hands are on the controller
be like didn't sell the third oh the jet didn't see the turret sorry it's on
you're doing good I've got two songs I think so far
I'm sure by the way you missed the cutscene gate flying like a rocket launcher honestly
yeah you leveled so far I wonder if the rda mission is actually like smaller than the main
wait I want to unlock the fast travel before takeoff just in case level up
whoops hey I like you too rider
she said whoops I like you too rider
whoa wait I'm not driving oh thank god right let's see how this develops
oh
the aim is a bit in front of us are you jung are you jung
dad just ignore the ones from behind or
what's the what's the deal did I just go for it
it's just an XP run I think it's just an XP run I'll just destroy everything
oh my gosh oh no
oh that's getting that's all out of my head that's too loud for stream
oh that's like just a little deafening
okay this just looks like an XP farm run I'm gonna say it but
I can't even see what's ahead of me there's so much
oh oh excuse me oh no whoa I don't even know you're just riding those like that
oh what's going on what's going on
oh
the camera angle is like I'm not even driving who's driving this warthog
did a terrible job of it um overheating oops hold on
over here and I'm getting a little too overzealous with this weaponry okay
this is just annihilation I'm starting to feel bad for the navi like as much as they're annoying
when they're trying to kill me damn it engine won't start
oh as they hold them off where I can't see oh god they're everywhere
oh I don't know if I'm going to make this alive
I'm trying I'm trying I'm trying
hard
oh my goodness
can I see oh it's a blue plan I keep thinking it's a navi it's a blue plan
come on start the car there's only so much back and forth I can do before we actually perish
seriously
oh my goodness right it seems like they're just falling back and
thank good right don't do that again
I'm sorry I yelled at you sweetheart he says to the car
reflinges I'm sorry I yelled at you sweetheart
I just get stressed when I'm playing the bad guys and everything's all skewed
and I'm sorry if I skewed
oh I don't want that to break
she's doing her best for humanity
absolutely denying it denying it sorry destroying it
if I'm getting xp
the first things are running away
that's my car that's small that's one of more guys my oh I even know
oh first things I just feel bad I feel like we're we're entering a zoo and then just executing
all the animals inside the zoo this is what this run feels like honestly
like they're literally running away now
oh for xp so I can unlock a new armor why not
perish that plan
in front are you don't oh
is that supposed to happen
what a unique game mode to say the least I think you see about three of these guys
if you play navi and you see 100 on this one section of the game alone
we're strum beast pulling
it's what it's been oh my god that was
that was a slaughter I'm not even happy with that that was awful
you're a lifesaver you're a lifesaver how about that strike stubby stakes all around okay the
second shards right in this sector go grab it and report back to me and the third I'm working on it
radios are toast everything slower here this is why the navi section has so few human
campaign colors them now you know why you don't see them in this oh is it like all this damage
has been done and we're just coming at the back end of it
oh that actually makes so much sense
and we're basic we basically come in when they're like at the end of the losing fight and we turn
the tide okay oh my god that's so smart I didn't give the devs team like as much benefit as a doubt
but that's so smart
don't let him I was gonna say don't let him kill you because he's gonna aggro to me and I can just tell
you is oh wait hold on where I'm trying to go hold on a minute let me pick
there we go I'll just let him get in the back thing what new drift would be got um wait I think
we're about to unlock the new one because now our arms are on show and I'm like that's the opposite
of what our it does the hero maybe oh no clue if it's kind of it's just a joke of mine I mean it
maybe because literally you only see two of them right where we need to go well I'm taking a car
for that I'm not taking that back thing can I drive this oh can draw how do I shoot I don't know
can I drive him over oh that was I was actually really mean I shouldn't have come up I kind of
deserved it what are all those things are those reports
um so can I not shoot I don't think I can I think I can only drive we're driving this buggy
oh that's like such a long way to go I'll go on the outskirts to get the
uh like uncovered map thing actually smash them against the wall
oh I can't go that way
this is so much more responsive than the buggy I have to admit I like that they make that differentiation
uh okay we can't go this way I thought we couldn't come through the way the map made it look but we
no I did not just do that oh I did not just do that oh I freaking did oh no no no hello game oh my gosh
oh this is the worst thing that could have happened has not happened
door stuck literally door stuck oh and I have to do all of this on foot whilst everything is aggressive
to me right how much further do I have to go just a wee bit for it just down the street
it's fine I just need to pop down the street it's like going to the corner shop it's just around
the corner it's okay you can just teleport down I can't because I've not unlocked whatever it is
it's not unlocked is it quiet is it safe question mark other than the fly trap
just a wee bit more all is good this is called sniper's point implying that they're
sniper navi looking at me right now question mark the ho hum okay whoa whoa whoa something's
getting me I don't want a fly a fly got me a mosquito a mosquito got me oh whoa look at it freaking
ready to like get me all right I'll wait until my inverse comes back yeah yeah that's right go
back to sleep give me a stinky stinky plant don't like you abandoned rda camp well that doesn't
that doesn't this is this this is not good for me I can tell you that much this is absolutely
awful for me um I will take the teleport point just so I don't have to do that again um
um can I hide here well he looks pretty enraged to me um
I have nowhere I'm gonna go up oh no I can't go up I'm too small
where where's the crystal guys I don't really want to go abandon hope yo you who may enter
on the floor finger it's about hole oh there's this to spray them down
hmm okay
did they just run away from me now
okay okay not too bad if I have a too little really destroy all this stuff too I mean it's
10 xp I'm not really sure it's worth taking the time to do that I will try and clear up this area
because if I'm to like try and find a crystal in the middle we're still free jumping I don't even know
what I'm supposed to look
oh now you come around the corner no you're such a liar you're actually such a liar you're telling
fivers why would you come around the corner now after I'd already sprayed you where on earth is this
thing and he's already AI locked on me I don't know why the game pretends otherwise
is there another turret over here that I can use I know the things back in that other section
I'm just wondering what's up here why is there a dead end oh and it's just like one of these things
jeez that gorilla and you're a lifesaver it's just abandon kind of showing you it's old
abandoned hope you know dog pet dog it's a turtle I have no idea with pecking crystals
already I go to me but I can't see maybe inside that building and that's why it's like flashing
here
oh pardon me
wait I'm gonna go invisible and see if I can shoot it from that turret or is it already
glued on to me no uh was it in here
bro where is this freaking cell sample I don't know
I'm gonna see if I can get rid of that last guy with us because he I just saw a second one
wait let's get rid of you because you're in my way you're in my way you're in my way
right no I think wherever the heck it is it's somewhere over here it's not been here yet
I hate you what even if you're invisible oh he's got protection prayer on I can see it that's what
that bloom boy here oh I just what did I get I got new armor and speed four I'll take that
bro am I actually gonna have to look up a tutorial
that was big oh a different outfit I'm like
it's not that way it's out of bounds over there
it's not like up here whoa sorry sorry it wasn't paying attention is it off could it be on
where the heck is this one thing
no don't spray on me no it's not time for that
hello we're currently looking for something that my blind eyes cannot perceive
it says it's somewhere in this area and I keep perfectly avoiding it wherever it is
okay um now the avatars are coming in this area is it inside that maybe maybe it's inside
this one whatever it is it's in the building oh if it's in this one I'm gonna be mad because
I went in the other one oh for goodness gravy thank you what are the odds
right finally got there in the end and there of course there's not fast travel to that guy
because that would be too easy wouldn't that
uh that speed is fast though like I'm pretty speed
of course it was in the building that I wasn't looking at
how could I be such a silly sausage I was beating up my car
yeah I had to put a down payment on that right this is gonna be off topic I don't know if you
guys have been watching a there's this youtuber that looks at people's finances like for entertainment
but he always shouts at them for having a car and I didn't realize that a car loans were like
really predatory in America and where they like make you pay like a ridiculous like percentage
and stuff whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa you just relax little flies you just relax thank you thank you
these jumped us let's have been hiding all over the green and me two more
no one more crystal and then I'm gonna go on the fritz you two huh
how these guys be jammed and it took four times bad day for bets it seems no take these don't be
better on me honestly I want you to collect the shard from a nearby navvy village okay let's give
it a shot I believe this is the second last shard collection map and then we've done the
campaign unbelievably uh we are just going for it I love being ignored in battle yay I love going
so fast that the enemies don't target me yay I love not being a part of the fight ow he just spanked
my boat good night rest well those who need to sleep uh sorry about kind of the surprise endurance
stream I thought it was only four hours what we are oh for seven hours oh my gosh sorry sorry to
anyone good night and rest well those who need to go please do not stay up against your health
just to watch the vaude will be remaining for you soon tm
you must kill tan jala before you collect the harmonic and the willow tree where we've got a
boss fight but we can do it we can do it we can do it if we put our mind to uh we can do
we're um Eric I'm not trying to go I'm behind a tent right now
living up to the endurance streamer tag enemy yeah I wonder how many people
didn't realize like when I said endurance streamer I meant endurance strummer okay
right what am I doing just kind of kind of half follow the map
oh oh I'm in the battle field by accident
strummer look at his tail
tan jala near me watch pride
look at my speed my speed is amazing I'm a super soldier hmm it tastes like reasons
I was surprised but I haven't missed them how
I have streamed a heck of a lot of time I feel like maybe right or tan jala's been spotted near
the willow tree it's like he's waiting there waiting for you I think watch yourself
I can't even see the enemy you know that I actually can't eat I'm not being funny
I didn't mean to good battle but if I genuinely can't see the freaking enemy what are you wanting
me to do oh no way I've just engaged the freaking boss fight stop stop I've engaged the boss fight
and there's like a literally a billion you're gonna make me pay myself please oh my god I think I
need flamethrower to like oh my god I'm just getting absolutely gang violence here what am I supposed
I need I need pop malts I need pop malts like right now they're all using freaking prayer
protection I'm out of mana I'm out of mana I actually can't do prayer protection because I'm
out of mana when I'm running out of freaking strength potion as if we were playing rescape
right now oh my gosh what have I done what have I done what have I done I've just dived into the
enemy I like literally can't see them prep the time oh and there's someone sniping me from behind
as well not sorry but no it's just no on like you can't even just snake me from halfway across the
map and why did that one run away I have no idea I guess I'm at range whatever the sniper one is
still wound for me but at least that other one ran away okay that's the problem I have with the
snipers they can do that yes thank you for coming freaking point blank why oh wow Tanjala pushed me
so far out of his battle area he had literally DC no I can see that other NPC though can I shoot him
oh that's the flamethrower darling that's the shotgun can I I just want him there we go
I just wanted him to attack me no one else
okay let's let's take it nice and easy nice and easy she says that she gets caught in trees
no that no shotgun shotgun no no no no no no I missed okay this is what I want
the shotgun stagger is exactly what I'm looking for right now it can be what what's the name of
shotgun so it can be a spaz 12 is the name of a shotgun a stakeout is the name of a shotgun
oh they're gun I don't remember any other ones off the top of my head
not very good with gun names unless they're in black ops one and all on us too
like Famous AK-47 submachine guns Susie's AK-47 new um MP5 very classic normally shown in movies
mp5 k brian I have returned from the job strongy hope it's going well we're currently doing a
boss battle and I'm getting absolutely wrecked tiny spiny but I can only do as much as I can
it's taking a while I don't know I feel like maybe there's something I should know like maybe I
should be in a mech at this point it's very plausible um but thank you for the ship we're
getting there he's just cast protection sorry I like I don't want to waste the ammo since I've
a little bit too left like stop with the prayer protection whoa whoa whoa okay I'm out of that
so next is flamethrower we're just gonna no he gets so close when I do flamethrower like so close
is he got fury on so he does double damage to me I think so I think that's what that was
right we're just gonna have to do it seems he staggers with the assault right
I think he's got light machine gun actually
he's getting low so if he doesn't heal then I think we're in I think we're cooking by gas if he
doesn't heal oh okay we did it we did it we did it we did it I cast mystic barrier honestly
getting right isn't needing to use ult and hasn't poked the damage but someone either honestly
first try like I'm just glad I'm not dying and getting stun locked where or why am I here
why
what am I to do oh wait I'm to do the song I'm to do the song I understand my apologies
whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa you need to relax and take your little acrobatic self away I need
to do the song right now where is it right one and then do a triangle somewhere here
no someone over here someone in the water
okay okay triangle triangle
triangle
oh you don't attack whoa they are humongous if you're a baby
wait where triangle
well that would be a triangle maybe here okay okay not a perfect triangle
so we're about through cages staggered to death honestly humongous wall
strongy doesn't work for democracy wait wrong thing what did you guys think of hell divers
I I got a chance to play it and I was like hmm I'm wondering if one of those things like if you
have good company and then it's a fun game but who goes there identify yourself whoa get me out
here because I just heard that we're just doing this only played one need friends for it right
it was good until Sony oh yeah wait actually holy crap we like completely missed out on all the
war hammer and all the um freaking
okay
can I die in a fucking you did it oh right last song
I would like to return to hell's gate please thank you very much
oh sorry my little feet sees removing my feet are my hands are very sweaty but my feet are very
dry right now and I don't know if that means I'm dehydrated
I will have a mention here's pop up sorry I misnamed it I meant hell divers
Sam um the hell divers like it was like people were they tried to make it so you had to have a
PSN account or something just to play the game even though they advertised like
you can still play your game even without the PSN part
when in doubt drink
okay is this good you're back quickly let's upload that harmonic okay this is the third song
things are turning nasty around here Falco said if the emulator didn't work perfectly
he put a bullet in my brain I doubt he was serious he was holding a gun to my head when
he said that's serious enough for me hurry the harmonic Jesus that's so um he's so stinky level up
yeah they tried to force PSN accounts to play which would have blocked a lot of people out
and they're known for getting uh leaks
deep rock galactic they made a lord of the rings version I think they called it mines of moria
I've not played it but I hope it's multiplayer and I can like play with you guys I'd be so fun
I'm going to bring my recommendation to Falco speaking of which you should check with him for your
next mission we got the harmonic sir listen to me I want harper shut down now if you're too
incompetent to stop his avatar all of an avatar right with him you think you can handle it or do
I need to get a real jar head to do it I got it jar head recon shows link signals on the hanging
I'll prove to you that I'm a real trooper I'll eat crayons and smile about it
deep rock is crazy fun we're it we are going to the hanging gardens
this guy's very ergo part of the jar head clean oh that's right in the movies these are
part of the jar head clan movie quote spotted
mushroom rock and star
hello let's hit the envelope just promise me no power cubes we already let's hit the envelope
I've never heard that before let's hit the envelope the hanging gardens
did I hear rock and stone you did
do you think I can convince the girls to play main zemorial with me
triple cannibal
it kept growing back so fast run finally just pulled out left everything behind
oh dear all right here you go uh hello no airstrikes gonna come stay here at your
we've just landed
can I reload I'm already out of money money ammunitions did I not did it begin to automatically
reload it for me I want rid of these bow and arrow guys first
I only have three revised I need to keep pick it wow this is why I won't rid of these
bow and arrows
oh goodness me I can't get a breathing space
oh this is crazy give me some space give me some space please
oh space space space they just keep coming
oh I'm getting spanked about oh wrong button but actually no protection spine
oh they keep going around
oh
stop with the bow and arrow
they oh this is like so unpredictable where they move
all right I need kill one more and then I think they stop responding because this is
I'm I'm just getting stunned log I wish I had that is that what my belly did when I was a mavi
oh my gosh what a rough landing yeah what does it feel oh it's a heady London
why why why why is he hearing why hearing my hearing
it was a miss input miss input oh it's chaos let's just drop marina
but he's gone west looking for powder no supply destroyed the navi
harry as opposed to a smooth oh now that you have said that out loud that makes so much more
sense I always wondered why the heck they always mentioned that oh that was that was harry that
was harry harry harry and I'm like I'm missing something clearly brain cells of all things
right how do I get to this location
uh take the skinny path behind me I need to do a big old 180
why is the camera angle so bad in this game
wait oh no oh no yeah we're not doing that in the buggy uh please let me out
we will do this by foot
is this where the flamethrower comes in can I even get close enough oh I can
okay flamethrower for the wildlife for the plant
that's feigned by me I will try to remember this
right if I make it across here the dogs will go everyone tell get right
wait am I going the right way yeah just keep going and then go to the right okay
brilliant driving look I'm thank goodness I don't actually have a driver's license because
not gonna lie would not uh not go down well I can hear tramping
I'll take that you're so rich
oh there's quite a lot of you as long as I can jump past you it's fine I'll let you live you know I'm
doing um I'm doing a while we favor not killing you at all actually so you should be should be
grateful you should be thankful I said you should be grateful and you should be thankful
oh what the heck is this I don't know a repulsor
a repul a zone repulse oh that's right please no no please just let me do it so you guys
leave okay they're safe now I've seen worse drivers I can't believe it can't believe I
contribute to the stereotype wait is this grunt here to help us or
uh no he's here to give us our next job
still alive huh booyah booyah let's have a look at those explosives don't worry we're almost
in a few grunts oh you need new DT's if we're gonna make some noise I saw a chopper crash southwest
of here maybe you can salvage some of the detonators from the rock get them back to winslow
you'll know where to fire them all
DT's sure DT's I know something should oh that makes broken I was gonna go in it
uh if I go straight ahead then should be fine let's go why not wait straight ahead yeah straight
ahead okay let's don't flip the buggy it's my only request it's killing
why why would you do that you knew exactly what you were doing
I can't get up oh I can't get up and everything's gonna attack me literally look on the
map there's like a freaking massive ass battle bone it's over this is over for me
yeah oh my gosh oh my gosh oh my gosh golly oh gosh golly gee that really was not supposed to
happen the dev who have created this map knew exactly what he was doing giving me a heart
they're still here they're literally waiting to attack me
it's getting a bit it's getting a bit non smooth it's getting a bit heady lads it's getting a
bit heady okay we're with friends it's fine
actually there's no way you're supposed to actually play the game by just dodging everything
all the time but this is the best I can do under the turquoise and oh can I get this package please
thank you objective complete let's get the heck out of here jeez whee
where'd I need bro can you stop sending me like one side of the map to the other uh I don't
this game is having an awfully fun time doing that how I can't even teleport there there's not even
anything to teleport from if I take a right and don't fall off man you feel oh let's go let's go let's go
just ignore me I'm not part of the field uh I'm actually oh I'm just a field medic
you what is it that British Red Cross rule or something
I can't get over I have to go to a low all the one taking fall damage and I'm literally
two centimeters off the grind so oh we have to take the long round through all those navi
and they're attacking me oh the navi and attacking me name a better drill do I go that way
yes I can go that way I literally went invisible as that guy struck me
no white crosses for health packs and games and stuff apparently that's a war crime
also shooting unarmed medics exactly like seriously what's going on here
you cannae jump it no I cannae jump it right I'm sure these are bombs yeah okay I was gonna say
I'm sure there's something off of those I had to find out for myself I'd find out the hard way
so many of them
um
okay you don't you don't even respond to that oh oh my guess they don't hurt the
oh oh no no no there's no human here I'm actually a I'm a mouse I'm a mammal no wait navi aren't
considered mammals rather I'm actually gonna claim this pod first and then going with
I'm probably gonna get shot in the bum with an arrow though oh oh and there's another one right
there ha ha ha very funny game no human here only a cut literally I'm a I'm just an innocent little
seh full of pod doing my thing you know you're in a good time just need to try and speed run
getting out of all these absolutely atrociously dangerous areas and then we can finally destroy
pandora and live happily ever after wait oh wait no you do that myself wait this is a dead end
can you stop please I'm literally stuck here with you is this a dead end yes or no
have I just gone a horrifically wrong way
why would you do that okay I need to now take the biggest freaking circle over
hi everyone I'm back thank you for joining again we are still the rd we're still the bad guys
and we're still avoiding every fight possible under the sun because this is just impossible there's
no way I refuse to believe this is even plausible humans number one baby innocent innocent no
I'm an innocent cuttlefish hold on a minute I don't know if you've seen them or anything
oh that scared me I'm gonna I'm gonna I actually need to heal I need to heal but I want to stop
because I think I'm gonna get my bum bitten
oh my god the paralysis from those flies are so punishing so punishing I'm gonna see if I can
run past both of these but oh poison poison poison hello am I walled off again what have I done
to me why what have I done to deserve this name why I'm so confused why I can't access this area
I literally need to go down
okay that dog can't come on me on the branch oh can I climb down this or is this Navi
no it can't be Navi only I'm human I can't freaking do it
bro I'm gonna explore the whole map before I actually get to my my location
I can't believe
explore the whole map I mean drowning people might have been a thing I've not done it yet
I'm not even being successful in doing my first hypnosis stream this is I'm getting absolutely
spun about in this game you know that
well I'm about to discover an outpost I don't know what's gonna happen when I get to it but
I literally discover the whole map before I get unlock the next objective
oh goodness me everything's abandoned and there's the name one I freaking saved me
so if I go down here
it's still the wrong place I need to drop below can I drop below on the upcoming thing
did I miss that please don't put me all the way back I have been traveling for a day and why would
just upon me I need to I need to gently go down on the map gently go down on the map
getting the buggy we're driving because this is taking far too long to unlock the next objective
I don't know how I perish from that but what whatever right so that's a crossing right so
so
okay okay okay there's a really I'm getting trolled I'm getting trolled
where am I how
I need to go backwards like this way no like this way go back and do a U turn right I need to do a U
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah I need I figured out how I get there I think
oh my goodness that was a fun noise that was just the noise of pure shock and horror
oh and I'm about to hit a navi driver of course I am because why would I why wouldn't I hit a
massive navi driver straight ahead and I'm about to uncluck right in front of them all hi guys
do you just want to totally annihilate me one by one you might as well line up and have a little
conga going you know just to really drive at home how much I am dead me in this game
I like how actually I just uh I will say one thing I like how I'm always like congratulated
like from how much I'm achieving but the reality of the situation is I am just like
cheesing all the way through the battles I'm like literally not injuring any navi whatsoever
and they're like wow you're doing amazing out there on the battlefield and reality
like I'm just doing backflips all the time and getting away from the enemy
finally got there and yeah that took so long take us out to dinner first
this can happen to you you love nature that's what I get for loving nature that took
wait this teleport site was already on
um
I'm fine that took me how long together
please try not to blow yourself up
I can't believe that 10 saying
did they both blow up or what are just the one
what am I blowing up something anyway oh I'm blowing up the freaking rocks that
blocked me from moving in the first place hardy hardy hard very funny already freaking
that's not supposed to happen what was it
what am I getting shot by that's nice oh this game's trawling me
sounds like we've got company seems like we've got company
I don't like the sounds too many vital words it's going to be some way to slow them down
I'm on it it's got to be some way to slow them down
uh okay we're on your mark oh we're almost there hold on hold on for me you're so close
right I've got healing four that's what I like to see
let us put down these
oh is that a bomb oh that's a bomb has to be bombed anyway me that's supposed to be bomb yeah
all right the bomb did activate even though I did it like that at the same time
okay okay just to do it one more time one more time
it's okay it's okay right they're both they're both
wow I'm getting slowed down by the
enough enough enough I'm getting slowed down
oh
that's all right you just want to spend more time
yeah see how you journey you have to say you're over you know you're still
running through the dank thing
but how about that
half the gears all day gone on
hydration check
when there's orders to fill the power cell in the system reactivate the thing
okay I'm analyzing the map so I can basically go everywhere
I just got the sweep since I was looking at it dog was getting shot in the background
literally the purvy thing
it's no therefore they spawned on time
uh
me oh it's such a shame purvy dogs also me the dogs won't leave me alone
I've had enough no that's too many no that's one too many so that's actually one too many
that's three too many if any more come at me I'm actually be region
this is too much how are you supposed to genuinely do this like
does the devs expect you to pause and do this every single time
there's no way I'm getting bit to death though
there's no way in heck I refuse I refuse
then we're gonna get spat on by the flies and then there's mere dogs
okay I somehow am making it do I need to take a little to the
okay I need to drop the buggy when I get ahead here
and then I'll have gone through the section pretty quickly
there okay we're all good again that is a pretty plan I honestly
I'm surprised I can
wow
okay there's allies ahead that's all I could see
mate you're just letting that plant absolutely decimate you for no reason
okay this is like so much easier can you actually burn the plants you know that oh wait wait wait
it's too many too many dogs
why are there so many multi-different colors but when you play like the navi side where you're
supposed to like be appreciating nature and stuff it's just like
if I have the backtrack one more time right thankfully I can teleport here
you make me backtrack one more time game I'm gonna have it out for you then I'll make myself clear
we surely must be getting back up soon with this one
I feel like we grabbed all the songs so what now
so we're to get in hard for deeds
um the navi side did the game is good the rda side
I'm just wanting it to be over with it's too hard like I'm genuinely hard no I'm not hard
sorry the game is genuinely hard on the rda side
okay so Kendra's got in doubts of what the thing is
and I don't mean I don't mean that um
so when we get the offer
why is it sending me this map is a nightmare to navigate I'm not being funny
this is probably one of the hardest maps this no this will this will be the hardest map ever
that I've had to navigate and do all this stuff and I don't even know where to start maybe the one
to my left if I take a left and then before no if I take a left and then take a right
this is the filter for the human campaign literally like
it's getting rough it's getting rough being like told to go and I know they provide transport
via the the mechs and the the buggies and that but if you're going to do it that your buggy health
makes you explode and you have to reload there's no point in providing that kind of thing like it's
just name is gonna be wait if I can okay I can resurrect I need to take the first right though
I can resurrect but it's fine oh please don't I'm gonna run out of hiding
I am running for my life I didn't even know they were going to do Thanos in the middle no no
please leave me alone please I ask kindly and respectfully to respect my space
I very kindly ask you to respect my social distance social distance please I don't know if
you've seen that Scottish meme where the guy goes social distance please but you said it so politely
I'm I'm just hauling ass there's no way I'd make this without oh right where's it up here to be honest
okay this is actually okay I'll give the game devs something this is actually kind of cool I like
the classic like spiral up something I'll see it I'll see it whoa lovely lovely thank you devs
thank you devs for putting a crack in the fricked rock stairwell I'll take everything I said back
about this design take it all back random gap in the stairwell whilst you're getting
whacked by Navi and the dogs are biting your ankles at the bottom of the rock face and things
are exploding there's like an exploding plan that's aiming on me right now that's what that is oh
speaking of exploding plans here's the bam himself yeah yeah yeah yeah okay right
I am now going to use that teleport to go back to that wiggly one up there
no
I'm losing the will to live just get me out of here right um take if I go here and I take a
right I definitely have access to whatever that right one is get wasted surely saved yes thank
god mission failed we'll get him next time just spawn me on whatever you want it's fine I need to
take a right like this way yeah go that way and get it going
oh is this the last NDA mission NDA I just saw that in the corner of my eye
nope you can AI lock to something else because it ain't me buddy it ain't me that you're AI
lock into get out of here get out of here with that I'm no even entertaining I am taking so much
fall damage just to wait I've already been here before I just need to go left now I might actually
have to pop heal and yeah okay lovely can you yeah do that yeah and then get the heck out of here
oh my gosh golly this is just running simulator I'm literally Tracer from Overwatch maybe I'll
be Tracer should it be we don't make her what about we don't make her what about Bastion
they're Bastion you're a race of Winston I will not be Winston how about Genji I'm already Genji
what about McCree I already chose McCree right what's your idea should have been
any other uh right if I come back Lily I came from I can hit whatever that big sector is
I assume this has to be the last mission like this is for map design uh for map oh maybe not
right now whilst like all the navi are on my butthole that'd be great not to get some luck
um oh just make me invisible should I pick Mercy okay watch our stream uh Mercy up in one hour
10 I repeat Mercy up in one hour 10 I believe everyone is offline for the day uh but Mercy
is online in one outward 10 and of course my invis is gonna run out right on this guy
if I go straight ahead actually I don't know what to do I'm getting so close to him yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah we we knew we knew we knew there's no no point in being pretending
Azura is still playing one shot oh Azura is still on map apologies Azura is currently playing one
shot if you are interested in that if you are by Azura by Azura by Azura she's playing one shot
which is not super hot which I actually thought it was super hot I'm currently sharing tree branches
I don't know what to do because I'm gonna get knocked off which is not what I want at all
so I'm actually gonna have to fight I can't believe it I'm actually gonna have to fight for
yeah sorry we cannot be sharing tree branches these trees are too skinny for me to not perish
Azura what is getting me in oh my god it's a boss this is a boss ring
this this is a boss ring you have thought to be kidding me
I don't this is exactly what I didn't want to happen I'm sorry but he's gonna have to come
down here and fight me like a man I can clear out all these guys at least
ooh I'm not gonna enjoy this fight I can tell you that much uh yeah I need to clear out all the other
little guys first well little I'm little but there's literally nothing I can do until all
of these guys are gone I I'm just I'm just relax I am literally they are going invisible
so I can't see anything right back off seriously back off this isn't funny anymore
I'm no laughing I'm now getting sniped I'm now getting sniped well
the quest no
bro bro you're gonna have to give me a chance AI AI you're gonna have to give me a chance to
clear these guys out and now the dogs are joining in it's fine it's fine everyone just
freaking unanimously gang no I can't say that word but you know what I mean
this is game
what am I supposed to do what am I supposed to do come be real be real be real be hashtag real
these are gonna need gears upgrade gear break gear break gear break gear break gear break
are you guys infinitely spawning or is this just getting like really unlucky
are they infinitely spawning or am I right no let's get rid of the freaking flame sword
because it's just absolutely nothing for us a bush boss mate well sure whatever wait
it's never gonna go right now
I've killed his thing oh his navi's gone so he's a human though
am I done no oh
this has to be the last mission
hold on let me reload what's going on here wait hold on I need ammo
he like blew off I'm sorry but the full damage would be enough oh thank goodness gravy he's
perished don't ever come back again you're not fun to deal with right where'd any go
I'll go here and then if I go like southward I'll get the next one the anti-strongy coalition
has been founded by the navi literally literally let me destroy nature in peace right faggo this way
yes let's get to it
let's get to it everybody look good to do
oh you weren't wait what they're fighting they're fighting each other right go no no go fight the
navi then they border with me you were fighting him a minute ago all willy-nilly then you look at me
all of a sudden no having it what am I supposed to be doing here hold on put me up here so I can see
oh I'm supposed to go down um oh oh that's not nice who's doing that what's that whoever's doing that
you stop that I can see you shouldn't have I can't see you yeah stop cease your activities
I said cease your activities that's ridiculous of plant being able to freaking send off a bone like that
who wrote this game I'd say I can rate better but that's not true oh no I have to go all the way around
to get down there there's no way to fall down there safely well well I need to do a big old U-turn
do you hate the navi yet no I hate playing the RDA say to deal with the navi I can see that much
very strongly but I don't understand how there's plants around here that the navi can claim
because that it's not like I can you like it
I'm just bombing everything actually I probably just bought myself you know that
unless I can get out here fast enough whoa whoa whoa whoa we need to do that
okay please tell me I did them all
I didn't do them all
oh it was to grab a crystal my apologies didn't realize
my apologies my apologies I suck I suck but it's okay please don't do that please don't do that
please don't corner me because that's not really oh not good I am in the rock I am in the rock I'm in
the rock I'm in the rock I'm in the rock I'm in the rock
yeah it's right you can throw me in that direction throw me in that right no no no no you're taking
the pest you're taking the pest you're taking the fist
you don't need to do that please stop embodying on me I'm trying to dodge the AIM but I don't have
health unlock I can heal now I can even go next I can almost go Gon vice I can almost go
go in viz hold on where's the last thing that I need to go if I take if I just go
back to where I came from that sounds I mean if I go back to my hotel for how
did I get there though I go forward and take a right
surely I'm a bit I'm a bit disoriented on this map if I take a right on this
log if I get on that log then I should be able to do you mind honestly give me a
jump scare whenever he is like hanging about honestly I can't believe it I
can't believe that you're hanging about on your planet they really wanted you to
know that the RDA or the bad guys literally so punishing to play the RDA
side sorry but it like Navi so easy I was an overcritical but I don't think the
game is balanced well it just it just seems like unless I'm missing like the
gun that you're supposed to use in quotation marks I am getting brutally
oh no I don't use the teleport I do 180 and I go this way just to make triple
sure yeah I do not want to take off in the wrong direction it's punishing but
fun if it's fun for you to watch me get punished then sure punish me away but
this is region just think I'm just doing so bad I can hear again they gave you a
guard down for stealth no run kills off I hope this is the area I'm gonna cry if
this is like a dead end up here both to play and watch you honestly I never
understood like streamers that can like punish themselves over and over the same
game like I just don't well that's what I don't want none of that I swear if
there's a dog behind me stop it okay that's him there I'm really not
interested in going down to get wrecked by all the other NPCs as well but I don't
think I almost just forfeit all that progress right there that's my shotgun
and you put that way so I can do rounds who are you oh come on come on do it do it do it do it do it do it you
know you want to you know you want to you know you want to get that health bar is
zero for me baby oh no fall dammit hmm right I'm not gonna go in the vines
next time he was honestly taking a hammer in I feel sorry for me can you play
the RDA side okay I've respawned in the area which is good but bad because the
NPCs are literally all okay okay we actually didn't lose the progress on the
health bar I don't think I've seen that before but lol
oh wow just spawn all the NPCs together I don't you know it's fine I didn't want
anyone let me reload let me reload and I can deal you oh wow I'm actually out of
ammo that's how much you've made me spam that shit no can you aim can you aim
hello oh for crying out loud can you aim at the frickin guy that is literally one
millimeter from your eyeball yeah you're getting I thought I dealt with you don't
even bother my was he shooting the buggy I think he was oh I just need to make
it back to this person and then I think I'm done with the worst map ever this map
belongs under my sweaty feet never to be allowed to breathe fresh dry air again
that was awful and I wish not to ever be subjected to this because oh my gosh I
know there's buggies everywhere but I don't even want to get in them because
they just explode in a millisecond goes to the trash ah so it's a good map no it
deserves nothing but my manky sweaty grippers perma sweat oh my god don't don't
give me another map like hanging gardens again hanging gardens more like I it
makes me want to hang myself thank you'll be here all week and bad news both
avatars are dead let me guess neither one of them was harper oh I've still not
defeated harper okay I guess we've got another map after that it's deeper in
the forest how to pin check with officer Midori she might have an update three rock
shards so where do I grab this harmonic yeah good question it's thick out there
and that radar serious service but I got something more I'm picking up a faint more
it's not over just might be our willow tree wait say it again with the bidim's
wait say what again tell me tell me I've already forgotten what I'm supposed to
say what did I say I've already forgotten
what I'm supposed to say I'm ready I'm ready for where I'm supposed to say I was
it what's the map called I've already forgotten Kendra's picked up a signal way
out there it's not much but it's something all right so the maps called
hanging gardens more like I want to hang myself thank you thank you
oh my god they're still not done of the fucking I'm not really able we'll be
should be here all week bro we'll be here all week on this freaking one map on
this one map they really did not want anyone to have fun on the RDA so it's
like literally I want to say this is the harper fight and then I think that's it
no no I'm not even scared anymore I am annoyed if I take a right then either
way I'm gonna make it to the location some people enjoy suffering myself
included but do you enjoy watching suffering like I actually don't mind
watching like a binding of Isaac runs and if the person like struggles to get
through it but still wins like I don't mind watching like I find it quite
entertaining all right if I take the vines across yeah yeah okay oh and there
you are thank you yeah yeah yeah please don't do that oh wait no they're gonna
push me off the freaking veins if I go up stop
stop spanking me it's Emmy who has that audio this month okay not me I do not
have that kind of audio I need to go down no I better not need to go down
something they are
what I need well I'm a bit scared to go on this and all honestly I found it the
willow tree oh right a boss fight with harper but I got no way down it's in a
deep cavern I got to find another way in
a lot of good that didn't it looks like a corp graveyard around here got it what
kind of audience we have this one leave it to grunts to add some mellow I have
sent training one I'm trying to remember the other two off the top of my hand
I should have a call one of them is part of my 1.4 a I have to four part of
series and part one comes out this I almost just did what you think I almost
just did I almost fell off the map doing that man over there that was very
scary yeah rather than you should change yourself to suffering oh that just
cancelled my invisibility okay that's fine no I totally didn't need that it's
not like the cool-down times like a whole 60 seconds or something oh yes
thank you please oh shoot them I can't be bothered anymore after this I don't
really like oh after things I don't really like when you have that
saleswoman the year if this human is just miserable I mean it's fun it's not
too bad like honestly I'm actually enjoying to see what RDA say this but
this map size is mercenary oh you ever alright right girl moment wait oh right
no so this is max max protection well I'll take max protection and now we need
to go this way what's that I'm to take one of these
head or shoot I'm right up on oh a jeez looey let's do that one
over here oh oh loss cathedral a kinder remains me of the underground cave in
Skyrim why is the music even scarier oh please be a small map oh it's a small
map like y'all do thank you if it's small what just got me who are they
above me it must be the Navi above me okay the Navi are oh there he is
mm-hmm I have a problem and that problem is everyone has heists advantage over me
yeah this unless they come down and bite me I am in so much trouble oh dear I'm
gonna get snagged out of it I don't have infinite ammo I can't be messing around
like that I don't have it now is there really no way for me to go unless it's
over here I get out no it's wow this is like really rare to see in a video game
unless I'm just I don't play many video games I really do not recall levels
where you can't even reach the person I don't know maybe I'm being silly yeah
see this is right you can go right one down I don't know how much health he has
but bro I can't I cannot be spraying him with pistols like oh wait I have infinite
ammo here silly me silly Billy hold on I saw that shooting I just spray him the
entire time then I mean I'll do it don't think I won't you don't have to tell me
twice if it's a spring free mission sure he just runs around in circles over and
sadly I can't seem to reach the other NPCs oh they're attacking me actually
getting they jump in yeah whoa the AI is so brutal as a mavi sorry hold on I'm
starting to I don't know if I should actually just focus on the main guy you
said the I don't know if they're infinitely respawning or not that's the
reason why I want to clear them out but I'm getting the feeling they're
infinitely responding maybe oh I just destroyed that plant where is it wow I'm
like actually struggling wow okay half hell I think just more I think just more
down it's the best I got I'm just gonna tank it I'm I really am I'm just gonna
tank it yeah this definitely is given like battle dome unending and thanks
for waiting around until I stand up again actually do appreciate that AI oh that's
not good that's really not good oh this is what I was worried about but there's
definitely more spawning and I'm not way sure what the answer is other than
spray him that's really the best I can do just hope that we mavi cross hairs
going on he is getting staggered he is getting staggered there's there's no
denying that but the Navier again our control up here I don't have high the
plants keep respawning I don't know if maybe the plants the battle rifle can
help you in this moment oh my god shotgun and shotgun ah well let me
thought since way doesn't feel like nothing's happening right now what gun the
battle rifle battle rifle or any launcher Neil Gunn is it actually called
battle rifle issue rifle I've got machine gun ish standard issue
hold on he looks oh hold on hold on hold on I'm just flopping on my face hold
on leave it oh okay okay it's like a triple bar okay it's triple bar we're
trying we're trying that's the main thing like we can do it we can 100% do
that I believe I believe it's just gonna take a sweet time like especially if the
game just constantly is resupplying with new Navi for this guy it makes me
think this is the last boss fight in the last match though because this is big
like this is big this is protection prayer on I can hardly see his body to
okay yeah okay okay okay frickin did it we don't do okay oh oh he's mad I foiled
his plans he said resin for us and okay let's okay okay hold on let me let me
get off let me go let me go let me go let me go hello hello I can't even heal
because I'm getting pushed against the wall oh I've swapped to pistols thank
you for swapping to pistols the most useless out of everything no it is very
much needed right now very much needed the most useless no I need to go I'm
in viz yeah man viz literally I'm gonna heal on rock I'm gonna heal on rock yeah
and I'm pressed up against this dog you're gonna have to let me breathe
seriously video game this is like I'm just gonna run away so best thing I can
do right now do not engage do not engage oh come on who said the same thing
who said the same thing no no I did not want this oh goodness yeah I think I've
actually died you know that I've only got one like cell thing oh I'm glad I have
protection up but I'm I'm I actually don't have faith you know that I'm losing
faith I do not believe unless I can grab these quick enough I literally don't have
a revive if I go down by the way yeah see this that this the amount of abilities
they use I'm sure I could probably be utilizing my abilities better but like
this prayer protection is so constant it's so fucking constant I really hope
nothing else responds I can't tolerate if he's gonna get stuck I will happily
take that oh my god more spawned in please I literally don't have a revive I
honestly don't have a revive I don't have ammo looking where did he go
oh lovely I feel like Lara Croft oh my god they have reef I don't even have it please no
more battles please I'm on my knees I can't I genuinely wholeheartedly I'm not
gonna make it if they make me do it anymore up here sorry I need to find
revives but I don't have any more revives and I keep getting like that a lot like
locked in on your knees I'm not even getting like on my knees like please
tell me you didn't do it anymore I think I'm genuinely gonna lose this like lose
the game because I don't have a I don't have a revive and I don't know what
happens if you perish without a revive on your knees for a head fat oh I
genuinely don't have a revive and I feel like we're about to enter like some
boss get me out of the hangin gardens you down the game town really shocking
behavior oh how am I back here again you've done it and clean Harper's clock
in the process great work writer we should have enough harmonics now to find
that dormant site hook up with Trudy and be lined back to base I'll meet you
there I think because I'm not killing maybe there's a medal or two well teammates
and all right yeah right meet me back at Hell's Gate this should be the last
harmonic
have protection for now I think it is because I'm not because I'm not picking
like a heart and Navi I'm not able to pick up more revives but like I'm in
danger oh I don't know if I'm gonna win this I don't know what happened on your
knees ready to create a dreams camera in himself literally I'm like did they play
test this for like noobs this is like soul play Monro's gone missing things are
going bad or worse you'll have to upload the harmonic without it Monro's missing
the guy he's been running out of time we need to find that he really is the
body geez it has to be you who activates the emulator if you get control of the
well of souls you can put a stop to this madness get started I'm gonna go check
from Monroe okay let's deal so we are about to hit end game oh yeah we're in
the end game now but I'll cool actually kills your scientist man yeah they
probes didn't play any all that the one play tester and he just he just did the
Navi side as well are you trying to finish the campaign yes we finish the
Navi we're about to finish the RDA side however it is my he's not in his office
resource development oh wow actually can't go I actually can't go like in his
office space that's a very small detail
well the office is scared Falco is always evil yeah he's like evil till the
end we can do it we just not need to die or get walled off by like three Navi at
one going into his office space to take his red links safer that for safer
okay she gives me a thumbs up now I went to the avatar station and found Monroe
he's dead and the it's Falco writer you've got to reach the planes at the
oh there you can get to the dormant site and stop Falco wait so you need to stop
Falco and either scenario anyway Falco's gone rogue I gotta reach HQ and alert
them oh
oh so you never actually hurt Pandora either way
path of Goliath hydration chair my voice is dying
I hope we can put a stop to Falco with a wait no I was gonna make a joke and then
that's not funny because it doesn't work my job doesn't work so I can't make it rip
Falco's gone nuts basically scenario he's planning on using it to take over the
plan for himself lightly scenario I was gonna make a Falcon punch joke
and be like I'm gonna falcon punch tell it okay okay oh we need to stop Falcon
Mates will give him a Falcon punch oh sorry sorry guys sorry
you want crickets on that one instead writer we're getting ready to move taking
the fight the blues once and for all sorry about that please well this map
looks more forgiven for one right away because my goodness that last one was
just a nightmare I have access to make some this map which is curious I don't
always have an access that make Chris yeah rough bro tough bro not let's go
out the way or excuse me I would like to wait please okay can only go out of the
green doors got it that one green no that one's red not only one door to go
out of for some odd reason give them a falcon need to
question oh to the nuts sorry I basically just go all the way straight ahead
and I can pick a tree and then come back and get a section challenge
I don't know if I should get out and pick up these RDA things you know that
I might against my better judgment at least if I can have one revive I don't
need to like just need one I don't know should I camp for it maybe not maybe
not I still don't have one no I need one more kill I'll get out when I find the
nice one I'm gonna sign for three I need one RDA one
RDA token I'm just glad I'm allowed to bring the mech for once
there's a warhol too okay there's one there
but if it's safe to get out I will pick it up okay I'm getting hammered
there we'll grab this one whoa whoa this is what I didn't want no I can't
I'm not let's get back in because I've just gone ahead and destroyed it lovely
I'm gonna quickly get this teleport up here yeah yeah yeah yeah the make it so
fun just moving down it just moing down the Nuffie in the little way but it's
right let's try this maybe we can get around and not be so I'm not oh lovely
it doesn't let you have trouble driving oh okay hold on hold on hold on hold on
hold on hold on they've made it nice and impossible to drive as they always do
not even get past that okay Justin no more I can it's green thank goodness
let's activate this teleport station then we can start the mission location you
can boing so hard I've heard good things I'm Colonel Clark Colonel Clark salt is
underway on the Navi strongholds but these guys fight like animals I need you to
go in and break the morale and turn the tide in our favor with all the rest of
the time commander Falco's running on his own if I don't stop him you think you're
running your own show that was talking to me we're trying to stop but if we
don't take out the commander's first those blue bastards so I saw the amp
between the gate and we were never reach panelists that clear enough for you yes
sir a free amp oh sorry possible they've got your order and he spawned it
I'll get you a dragon to channel isn't cars from the guy from the first movie I
think so they seem to have been able to get the likeness of everyone like
Sigourney weaver was at the start of it as well so it seems like when this game
was made they got the rates the new brass said they were sending me a problem
solver I should have known it was you how's your day been Batista painful I
got a whole list of ever heard that name waiting the blues keep sending in their
damn birds to turn us back back and I help they ain't moving until they're
there but you stop
okay another boss you say yeah where is it um right can I take a car please just
to really speed things up I don't I have to admit that last map absolutely oof
that was rough but this map I like literally they're giving you like so
much stuff I assume I can glide over the water over this automatically break
now sorry if they give you literally give me a bit of mobility make it easy to
move around then it's all good left or right up here it's alright
oops sorry that was a rock I didn't see it I'm not gonna glass it's on oops I'm
hitting the curb tea just TV a little tea he moment sorry sorry
you like oh sorry never saw that my bad right I'm gonna circle I guess and I'm
going back on the road over here oh sorry oh right oh it's a tight it's a
tight left sorry I don't know the difference between my left and right
okay okay let's just speed around yeah just do that and we just gently can
claim it can't claim it can claim it or can't claim it oh thank oh thank my
two of them at once please don't did they know how to claim or how oh they've
not been coded to claim I like it I like it
oh let's go cut a fish drive in a moment look I got a arms it's hard to like
really figure it one I'm trying to I'm claiming very high final boss question
work maybe whoa why is he expected I know why you are here I know what you
have done oh these drugs John why to help RDA they are responsible for your
Falco's madness you can stop Falco and you can help people wait that I'm allowed
to join them or am I not to join them stop RDA oh I don't even have a choose
a side in this final battle wait what I do freedom of choice attempt good or
remain evil not join I'm supposed to be evil RDA okay wait what I do that choose
I want to choose RDA so I stand in RDA right I I want to be evil so I stand in
the RDA side right choose to stay with RDA he's taking his bow out he's taking
his bow out oh my god I literally just heard the sound effect
mate you're gonna have to give me some space mate you never tasted lead before
I'm sure you haven't since we humans came here oh fuck and now I'm eating lead
I mean freaking ball string oh I didn't oh oh my well I leave you in the hands of
fate um I did not expect that Lamal I guess I just go back please
it's that yeah get move fast so honestly right if I go wait how did I even get
here I climbed up can I climb down on these or does it not like you climb down
I don't want to get oh no it does let you climb down how strange I remember I
touched that rope another one and and and and the option never came up still
going strong as RDA looks like what did I miss um you missed the last map which
was horrific and you should actually be you should be really glad you missed it
the map layout was horrific like it was telling you to go like all these
different ways and it was all squiggly wiggly and super like calm detail and
complete you scared me oh please drive right just get back on the road and go
the path I've already been oh oh I'm so sorry I didn't mean to hurt you a little
then take a right or a left take a right whoa well camera angle you could be I
have to admit the camera angle could be a wee bit more like forgiven it's like
constantly wanting to like drive me into the ground for some reason it my way
RDA my way RDA because you're in my way RDA I said you're in my way RDA
say it's not me it's not me
it's not me jump scare after all these struggles getting bullied by the AI the
game felt bad and is just letting me do like get through it seriously that last
map though I'll take that one to my grave we hate the hanging cliff
we should be clear to move your team now rolling thunder yeah just wait till I
get out of here before you start blasting I can't make any promises you're not
gonna wait until it get one out of three field commanders okay then surely the
games up somehow I knew you'd end up right in the eye of the storm feels like
the storm is following me courage said you need some help right I've hit a bit
of a snag in my operation his name's Akado savage but a bloody skilled one
responsible for at least a dozen missing men and he's left the rest of them
spooked I need you to put this animal down I'll try all right we're heading
oh someone was smart enough to go ahead and activate that teleport just in case
we were doing a little back and forth and we actually need to teleport to it I
am so smart that's gonna do the Homer Simpson way it's them working I am so
smart said you're in my way RDA oh well you know what I've literally
just spawned here go into an actually actually do everyone just pause I
teleported here and I'm already getting rolled oh so now you're green with me
smart no the S MRT that there's not how is there a tree of souls here unless when
you swap to the Navi you get a Navi body oh that's what I need
um yeah I need a advantage is there anything I can take a advantage on
there's a fucking thing gonna chase me on my ball I'm now getting I'm not getting
wrecked by his pals as well not test protection I just activated like five
NPCs to join in I can't even run out of the way in time this is insane this is
insane I don't know what to do there's like literally nothing I can cheese on
please can I cheese on this oh please oh please let me cheese on this so badly
please please I'm cheating I'm cheating I'm cheating so hard right now I'm not
okay okay okay they all got pushed off let's go
uncheese uncheese uncheese command and she's command and she's command and
choose command right now uncheasing uncheasing commence uncheasing
commence uncheasing commence uncheasing commence untruth you are all gonna need
to like stop with this freaking blasting thing. This is an absolute nightmare. Like all of
them are using... I can't. I can't. I hate to be the UwU girl that goes, I literally
can't right now. I literally can't right now. I don't even know where the Thanator is.
Is the Thanator stuck? At least she's the Thanator. Are you stuck? Oh thank the maker.
Thank the maker, this is a buggy old 2009 game. Eat lead in puke because oh my gosh this game
is so hard. I heard that, I heard you, I literally just heard you spawning. Oh yeah and just heal
up. No it's fine, it's fine, just heal all your health. It's fine, it doesn't matter.
It doesn't matter. No it doesn't matter at all. Get out of my face. No, no! All the time.
Get out, I'm literally freaking walling on stuff. Go away. Stop healing, stop healing.
Stop! I need to reload like this right now. Yeah, hold on, let me take a breather. I just
needed one breather, like literally a second to formulate a thought. Ah! Ah the freaking...
I'm trying so hard, I literally am trying so hard. This is just, and then just spawn
more navi there, they're coming down the hill. I'm stuck against something. Oh please, please!
Oh, um, uh, I cast protection. Oh, oh and um, oh, oh, don't do that, don't do that again,
that's not funny. Talk meeeeere! I'm gonna fucking lose it if I actually die here. Go and just
perish to the elements or something. This is insane. This is standing the field up. No.
Get staggered beyond belief and they don't stagger when they use that ability. And their
ability to freaking his own cooldown, there's no such thing as cooldown to them, they actually
don't know what it is. But my cooldown lasts forever! Literally I can't even cast protection.
Oh and I need to reload at the stupid freaking orange box! And I've got one. Yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. No one's surprised. Freaking spraying. It's literally the more health...
No, yeah, you just do it again. Again with the same move. Oh this is getting ridiculous,
mate. Go and just get a rest, honestly. Oh and you'd repel back to health again because
you can't even just 1v fucking 1v. Literally, I'm not being funny, but if these are like
supposed to be avatars with like titanium bones and stuff and you literally can't 1v 1v without
fucking prayer protection on every 2 seconds with that stupid move!
Oh, fucking terrible, actually. Just perish! Honestly, stop using these abilities. Oh my god, man.
Yay, we did it! Let's go! Oh, I'm so glad that's over. Right, let's move on to the next one.
Yeah, and they're already shooting me. Already, already, already. Right, okay, we'll teleport.
Gigi easy. Oh, I just... I keep forgetting that I'm not as tall as Navi so I can't just
jump that. Oh, well, I didn't need to go on that so sure, whatever. We did it! That was awful.
That was awful. You don't even pick the difficulty in this thing. My controller is literally dripping
with sweat. I thought you loved having autism. It's such a nice little fun tree on the side,
doesn't it? Not. Oh, and I get to do one more. The protection prayer made me think this was
a runescape stream for a second. Yeah, literally. If I could cast it. Oh.
Is there a donation? Did I miss a donation? I think it's working. I don't know. Someone said
they couldn't but then I think a few more donations came through after that so I don't
know if it's messing up on Firefox or things are just not happy. Don't worry about it if
it's not working. Oh, sorry. I just... Oh, I just choked on that. What month to go?
Plain? Take a scorpion and report to the last commander. Yeah, let's try it. Oh. You'll read
it later. I just sent one a bit ago. I don't see it. You're not the only one to say that
you've sent a thingy but it's not came through. I don't know why. The last one I see is from
TinySpiny. It says I've returned from the dog. Wait, did it actually not go through? I don't
want you to don't know if it's not showing up seriously though. Like if it's not showing
up, don't know. I don't know what's going on. Where the heck? What am I supposed to go
on my... Can I just fly through that? Oh, no. I have to fly through the gap. I can already
tell. The last commander seems promising. I can hope so. The RDA site is... It's been
an experience but I'm not sure it's been won for... Yeah, okay. Okay, okay. Let's just
break through the rocks. Don't mind me. Don't worry. I'm always happy to escort my local
calm fish. I know I wouldn't display them. Where am I going? Just a little to the right.
Oh, my goodness. Okay, there's the helipad that I'm supposed to land on. Thank goodness. Make
it nice and easy for me. A little cheeky crash land in there. Don't mind me. Is this not it?
Looks like it. At least when it's over, you can see you've finally completed the game.
Honestly, it's been fun but there's a reason my Tism didn't attach on this game too much
because there's quite a few things like that that are really annoying. Hey, last one.
Oh.
The only reason I could even win that last fight is because I managed to cheat that Thanotaur.
I cannot imagine if I would even get past that if that Thanotaur didn't get caught in the
roll. I'm sorry. I said that wrong.
Am I allowed to slide to get there?
I'm going to be giving me a mix. I'll take a mix because he's giving me a mix.
Then you can play the domination minigame. I like on the navi side. I've never played it on this side.
Alrighty. If I take a right, then everything shall be alright.
Let's hope this last one. Strony, you sound sleepy. I hope you're having fun.
You know, I'm having fun. I know that sounds like a-
That's a fat punch. I'm getting spawned spanked by a freaking plant.
I'm enjoying it. It's just because I've never played it before.
I just did not expect at all how unbelievably hard it was.
For example, there's RDA soldiers literally getting messed up by these plants.
They're just letting it happen. I had no idea they would make it so hard.
On the navi side, you can just ignore everything.
But when you're a wee human, you actually can't ignore everything.
Or else you're like a big doo-doo.
I'm hoping I do get a good night's sleep soon because it's really hard to be creative.
RDAs and MarkoLabs are coming up with scripts when I've literally got no thoughts going on behind my skull.
There's RDAs.
I'm actually going to pick it up because they're too valuable.
Wait, I can't even go up on my head.
Okay, I need to climb on foot.
RDAs say it's too real sad.
I hope you're doing a good night's sleep.
Yeah, I've not had a decent one in quite a while.
Oh my god, there's so many of them.
Okay, that was good. I like that.
I think it tears that fast all the time. That's great.
See, when it misses, it really bothers me.
Oh, I'm just going in biz. I don't know. There's enemies everywhere.
Oh, I can hear one right behind me.
I'm going to try and claim this before default.
Get some rest. I will get some good rest.
I don't know what my stream is tomorrow. I can't remember.
Is it ASMR?
Or is that a small game?
I think it goes ASMR sweets.
Oh, this is a boss fight.
Yeah, I'm already getting ruled.
Oh, I'm already getting ruled by boss.
Okay, this is what I can't stand.
I'm about to go do a boss fight and there's like a billion rub.
Nah, nah, come on, mate.
Yeah, this is getting ridiculous.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Thank goodness I was picking up RDA things.
Whoa.
No, no, you're so dead.
Get that.
Right, a spell of protection, spell of invincibility,
because what the actual?
Bro, you're going to need to let...
I'm dead on the last one.
I need a breather.
I literally need a health breather.
The AI can freaking see me.
Yeah, she literally won't go down
because she keeps activating all of her abilities.
This is ridiculous.
Right, so they're...
Okay.
Bro, you're just stun-locking me.
I literally can't get close enough.
Yeah, how do you like being fucking stun-locked?
Oh, fuck off!
Just infinite spawn after spot.
So get the fucking moab out, honestly.
What the fucking is this shit, honestly?
Have I activated it?
Hello, stamina?
Lovely.
Let me analize.
That did a sweet fuck all.
Lovely, lovely.
Don't ever show your fucking hideous face again.
That was what bloody waste that was.
Right, that's the best I got, Berserk.
Berserk's literally the best I got.
And I get stunned the moment I use it.
Bro, I need to put a little invisible on
so I can literally heal in time.
I'm gonna get stunned the millisecond.
This is why I don't play read games on stream
because I literally can't even handle a normal game.
And then invisible again so I can't get him
and then tarot him shooting at me
and then stun me, and stun me, and stun me,
and stun me, and stun me, and stun me.
Okay, we get it, we get it, we get it, we get it, we get it.
We love a good stun, we all...
And then, yeah, and then into the spawn rate.
What are their abilities?
You literally just use that one
so you don't even have a cooldown at all.
Oh, and then in comes your buddy use.
Yeah, and then your buddy uses their ability.
And then I'm away wasting ammo yet again.
Oh, yeah, again, I'm not the frickin' boss.
You're gonna need to get a great game.
Honestly, you're gonna need, again, a straight to ability.
Can't, need to wait, need to wait.
Again, straight to ability.
Fucking infinite, buddy.
Yep, and then the gift.
No, oh, a Christmas miracle.
I actually got a fucking thing from it.
Wow.
Oh, and your pal's already back.
I've not even been away for, like, on the list, I think.
I'm gonna have to go into this and fucking do this, right?
At least I've reloaded, but...
Yeah, and I'm already in spanked.
I don't even remember the fucking enemy that I'm supposed to be killing is.
Oh, and straight to the ability.
What a classic.
Oh, more of your pal's!
There's nothing I can do.
There's actually nothing I can do other than tick damage.
This is just the tiniest amount of damage that can be dealt at any moment.
And it just...
Over and over again!
Literally playing this game over and over again.
One hit, get nothing more.
Have to heal, get nothing more.
Just fucking perish off.
Fucking map!
Uh, I'm dead. I'm actually dead.
I don't have a invis, and I don't have a heal.
I don't know what you want me to do.
Who made this? Ubisoft?
How many game...
How many fucking playtesters have you got?
Like, one max, maybe?
Do you share one for, like, one fucking region?
One for whole of Oceanic?
One for whole of Bloody Europe?
One for whole of fucking America?
Like, what's going on?
None of you's playtested this.
Not one person.
Not one person!
Listen!
Oh, let me just analyze and see if this is...
There seems fair.
Hmm...
Right, let's do infinite spawning.
Let's make sure you get stun law, right?
Okay, hmm...
Alright, let's do it.
Let's do it!
Let's do a cheeky gangbang!
Oh my God!
Let's just do a cheeky gangbang and make sure that the enemies...
Enemies are allowed to infinite heal.
It's fine. Enemies can infinite heal.
Enemies can infinite fucking use their abilities.
All the fucking time!
And as soon as you give them a Santa me are off of their HP bar
Oh, let's just make sure they just give them everything all it wants infinite fucking mana. Oh
My god
Just let it be over with
Just let it happen. Oh my god
Like I literally need to go invisible
Oh my god, just let it be over
Just let it be over
Again, yeah instant stun lock as soon as you shit. I don't even have that ability is Navi when I play Navi
I don't even have this ability
Just instant fucking lock over and over and and your pals are back
I
Would absolutely love to have a whole fucking trade behind me, but I've nobody got that extension have a
Best I can do
100 got 100 shotgun shells was there enough may you go get more
Because it was now of course it was down off. Oh, yeah, no, it's fine. No, it's fine. I didn't want one
Yep, no, it's fine. I
Love being absolutely incapacitated
No, this is so fun
I
Love it. You should do it more Ashley. How about you just spawn eight NPCs all fucking one said one time. Oh my fucking god
Fucking RDA fan is honestly. Oh, and I'm probably gonna die jumping off this clutch looking me
Just to really fucking ace it on the cake. They just actually can he stop it. They actually
Yeah
Yep, and all aimed even though in viz all in will continue probably not even be able to heal and play man
I get to die
Because I only have one fucking RDA element to my fucking name
But here
Yeah
This better be the last mission. I am like fucking correct right now. I
Really hope like I severely hope this is the last mission
I
Instant damage to the mech not even in the body sign
For the cheeky gang bang party parrot party parrot party parrot
It's never fucking ending volt was it vault
Vulcan thank you for the tip. It's never ending. There is no way that was
appropriately play tested unless I'm missing like
Some major notes and I missed a massive patch that came out for this game in 2009 that there's no
way
That is the gameplay and then the dev team happy with that game
Refused to accept that that even got passed
Absolutely refused to accept that got passed I
Don't think anyone got this far in the police say I completely agree with that statement because what on earth was that
Literally, I don't have an ability when I play Navi if I get hit I have a massive fucking throbbing
Fucking pulse coming from a bloody groin. No, I don't want to teleport. I want to talk to the man
Please let it be over
Hmm let it be over
Let it be over. Yeah, I'm not
Let it be over
Yeah, that Moab did absolutely nothing. I don't even know what the point of that was
Let it be over let it be over let it be over let it be over let it be over let it be over
Thanks for borrowing a condom
This game was pretty bad pretty fast after lunch thanks to the game getting canned hard
And took their money in around I mean they made them if they got two points seven million sales. Yeah
Are we there
You so much you put a scratch there there last at least the section saying you were you mean that wasn't the last section
Are you implying there is more to this fucking thing?
Horses or did you to board a dragon to fly to some location?
This is why mommy likes me hold her hand. Yes. This is why I like
You're still streaming. Oh, you just missed the part where I screamed down the make so yeah
Oh
Please let me go with this right why does the conductor keep putting me on?
Why did they keep creating more and more sections of this fucking site of the map?
Okay, this is it this is it the map looks like this is it there's nothing more of the matter
We just got worth it fuck was gone broke. Oh
Well, we all pretended that you finished the game and you can go risk. No, this is it
Look at the map. There's no way this map is a fetch quest because look at the state of it. There's nothing on it. Oh
Did I get to drive this at least
It's over
Oh, how do I fly this? Oh fuck me, man. Oh
No, oh no, I don't like that. Oh, no
Right, okay. Oh, yeah. Oh, huh. Oh, yeah, I can fly I can fly
Call me Peter Pan because you can fly you can fly you can fly
Okay, take it easy easy on the corners easy
Pandora is a little wild for the road bumps and by road bumps the full mass of asphalt
You can shoot the rocks
Oh
Wait, I'm gonna run out of missiles
That was a very successful drive, I think I don't think I actually bumped into one thing
Easy easy
Oh
Okay, there are wolves, but that's fine. Nothing I can't handle. Oh
I can't do my little flip in the war. It will flip
What kind of sadistic
Made to say you should be able to run out of missiles honestly
It does seem about like that flight thing that flying dragon is massive and you're telling me they can't hold more than like 20
missiles. Oh
Here we go. Here we go. Here we go. Here we go. Here we go. Why are you holding that piece of paper? Oh
What's the plan
I'm not going anywhere near me
We could use your help get that wall down and dig in I'm gonna do I'm gonna put down TNT
As long as there's no boss fight, I couldn't be less of a rats or what fetch quest you send me on name your boss fights
What is this? What is this armor?
Protection down but everything else up. I think I'd rather protection up
Just leave it leave it
What's this? Right? What's the deal?
What much I do?
As long as there's no boss fight on the other side, I couldn't give the last of a rat
I couldn't give the last rat
Anymore
If the goal was to make the count and pain memorable they should be sure succeeded
Oh, I'd say more like miserable because
Again, like literally the Navi instantly do that as soon as you injure them. They do their thing
Except that one I guess
Let's just let's navigate we're appropriate
I don't know if I should just speed run it
Can the make even go on the bridge that's up ahead?
Oh
Like this game parish definitely, yeah, thanks for that really appreciate that. Um
Why am I being shot? I'm being chased. I'm being chased
Um
Oh, yeah, definitely happy to replay that's true brotherhood not happy to replay
The Navi side yay fun the RDA side. Oh my god
I think I've almost got two revives, but I don't think I have a boss fight anymore
I think this is literally just
Spring pray from here on out
Oh
That's a lot of Navi and they're probably gonna destroy my make-up. I'm not careful
Where's BT when you need them honestly?
I
Might get out for that RDA dangerous, but I'm like it seems to be I just want a few revives on hand
Oh, right. I've got two revives now
As long as I can choose a hate thing if there's a fight ahead. I
Just hope this oh my god, my mix
Well, look at me. Let's just go for it
I
Right just go keep going
Just like there's fates all the way up ahead
We need BT
Honestly sorry for reason the idea of RDA, but thank you for experience in it
Thank you for experiencing the pain. I mean some people enjoy when streamers rage. I don't know
I
Got taken out in viz for that like some people genuinely love when streamers rage and I'm like
Hold off the Navi. No, you are not gonna make them literally
I don't know how freaking strong you think I am I am not that good. I that's
Okay, I'm gonna try and keep a lid on it and not get overwhelmed very quickly. I am so glad I picked up the other RDA
I can't do anything
Yeah, I'm gonna need you guys
I
Need everyone to start spamming needs everywhere because I'm pretty sure those are RDA needs
I'm gonna need everyone to do that unanimously unanimously right now
It's not it's okay, just sacrifice me in the fire
Oh, and I'm taking out in viz, which is the only time it helps to redo my
Okay, I feel and then the damage protection to tell I can get my heal back up
I need long range
Our bombs, okay, those are definitely our needs. I feel like if the Navi were doing needs like that, I'd be a goner already
Okay, okay, we're not overrun
But don't want to jinx it, but I'm gonna grab that it's really important
I'm really jinxed it but it's looking good only a minute 30 of this and then we're done
Okay
Protection on I don't really want to make me too much
I'll take
Okay, I don't know every spamming needs to keep doing that shit. Oh my god
It's literally sunlocking them from hitting us. Oh, that's a lot. That's a lot. Hold on. Oh
Dear I think I think maybe some of our soldiers went down because we're getting no, okay now we're overrun again
If I can just whittle down some base health on them, it just makes all the world is different
Oh, we might actually have three roses. Oh, I'm getting sunlocked my pardon
I'm not that mad because I'm actually getting help like genuinely getting help and like they're not all all
On to me it's when they all all often there's like nothing I can do hold on sorry
Because I'm too busy
freezing the game for not being absolutely
I take it back
Why do you fill out your pistols every time why do you insist on filling out the pistols?
Well, I hope it didn't die because of that freaking cutscene
Oh
Is mercy up by the way, I think mercy may be alive. I may have completely missed it during my reach
Okay, no, so they are still attacking whatever but I mean I'm getting left them own devices. I'll take it
Danger danger danger high voltage. Okay. Mercy is live. Yes. Uh, monster. Welcome to link her. We will redirect into her
I think we're almost done. I am going for a nap after this stream. I can tell you that much
Wow
Mercy's region. Yeah, if you want it, I don't know you'll need to see who reaches more me or mercy
Oh, I'm done
I can sense it
I'm licking the screen right now
Almost done
You know, that's what I'm talking about now. We can take it to the room
You need more than enough
One reach stream to the next return to your dragon and fly to the well of souls. We've done it
The evil has been defeated. I will never I'm very happy to say I will never play the rda side again
Oh, uh a rank rotten experience
Dev team do not speak ever again and do not cook ever again
Thank you and good night. That's my review
Forward a little to the right
The gamer region real I was just it was just rinse and repeat rinse and repeat in the moment. I've got even uh
A hint of damage a lick of damage to speed things up. Uh, either new guys were brought in
Oh, it is I actually have a health bar just
Definitely shouldn't be taking these corners too willy-nilly then
I'm gonna start showing you but I can't help but find out whole when you're angry. Oh my god. I feel like that would be terrifying
I'm making that PP shrivel up and go back and save me. I'm just gonna be terrified
If I was on the receiving end of that
Same here it's kind of what no
Oh, my god. Sorry. Sorry women moments
Looks partners bad boy
Right we did it we have confirmed the evil
Is the game gonna let us get there without being attacked by a plan
Oh
No fighting here or I'm gonna cry. I'm gonna angry spot is more. I'm sorry so but terrifies mommy
Right oh
Oh
I'm going
Listen to you
The new recruit fresh from earth. I've been working on this for over 10 years
This is my moment right now. So if it doesn't work
I'll see you on the other side. Oh wait. I have to I need to end him anyway
Oh
Well, this is gonna be beautifully satisfying
Just let me cook a bit. Okay. It's fine. He has a belly. He's allowed him
But yeah, it's just gonna be satisfying all things considered. Actually, you know what I could probably put on that double aggression thing
Preserver. Yeah, let's do that
Okay, that's fine
Oh, he healed up
I'm not sure I can send it to you healing up. So don't do that again
Okay, I kind of like some walking and more I'm not gonna lie
That's okay. He doesn't really seem to do anything. It seems like he blows
Hmm
I'm just giving him it. I'm just throwing everything out. I'm hold on a minute
Oh, wow, so the sonic pulse is too far away none. Okay, he's full healed again
Now sadly I am going to run out of ammo doing this method
So not really sure what's supposed to happen
It's fine you're allowed to do that, but maybe don't heal again
Um
Um, am I supposed to do something special for this fight?
I don't know how many heals you get. If you get like five and then the game's like, okay, no more heals for you
Well, why did the aim do it?
Uh, is there like a ammo station? There was one back there. Uh, I'm literally out other than my shorty
Oh
I'm not like mad at this fight or anything, but like bro you keep healing like there's nothing I can do
I don't like
You use my mortar strike on him
I did nothing to him
Hello
Um
I'm a bit confused. Sorry. I need to change out my weapons because they're all empty. So I can't
the nail gun sure
Uh, it's already full me and there's no point in making it at flame doors or
Uh, machine gun? I don't know. Okay. Oh, this one's different
Okay, nail gun again
All right, healed again
I don't know if I'm supposed to call upon Awa to do something
The utility looks like it's less literally sneaking on. I guess he's just a damage on
Wait, just go to the glowing thing
The thing back here
No, it's a bit of a glowing thing
I'm
Blowing
Sorry, I'm brain
I'm both brain dead. I'm bling bling thing
I'm looking
But yeah, I'm starting to think I'm needing to like call upon Awa to like end him because
I'm literally like swimming right now. Excuse me. I tried to go for a wee swim before I ended you
I'm just gonna like up on Awa. Oops. Sorry
Oh
Blowing
I'm definitely not to claim Awa right now glowing
I thought that stick. I mean that stick is glowing. What the fuck it is
I
Warning de synchronization imminent honestly, can you bring him to a ledge?
I feel like I'm supposed to do something here
I think it's broke. Okay, so I watched a quick video and the guy
He uses a green angel. Oh greening greening launcher. Okay
Is this a grenade launcher? I only have 20 on the grenade
Oh
Oh, wow, really? Okay after all of that bro
I'm starting to think this shit wasn't playtested at all past this point
Are we the baddies
All right
Um, yeah, let's see where the baddies all right
Ryder you there colonel quarch
Analyst is going like a baseball stadium. What the hell did you do? I'm not sure
Whatever you did it worked, but now we are making a quick retreat. I'm getting reports. They lost control of their band cheese
That makes sense to you. Yeah
It actually does
Congrats Ryder. You're gonna be a hero for this
I'll get your butt down here and that dragon better be spotless. He had damage on the dragon
Eat that you grace. I heard we lost Kendra, but you need to know you did the right thing
I hope it was all right
This better bring peace. You've stopped a catastrophe, but this isn't over
We can't keep control available for long nor should we and we've got more shit
of humans do to arrive
More is inevitable. So what was this all for?
A we needed to see what we're not there being part two spoilers from the movie in the video game
Next time she'll be ready
Am I here
Development team should be ashamed of yourself for the rda side
Development team should be proud of yourselves from the navi side. Don't ever make me do that again. That's awful
Oh my god
I have no idea how hard I reach because I can't remember in the moment
But oh my god
Am I going mental or was that terrible?
I think I must have I think I should have been using the grenade launcher clearly from that last fight
and and because I didn't use the grenade launcher
and
It just got from like bad to worse or
You blacked out when you raised. I don't remember really what I just remember like I did get angry
But I don't remember anything that actually happened like one minute
I was like getting annoyed and then the next minute the fight was over and I got stuck on a rock and I was trying to get down
A grenade launcher is op. Okay, I guess that's probably you're shouting quite a bit
I'm cheeky. Bye
She literally saw red. Honestly. It was beautiful. Monka is you're rage is hot, but the mission was bad
Angry girl, you were fuming at the man. I was frothing for mama. I clipped it. So show up one stream and it's Monka
I don't even know. Am I going to be embarrassed if I look back on it like I don't feel that bad right now
So kind of been that bad
The game got dunked on hard and forgotten pretty quickly, but for the general community for a lot of good reasons
At least you finished it. You deserve a good rest. Good girl. I'm proud of you for not driving up
The rage has talked to your content. Well, that is literally why I do not play rage games like mercies unironically so brave
For playing that game. Like I couldn't I'd just be scurrying and
It may be a bit embarrassing, but at least it seems to have been for a good reason. I felt that rage. It's so funny
Also, you might want to make more tea before sleeping or after waking up or for my voice
I mean, it felt like a justifiable rage or he just won't make us cause the rage was justified. Okay
Congrats. You did good job thing
So you need more than an app. You may need to fill it. Oh, I hope I can get like a full eight hours. I've been needing it for a while
Hmm, you didn't give up. So you did a good job at least. Heck yeah
Mad cause bad. Lamar true. Literally all I had to do was pull out the grinny launcher
apparently
Lucky me
Lucky me. All I had to do was pull it
Take these head pads
I would have went insane. You're amazing
Well, then I feel like you guys probably would have figured out to swap to the weapon way before I did so
Sending hugs if they're welcome. Otherwise you did so good. I'll take those hugs
Are you the first person to finish this campaign on stream?
Stop imagine if I was like the first vtuber to play this game. That would be hilarious
And and the pov is like isn't the navi side amazing and then the rd side is me just screaming
Sorry for forcing you to play that. I feel bad now. Nah, come on. I can stop at any time
I just say stilettos and then I would stop. Don't worry
If you're the first that counts as a world record, I would have thrown my monitor before changing weapons
making vtuber history
So when an angry scot rages. Oh, so wins the angry scotch rages somewhere on
the floor
I'm pretty sure you are though. Oh, no, I'm what sorry. I've already I've already forgotten what I'm probably would have overgranted
Before and killed it with a bigger number. You're probably the only one that ever will you can be the avatar of youtuber
The way of the water the way of the scot
You did great powering through that heck. Yeah, think about it. You used the worst weapon to beat the game. Honestly
I actually think you are the first vtuber to do answer every shipper history
Not even a weekend after debut and i'm already making history
But see fully the rda was a lot more fun than the navi
Why because of the rage apparently everyone's got you know, half masked at the moment because they liked my rage
The way of the scot the cut fish the way school and
You have a full monopoly on this game now. Okay. Okay. I'll take it. I'll take it
I'm the type to pause the game and watch a video spin feeding me on what to do
Honestly small streamer did two years ago, but for both campaigns. Yes
half half
Now i'm going to get the game to relieve or to relive the pain
You can't me
Yeah, let's say half only half wait, there's no way i'll need to make a rage ASMR if that's okay
I don't mean suffering like that
Like honestly, I feel fine now, but I guess in the moment. I was like scary region
Sorry if I scared anyone. I apologize
Got some ancestral rage build up in me, I guess
Me just skipping 60 percent past all the enemies honestly
60 percent probably like 100 percent of the optional fights i skipped like i'm not even kidding
Now you scare us more. No, you didn't scare
You could do it more. You're like, well, I do have a
Donut's lawn reward potentially being that rage, but yeah
Stormy rage should be like you call that a willy. That's just prophetic, you know
That was uh, that wasn't scary. It was the opposite. Oh the fabled Scottish rage
I mean, I was scared and felt something else at the same time. I'm not gonna explain. That's actually hilarious
I didn't know that had that effect. It makes me remember the banshee scream. Oh
I'm not sure I can even banshee scream
Like I can do it. Like my screams very loud, but I'm not gonna scream because I
I think after the rage, I don't know if one of the neighbors will probably try to listen in on me right now
And be like what is going on
Angry hypnosis ASMR
Get hypnotized. Get hypnotized. Get hypnotized. I still prefer subspace
Just yelling get up
Right, um, they're gonna call the police on you. I've actually wondered if it's a possibility
I did speak to my neighbors at one point
And I explained to them that i'm a voice actress
So if they hear anything at night, don't be too worried. It's just me
So my voice acting's a bit different
Um, can you make a reward that you just scream Scotland forever Scotland forever
Passive aggressive ASMR guys. They're like, is she okay in there? Does she need help?
If someone clip that moment the clip will get but will get pretty
Oh the toothbrushing I'm gonna go get my toothbrush. Okay
I'll be right back. We're gonna if you want to get your toothbrush and brush your teeth
Before we go off-stream you can most certainly do it
I
Got one out of 21 days to brush our teeth
Like let me put my headset on so I can listen to the
Thingy right. I've got my toothbrush. It could be a sound pack from morning alarms. Just full bag pouch
I have toothpaste because I salivate a lot. I don't know about you
But whenever something enters my mouth, it starts to salivate like crazy
We're gonna brush our teeth and then we'll read into
Yeah, mercy. I was gonna call her mousy for a second. What she ate a mouse?
Are you ready?
Are you ready to brush your teethies
With me
I'm gonna do it for two minutes. Okay. That's how long you brush your teeth
So just start with the front of your teeth, right?
I see you. I do you want me to mute the game so you can like really hear the brushy brush
Yeah
I don't think you're gonna hear it over the thing. No, I will start a two minute counter now
Uh, oh, yeah, sorry. Let me mute the game
I was probably gonna break now that I'm out and it's tabbed out the game. There we go
Do you have a chatting? I do have chatting. Hold on
Uh, whoa, that's a lot of words to speed up one. Hold on
Uh, I got sorry. I've got toothpaste on my mouth right now. Pardon me. One second one second
I will do that and I do this
Okay, we're brushing our teethies
Hmm
Okay, two minutes of teeth brushing is a lot
Oh, no, you can hear my background music shift back my music you're ruining it. Uh
Wait two minutes so um 39 minutes past
Wait make sure you do the outside first
Oh my god, my shoe floor is quite all ready. Um, I don't think this is enough product paper
Okay, now the bed that most people mess I'm spitting everywhere. Hold on. I need more
Does that have a pillow in this room? I don't
I have so much saliva coming out of my mouth
Do the back of your front teeth and the back of your front bottom teeth that's the most forgotten science when you brush your teeth, okay?
I'll go cook some tea
I
We get no cavities over here. We get no how you call them
uh
What what are you called haemorrhoids? No haemorrhoids. No cavities
We are good with things
and we go that
Don't brush too hard on your gondola. We're free. I don't
No root canals. We don't believe in root canals in this house
root canal blood
Haemorrhoids, yeah, we don't have haemorrhoids in this community
Uh, I can't pull off because I don't know about the foster but we're just gonna brush our teeth in general
and we're gonna do it for quite one day in a row
and then
Everyone's gonna have a teeth brush and have it, okay? And life is nice and easy. Oh my god. This bit is going over the paper towel. Well, it's not on a toilet roll, but uh
Get the back of your wisdom tooth for you still got them
No, not mouth haemorrhoids booty haemorrhoids
Okay, and make sure you do circular motions. That's how you get all the the peas and poos off your teeth
Mm-hmm. Okay. I think I'm almost done
Is there a toothbrush out for a retailer? No, no, I don't brush in our teeth
Yeah, we're getting the because we didn't know
The reason why hold on I need to spit I'm gonna spit into my little mcdonald
Uh, crazy. Are you ready here there?
That's so much spit. I didn't need to generate that much, but I did
So minty
We did it. We have established day one of a 21 day habit of brushing our teeth
Thank you for the drink. No, not my used toothpaste, but
The only thing I don't like about toothpaste is that it keeps sitting
Like it keeps in your you're not to you're not to rinse that way, but if you need to spit it out like
Yeah
Okay
Did it we played the world's most annoying game
Right, I'm going to make triple sure I am redirecting into mary
Oh, I just minimized the tab by accident
Oh, I'm all docky too
No, that's mersey's umari stream
Stony cuttage a bit of stony cuttage
Thanks for the stream. You're most welcome. Thanks for hanging. Sorry for scared anyone to do apologize, but that
Sorry about that old chap didn't really mean to scare you did I? Oh, but just kind of came out
Kind of just came out
I said what everyone was thinking and saying
But uh, yeah, that game needs a hot patch for weapon drill. That's all I'm saying
It won't let me open the redirect thing. Why not?
YouTube you're so stinky sometimes it won't let me load so I can redirect into mary. I need to wait for it to load
Okay, I did it now
Oh tomorrow we have old school runesgate. Oh, I need to make my account
But what do I call my account is the question?
my
meaning
customization redirect add
A difficulty right into mersey say
Mersey
Good better work
Because
Right my little reeflings. I honestly didn't think we were gonna. I honestly thought we're going to end out four hours
but we've made it to almost 10 hours! Look at us go. You guys have so much stamina.
Wait, wait, can I try this out? Hold on, I don't know if I can try this out right now.
Is this gonna work or is this gonna break?
You did so well. You make me so proud.
You made such a long, unending stamina for me.
Did it work?
Did it work? Did I have a reverb effect when I did that? I don't know if that worked or not,
or did I mess it up. What do you mean, look at your skull? You're the crazy one who took
stuff. I'm feeling like it is. Yeah, the reverb was like, yes, it worked. I'm so happy.
If my voice wasn't so burst, I'd do a bit more, but it's burst right now.
Big burst, big burst.
All hail the glowfish.
It looks good when my eyes and my little shells, you can kind of see the transparency of my
shells a bit better like this. Maybe you can see my reflective thing going on. It works, so
wait, talk a bit. Okay, I'm glad it worked. Right, I am going to end it there without a
fantastic endurance room. Tomorrow is old-school runescape, so just so you know the plan, the plan
is that I'm going to make a new fresh account. You don't have to, but my idea was that we do
some questing to level up, and then we basically just have fun leveling up cooking and see where
it goes. But I'm a bit rubbish at quests, so it would be nice to try them together, like Cook's
Assistant. I'm sure there's a Vam, that haunted house quest. I can't remember its name right now,
but we're going to do those kind of questings, and then we can do some fishing together, and we'll
cook the fish outside of the barbarian village, because that's free, and we can cook crayfish for
free. I'm pretty sure you just need to get a net. Are you doing members? I think so, that's my only
issue. I'm going to buy membership, but I'll play, like I'll go into a free-to-play lobby, and we can
do the free-to-play quests, and take it from there, because I'm not entirely sure what the plan is after
that. I joined you on old-school RuneScape Sheebie. I hate to break it to you, my name's
Ronnie. My own tags level drain hypnosis. Yes, RuneScape membership. Time to make my account
tonight too. Yes, I'll share whatever we're on, and we can all go questing together, and we can
see all the reefling gang gang. I'm tired, it's pain. I know, I know what you meant. I need to go
sleep. The fangs are so much easier to admire this school. Yeah. Some people thought they were
vampire fangs, but they're not. You can't really see my ears, but they're slightly pointed. No,
pointy ears. I haven't played in ages, I need to learn. Yeah, we can all get like the same level.
We can all like hack the same yew tree when we're trying to level up our woodcraft.
Are you planning on playing something that follows 76? I think that's multiplayer,
but I don't know how to get you in my lobby. Like, how do I get reeflings in the lobby?
Or is it like, can we make a lobby code, and it's like a server like they host? I'm not sure how 76
works. Get bit by the fish, you wonder why? Would you let me bite you, reefling? That's terrible,
you should let me do it. Love your choice of games so far makes me safe to see where else you got
blood. Well, I'm glad you like the game so far. I'm literally just picking childhood stuff and
stuff that makes me happy. So I'm glad. But yes, old school RuneScape definitely
might be a recurring multiplayer for a little bit. I'm not really gonna, I'm not sure what happens
when membership, what membership streams are planned. I think we'll also do, I think three
membership streams a week possibly. One for react movie, one for membership
multiplayer. I'll decide. Like, I wouldn't do like progression on old school RuneScape
multiplayer behind a membership stream because that's not fair for those invested. So maybe,
maybe, maybe. I first played again yesterday for the first time, used old school RuneScape,
and a goblin got you, you got done at Goblin Village. A Dead by Daylight member stream? Yeah,
I'm open to these kind of things. But yeah, one, I want to consistently have a member stream
when membership's open. A react Andy, like we'll watch a movie together. And then I might also do
a script writing stream. Or maybe show you some behind the scenes stuff, like maybe we write
shorts. I don't know. I'm trying to think of like stuff you guys want to see. And then of course,
we could just like maybe smaller games that aren't necessarily stream worthy on main. So for those of
you who are unable to membership, please don't worry. I always have free content coming out and I
for days, like so you know how we played needy streamer overload yesterday? Because it was only
two hours long, like that's a short game. I would then come back online after maybe like a 30 minute
rest and then do a membership stream. So you still get like content that day and then like I'll raid
into whoever's online and like keep going. So yeah, don't worry. She streams eight days a week.
Yeah, don't ever worry. And like obviously the ASMR comes out as well. That's like free on YouTube.
You can watch on YouTube anytime. Script writing stream or submit scripts? Yes, it would be a bit
hard to review scripts live because I would need to use euphemism and stuff. That's nice as long
as you're not overworking yourself. I will make what I can handle and we can take it from there.
Yeah. Get that Hermione to rewind time and overlap herself streaming honestly.
True. True. I'll need to see eventually you'll be able to close your eyes and see her for a moment
and you're out watching. Yeah. Always on that. There are always streams. So yes, please never worry
if you don't have the money for membership because I stream every day and you can come see me every
day. And yeah, I'll make sure everyone gets their money's worth either way because I don't like
when streamers don't get their money's worth. Sorry, I don't like when streamers don't get their
money's worth. So that's just me. So yeah. Strony is a streaming beast. I'm sure she'll have something
for you. Yeah, I've got something for everyone. Or that's the plan anyway. Hopefully I got something
for everyone. So you're saying is I should never become a member. Only if you are financially
capable. And if you're only financially capable to support one person, I recommend doing my daughters
over me. Okay. Because I always have free accessible content. Always coming out. So yeah.
We love you, Strony. Please don't try my blood bliss.
Yes. You're such a good girl. I will skip meals to members. Stop. No, we're not doing these jokes.
I don't actually don't like these. There was like one joke that was like, oh, I'm like in a homeless
shelter. And then I've given you like membership or whatever. I'm like, no, it's actually probably
I am like so goofy and non serious all the time. Those kind of jokes are like, I don't like them.
I sold my kidney. You definitely have a few streams that I need to rewatch. I love it though.
Oh, they're long streams. You'll be rewatching for a while. But I'm good for putting on in the
background for a rambling. If you ever like, I need I want to listen to something in the
background, but I don't want to actually focus in. Yeah, just put the avatar stream on. And then
when it comes to the RDA part, we're going to start screaming my head off. My, my, my scarier.
But I'm looking forward to your first asterisk. I hope YouTube doesn't do anything. I'm a bit
worried, but I'm not going to be doing ear licking or anything like that. I don't know what the heck
YouTube's been playing at recently. It's making me nervous to even upload my like 1000 rewards.
And there's literally nothing wrong with that fricking audios.
Well, I just made a brand new or school roadscape. It's been years and I look forward to it. Yay.
I will tell everyone the server when we get on tomorrow. Like I'll put it on screen and I'll
say like, this is the world that we're in. And we'll start outside Lumbridge Castle where the
starting point is. I'm literally going to make an account, put membership on it and then
I get online for stream and we'll take it from there. I don't know what to name myself. So I
need to name myself something mildly humorous, but I haven't decided yet. Maybe Scottlefish.
That'd be nice. Oh, no, someone, someone. Ah, well, if you take my name, it's fine.
I don't know. I'll need to think of something. Do you have a place where you'll upload?
Monies for Vegemite. No, I don't have to try Vegemite.
I'll get Vegemite then for the hand cam stream. Thank you reluctantly saying I'll get Vegemite
in freaking toast. I don't even buy bread. I don't even get buy bread. Scottlefish is a good one.
Thanks. I stole it from a leafling. Thank you for giving me that. Wait,
do we need a membership on old school runescape too? Not necessarily for what we're going to do,
but I think if we, I don't know yet. Like I don't know. We're going to do some quests,
but I'm pretty sure like everything's behind a freaking lock and it's so expensive for old school
runescape membership. I don't know if maybe there's a rich reefling that's willing to buy
bonds and gift it to reeflings, but that's not like my place to ask for. It's a bit. I don't
know if we have any try hard reeflings on old school runescape. Like I think I have about 12,000
coins in those runescape, so I can't buy anyone a bond. Sorry. And I'm starting on a fresh account.
I don't know. Maybe we can like pull our money together to buy bonds to like share to reeflings.
Will there be, you're looking on Patreon. Yeah, yeah, yeah. You're looking on Patreon.
It's not a problem for me. Do what we want on Patreon. Do you have a place where you upload
words that you asked that and I read that out and then I didn't even reply to you? No, well,
the girls have been using Twitter and like putting a go, like a download link out.
Um, I don't think any of my content is going to get taken down because
I know the rules. I know how to scare them.
Um, so I don't think we're going to any any Oilers in chat, literally any old school runescape
Oilers. We summon you. I'd like to call upon you. My membership is still six dollars because
I've had an active substance. Wait, you lock in the same subscription price because you did it
all the way back then, but then you do that you're looking anyway. I can look this way.
She knows the cheese. Strone is never touch runescape. Unfortunately, it's like a really,
it's not a hard game. It's literally point and click. If you wanted to try it for the first
time, you can always start up with us. But if it's not for you, you don't have to play along.
It's okay. Please don't worry. I know you've been going for nine hours. That's crazy. Look,
I'm just going to yapping. Okay. I mean, I could check out Marshmallow and we can make it to 10
hours if you want. Like I could put my little Marshmallow link in the chat.
Ah, hee hee hee hee. Hee hee hee hee hee. Oh, my Marshmallow's in the description. Hold on.
I even have, I can't even see my screen right now. My stream, not my screen. I can see my screen
because it's right in front of me. Um, but hold on. How did I do this? How did I put it in chat?
I am about to sneeze. Boom. Oh no. Oh no, it'd be such a shame if you guys asked me questions to
round this up to a 10 hour stream. Stop. Stop it. We're right on the verge of 10 hours.
Oh, we'll count down to 10 hours, shall we? Only four minutes left.
Oh, I have a lot of Marshmallows. Whoopsies. Someone says, I'd love to spread your cheeks
in liquefaction. Oh, I wasn't supposed to read that part out loud. Hey, I'm glad you do.
God, your salty gamer rage makes me want to have hard, sweaty, angry stuff.
I can't read that one either. Um,
Hi, Stormy. Hopefully you're well. This is my first time using Marshmallow. Glad I could
pop your Marshmallow, Cherry. I don't know if you read any of these. Oh, I read all my Marshmallows.
I have a few questions. You stream so much that I'm wondering if you'll be taking a break from ASMR.
No, I'm streaming ASMR in two days. No break from ASMR. I've got ASMR cards coming out as well.
I just need to write the scripts and send them off. Let's go again.
Yeah, I've got time for ASMR all the time because, yeah, I also got loads of managers in place.
So the only thing I need to do really is be the messenger owl that sends clips to editors now
and uploads stuff on behalf of the girls. Like, Mercy just wakes up and she's like,
got new shorts on her channel. She has no idea. That's me doing it. Actually, Emmy has another,
is that short? Yeah, Emmy has a short and she's just going to wake up and it's going to be on her
channel. Already tagged up and everything for her. Yeah. Unless I didn't read that right.
Yeah, I know how my ASMR is going to be. I can also upload full videos to Twitter as well if
anything ever did become an issue. Like, if I did a little ASMR video. So it's not a problem.
The level organization is astounding. I saw the girls aren't stressed. If the girls had to stream
and they had to run around and worry about trying to get clips out and shorts out,
not good combo. Not nice. Not nice. Oh, no, wait, what? Hi, Stroni. Feel a bit embarrassed.
Oh, no, it's okay. Someone says they feel embarrassed because they messed up in chat at some point.
Don't be silly. You're allowed to mess up in chat all you want. I can't even write in English.
Like, don't worry. Like, Emmy had a script where she had to say a putty cat and I accidentally typed
P-I-S-S-Y. Like, don't be afraid of making embarrassing mistakes. They're not embarrassing at all.
Actually, you only feel embarrassment if you let yourself feel embarrassment or something like
that. It's something about psychology. Like, if you make mistakes. Yeah.
Viewer girls trying to find a non-lid marshmallow and read on stream impossible. It's honestly
not that bad. I don't get that many. I honestly don't get that many. Like, the girls show me what
they get and I don't seem to get, but I haven't been using the other Twitter. I think once I
start using it properly, then. Yeah. Question for you. The other day we talked with Castle
Green Brotherhood about how you're the mother of the girls and the reeflings are the father.
Does that make Emmy or a daughter or sister or a daughter or sister?
If you're a reefling, then technically daughter or sister, but if you're not a reefling, then it's
just a little sister. New audio idea. Anger Scots woman mounts and rides you after being
all day as a fellow Scots nun. We're hotter than here and so on.
So I listened to the Assassin's Creed stream and I was happy that you remembered me. I'm
like, yeah, you're like the main clipper. I actually didn't ask that question. I think there
was someone else who made a few clips as well. I thought I'd be making clips and posting them,
but I wasn't too sure if I could use that. Oh, no, you can go. Brother, that's your channel. You own it.
You make custom content. You have made new creative content. Then guess what? Copyright is
in your favor. Don't worry about copyright, okay? You don't have to worry about copyright
or are you joking me? Clip the girls away. Have fun. Have that ye.
I'm friends with a guy who's already itching to draw the fan art. Fan art of who? What door?
What door is getting fan art? Please tell me. I want to know. I love seeing them get fan art.
I like with the Olympians better, better not think about the family.
What type of hypnotism is your favorite?
That's too hard to answer, honestly. I like hypnoloss. I really like hypnoloss,
where I'm supposed to hypnotize you, but they're backfires and I do as you say.
Ah, so good. Any chance of a spiral let's play? I've never played spiral like that before.
I would like to try it. I'm pretty sure they remastered them and they're like nice,
calm, friendly, casual. It seems like something that's like cameo-esque,
where it's like nice and simple to get through, so I think yeah.
Hmm. I would say yes overall.
It's the one where you go into like a difference or am I- am I messing up for subspace? I may
mess you up for subspace. Hold on. Hey, story. I'm probably being a dumb dumb and I haven't
found them yet, but I was wondering if you could get reference sheets for all the girls chat
mascots. Yes.
Amy's chat mascot is in her debut stream. You are the light in my dark. You are the beating
in my heart. I showed you yesterday. I should get a reference sheet from them all put together.
Maybe I'll get a tweet from the bee alone. Hmm. I can't because Amy's is in a different art style.
Hmm. I know what you're asking for. I don't know the best way to do it. Maybe the discord can post
them. Maybe the discord should have a reference sheet for all the girls and their mascots.
That might be the solution that we can come to. Would you like to come together on a solution?
Or would you like to come together? Hmm.
I'm a little late but congrats on the debuts. Can't wait to see you and the rest of the girls
having store. And it was nice hearing her Scottish momay again. Glad you're back.
Sincerely a H little Rajesh boy. Oh yeah. It's good to be back terrorizing you.
I cannot wait. I cannot wait for the A's in my stream.
Thanks for being so funny, amazing and cute. You make my day better in all its aspects. I wish
for you and the girls eternal success. Thank you for such kind words. That's so nice. I'm glad
you somehow found me funny. Because yeah, literally, yeah, it's not good. It's hard to make jokes. Okay,
my first one. Oh yeah, there's an official discord that has notification only. None of the girls
are in it. So remember what I said in debut 2.0. You don't groom us. We groom you. So none of us
are in it. But if you want notifications for when we go live and all that.
What does it say? I need to push you against the wall holding both your hands above your head.
Uh, am I supposed to say this out loud? I don't know if I'm supposed to say this out loud. I don't
think I'm supposed to say that out loud at all. By the way, along with the zinc supplements,
I've started eating celery for you. Oh, celery is mingin, though. Thanks for your sacrifice.
They taste between boring and bitter and I don't like them, but I'll persevere for you.
Are you sure you eat? Even I draw the line at celery. Sorry. It's so tasteless. I don't understand
how it was even. And that celery has been genetically selected to produce like that.
The only way celery is redeemable is in a soup because it's got stock and completely covers
the taste of celery. Your dedication is appreciated. Celery sucks. Celery is a peanut butter delivery
device. Oh, like a spoon. Celials worse though. I'm going to zail them up,
form down. Hold on, I'm just grabbing some water. I need to hydrate.
I have been hydrated. Oh no, it's 2pm already. Oh, it's my bedtime soon.
Oh no. Wait, no. Actually, it's good that it's my bedtime soon because that means I get to be on
old school Rinscape with you even. Wait, actually, I just realized we're doing a first freaking
stream snipe game tomorrow. Oh my God. Why did that not register? We've literally been talking
about old school Rinscape. We get to play our first freaking stream snipe and I get to see you all.
Ah, oh my God. Okay, I'm an idiot. I'm an idiot. I'm an idiot. Oh my God, it's tomorrow. I want to
go to sleep right now. I'm not going to be able to sleep. It's like Christmas. It's like Christmas.
I'm going to be so excited. Are we all going to like have code names? I don't know. Should we have
theme names? Are we all just going to name our names like how we are? Five. I'm just going to see
this right now. Someone says hopefully you will play five hours. Five hours? No, we're doing 12
hours. Okay, 12 hours or go home. So I'm going to give everyone as much of a chance as possible to
show up in old school Rinscape. I will put the world we are on in the top corner or something
so you can see it any minute. What is Rinscape? Rinscape is an old web game. Is that a web game?
I don't know if it's a web game now. But yeah, if you have trouble falling asleep,
just look in a mirror and hypnotize yourself. True. I'm aware that's below your average.
The most Rinscape players average on the game. Oh, do they had enough after five hours? Me just
like, right, let's do a fashion show. Everyone go to the Grand Exchange and get some pretty cold
dawn. I'm going to rate who has the best. Oh wait, there's houses and can I bring you to my house
in Rinscape? Right, I don't know how membership works, but I'm pretty sure you can get house
in Rinscape because I remember watching someone play hide and seek in Rinscape and he was like
chasing around like the people in stream. We can play hide and seek in tag in Rinscape.
Oh my god. Yeah. And it has this one's go. Oh my god. Oh my god, could we play hide and seek?
I want to be the seeker and I get to touch you all. And if you're touched, you have to like go in
the corner until the winner is crowned. We really are getting crowned. I've never played Rinscape,
but whatever hint you're describing, it sounds very close to Oji Cup Penguin.
Oh my god, I want to play tag. And I'll be like, right, run away from, oh no, who's that? Oh no,
but we won't be able to know who's that. So we can go to the hide and seek. Okay.
Shawnee, if you phrase it like that, everyone will like touch them.
No, no, you're not wanting to get caught. What if we use our Rinscape beds next to each other?
I sadly can't start a new game. I already have three games that take full time and one of them
I play. Well, World of Warcraft. Someone was like, well, I say something. They were like,
I'm no longer doing wow raids to watch your streams. I'm like, no, your girls are going to be so
annoyed at you. Like I've had the chance to play World of War. What was the expansion called?
It was like the second last expansion of wow. And I had a chance to play it. And apparently,
people role play in this place called Goldheim. And I'm like, should we play wow and just like
be like really weird role players that I like. Shadowlands. I think it's Shadowlands is why
played. No, not the battle. Not the battle about the dwarf. Oh, okay, brain needs to catch up. Hold
on, hold on, brain needs to catch up. Not the battle of Azeroth. Goldchart and something like that.
Yeah, the gold chart and we should all go role play there. I would like make like make people
really uncomfortable and we're all just like role playing. Wow, ascension is a thing. I don't know
what that is. The elf and her dwarves. Oh, wait, what would we be? Can I be a cute night elf and
then you guys could all be wargans for some unwritten reason? Pop Tropica is still a thing too.
Pop Tropica.
Guild Wars 2 role plays were at, I don't know, Wink Wank? Really Wink Wank? Oh, wait, wait, wait,
do that again. Wink Wank? Really Wink Wank? Did that, did that work? Oh, no, it doesn't work.
Wait, for some reason the sound works on my freaking game. Hold on, we're like Wink Wank.
Here we go. Wait, that played twice. I don't know why it doesn't do it on the screen. That's
strange. It's the same instance. Oh well. Sorry, that took me so long to do. We should be orcs and
you should be an elf for no reason at all. Oh gee, I sure wouldn't love to be overpowered.
I take a drink of hydration of water. To hydrate.
Hi, good morrow, dear silly cuttlefish. I'm very sleepy, so I'mma be brief.
I absolutely adore watching yours. That's okay, shame! And today,
and it's been so unreal to watch you be all silly again, I absolutely adore you and I hope all of
you are girls and I absolutely adore you and your hopes for the veal or girls and everything and I
hope you all make it happen for your happiness as mine and I'm always kicking my feet, blushing,
tapping and stuff. Thank you for making, thank you for such kind words. Got you twirling your hair
and stuff, huh? Got you twirling your hair and stream. Are you and the girls ever going to play
Minecraft together? Yes, July is when the group Minecraft server goes up. Amy, definitely the
most Minecraft-y out of us all. I don't know how the scale goes, but I'mma confidently say I'm
probably the lowest on the scale of like Minecraft knowledge. All I know is that apparently the mob
votes are the vote, people voted for the freaking stealth phantom things. If you don't sleep for
more than two days they attack you through walls and stuff and I know that was the mob vote and
apparently the mod vote is also rigged because it doesn't make sense. I don't know, but I don't
know if it's rigged. I think it's because people don't understand like kids will vote and kids don't
vote for things that are like good. They vote for what kids want and maybe that's why the votes are
always so skewed. Yeah, mob vote's terrible. I tried and voted for the crab. Wasn't there not
like an alternative? I can't remember. I assume Mercy and her motion sickness might be a bit
of a struggle. Yes, Mercy... I would love... it's hard. I don't know if Minecraft would set it off,
although she can change the camera so it might not affect her motion sickness.
I'll need to ask a bit more about it because I don't have it. I don't know what kind of like
sets it off all the time. Kids running around... I can't believe it. Kids ruling the way that kids
game isn't used. Terrible. I hydrate again. Oh my voice is feeling it Mr. Krabs.
I'm pretty sure you can move out your camera angle. Can you not on Minecraft or am I just
making that up? Does it look cool? Never stuck with him forever. Yeah, I will agree. The design
of it looked cool but its actual thing in game is rubbish. Like rubbish. What does that mean?
What are you asking me? Forgot to send this. Thank you mommy for all your girls. So cute.
I wanted to mention that. So many people are like thanking me for like
the girls being the girls. I'm like no, you thank the girls. I didn't do anything.
If you're thanking me for picking them. Again, that's the girls that did that. It was through
either their introduction or their own content. It's the girls. It's the girls you should be
thanking. Not me, you goofy gobers. It's the girls. So thank the girls. The reason people
say that the vote is rigged is because Compton created tell people to vote for a certain more.
Therefore, I picked the vote. Compton. Compton. Who's Compton? Sounds like a town in London
somewhere. Or a bottle. Sorry, a bottle in London. You picked an amazing bunch though. They're all
awesome. I'm glad you agree. There'd be nothing short of perfect. As in they are perfect. That's
how you say they're perfect, right? They're nothing. They have been nothing but perfect.
Yeah. That's how you say it. Yeah. Okay. Man of heat and ghosts.
Wait. Oh, no. Right. You guys are welcome to laugh. I think this is terminology I'm not familiar with.
If I see a pest trooper, what's a hollow live home? What's a needy male? What?
What's that? Am I being dumb? I don't know what that is.
They're asking, do I have, am I able to shadow ban them?
Maybe this, no. Maybe this, no. I don't quite understand it. Sorry.
Why is someone sending me a detailed, no. Is this far and on? Is this toilet bowl far and on?
Oh, ye gods, how I wish for that most delightful of noise to curl into mine deprived ears. With
such intensity, I yearn to experience the sound of Strawny's splutter gutter as it
flaps a flutter, the noise like a walrus burping up butter, the harps and splurts like a chorus of
angels unleashing their art, the pungent bass bass that can only be played alongside golden harps to
shepherd the dead whom has come and died when hearing Strawny's fart. That is so toilet. There's
no way you're not toilet bowl and on. Just for very quick lore, someone ages ago sent me a thing
and was like, I really want to hear you fart on the toilet and I'm like, what? You want it to be
amplified by echoing off the rim of the toilet and from then he was crowned freaking toilet as bowl
annulment. I don't want to miss what cursed filth hath the eye brought upon, hath the eye
brought upon these lands. Hi, my love, I want to, hmm, in me right in front of you while you
hold her hand. Careful what you wish for, you might be getting it. You might be getting it
all the girls actually, possibly. There's, hmm, yes, I need to, I need to see you.
He wants to hear the reverb full acoustics, literally. Well, they wanted to hear that
chock. You're only allowed to hold hands with the harps, even better. I have a plan for my
Dora Thon, but it requires a team effort and it's quite a lot to ask the girls like, oh, Dora
Thons are like, you need to help each other out, type them, but I'm going to try my best to make it
as easy as possible. But I would like to release a certain audio and basically, in it, I give you
a pill that negates any need for a pause champ, if you will. And then I take you door by door.
It's so messed up saying how loud. But yeah, and I tell you like all the good things and encouragement.
I need to, I need to let it cook. Okay. I need to let it cook. And I need a Dora Thon in the
first place to even start cooking it up. But we ain't there yet. We ain't doing that. We aren't
even on that part. Well, that's a very silly pill. Lord, grant me strength. Would you please give us
a heads up for when it comes out so we can save? Oh my God, mon. Please do that. She kicked a whole
six course dinner. I'm a gourmet chef. Well, if I get 99 cooking on RuneScape, then yes, I am a chef.
Confirmed. Any plans for haptic support? I keep getting asked, but I don't know what it is. I don't
know what I need to do to the audience to make that happen. I don't know if it's like I run it
through a data thing or what? I don't know. I don't know. I'm too dumb. Hold on, I'm gonna
fix my calibration and I'm wiggling a bit too much. Okay, calibration, calibrate it.
Are we cooking in RuneScape something? Yes. I don't know how to make money in RuneScape,
but we're going to be buying lobster so we can level up. If not, we'll use Barbarian Village and
we'll pick up all the salmon, all the bought strobe and cook. Shawnee, do you reply to
marshmallows privately? No, I don't. I reply on stream or I put together a mosaic. A mosaic?
Is that the correct word? Where I put all the pictures together and post it. But I've only
done that once. I should maybe do it again sometime. And then I can talk about all the naughty things.
Why?
Here's a funny story about three medieval kingdoms. I'm scared to click on this piece.
Hey, Staroni, I love your work. Any chance to do a belly button camsuit? No, you don't
like to see my belly button. Why would you want to see my belly button? I don't like my belly button.
Belly button? Belly button? Is that your choice? Is that your choice of finishing location?
Hmm, your choice? Interesting.
Good night, Staroni. Just thought you'd want to know I'm going to jet.
I can't read the end of that. Enjoy your nighttime routine. Sleep well.
Oh my. Oh my.
Hi, Staroni. I want to hold your body again.
Oh. I can't read any of these. There's a free game called Fantasy Star Online 2.
I haven't played it in years, but every weekend there's a Hatsune Miku concert.
That's so specific. Why is there a Hatsune Miku concert in the middle of Fantasy Star Online 2?
I'm thinking Miku, Miku, Ui, Ui.
Blue air, blue eyes, hiding in your wi-fi.
Staroni, I just want to let you know for old school runescape, being on a member's world is
almost a requirement for any skill training. You can quest together with people and free to play,
but the gameplay is limited. Oh, but it's so expensive.
Stop reading them out loud. Ah, I like reading them. It's only me, or is it me, seeing a lot more
things than she would.
Eh? Are they both on? No, they're not online right now. You mean in the ASMRs?
People are bored. Bold on Marshmallow. Yeah, that's the best part.
They tell me everything they want, and I give them everything they want.
That's a good exchange.
Can you please say...
What are you gonna use it for if I say it?
And you didn't tell me what tone to say it in either.
You didn't tell me what tone to say the sentence in either.
I need to think. How would you want me to say it?
Mmm, I lost the game. This? Is that the tone you wanted this?
If you want me to say something, you need to give me tone. You need to give me the emotion.
Wait, strong enough. Wait, what?
What?
Wait, is that that goofy game where if someone says you lost the game, you've lost us?
Wait, is that what it? Rip game players. Wait, what does it mean? It's a silly game,
right, where people say I lost the game and then you lose it until you win it on your streak?
If you think about the game you lost, okay.
The only objective of the game is to not think about the game.
Oh, okay. Oh, I'm sorry. Oh, I just made you all lose. I'm sorry. I wasn't thinking that far ahead.
I'm sorry. I didn't think that far ahead.
Can I suggest something secret totally say so confession maros to read on stream?
Yeah, you can like, you can literally type in the maros right now.
Can I send it like this? Did that work? It did. Yeah, you can just put it in there.
And if you want me to say something, just put that emotion and then like,
like quotation marks. I'll also take requests here in the ASMR stream as well.
So if you ever wanted me to hear it, kind of whispered a bit on a different microphone,
because this is an SMB7 I'm using. At least we lost this drawing. I heard about this like
25 years ago in elementary. My discipline. I'm sorry. Okay, I distract you. I will say other things.
Did you see the refling zip up hoodie design? Maro, I send other deer. What do we bear?
Oh, if you've got those, if you've got those kind of pictures, please send on Twitter.
But I will say my Twitter tags are freaking working. I'm trying to find this freaking artwork
on Smuttle and it doesn't show up. I don't know why it doesn't show up.
What's your favorite type of hypnotic induction to use?
I think, I like repeated pattern. Come to the ASMR stream and I'll show you what I like. Okay,
deal. Huh? Are you going to show up? And I'll show you what I like. She will like.
And people are going to judge me, but I like it. So I'll do what I like.
Sometimes the Strony is a good girl. Hell yeah, a good girl.
You, oh, I'm good at advertising. Okay, I'm in. I'm in. Hey Strony, here's the song.
Safe for work, Mario. Do you have a throne? I do, but I've unlinked it because
I have everything I need now that I've got my reef links. I don't need a single thing else.
And that's the 12th. I don't need anything. So I've unlinked my throne.
I'm going to say how many triples have you received so far? Um, not a lot.
The girls are getting a lot more than me. I think the reef links are a little shy,
a little shy, a little scared. Will you and the girls be able to
yourself and members streams? Most likely, yes. Strony, does it make you happy when people send
you the spicy messages? Please let me. Please tell me all the scenarios you want to do to me.
Are there any games where there's an alt path you haven't tried?
I can't think of any off the top of my head. I normally probably like
game starts, game ends. I never pick the bad team if there's a bad side. Stinky.
Unless you count the companions in Skyrim.
Does anyone here like the companions in Skyrim?
Oh wait, I'm on the fricking wrong thing. Sorry, hold on. Let me try that again.
Yeah, exactly. That's what I thought. That's what I thought. No one likes them.
Companion. Stinky. Yeah, exactly.
You think they're fine? I don't, I never, although the first time you play it, it's like,
wow, really good, but the fricking on Xbox, the girl always glitches out and disappears in the
middle of the map and she never comes back. Hi, just a time waster for cute fish.
Someone says, someone says, wife? Husband?
Have you heard a joke about afar? It stinks. You know what? You're done. Wait, why?
Oh, there's no background. No, no, no background. What's going on here? Why the heck do you know work?
Oh, right, I think that's all the marshmallows that I can, I refresh and it's just gone up my quiver.
Oh my god, I love you and the girls so much. I created a Twitter account just to follow the
six of you. I hate that I had to turn into it. I know. Thank you for going through it. It's such a
pain. My account keeps getting fricking locked and it keeps making me prove that I'm not bought over
and over and over and over and over and over and over again. Look, I just want to look at
small fish. I want to, and then I want to go to sleep, you know what I'm saying? Hi, Johnny.
Oh, sorry, I don't know why I gave you that voice. I'm so sorry. I apologize. Hi,
Stronny. I woke up in a Euro time zone and found out the party was still going 10 hours in the
avatar stream. Hell yeah. I really admire your energy and autism as you call it. Thank you.
If you want to play old school RuneScape tomorrow, we are going to be live for 12 hours. Cheeky
endurance stream. What's that? I stream more in one week than the average we should have
done in a month. I'll wear that with pride. So I don't have snot coming out my nose. I'm drinking
water. Your wishes. Hi, Stronny. Thanks for being a butt. So,
okay. You can finish the rest. Stronny, guess what? You just took my marshmallow
of engineering. Get plapped. Get plapped. Get plapped. Looking forward to the old school
RuneScape. I also recommend Final Fantasy if you want more MMOs. Also, would you accept
script ideas, fan-made scripts? Yes, I would. I don't have a problem. There may, at a later
date, not now, not in this month, things need to settle where we can take official script submissions.
However, if we are aware to take subscriptions submissions for audios purposes, sadly, you
have to fully hand over the rights. So we have the right to monetize. We have ownership.
We're happy to give credit. I think, I don't know if there's going to be a problem giving credit.
I haven't thought that far ahead at the moment. But there's a lot of issues and it's quite a shame
and it's really hard to iron out at this point in time. But once the dust settles and things get
better. Wait, get plapped. What are you doing to us? Blap, blap, blap, blap, blap.
Do you still have love for the big boy wiflings out there? I can't help but notice a
lane in your lore video. Yes.
There's just something I've got to say. You're as beautiful as the day I lost you.
Oh, thank you. That's how to train your dragon. That's one of the only books I write as a child.
I think I read like three books as a childhood. And one of them was how to train your dragon.
I don't know how I read a book, honestly, but I did it. She's dunking us in the water.
The books were so good. Literally one of the only books I read as a child. I've read more books
this year than I have in my entire life, which is crazy. I'd pretend that I can do book reviews,
but I'm not even smart enough for that. I'm currently trying to get through the Handmaiden's
Tale. I actually am enjoying the Handmaiden's Tale. I'm like a few chapters in, but I don't
know if people find this cheating, but I have to have the book read to me or I can't read it.
This sounds really bad, but it takes up too much brain power to read the words manually,
so I read along whilst being spoken to by TTS voice. And I can speed it up like super fast.
Oh, thank you for the raid. How did your stream go?
How did your stream go rain? Oh, you might be tired, so don't feel forced to talk.
Don't feel forced to talk if you're a tired little barbie.
I should have said background music. It's really quiet in the stream. I don't know if it's
maybe nice. I hope your stream was good. Endurance streamer, creative director,
and so has time to... I've not read any books since debut. I can tell you that much.
But hi, Raiders. I'm Strony Cuttlews from Via Lure. I'm really inappropriate,
so I do apologize if I'm new. You're a cup of tea, and I'm also Scottish, so I'm super hard to
understand, but thanks for hanging out anyway. Which is... I hope your stream went fantastic.
Please rest up after your stream. I'm sure you're tired, and last thing you want to do is get
bombarded with loads of questions from the person you have kindly rated into. So I thank you kindly,
rain cloud, and I hope you have a fantastic rest after your game. Game? Maybe that too.
Never know. May not be a game. She may not be... Entry all in one breath. She's got lungs.
Strony looking to push 11 hours at this rate. Should we? Should we just yap and then make
it another 12 hours? Why is the raid message wait? Wait, I saw it as wait as well. Like,
I could hardly read, but I had to scroll over. I mean, if I make another cup of tea,
we could in theory make it 12 hours again, and we just like... And we can just talk,
and I can ask you questions, and then you ask me questions, and then I'm going to ramble about
something, and then you distract me. And then we're going to another ramble. Do you want that?
Yes, please? Oh, okay, okay, okay, okay. Her favorite form of introduction is tying you
into the cannonball fall streak. The yabba-nay. You feel yourself getting so sleepy, don't you,
little leaf-ling? Yeah, it's okay. Let's sleep and brace you slowly, okay?
Shhh. And then here for 13 and then 14. I mark my words when and if YouTube ever
fix VODs, 14 hour streams. Not even kidding. I can't get enough of you. I can't. I can't
get enough of you. And when we do Elden Ring, I am incredibly tempted to possibly figure
do a 12 hour and then raid into a six hour afterwards. I don't know. It's plausible. I'll
be a tired bean. I don't know. I wish we could get 14 hours. 14 is the like perfect slot of like,
I can still get a full night's rest. Lord, inject the Scottish lass. Lord, if you can
hear me right now, inject the Scottish lass into my veins. Scott Fish is too powerful.
Thank God it's daytime where I live. I don't have to sleep. Stop. I can't be more addicted
than I am. You're too good, Strawny. I'm coming for you. Trying to kill us. Thank you.
Do rest if you need to rest. Never worry, okay? Strawny, I've got to go to sleep. Can you please
show us those pretty pink swirls? Oh, now that I'm so close to you, I absolutely can. Hold on.
Uh, will I go in? Wow, I'm reacting to myself. Please don't react. There. Okay, that's more like
me. Hold on. Let me put chat behind me just for a moment. Okay, let's see if I can do this properly.
Sorry, I'm so close. Okay, let me move my water out of the way so I can at least attempt to do
something mildly professional for once in my life. Okay? Once in my life, I did something
a little bit. Oh, maybe a little bit.
It's okay to be sleeping. It's been a while since you've rested. Well, really, okay?
Shhh.
Slowly, your phone. Slow, slow, slow.
And your muscles relax. Slow, slow, slow.
And your brain is quiet. Slow, slow, slow.
Good name, but don't be stingy. Until the morning.
Did I do it? Did I do it right? Slow, slow, slow.
Until the slumber you fall, I tell you. I don't know if I was too close because I might hold.
But I need to show her. Seems like you did.
A little sleepy moment. Thank you so much. Good night.
I just woke up. Can I put you to sleep again?
You did great, good girl. You can't catch me off guard. I've already been called good girl.
Good luck getting me in subspace. I'm in dumb space. When I do hypnosis, I feel very dumb.
It's early in the morning. We need a bedtime ASMR. Absolutely. I am more than open to that.
We can absolutely do bedtime ASMR. Am I allowed to go for a tinkle and a cup of tea as my voice is
croaking like a frog? And then we'll just ramble until the 12 hours? Does that sound like a deal?
You made my boss fall asleep.
Super early. Hi, Stronny. Tanner is in... I'm getting a frog.
Thank you very much for the tiff. I'm glad you liked it. Oh no, my Elden Ring. My stream elements
is gone. So I can't freaking shoot you. Stream elements. Stream elements are so finicky sometimes.
Oh, I'm already logged in. Go to my dashboard right now.
Let's try that again. Shall we? My fraud, my fraud phone call. I can't believe that they're not
getting any, not getting it from me. Thank you, Beryl, for the tip. I appreciate it. I'm glad.
For our good dumb, keep it up, mom. Yeah. Right, I'm going to very quickly go make a cup of tea
and do a quick tinkle. You are... I'm actually going to pin my...
Rain cloud. Please rest well, rain. Okay. And sleep well. I'm not gonna force you to talk. Okay,
I'm actually going to pin my... Any questions? Question mark? Did that work? Yeah, it did work.
I'm going to pin it. So you're welcome to think it, but please rest well, rain. You work so hard.
And you did fantastic. Hi, Stronny Tenors, Polk. Happy first week. This was my first rain.
Oh my god, thank you so much. There's so kind of you. Oh my gosh. I'm glad I could take your rate,
Cherry. Am I allowed to say that? I'm sorry. I'm sorry if I'm not allowed to say that, but I'm
glad I could take it anyway. Okay, I've pinned that. I'm going to go make a cup of tea. I will be
roughly three minutes because it takes three minutes for the kettle to boil. It takes three
minutes for the kettle to boil, yeah? So you're welcome to ask me any questions of any variety.
But please sleep well, rain cloud. Thank you for the rate. I really appreciate that.
I need to add you on Discord, actually. I need DM, the whole Umi Plus squad, actually,
and get everyone on Discord. And then once I have access to you on Discord, the possibility.
Right, I'll very quickly mute and I'll go and make a cup of tea, okay? Okay, cup of tea time.
Tea time. Oh wait, I'll do that. I'll close my eyes first. Oh wait, close eyes. I'm not very smart
whenever I do that. Never mind.
That time we brushed our teeth and I was like fully ready to go bed.
Yeah, yeah, remember that time? Yeah, okay. I entered the room with a cup of tea. My tongue's
sticking out. I was like, yeah, what time? Yeah. I mean, do we need a brush or two
twice now? I don't know. You're not really supposed to brush it like too much.
Yeah, I just got caught up. Apparently, shebe's alternative Twitter is over 10K followers,
so what the heck just happened whilst I was streaming? I don't know what I've missed,
but congrats girls, oh my gosh. Right, shall we? Shall we get to the bottom of it?
Oh, she offered feet for 10K.
Shut up. My toes are out right now. Hold on, I'm putting Goop on my toes right now
for the money shot and everything. She has lovely feet. True. Yeah, she left the containment zone.
Oh, okay, she componds, she componds. Right, let me refresh these marshmallows.
Ooh, I got 20 more questions. Thank you for all the questions.
Some reason it shows marshmallows from like a week ago at the top. I don't know what that means.
Does that mean someone's verified is like put it up there on purpose? I don't know how it works.
My stream disconnected. Why does OBS do that? I said OBS disconnected. I'm still here.
Stream. You give me a heart attack every time you freaking do that. Please don't do that.
Oh, I just get notifications that says OBS, you've disconnected. I'm like, please no.
Please no. I'm trying to make it to the 12 hour mark, please, please. We're only one hour away.
Someone said, oh yeah, you can request me to say stuff on my accent by the way. Someone says,
please can you say ravioli in a seductive tone? Ravioli in a seductive, ravioli, ravioli, ravioli.
That little sleep hypnosis thing you did was amazing. I'm convinced you'd be amazing at a
meditation type sleep bottle. Yes, I want to do like bedtime hypnosis stuff as well, like completely
like fine on the table. You haven't even started your hypnosis content yet and you're already
infiltrating my mind by turning my internal monologue scotch. I can't wait for you to turn my brain
into your bin, into your female doll. Oh my. Ever since you've debuted, I've gone from a man lost
in a desert drawing of thirst to one drowning in a flood of nonstop good times. Yes. And all I want
to do is just close my eyes and let the waves take me. Would you drag me into the depths? I want
you to. I'm glad you can have good times here. It was, it was dry for a while but I hope, I hope
it's good times here, good vibes. Yeah. We go swimming together, you know. I playfully dunk
your head under the water a little bit. Just playfully. And no other reason. No other lower
related reason. It was awfully cold in the depths but now we're in warmer waters I think you could
say. Can you run from Prime Minister of Australia? So at least through, if it's bad ideas, it sounds
nice coming from me but I've not even been granted rights into the country yet. There, there is a
timeline where I get rejected and I can't, I have to go back to Scotland and I can't run the business.
Let's hope we're not on that timeline. That would be terrible. Could you imagine if I got kicked out
of, oh my god. Munga, munga. Uh, hi, Strony. I don't know if it's been answered already. It's okay to
ask something you're not sure that's been answered. It's not possible for someone to be here all the
time so please don't ever be afraid to ask a question you think that's already been answered.
It's not possible for you to be here all the time. I know, I know it's terrible but it's not possible.
Sorry if you did but I just want to know if you're interested in the game Lost Planet 2. It's on
Xbox and I think you'd like it. Could easily play the whole thing in one stream. Also, you
played Elden Ring. Would you be open to playing Armor Core 6? Armor Core 6 has been popping up over,
I've heard the name a few times now. Love your streams that I can't wait to bounce those hypnotic
eyes back on you. Stinky. Armor Core 6. I don't know what it is but it keeps coming up.
Lost Planet 2. I should actually write down game ideas because I trust your guys's like
suggestions over anything that I could possibly come up with.
8c6. It's phenomenal. It's great. It's really good. Highly rated game.
Not my. Every strongy tone has it's synced up. No my default. I feel like my default and I'm
like that and I'm all monotone. Like you can't even understand. Lost Planet 2 is an OG Xbox game.
How did I never come across it then? I don't know when it came out. Maybe it was still at
the stage where like so I used to get attached to one game and when Assassin's Creed Brotherhood
came out like I hardly got any new games. I got Skyrim, I got Black Ops, AC Brotherhood and the rate
of like new games like went down astronomically. If it's probes of 2006, 2008 and then Armor Core
6. I'll definitely, these games keep coming up and I trust your guys's judgment.
Hi strongy, I was curious if you would follow guys's chat one day.
Yeah, of course we're doing the jelly bean game. Are you silly? Are you being a silly sausage? Of
course we're playing the jelly bean game again. How else are you gonna touch me and grab me and
hold me back? You guys wouldn't stop grabbing me. You all grabbed me. You stinky stinker things.
Ah my calibration is having a hard time today. Hold on. Let me re-calibrate.
Hopefully my mouth stops wiggling. Okay it's not wiggling anymore. Jelly bean game.
We do what? So in the jelly bean game you can like grab opponents and hold them back
to like stop them from jumping to the objective or whatever and I used to have to beg. I was so
bad at the game. I would basically have to beg till people would hold back to let me through the
first level because I ended up losing it so many times that I wasn't playing the game and I respect
it and you guys play because I was that freaking bad at the game. That is so much fun. So yes you
will absolutely be playing that again. I will always do like a stream snipe game every month.
One that's like public and one I do prioritize free to play games. Unfortunately I've started off
a rune scoop which normally premium is the only way to play it so I've picked a bit pearly.
I do apologize but I would like to get 99 cooking and it would be fun to kind of like
achieve goals along the way. So going strong girls. Strony what type of fan are you like the most?
Any. Like whatever inspires you. Like some people do like a meme funny moment. Like I uploaded a short
and like in the short I was like and yes before you ask and I went back in the like the bagpipes
and like the Scottish flag appear behind me and then someone liked it so much they basically made
a Scottish beam come out of my mouth and like the first panel was me going and then the second
panel was like I was like throwing this Scottish beam out of my mouth and it reminded me there's a
trend on how it's the Mika world and she goes Mika no no this time you've been waiting for see
two one Mika Mika beam and it reminded me of that and it's so good. Like whatever you enjoy
like if you enjoy meme make a meme if you enjoy the other side of things you're more than welcome
to make the other side of things because I like that stuff too. And yeah like anything 10 hours
deep let's go yeah we're gonna make it a 12 hour stream uh so I'm just ranting ranting rambling
for the last uh hour hour last hour. I've got a little cup of tea don't know if you can hear
my nails on it. I'm just waiting for it to cool down before I can sip it. Stroney any chance of
you making a 2D platform video game in the future that's so specific why are you wanting to bounce
on me in 2D? I'm I'm not making a video game no. I have plans to make video game in the future
but that's the future future like now meow. What should a lad do if he makes a fan made album?
What should uh sorry make a fan made album? What should he send us general or art?
What does that mean? Fan made album? Album? Like a music or am I being dumb? I'm in it for the
long haul today I'm here we go I'm oh please don't stay up if it's gonna be bad for your health
I don't want you to do anything bad for health okay see me I can be up for 12 hour stream because
you know Rottos and Mirona
a rap stuff oh my god can you do a diss track on me? Stroney cuttles more like Stroney can't make
her mind up. Uttles on her 15th persona. Muttles got tape on her tape the only reason she's a
VTuber is to give herself boobies because she ain't got any in real life yeah whoo diss tracks
Stroney diss track no the diss tracks yeah that's right you're getting diss tracks again oh I just
punched my knuckle against the desk by accident someone says I kneel you are too powerful so much
kneeling I like it do it again it is humbling to know someone like you exist I've never dumped so
much ink before within a span of a week and from it so happy from watching you and the girls I
hope for your success and it's one of the few I feel that is deserved oh thank you so much thank
you for spilling your ink I do like hearing about ink spilling like why yes maybe I am a V sucky after
oh maybe there is sucky by blood the pause after hearing where I live it smells like freshly baked
cookies because I'm near a cookie factory and I'm and I'm already awake for today we're still going
strong oh that's dangerous for your health it's dangerous to be awake for more than like 16 hours
I think is when it's bad like your brain function your cognitive function goes down like big big
I knew it velar is going to be my oval my version of meet the grams will be meet the indulgers
what did you think about the generation name indulge because if I told you technically if I
told you a secret this is a secret for only who watch this stream right now um gen one's name
indulge plays into gen two and three um and if we do get to three gens oh I'm gonna be so excited
because to reveal the full names because they all play into each other and I'm so excited I wonder
if anyone could guess I don't I think it's impossible to get there's too many variations like
someone says is there a chance for a stream of a software game other than Elden Ring I don't think
I can get any help in the other Elden Rings though however I think she be as interested in Bloodborne
but unfortunately I'm not very good and the reason I like Elden Ring so much is because you
guys can come in and help me but I'm not good on my own um three gens worth the tubers I will become
a husk I'll become a husk honestly maybe we can guess after the second gen
um
oh no you can't guess it because there's two secret words that aren't present
it it forms a sentence basically all three gens perform a sentence that perfectly encapsulates
won't be where it is indulge marionette and you're like nah yeah you're no the secret words
makes it impossible just wanted to drop one more marrow I've watched all the velo girls and well
I like them a lot you're my oh thank you are you sure I'm your oh she though like I'm not gonna say
anything but like Emmys T's and Oof A.C's accent like I'm not killed and she sounds so
fucking adorable and her accent I wish I could copy it but I can't why is she irish I see why are
you irish I don't know I just love the way she sounds but I feel like I'm doing a terrible
that's terrible you have your own accent power power
sure well the sentence will look good but what gen no I am not I am absolutely not doing any further
so there some people were like are you doing a spin-off gen are you doing like a safer work
variation no I've absolutely no interest I am exhausted I took so much HP damage getting gen
one out I am very thankful to say that if gen two and three do happen the HP damage is reduced
significantly because I learned so much I learned so much and when you do the first time you do it
it's so hard but anytime after it just gets easier but I am I have no interest I feel like absolutely
no shade or anything to any other VTuber agency if you start throwing gen after gen it is very
clear you do not give an absolute rats arse about the content for your girls and it's just it's
such a shame that those girls put faith in you as an agency and your response is throw another gen
out throw another no absolutely no no very disappointing I don't like that that's just me
uh you like instantly became my or she I don't have an endurance for long streamers but I really
enjoy stopping in on stream throughout the day I'm glad I'm glad I can catch you I'll see you
tomorrow in old school runscape huh huh you might you might not be in the game but I'll be online
I'll be online okay 55 HP honestly you keep talking with her damage yeah I keep taking damage
with her with her damage human wave tactic based running strongy are there any ASMR stories based
on real life um I have rambling ASMR coming out where I'm just kind of talking about stuff that's
happening now that's me if you mean the small pp audio then uh there's an anon that's very passionate
about it and he sent me a prompt and well he didn't he didn't actually even mean to make it
into a script or anything he just sent me a prompt of what he liked and I was like you know what
you know what I'll make it into something as so your guys are more than welcome to use marshmallows
to put down your things because it unironically can inspire me to make like an entire script
um I am happy to take inspiration I'll yonk it I like reading your deep dark fantasy
I want to hit them with a diss track I know but also I don't want to go into them and be like
public anime number one in veilerland I talk a lot of hmm but I'm such a little teddy bear
nah it's all funny I have to admit something I fall asleep to your voice during streams
only for a little bit like 30 minutes to an hour the volume doesn't matter your voice just knocks
me out I get so cozy from the yapping that I wake you up through the rage part against
against the RDA guy in section I'm sorry if I woke you up with my screen
hey stroney I'm glad to catch some of your lives I've been recovering from
the unmentionable one and I'm finally feeling better I hope to see many more streams from you and the girls
someone's signed this with their name sorry I think this might be um
uh I'm hope you're okay and I'm glad you feel better you're starting to feel more like yourself
sorry you've signed it and I don't know if I should see your name out so for respect I'm not
gonna I'm not gonna think it but you guys are welcome to sign maros but I won't see your name
if you sign a maro at the bomb okay I'm glad you picked Samwise the brave I am so glad
you my refling gave me the courage seriously why the refling I don't know maybe it's because he gives
me courage hi stroney saying this is the Scott so when I say this you know it's not just because
of the accent I love your voice listen to you up on stream is my favorite part of your stream and
when you talk gently it gives me tingles I'm really looking forward to the ASMR wait I can give you
tingles just when I be a bit more gentler in the morning that's interesting normally I like I only
happen in the the thing the thingy goodbye those who are sleeping I gotta go finish up work have
good day yeah have a good day thanks for hanging uh like yeah definitely a not safe
what are you saying read out your own risk but are you gonna do a hmm audio involving oh
let's call it joystick and we'll take the first three letters are you gonna do hip no joystick
uh yes it's one of the main things I'm interested in I want to take full control
the question is can I put you under though I'm I'm a bit unskilled at the under part it's scary to
put you under because I'm not sure how good I am at it and as well I don't know if the accent is
actually a debuff on putting you under a spell or the control type section of it so I'm a bit worried
we'll see what happens as I said I'm learning and you guys have been fantastic and it will be
like you guys are always fantastic and give me like a lot of space it'll take time to get
to get there I'm good at pretending I believe in you I love that you're
I'm going to try and I woke up and so you're still streaming now come home and you're still
at it you're on another level yeah we we finished up a cup maybe an hour ago
I kind of leaked kind of who goes there identify yourself um about now oh my cold my tea's getting
cold I'm sorry I'm gonna drink my tea I completely forgot I had a tea sorry
I'm getting cold sorry
someone says do not open on stream that makes me want to open it even more just for the hell of it
will you ever do a stream with incur the viewers are encouraged to make it to the end
I would never do something like that bye no no no not right now not right now
no right now
I couldn't be so dastard break it off oh that's so bad for no no I'm joking actually I'm joking
I'm joking relax relax no no no no I take I take more drink some of tea because I don't want it to
get too cold what did did you see what me did 0.5 that little brat oh it's punishment
0.5 is genius
yeah
I think I caught up on all the questions already I hopefully I don't miss too many oh well we just
got another 15 so it's okay we're not going anywhere
um
I've almost finished almost finished
someone made a meme based on stream today monkey is I'm fast when you make a meme or is it just
me screaming be honest hold on let me see if I can open it up
okay hold on let me see if I can put this on screen right now hold on let me kick let me kick
add image someone made this um uh
okay
and if I go on desktop and then I can put it on stream
so this is the meme this is the meme the victory strongy fighting for the navi freedom strongy
fighting for the rda angry Scottish noises
hmm good night to those who sleep which one of the girls do you think has
um
uh sheebie I want to say sheebie
um but yeah sheebie sorry sheebie
uh yeah sheebie I'm only with that but thank you for the meme I love it I was very angry
I am scared to listen back to stream
I remember you did small pp time um but have you thought of ntr I am so sorry
that I can't fulfill this fantasy unfortunately it actually alienates people um I am interested
in the opposite though where I I help you to my daughters
I apologize but unfortunately it is a like a no no and it's it's basically career death
and I'm so sorry I really do apologize because I do like the idea of like everyone gets to hear
their thing like my attempt at their thing but unfortunately I would never do anything that
would risk the girls and stuff and I do apologize um yeah our cami for real you made this happen
through your determinant through my freaking brain deadness free but okay I'll read it because
you're actually being very kind to me and I'm just being harsh to myself I wear cami for real you
made this happen through your determination innovation love kindness and meaningless take this
w you have deserved it and of course will still support the doors they are so wonderful they
are I need to burp who goes there I don't know who keeps coming into my room and burping but
I keep asking them who goes there and no one responds it's really weird like I ask them to
identify themselves I ask them I say by the pope you have to respond to me but just someone keeps
coming in burping and then leaving it's bizarre it's totally not me not a question just an old
radish happy to be back and swimming in the reef oh do you like the reef should I get you
little armbands oh no you're well you're a squid so you don't know any armbands do you
we're both aquatic just wanted to say that I'm proud to call you my cami oh I'll stop you can't
call me you call me oh she yes you dork you are my cami oh she and I'm wishing you and the girl's
success and men may your achievements be many and tributes plentiful now can I make a request for
a wake-up alarm could you see your best Scottish battle cry
oh can I do it now I don't know if my voice is too fried to do it now hold on I'll meet
now see if we can do it right the sentence is rise warrior jar wake up and make it everyone's
problem you can do it oh I think my voice is too fried but we'll try it anyway we'll try it anywhere
rise warrior jar make make up okay sorry sorry hold on hold on I got stage fright I got stage
right I'm sorry rise warrior jar wake up and make it everyone's problem you can do it yes
yeah sorry I messed it up I apologize
how does it feel to know that you have me addicted to women of Scottish accents it's over for you
it's over for you you crave the rolling ours you crave the in luck and most of all you crave the
smell of iron brew on the breath of the woman you've just kissed
you're you've been scot-pilled and there's no turning back
the peak I'll say oh should she still go ahead yeah we've got another t-minus 40 minutes uh is
mercy going to be online in 40 minutes I never thought about that
already had a taste for the Scottish accent it's uh bettish I'm sure no one
but found out when I have my scot-pilled oh yeah yeah she's still online okay um before I go offline
please remind me to make sure that mercy's like still actually going to be online if not I'm probably
going to redirect you into one of her songs I'll make you listen to ac's furry cover thing
xt nestle pouses on your ooh you so warm I love emmy's emmy aces
frankly the right the reason why I get ac and emmy mixed up all the time is it because they both
begin with I is because I used to call them the twins in development they were called the twins
in development I know they're not twins they I just called them twins it just happened okay
so emmy and ac always get referred to each other by accident now there's few problems with my
if you had a chance to change your oh I changed forget changing fate I put it into my own hands
and I am strong it calls the cullfish of the war
sending them out to say that you and emmy's are my favorites it means incredibly talented
and entertaining and she's an absolute sucky mom but there's something about you that makes you
so easy to listen to it's probably because you can tell how low IQ I am so I make you feel safe
see mersey's a dork so you lure your guard around her but me because I'm brain dead yeah
you can't help it you can't help it thank you for the kind words kind kind of mark
warning for stream let's see how far I can read into this before we can
as you stare into your reeflings eyes to hypnotize them you get a little too close to one and catch
your reflection in the eye you suddenly feel tired and a desire to bend to their oh good girl
cuddles you want to give everything to your little reeflings stop oh my god you're no I can't read that
I need to finish reading that though
no I can't read that no I can't read that it's gonna change my brain thinking right now I can't
read that oh my god excuse me mom I am sure you're my oh yes thank you
take it that's it ever said that Mario has made the seal of
bruv I'm not being funny I felt it flour
my favorite pokemon oh you can't make me pick oh there's so many I like creepy pokemon I like
when they look cute and creepy who wrote that no no no subspace stop it we're not going into
subspace another another time but not not no subspace no subspace all right I bite it
because if no the problem is if I go into subspace I can't talk I literally can't talk
how am I supposed to entertain if I can't talk if I'm just here squealing like a little
picky subspace emissary reference subspace emissary reference no subspace is a thinking type
and it makes it really hard for me to freaking talk through it it's really freaking hard
no I can't talk and I need to be able to talk you can't just stare at my face while I go
I'm so happy that I saw you on my Twitter feed oh is that how you found me on Twitter oh maybe
I should actually start using Twitter then oh but I don't like using Twitter all the girls have
been so fantastic like I'm streaming in one hour I'm doing this I'm doing that I literally
have put nothing on Twitter I can't like I've used Twitter to make ASMR
collabs that's it I can't do it okay please please look at the Twitter please it's so
can't could stare at your face for an age less you underestimate what you do a karaoke stream
with the girls I think latency is too much for me with the girls however the girls might be able
to do it with one another because latency wouldn't be an issue um I have to put your stream schedule
on my desk to make sure I remember I'm so bad I apologize if people use Twitter for notifications
I adjust I don't like it I don't like it I actually don't like it I'm sorry well I'm off to work
good night and don't forget to wash you to brush my teeth yes I won't forget uh if it's been 30
minutes since I last drank yes it will be okay we'll brush your teeth right before you end
Twitter recently uh officially allowed the content and it's signal boosting the words
mentioning oh is it I'm gonna make a certain video then I've been needing to make a video
as a thank you for ages and I'm stalling I'm scared because maybe I should do it no no
maybe yeah shimmy shimmy yeah shimmy yeah shimmy y'all
I wonder what I could be doing
and I really strongly made me have a good sleep schedule because I wake up early to watch
I'm glad ah yes the bits get upside down when they go to Australia so it takes places long for
computer uh it's a bit squid me right now by the pope wow you really are still online
good morning good morning thank you for Jenga yes um we finished the game around the nine hour mark
and then ended up rambling so much we got to the 10 hour mark and then I made a cup of tea and it
just made sense that we're just gonna ramble until the 12 hour mark just because we can yeah
yeah no no we're just having a good time we just done our thing but good morning
I hope you're all ready for it happening again tomorrow because I'll be online all day
I think I got everything
but yeah I couldn't I couldn't pick a pokemon I like creepy wee pokemon
also no creepy all right I've refreshed again and there's quite a few more questions so hopefully I
can get to this stream warning this is meant to miss am I supposed to read it then or not
yeah well it didn't work get ready it didn't work
hmm he said kneel and submit who bad you're not getting me today I've done see when I do a little bit
of the a little bit of the gnosis when I do the gnosis I get very you know so good luck
another another day maybe
good girls are entertaining with even stop right right whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa
scrolling past that stop it even the rest of the viewer are the first I ran into to lean
into the other side of content I wasn't sure how to take it at first because it's not my cup of tea
but you love being genuinely entertaining regardless wishing on but but thank you so much yes
there is a lot of information on the website and like a lot of people didn't realize what the heck
what we're doing and it was like bro we're still beach over so we'll be playing games like of course
I'm still going to talk about satan creep brotherhood tune and stream snake and all that you know
it just means we offer the goods on the other side and we're not a blue ball in you like
because there's quite a lot of each of us that like to do the blue ball part and I was like well
if you if you want the goods then yeah we'll go there for free you can go on all
twitter so if you really if you want to support uh then with your with your money then you can just
do it be a patreon or membership if youtube updates it stats tomorrow you almost went into
stop I'm not I'm not
but yeah well you occasionally dip into the thingy like in pdb
that was to paint you all up though I think everyone did a good job we all we all collectively
were like you know the meme that's like wait hold on maybe I can find it
oh yeah this was literally it
basically this meme if I can see the image
this was the meme so it was like chaos behind the scenes setting up for debut
but like we all came together to discuss how we're like absolutely going to destroy everyone
unanimously and like do all these like things to like get everyone pent up I'm not even pretending
otherwise like literally chaos is the top one all of us preparing for debut but when it came to
discussing like okay let's release the alt twitters it was that was by the pope I admire your work
strongy you are fantastic oh thank you so much thank you so much senior mill kerton why senior
in your title do I give you an accent thank you for the tip though senior I appreciate it and yeah
I'm glad you enjoyed my work doesn't really feel like work I just feel like I'm you know
a rainbow in a way
I'm stressing out over nothing my butt said I'm marshmallow now I'm doom spare what
do you need a is it I think it's called a setter if you if you don't um if you partake I think it's
called a setter like oh setter with you you're evil hey and now you gave us the most wholesome
girl and exist I've got a lot of those comments where people are like the whole agency was based
around like this alternative thing and then like everyone's just like me men along and having a
good time and all that and it's like yeah surprise like we're we're here for enjoy ourselves I think
it can get quite tiresome of every breathing second it's you know are you squid me right now
identify yourself high strontian reeflings from euro time zone good morning good morning oh did you
enjoy your sleep thank you alessandro I did enjoy your sleep we made it we made it your girls are
amazing at getting people in credit with first day my girl so first day she a Lamborghini that's not
that song at all what's that song my girl so Thursday yellow lumber purple Lamborghini I have
absolutely not clue what that song supposed to be thank you for the tip alessandro yeah it could be
everything but it makes a nice thing a bit of a bit of a male just curious but are there any
creators you would like to collaborate with outside the group sadly I am uh very I don't know what the
word is if people reach out to me I am more than happy to but I feel like if I reach out then I'm
bothering so like the yumi plus girls will be nothing but receptive to me I absolutely adore
them so I'm I'm gonna try and get a collab going with them or something or ASMR or anything like
that um but like anyone basically the sentence if you f with me I f with you but because like
all strongies from um veal or like I don't want anyone feeling forced and I'm also quite
appropriate with certain jokes and I don't want to make anyone uncomfortable during a collab so I
only I don't know I'm just shy like I really like fen but I would never ask for a collab because I
just I I know for a fact like I would just make her uncomfortable so I'm just gonna be like thumbs up
from afar love your stuff you know can't wait for the next song cover stop singing I'm trying to
turn on my head oh my god that was like so fun
sadly most potential clubs speak English instead of scott oh they'll never understand me well there
was actually something really funny um was that a zura in debut called me a fish and when we were
doing the mock I was with the girls like um we were doing the mock so five of us were in the voice
call and whoever was doing the mock went and did it um and as they were called me a fish and I was
like a fish in my accent and the girls were like laughing up a storm over it and I was like oh yeah
I freaking love it here like they're just so amazing and they they just get it but like I feel
like if I collabed with someone outside of veal or like they're afraid to make fun of my accent I'm
like no make fun of it are you joking me I say words funny someone was saying like the way I say
jewel wheel they're earlier in that like come on man why is my freaking mouth wiggling and now
I see you doing that I see you doing that iPhone don't make my mouth wiggle
I don't know if it's it's not that dark in this room jewel wheel I jewel wheel
now v v for Mari may have the same vibes maybe
oh I'm gonna recalibrate the stinky form you're so stinky mr form
secret tunnel oh sorry I'm just put that back in his head sorry I apologize
I'm just
meant jewel so it's just gone forever I'm worried this get lost in twitter algorithms
but I couldn't get the reeflings out of my head hold on in my head isn't that a thong
wait why didn't they're not open
someone tied up the reeflings III fits a day what III fits a day
that's a day that's a day what it says the message says III fits a day
what but is that my accent and how I pronounce something
I'm so sad that the girls these mushrooms get getting yanked because I'm refined to loads uh
I think they're tweeting them out you need to check their tweeters somebody come get them their
tweeters have their mega lengths strawney what is it hmm what is it hottest it's more that you've
floating on that people the idea to you I like the idea of taking control and like demanding the pay
a little joystick I definitely enjoyed it hey strawney is the uh reefling again hope you
don't read the word out loud on stream the same time so I guess it's only natural to ask
as people are asking about the patreon audio is any stuff coming out for us yeah
gon be stuff on me gon be stuff on you it's all over for you it's all over for the both of us
actually you were not joking when you said Euro time zone gang would be eating good thanks mom
it you're welcome we're playing old school runescape it's another 12 hour stream tomorrow so hi europe
hi uh oceanic hi uh americas hello hi everyone no not night night prayer night and cooking because
I'm a woman so we need to cook all the food do lobsters I don't know if sharks work
one prompt for a possible audio free use it's not the same as the other one but I get ignored oh
I can do that um I'll need to research a little bit because I'm not sure what to say during that
I'll never say young
oh maybe can I say that I'm not sure I might say that maybe you help me with training no it doesn't
work though it doesn't work
hmm I'll have to thank you you'll have to make me use my my brain I can't believe that you made
me use my brain how dare you how dare you
well there always do one new page on them there's four audios per month
if that's what you mean I really get to watch streams since it starts at 2am for me
I'm so sorry where are you from you must be you must be paired
I've found your location I'm now coming to your house I love when people put their
time zone in the chat and then I get to figure out like roughly where they're from I'm just like
I'm coming over now it's over for you the girl was streaming when I got home from working to
still streaming when I went to sleep and I'm about to go back to work I fear you're scared of me
I work at third shifts the streams are hard to come by oh
for who are you three chefs that's rough okay and I found four we will be in good
zeal good yeah yeah zeal good uh sir I don't know how to say sir in German
museo no that's french starting zero meter from your car at zero meters and getting in
I'm losing the ep fate on your unit falsely can you last another 20 minutes or is it over
it's 20 minutes putting the kettle on for you now oh thanks thanks I don't need a wee cup of tea
when I come in is that a threat or an offer off for real though thanks for streaming them because
your streams are so long yeah uh streams are completely impossible for vod watchers it's uh
pretty crazy unless you kind of use my streams as like something to listen in the
background as you work it's like impossible for vod watchers to uh get up to date
I always miss streams because of work oh work is so stinky you're telling me capitalism is in
is the reason why I don't have more ink we will destroy capitalism I want all the ink
like vod watchers they lose and unfortunately with a streamer like me vod watchers are very rough
what happens in 20 minutes I go offline we reach the 12 hour stream mark where the vod blows up
if I go one second after 12 12 hours so I have to go sadly oh I've been drinking cola I can't
brush my teeth you're not to brush your teeth for 30 minutes because of the enamel sorry we did
technically brush our teeth today so I didn't do a bad job just a rubbish one if it reaches 12 hours
weeks but literally the vod just self combusts clips will come in for the wind for these long
yeah it's if you ever clip a section I get to see it and send it to an editor
good morning good morning Europe hope you all slept well please don't explode
there's only one kind of explosion I want from you I should probably go to bed good night good
night rest well those who need to sleep did you do the rda run oh boy I did and I screamed
in rage I saw red and I don't remember what I said but hopefully I didn't say hopefully I didn't pass
around any uh gamer words kidding kidding relax uh warning do not read on stream is that a challenge
are you challenging me right now
oh well I've made a pact with Emmy if Emmy gets her not safe for work oh no I'm not
supposed to say that I'm supposed to say oh sorry if Emmy gets her all banned you get your wish
I made a pact and Emmy agreed instantly
so yeah you may get your wish
strongy lasagne or sushi what does that mean I mean I'm a fish so sushi
is that possibly mean what does it mean now I'm curious what usually pulls you into subspace
this will not be used against you at all it's just if I don't expect it and it's like good girl or
like a scenario type thing where I'm like all submissive in that and I don't expect it that's when
it can like whack me for the side like that other that other good girl that I read out that almost
got me type thing but it definitely depends like on the mood and all that type thing but yeah
can you say wash your sister sauce I can buy a Worcestershire sauce is that how you say it I
don't know how you say it I'm sure there was a whole thing on shrek about Worcestershire sauce
yeah I know the feeling is a guy get me into it what we do don't open a video
or on stream wash your sister sauce I thought it was Worcestershire Worcestershire I actually
don't know the pronunciation I like how to actually say that do you ever think there'll be a full
viewer countdown what makes you think there wouldn't be
wait for Azura's donathon we're gonna be cooking with that and see what happens
Azura's birthday is august
23rd I believe is august 23rd is her birthday
you said wash your sister first I'm teasing you will wash your sister sauce
I need to ease up or you're gonna have to be patient you're not gonna hold it until august
that's too much even I'm saying that's too much um
um
do not read out load
I can't do that
wait what did you just ask
I'm me I'm sorry that that no that's not on please don't do that
that's not right I'm sorry that's not right
how was the acting did you guys like that did you like that action he said he said
please pretend you have been sent something really offensive and I'm really bad at acting
you put me on the spot I'm rubbish at that don't make me do that again did I nail it
oh did I have you spills oh maybe maybe I'm better than I think
did I get oh we got you got pranked you got pranked me refling pranked you I was getting anxious
oh no don't get excited sorry it was just a meme I'm sorry it was just a meme they just wanted me
to say something they put please pretend to have been sent something so offensive maybe RDA is
better than navi screw the environment faucet is on while person teeth
sorry I didn't mean to cause any anxiety I won't do that kind of pranky again
hey strony I've been commissioning something of alt fan art would there be any issue with
strony and merit no are you kidding me I accept everything bring it show me what you want
show me what you want to see
okay I'm all caught up I'm all caught up I think maybe some people might be getting their stuff
chopped up um rubbish I don't think there's ever gonna be wait does someone ask for a male member
I have terrible news for you if you think it's not that well someone said I don't think there's
gonna be a male member of veal or yeah sadly not the whole reason veal or is even possible is because
of female experience if guys want to start their own male feature agency be my guest but I ain't
gonna not do with me mate ain't gonna not from around these parts ain't ain't gonna not do with me
yeah I ain't gonna not do with me I have absolutely no advice I could give to male creators
because alas I am not a male content creator now Bob do something
yeah brother absolutely hi strony there's one vtuber outside of a lure think there is a
last that you'll play and ring with both have an accent I really love oh I think you're talking
about sin sister yee-ho I'm gonna be collaborating with her we're actually gonna be doing what
uh a shock collar I bought myself a shock collar and she got herself a shock collar and I'm going
to be shocking her and she's gonna be shocking me I'm so sorry I was just I don't I think I'm
starting to lose it mildly honestly considering how delirious I normally get at the end of the
stream that really wasn't that bad considering it was just an accent but if you didn't pick up on any
of that sin sister and myself have bought shock collars and we were going to play Elden ring
together and whoever causes us to lose the battle and perish we get to shock each other
yeah I'm gonna have a heart rate monitor I think she also has a heart rate monitor as well so
things are gonna get out of hand quick also we're really obnoxious streamers together
we don't mute to talk to chat or thank chat so if you do want to join in that stream just know
it's a bit of a sensory overload uh because we honestly don't mind each other um doing their thing
I mean it's gonna be interesting
Strani I know two tubers who possibly mentioned collabing
oh my god imagine naming them in marshmallow so I can reach out to them
only if they're shown indication though I don't want to offend anyone
okay I think that's enough cola for one day it's actually gonna be my bedtime
when I get off of stream audio idea you've been having a rough frustrating weekend suddenly
find us hide up at your door a gift from madame sheebie to relieve your oh I like that idea like
I kind of incorporate in the girl Strani how does it make you feel if I said I wanted to keep you
at home and pregnant all times no I want my pink nippies I don't want brown nippies
made her pink and puffy I want them to stay pink and puffy
pink and puffy
bedtime isn't like after this
yeah well because of my stream time it's bedtime I've been awake since
2 a.m. start streaming at 4 a.m. it's almost 4 p.m. now so I've been awake for 14 hours so my body
starts to shut down now this is when you're getting cognitive the irony that I start out on that word
this is when your cognitive function slows down after the 14 hour mark I take a sip of water
please hydrate if you have water with you
holy f strani wtf what you never made a passionate streamer before
you never met a vtuber that genuinely loves what she does and she gets to have an amazing time with
her wavelengths this is the good life drank the whole water but yeah is your pee nice and clear
for me and I'm sorry please get some rest I will hopefully I get a big boy sleep tonight because
I've been needing a good eight hours but if not old-school rinscape
I feel like that's alright it may be a good life but you should also make sure you're well
rest and hydrate you will deal with the problems when they come up but right now I don't really
have any problems other than vocal strain but my voice doesn't even sound broken over the stream so
yeah have a nice nap and don't rage well sleep it yeah
the quicker longer you sleep the faster old-school rinscape honestly that's what I'm thinking I'm
like the faster it comes I'm squidding me right now I'm trying to fire yourself
strongly you want to take over the world be honest
I want to take over your ink I want to be the reason why you ink
thank you for the tip XYZ
do I actually want to take over the world no
but do I want to main break you to the point I'm the only one you can ink to
oh that sounds good
you can take over my world oh I like that sentence structure less than 10 minutes no wait we have
less than 10 no we have less than 10 minutes oh thank you for the tip
oh have to go what do we what do we do before we go do you want to send do you want to send
marshmallows a voiceline do you want me to say or something
we're talking about ink for rayon yeah yeah ink for rayon yeah
what are we gonna do I don't know what to do I'm gonna make it good before we go
we'd love to see an ASMR collab between secret I'm a drag
hi strongy basing your ideas for the dragon girl gen 2 I think cute lolipop dragon could be popular
I'm done for everything honestly
an essential voice can you please say oh
all right
mm-hmm
you've been so oh wait ah get put on spot hold on
you've been such good boys my dear reframe no meal
that was a sense
did you like it did I do good did I deliver
I almost messed up I think I can speak for most of chat when I say
if you've done an angry scots audio and patreon with love every second as for me I would listen
to it over and over again and make a make ink I do have a kind of parody angry but if you mean
the actual scary angry would you ever force feeding or feederism it's not within patreon to us
so I can't do it
such I request in your most sultry verse voice but one word okay hold on
corn corn corn
corn corn there you get multiple versions because I didn't know what version you wanted
spacey but safer stream strongy sitting on the bed looking up at her she's
she's
cottonless so every time I look up I see oh I can't I can't be downstream to me silly
you're such a good for
oh I'm reaching for the coconut she reaches for the coconut oil asking me to massage it into her feet
I can't help but get an ink on she giggles again this teasing
she knows she owns me feel control I don't I thought that I can't finish it I can't finish this
can you please end the stream with I I inked myself I inked myself
you made me ink myself with everything you're sending
as mercy still alive I still I still redirect to mercy right now
you guys made me ink that's the plan
hopefully mercy still she has post game up and she finishing up oh no
no can you guys tell her that I'm coming or is she coming off is she going offline sorry
I've got ink on my mind I'm not even I'm not even gonna lie I've got ink on my mind
can can you bomb her chat and just say strongy's wanting to read into you but is she going offline