I'm so sorry you're so close to my PC can you hear me I'm like really far away from the mic
can you hear me I might have to talk cause I'm so far away from you the mic
yes we got monetized it's your local funny
what the whole reason I got pedicure was for a monetization stream for ASMR via fate
hello
thank you everyone who's applied to be a member
my voice is a bit scuffed and wait let me see if I can catch up with the list
for some reason stream elements doesn't count in memberships and I don't know why
hold on let's see if you can let me read your news
I need a list I need a list
thank you everyone just this morning
do it do it two taps
oh yeah
oh my god
that's crazy
because I said shit
the first thing the snowberries see are my feet
shh shh shh
hi AC and the snowberries
I don't know why I have to be our headlonger
I'm good and give one hi
we have our ASMR set up
we have all these little intricate
hold on I need the agility to do this
this is ridiculous
hi readers
just a little bit of a stick ASMR everyone
this is ridiculous
who thought of this
you just need to pick up this brush right here
okay
I almost hit the mic with that
hold on
just need to angle there
shh shh shh
go to sleep
you've got monkey feet
shh shh shh shh
okay
I've got face masks
I'm gonna see if YouTube will tell me who my members are
so I can show them out
I already did
right I can go back to the bottom I think
okay this is the list that YouTube is giving me
don't member me right now
because I can't read all of them
okay
I've got pen kai
thermonator
zarian drop
face tazism
out playboy
firefly
someone in chat
recon crusader
harriots
lolirica
viral
xan
bajinga
sassafras
neymar law
harquins
gyne or zib
ll
I was thinking I'm breaking your ear drums
harquins
gyne or 0
lll
kieherit
gazillionair
black blood
Blonde war, for real, choc.
Not Alessandro, Ratma, Nugget, Bridge T-45,
Base 64, Iron Reaper, 1871, Dibble, Inner Whip,
Glacono Samus.
Hold on, like I'll actually do this in one minute.
Hold on, I need to read Imperial Monarch, San Brawley,
King of Mufasa.
Hold on, let me take some of the toast on my own, please.
Sly, save words.
P.O. Josephinei, Jane Mansfield, Superhero.
Mr. McSpliff, Destiny 2 Enjoyer, Kaze Seda,
The Mango Cake, Larry, 28, Nova, Mahal.
There's too much, there's too much.
I can see all the new ones coming in and I'm trying to read the Ova.
Simon, Toby, 81, Otterbone Biscuit, Dapper, Bucket,
De Maia, De Maia, Fork, Super Grom,
Rilke Cadman, Astorix underscore, Penetone,
Akito Henne Nukwitchi, Jacob Otskos,
Yuel, PV, Mendez, stop giving me memberships.
I can't keep up.
Hold on, I can't read them all.
I don't know if this is terrible.
Silvus Nielilis, Firemaker, PV, Mendez,
Micah's Big Bang, Bic is to Fred.
You were Nightingale.
They're in a tiny spinny eye for Kissua Raman.
Kissua Raman, Soul Tinsert, Bero, I'm too old to read one.
What name? I'm too old to read one.
Oh my god, I can't read.
Oh, Bay Odex, Plastic Ghost.
I'm not going to actually have to do ASMR between them.
Oh my god, hold on.
There's a few tools like all that are like required,
real ambidextrous, but like crack pipes,
come on, oh shit.
Hold on, hold on, I can do this.
I'm actually having a problem with this toe, by the way.
I don't know what the lady did, but I think it's contracted
and I might have to go with the doctor about it,
because something's not right.
I cleaned the wound today,
and something's definitely not right,
but can we even get it to bloop?
Wait, hold on.
It's not blooping.
I can't do this.
It's a crazy amount of team effort to get this to bloop.
Hold on.
Oh, come on.
It's not turning over because of the way my feet are.
Oh my god, I figured it out.
Oh my god, a little toe just cracked.
Oh shit.
I'm going to be sorry if I get my dissent today.
That took me so long.
I also brought pop rocks to prove how sweaty my feet are.
I want to see if my feet sweat, can make them pop,
although just the feet sweat, nothing else.
I just realized I'm really covering that up,
so let me go over here.
Look, it's my feet.
Oh yeah, I also have a PC cleaner.
These are used for fan board type things,
but you need to squeeze them to get the air out.
So yeah, I brought a lot of tools to try and get rid of the freaking feet.
I also got the frog thing.
It goes like...
Yeah, it's into the frog.
I ain't working that one, hold on.
Okay, I'll try and say more names.
I'm so sorry.
I'm very flustered when it comes to these kinds of streams.
I feel a little pressured, like...
How are you so good with your feet?
I don't know, how are you not so good with your feet?
I'm trying not to knock over the webcam.
We'll do this.
We'll try and say some names, okay?
Although next, plastic goes,
ceruto, cookie, fungler, kids and gamer.
I've reluctantly said sakura and koku,
dimsidown, national panda,
dragon karma, toasty reef oracle, rikos,
voltage isaya, domino miku.
Okay, that was what was done offline.
Now what was done right now is freaking impossible to keep up with,
but I'm going to try my best, doesn't mean I can't try.
Okay, I'm going to try and keep up.
Please bear with me.
AC's in the room, bear with me.
Okay.
Could you wet...
Huh?
Could you...
Man, I wish I had a little feet.
Could you wet feet drying my...
Well, I bought pop rocks to see if I can actually get them to pop with my feet sweat alone,
which is pretty gross, but I thought it was really funny.
Right, let me check where the new names come in.
I think Zang, PV Mendes, Gaming Kitsune, Zarian, Outplayboy, Zero Bridge,
wait, Firemaker, Pio Giusefina, we have seen...
I recognize some of these names, hold on, I've already said them.
Larry Twenty, Dejan Parma.
Wait, I said these names.
Oh no, I don't know where it starts.
Viral, San Brulee, I said that too.
Draw?
You know what I'm saying?
Everyone get in the name right twice or like, yeah, that's right, forget,
you better forget my name, yeah.
I'm repeating sorry, I'm so sorry.
Right, I think we're here.
Ghizalina, I said Jacob Otskou.
Sleepy Fennec, Eye Flora, Super Grung,
not Alessandro Tenspene,
I don't know, I recognize I've already said these names.
Oh my god, George, it's so hard for me.
Are you getting ASMR at least?
Congrats on monetization, thank you so much, I'm so sorry,
I'm like really out of my element with these kind of streams.
I'm not used to it.
I don't know, I'm just used to it.
Hopefully I can at least do some actual ASMR in a moment.
I'm so sorry, I'm trying to catch up for a little.
Tachio, Carbonai, I had nothing.
Scarecrow, damn, okay, I don't recognize saying these.
Blackwing, 757, why did that just change?
Brayoko, I'm a heron.
I'm a heron, size...
Oh sorry, maybe your other ear should get something else.
Nak Naktoof, 17, Jackie A.
Busbun, Yummy, Ellie Ball, Jackie's,
Garaki, and Gentlemere,
and Scrumptious Nightmare, we did it, we did it.
I freaking caught up, I don't know how we did it.
Thank you so much for everyone who is becoming a member
and being so fantastic.
I'm completely out of my element, I do apologize,
but yeah, you like that?
But thank you so much for your support, you did it!
Can you please scare him like that?
I was gonna do a fake cam on Buckshot, really.
I don't know if I have to go to a doctor about my toe
because something is wrong with it,
and I don't know what on Earth is going on.
Oh she did, so on this toe, this bit here,
she cut into like really deep,
and I was like, oh no, it's fine, like accidents happen.
It was a little bit painful, but I didn't think anything of it.
And then it's actually pretty sore today,
so I don't know if I have to get a check though.
But yeah.
The only good thing with your toe is it's not,
the only thing wrong with your toe is it's not my max!
Oh my goodness, okay, you're done.
Scrumptious Nightmare, thank you.
Frosty Dino, thank you.
Grampo, thank you for becoming a man, sir.
Yeah, it's good, I do.
You're not supposed to cut it at all,
a lot of shops do it anyway, yeah.
I think I may have got hurt a little bit, but it's okay.
Turi, thank you.
I appreciate it.
Right, well let's see if we can open up Pop Rocks
with their feet and get my feet swept
to activate the Pop Rocks.
This might be very loud actually, hold on.
I'm going to take it a little bit away from you, okay?
I don't know if I can do it with my feet till it's open.
Anything is possible if you get your hands on it.
So we have the...
Grupper Repair Funds for 10, thank you so much.
Oh wait, wasn't there a red?
Why is it not displaying?
I could have sworn us all red earlier.
It was a red.
The Jingle of 100 in Celebration and Monetization
are giving my first ever red symbol.
Thank you, my goodness.
Thank you so much.
Do you guys think you better support the girls
more than this, I can't say.
Oh my God, I don't think I can rip it open.
Hold on.
Actually having to use my green power.
Monkey Feet Goop.
I can't see if there's like a green rip section on it.
I can't see anything at all.
That's why I've not turned my glasses.
Okay, I'm trying to rip it open, but it's gonna work.
Support the girls and the mama.
You got my neurons.
Congrats on the Monetization.
Thank you.
It really wasn't that hard in the nicest...
Streams, Assets, Creed, Brotherhood and Nerds
are about it.
Oh yeah, no thank you.
I've worked really hard for that.
Diddy, thank you for becoming a member.
Oh my God.
Hi Rain.
I am so sorry Rain, please don't look.
It's not what it looks like Rain.
It's a mistake, okay?
Hi Rain.
It really didn't mean anything.
Thank you for the 10.
Did you want to put down a pillow first or last?
Nah, it's fine.
The place I am renting the caskets
weren't even cleaned before I moved in,
so you get what you want back.
Thanks.
Thank you.
I'll let...
999, thank you for becoming a member.
Okay, I don't think I'm gonna have to choose my hand.
Sorry lads, hold on.
Oh wait, I'll do it off camera.
Watch this.
Oh look at my toes go.
Oh sorry.
Oh sorry, my toes weren't in frame.
Oh dear.
Oh my toes weren't in frame.
Oh you couldn't see that.
Oh dear.
But I did get them open.
So, the way my feet sweat the most is in this section
in between the toes,
so this is what I'm basically gonna aim for.
This is disgusting.
If this actually pops, this is awful.
If this genuinely pops because of my feet sweating,
this is terrible.
Okay, if the Spidey, thank you for becoming a member,
if this pops, I'm actually gonna cry.
I hope so it doesn't, but I'm at the same time anyway.
Hold on.
I need to sit on the floor for this.
Ooh, I need to do this with my foot.
As if this pops.
I can't hold them in my toes.
Did it pop?
No, I thought I could do it.
I think we're safe.
I can't do it.
Wait, did it pop?
No.
Oh, hold on.
I hear it, shut up.
Did it pop?
It's popping.
No, that's so gross.
I'm gonna sweat my feet this way.
Hold on.
It popped.
So now you're on the line about that.
That's disgusting.
But yeah, I got really sweaty feet.
I also have sweaty hands, maybe I would do it with my hand.
It's kind of the same thing where it's sweaty
in between my fingers more.
Salted feet.
Why, you wanna lick them?
Oh, wait.
Oh no, it's getting sticky,
because my feet are over.
I never thought this far ahead.
Why am I so low IQ?
It's such a curse sometimes.
Hold on.
Thank you Esteban Lomiel,
who I'm gonna remember.
Thank you Colin.
Four, three, one, six.
And thank you Shalom Plain.
She kinda dumb though.
Sticky feet mean sticky floors.
Oof.
You put socks on after this stream.
Oh, there's like bits and spots everywhere now.
You know what?
Maybe that reefling was right,
and I should have put a towel down.
Hold on, my sweaty hands are so sticky.
They're sticking to my hands.
Look, it's actually a benefit.
It's actually a benefit, okay?
You just have to think of the situation.
Hold on.
Let me just pop them up there.
Our experiment has been conducted.
Gross, I don't know.
My ears have a pop rock sometimes.
I'm trying to help.
Actual squid behaviors.
Honestly.
This is welcome to the reefling membership tier,
and this is message redacted.
I don't know how, but here you go.
Thank you Brayoko
for the super chat.
Oh my god, the super chat, because I'm monetized.
Found your credit card.
Congrats!
Maybe don't...
You don't have to support, by the way.
I always have free membership streams all the time.
Today we learned to always put damage up.
Right, and we're going to actually do ASMR
at the same time to hold up.
This is your boy.
This is ridiculous.
My offer counts.
Bull, I also got my Skyrim achievements to work.
I have like 12% Skyrim achievements.
I don't know why they weren't displayed,
but we might be able to actually go back
to the Skyrim stream at any time.
Bull, I thank you for becoming the streamers.
Totally bonkers.
Congrats, new membership. Thank you.
Thank you, boy, for being a member.
Thank you, uh, Sithmans for coming to member as well.
Yeah.
Oh, you're getting tangled up in Wazir right now.
Shhh.
Next week, yeah.
Our Endurance stream of the week is...
Hold on, let me put these on, yeah.
Thank you, uh, Shiori
for becoming a member.
And thank you, Dr. P, for becoming a member.
Hold on, this is going to take some manipulation
because this ear isn't sitting
the way ears actually sit.
Oh, wow, my feet are so talented.
You look on Skyrim achievements
and usually take, like, three streams
unless your stream's super long.
Yeah.
I'm a bit of an Endurance streamer, okay?
Shhh.
ASMR.
Thank you, Jay, for the membership.
Thank you.
Oh, woo-ee, for the membership.
Oh, no, they're coming off.
Shhh.
Say, just say.
Well, those feet grew arms and hands out of nowhere.
How about your next skill?
Look, I'm going to say for the pod.
I have eight arms, okay?
How do you buy membership?
Oh, you don't have to.
There should be a join button,
but it doesn't work everywhere,
so don't worry if you can't buy.
I always have free streams coming out
and the membership streams start next week.
Not this week,
because by the end of this week
I'll have everything in place
work-wise so I only have to do shorts.
And I'm very glad.
I am so glad that all the responsibility
is taken off me.
And I'm just a normal stromer.
We should have changed all our names
into Jamal for the stream,
knowing beforehand you would have said
every person.
We should have one reflame.
It's all arms anyway.
The logic checks out
and definitely isn't influenced by the membership.
And the join button is sometimes
not next to subscription on mobile.
Yeah, I guess if you're in the phone.
But don't worry,
you don't have to directly support me.
I'll always have free streams coming out
like all the time.
I'm not kidding.
You can't take me off.
Come on.
You can't.
It's not possible.
Okay?
So don't try and take me off.
Bless the shimi.
Thank you very much.
Remember?
Are you doing me with my dog?
Are you doing hypnosis soon?
Not right now.
No.
No of these.
I don't think anyone can get hypnotized
by fricking toes.
You can see how opaque my skin is.
You can see my blue veins.
Check them veins out.
You can literally see them.
I have my little tendons.
If you look hard enough for them.
Oh, there they are.
Look at them tendons.
Thank you for the tip.
I'll hold on a string on the swing.
Did Brian talk?
Did Brian say anything?
I hope not.
Oh, it's kind of working.
Okay.
Stream element says no.
Kind of working.
Mika's big fan.
Thank you for the five gifted memberships.
And then Boyce the Trigger
wore just purple burglar alarm honestly.
Brian said it but he was quiet.
Good.
I'm glad he didn't say it.
I did not say no.
Bejinga.
In celebration, I gave my first ever ritz.
Yes, I did.
I'm so sorry.
I'm very scared of brain right now.
Secret, thank you for becoming a member.
This is the craziest ASMR concept.
It's not even ASMR, let's be honest.
I'm just dumb.
I'm just dumb for you.
I'm from a field.
Thank you.
What?
At their name?
At their...
Strony, I just want to stream what I want and enjoy.
Corporals, you can't do that.
You'll never be successful.
Strony, who my beer makes whole companies
have life-mangered people to stream with.
I cannot tell you how unbelievably nice it is.
Thank you for that type of thing.
I cannot tell you how unbelievably nice it is
to have like-minded individuals,
knowing gays are rats.
I jumped on my alternative Twitter
and was listening to the feed.
I'm just sitting listening to A.C. Tinkle
and I'm just like, yeah, this is actually quite good quality.
Honestly, I wouldn't mind if she brought a 3D one there.
It is so nice to have like-minded individuals
that are like, yeah, let's provide the goods.
We say no to blue-balling here, okay?
You ask and you receive, okay?
You ask other agencies, you get donor-walled.
Hold on, I'm going to take a drink of water.
I'm going to put dehydrate.
Please take a drink of it now.
P.L.U.R. allegations are yet to be resolved.
I will make a public statement about the P.L.U.R. allegations.
As you can see, we're in very hot water about the P.L.U.R. allegations.
What is donor-walled?
Donor-walled is when someone gives a streamer a lot of money
via a donation and the streamer doesn't read it out loud
for whatever reason it may be.
They genuinely missed it.
That's very plausible.
They don't want to acknowledge it
because of maybe the contents,
but donor-walled is the term
when someone gives over money and still gets the money.
That's beyond.
Thank you for becoming a member.
Good luck with the P.L.U.R. campaign.
Mi-Win-Jin 2 comes out of the P.L.U.R. campaign.
P.L.U.R. is the best station in the world.
Okay, I genuinely think I managed to catch up to everyone.
Thank you so much for all of the love and support.
I'm really overwhelmed right now
and I feel so out of my element.
I'm like, oh my god, what do I do?
I figured out what I do to P.L.U.R.
Right, so you may notice that my tier 2 is $4.99.
I don't think it can be gifted unless on purpose, right?
Like, can you not just manually put in gift $1.99?
Internet-baz of fees.
Thank you for the member.
Hold on, I'm trying so hard to do this.
The P.L.U.R. needs to rehire a P.L.U.R. position.
A P.L.U.R. position.
Oh, jeez.
This is embarrassing, I can't grip it.
Oh, there we go.
Surprise, surprise.
If you use two feet, you can grip it really well.
Jeremy, thank you for coming to member.
I'm so sorry to end when I'm alienating right now in this room.
Literally, this is getting...
Come on, please.
Okay, here we go.
We'll do it like this.
Wow, Asterix.
Thank you for the five gifted members.
Did it do a moose?
You guys have a moose now.
Jake, Jake said pre-looked grippers.
Let's go, honestly.
Okay, just that.
I'm gonna put it like that.
Oh, there we go.
We got it.
Oh my god, we got it.
The Dexterix.
Just admit it.
No other streamer is even capable of doing this physically,
because they wouldn't be able to do it.
This is absolutely staggering.
Did anyone take a...
Or is everyone just blown away by this
even being a streamer concept?
Do you know how long I planned this for?
I planned this for...
I planned this
back when I was concepted
to have French tits and nails,
which is absolutely awful.
I've been waiting months on this idea
to utilize it.
Man is up one.
Thank you for...
Right, can I do two at once?
I think I can.
Hold them by the bottom.
Oh, this is...
Hold on.
We're losing them.
My feet are so sweaty that they're...
Right, they're up,
and then...
Oh, they're up a bit too much.
I can do this chat.
Let me do it.
Does that even work?
Oh, my ankle just cracked.
Did you hear that?
Literally jewel-wielding the tingles right now.
We're in uncharted territory.
I'll forget to say, why can I not do it with that one?
I wonder if the plaster is actually helping me grip this one.
I'm jewel-wielding tingles.
Why?
I think my feet are actually getting too sweaty
to pick this up because it's glass.
I think I'm gonna have to take off.
Right.
I think I'm literally...
Hold on, we'll just go the brush.
Calm, calm.
The migraine, thank you for becoming a member.
I appreciate it.
If this isn't peak streaming, I don't know what is.
Honestly, like, which year...
Which year's...
Where the heck is my other...
Oh, here.
Hold on, I'm cheating.
Just a little bit.
Jewel-wield brushes.
Come on.
Come on, admit it.
It's just so hard to do because of the ankle.
Oh, there we go.
I just need to relax the gripper.
ASMR.
I'm impressed.
Did you watch the new Echo Showcase?
Apparently Fable 4 is coming out.
Wait, hold on a second.
I'm gonna just grip it sideways.
Ta-da.
We love joe feet wielding tingles.
I bet you do.
Wah, thank you for becoming a member.
Yay, Fable.
But they were saying...
And apparently the new Dragon Age Origins
has, like, a ton of little G-fans really mad
because there's something wrong with that.
Like, how do you fix them then?
Oh, and my feet are actually too...
Getting too sweaty.
Correct the shit.
Hold on.
I need my pinkie.
I need my pinkie to join in on the grip.
I need my gripper.
She's put maxing on food?
I am.
From a two-handed build in Skyrim to a joe wield build
the next day, so talented.
I know.
Isn't it amazing?
God, look at the gel shine on that big toe.
Oh, look at that shine.
Oh, that's gorgeous.
I admire my own feet.
Yes, I do.
And such cool.
Rosso, thank you for becoming a member.
Omen.
So then thank you for becoming a member.
Oh, my ring light there.
That's what's lighting up the deck under here
because it's all dark.
So that's what the gel polish is doing.
Delicious brown waifu.
Thank you for becoming a member.
Not 3DO, it should have been me.
Hammerfell is going to come in 2026 if we're lucky.
I'll be so interested to see if I'll enjoy the game or not.
It might be one of those games where I have to play offline for the first time
to even appreciate it.
I don't know if you ever, like, you know, your first play through of a game,
you're so silent and so quiet
because you're just experiencing it for the first time.
So I feel like it would be hard to commentate.
Like, I really want to play Big Bobby's Gate,
but I'm worried I won't have a thought,
like a single thought formed because I've never played it before.
I'm sad I can't hear, but the visuals, the visuals, though.
Yeah, you like the visuals.
Can I do the middle finger on a toe?
Hold on.
Can I?
No, I'll just put this down.
And then bring you back up again.
And then everyone go down.
Oh, no, it's not going to work.
I don't have that kind of...
I don't have that kind of toe deck, though.
You have the kind where I can, like, grip around and stuff.
My appendages.
I'm actually tempted to leave these on
because it's helping to muffle me making any mistakes.
Crying.
Shimmer pants.
Thank you for the time.
Congrats on monetization, Stony.
Thank you!
Like, we had a direct support.
A fan made more remaster of oblivion made in Scourge Engine
is coming out to it with us.
Cue.
I do a little tapping these more.
It feels like I don't have the dexterity to do the frog thing.
If Wolves and Gromit aren't becoming cranes of beyond on our fellow...
Oh, does a Wolves and Gromit thing come out?
How far can your tanky pool?
What do you mean, far?
I can only go like this.
Sky Blivion.
Get Nordid.
Hmm.
It's commonly referred to as Sky Blivion by the project workers.
Aren't they not...
Wouldn't they not get a season to say that they're doing that?
What's going on?
Cup your ears.
I'm cupping your ears.
There's also a mod project that makes all of Nen...
Nen?
I would love if the Morrowind remake would come out, but we will hope.
Cheese, Gromit.
I'm sure there's a new Wolves and Gromit thing coming out.
I don't know if it's a movie or what.
Because everyone was like, oh, a new Wolves and Gromit before GTA 6.
No, because it's fantastic.
Fanmade mods are free.
Ah, that's how they got away with it.
But this, it doesn't actually get up a day about mods and assets they pack.
Fallout 3 and New Vegas are fine.
What were the accusations that Fallout 4 got the most useless update recently?
And it was to spite modders to break them all or something?
Was that Fallout 4 or did I make that up?
The amount of complete reworks on this current engine is crazy.
Danny Elorma make volume, by the way.
It keeps peaking red.
But...
Yeah, they had more than they would hope their studio got burned or other stuff and more.
I'm playing Fallout 4 right now.
The update Fallout 4 due to the show, and it broke all the mods and the mods.
Oh, okay, that makes more sense.
That makes it feel good.
Okay, it keeps peaking red and I'm like, am I, am I, am I grippers to OP for this microphone right now?
Wow.
Hmm.
Peter, Salis, whose voice grew on it passed away.
Oh.
I guess I don't have to get a fan, do I?
That sounds good.
I'm glad.
I thought right, my ears are fine, my ears are fine.
Good.
Just so you know, for the replays, this isn't an endurance stream.
I'm very out of my element with the webcam on and I'm like...
Okay, now what?
I'm like, okay.
But thank you so, so much to everyone who's membering.
Thank you so, so much to everyone who's super-chan or tiffin or anything.
It's such a fantastic help.
Like, obviously I don't want to say too much, but, you know, it takes a year to create a new generation, so this is very reassuring.
If there may or may not be some plans in the background, ho, ho, ho.
We love mommy, love you, Eastling.
Thank you, seriously.
Like, I'm a bit overwhelmed.
Like, I literally have my hands like this because I'm like, oh, okay.
I was nervous.
Like, I don't know what to do.
I was nervous to sleep.
Genius idea, please.
I was going to do a photo-cam stream on Buckshot Relay and then you guys can tell me to put my feet back on the floor because I always sit on them.
Absolutely.
There were the scores last, literally.
Thank you.
Yes, I just filled out my element.
I'm like, I'm used to meme-ing.
I'm used to, well, I guess the stream is a big meme, to be honest.
I don't need to put that much, like, what's the word, that much.
I did bring, I know everyone is tired of Japanese youth cleaning tools, and it gets done today, but it's true.
Thank you, Tiko Suwabi, for becoming a member.
I can't pick this up, hold on.
Thank you, Berenice Yuzette, for becoming a member.
And thank you, Eleka Riaz.
Wow, sorry I'm late.
No need to be sorry at all.
Thank you for becoming a member.
Forgiveness sake.
When it's really thin, it's so hard to grip.
Seriously.
This is, like, outrageously thin, right?
I'm not going to need to, like, bring it closer.
And then, I need to take this off gently, if I can even do that.
That's right, you're cleaning via foot, or whatever.
Ah, Internet, Bazoo, File, Mealtalk, it's cool to see you willing to be able to,
it's a challenge, even with a handful of people, much less.
300, eh, 300, that's like 600, throwing money, literally.
I'm definitely not a handcam streamer, I don't think I, I don't, don't expect any footcam, handcam.
After this, I'm going to be honest, I'm like, oh, it's not for me.
Right, we're going to do this as gently as possible, okay?
Gentle.
Thank you for coming to my ear cleaning foot spa experience.
I ran through, thank you for becoming a member.
Now just let the brush slowly glide across your ear.
And as the brush cleans the outer ear, hold on.
You will find yourself, hold on, and relax.
Just like this.
Instructional ASMR, just let me ASMR you.
Oh yeah, that's right, that's the money shot.
That's so hard to, to, I'm tripping, my poor pinky.
Look how hard my pinky is trying right now.
My pinky is like going to France without hard as trying.
You can't be feetlings anymore.
After the stream, I don't think you're feetlings.
I think I'll stick to the VTuber model because I'm like so nervous with the webcam on.
Plastic girl, thank you for the 10.
If you like feet though, Emmy's doing foot cam stream later this week, okay?
Emmy Bezu, her link is in the description.
Subscribe and hit the bell if you are into feet because she's, oh, I just dropped it.
I don't even notice I dropped it, hold on.
Right, and then pass it to this one.
This is my strong foot, take my strong foot.
Refling, take my strong foot.
Refling, no, don't fall, grab onto my foot.
Grab onto my French pedicure foot.
French pedicure pedicure.
Thank you.
Ruin desolations, as I remember.
Thank you, jargon hearts, for becoming a member.
This is literally my left foot.
Unless, unless I hold it like a pencil.
Hold on, I need to like dab it against myself.
Just know whenever you hear ear cleaning in my ASMR role plays, it's not done by my hands.
It's done by my foot.
Foot holding him.
Thank you everyone for memberships and supporting me.
I appreciate it.
We are testing if tier two needs to be higher than 4.99 US dollars.
But I don't think it has to be.
Not from what I've seen.
Oh no, it's dropped again, jeez.
This is really difficult.
I thought I had a bit more.
I think because it's so thin.
Okay, there we go.
This is easy.
It's gone again, jeez.
I'm going to have to joe wield this.
Double the twos, honestly.
B, yaku.
G, yaku.
Thank you for the membership.
I appreciate it.
Right, we're swapping.
We're swapping.
I can't do this anymore.
Okay, let's do the bubbles.
I said let's do the bubbles.
This is the most bizarre monetization celebration I've ever seen.
I've actually outdone myself.
I've actually surprised myself.
Weird, this concept.
Can the bubbles come?
Sorry, that was probably really loud.
I'm so sorry.
I hope no one's actually consuming this stream at a level of loud ASMR.
No, don't listen to the stream at ASMR levels.
Don't be silly.
My skull, we're faked.
Okay, I was going to say don't be silly and listen at ASMR levels.
My feet are literally the pilot.
You're telling me you trust my feet not to ever make a blip.
I know my ear drum's still there.
Ow, my ear.
Yeah, no.
Don't listen at ASMR levels.
Don't be silly and listen.
It's absolutely no way.
Right, so for some reason stream elements can see when you guys gift other people,
but it won't register a membership if you bought it yourself.
I don't know why.
You're kicking into my CPUs ASMR?
That's terrible.
Fiat, thank you for becoming a member.
Is your name Fiat for a particular reason in the stream?
That's strange.
Yeah, I don't know why.
I'm not going to lie to you, your voice overpowers any sound.
I could have heard so far would need a different session.
Hi, Stony, congrats on unlock and monetization.
Thank you.
I was thinking you can find yourself.
Oh, thank you.
Member just for anyone listening.
You don't actually have to member, by the way.
I always have free content coming up, so please don't worry.
Please make sure you look after yourself first such as you pay off your debts
because we live in a society and if you're debt free, it's good for you,
but bad for society.
But we can get into that in another stream.
John07, thank you for the membership.
I appreciate it.
Sorry about all the camera glitching, by the way.
This is a very dusty webcam.
A very dusty.
Nero, thank you for becoming a member.
Nero2276, I was supposed to say your phone number.
The camera's fine.
Peppermint.
Did I say that right?
There's no R.
Okay, ah, you never mind.
Okay, never mind.
Oh, we got there in the end.
Don't worry, Stony, even if we get our ears bumped, you're still the best put stream.
Ah, is that my new title now?
Like the best put streamer?
I would honestly take that title.
I'm quite happy with that title.
It's all right.
My feet are here to comfort you.
When it has been a long day, my sweaty grippers are here to pretend to tangle you
because let's be honest, this isn't an ASMR stream.
No one believes at all this is an ASMR stream.
Just because you have the 3D view, it doesn't make it an ASMR stream.
Which is why the title's called Monetization Celebration Stream and not ASMR.
Watch Mercy's stream.
I was wondering if you could do a Q&A too.
I would absolutely love to.
I would love to do a Q&A.
Maybe we can read membership.
Membership.
Marshmallow.
We can read marshmallow.
Absolutely.
Air Rocks.
Starley.
Yes.
We can 100% do a marshmallow reading.
That would be fantastic.
Although Mercy was purposely saying stuff wrong, which was quite funny.
Really giving bad advice.
Logan, have a lit.
Thank you so much.
If you hear my stomach, it's not because I'm hungry and starving.
It's because I got a massive loaf of bread and I wouldn't come out before the stream.
I went to the toilet three times and I never came out.
So I'm sorry if you hear my stomach.
This could be really funny for an April Fool's stream.
Well, you win the grippers out again.
What would the title of the stream be?
Too many people ask real questions, but most of Mercy's advice was real, was it?
Wait, hold on.
Let me get my marshmallow.
Because I was a movement.
And then I'll go up along.
I should only cut ones, yeah?
What?
You asked me anything.
And before I can hardly say anything, that was,
wait, where can I pin this?
I would like to pin it, but the love heart is in the way.
Someone at YouTube, you're telling me not one person at YouTube is aware of this issue?
I refuse.
Ten message.
April Fool's.
How is it April Fool's if I've already done it?
I've already got you.
The gag has been done.
You can do my breath on me.
Okay.
That's my marshmallow thing.
And what?
No, Tier 2 is what's getting gifted, mummy.
You have to raise a price for both ears.
Wait, no.
I only want emotes to be gifted.
I wanted to leave emotes as $1.99.
And I have to make it $5 for Tier 2?
Honestly, the mental stress of raising it by $0.02 is really good to me.
Okay.
Be bad in gagging.
Thank you for the membership.
I appreciate it.
We did warn you.
I was just wanting them to work so badly.
I don't want to raise the price.
I have to, apparently if I want to raise the price,
I need to close the tier and then open up a new one.
I don't even know what happens.
It only lets you donate the $4.99 tier.
I'm so happy to have you back.
I miss you.
I miss you too.
Oh, that's so annoying.
I have to raise the price by a freaking dollar.
So, by a dollar, by a cent.
So, if I make it, you would leave emotes at $1.99.
But Tier 2 has to go up to $5.99.
Does it actually have to be?
Say it right, sir.
I will not go.
Turn the lights off.
Carry me home.
Yeah.
It has to go up to $5.99.
It's just a dollar, do it.
But you don't understand.
You don't understand the principle
about how much I can gloat and brag
that it's only $9.99 to support your Oshi
for a month, I feel, or you don't understand.
Okay.
But it's kind of more of the YouTube channel
having to make problems, it's fine.
So, right, I guess after this stream,
for those of you who sign up now for the Tier 2,
I think you only have to pay the $1 difference
to get on the tier that is...
Oh, that's so annoying.
Can I make that new tier live, at least?
Or is this like...
I don't know how YouTube's going to take this.
Oh, I don't know if YouTube's going to like me.
Hold on.
Levels, edit levels.
No!
It locked in, the price is locked in.
I don't want to put up a dollar, but I have to.
Oh, my God.
Please, YouTube's not...
Right, I have to basically add a new tier...
For goodness' sake.
Reefling member stream tier.
Oh, and...
For goodness' sake.
You know tier...
Oh, okay.
Hold on, we're trying to do it together.
Right, we need to do it in American Double Laws.
United States, set a price...
$5.99.
That's a book in it.
Modes, give that man a backshot.
What?
Wait, what did that happen?
We're doing it live, we're doing it live.
We're doing it live, we are.
Reefling...
I'll just put it, Reefling member real tier.
Because I'm out of things.
And then add a peric...
membership stream.
Membership only live streams.
This is the real deal.
Y'all.
And then peric instructions, nothing,
because you guys don't need to do anything.
Then next, what happens?
I understand that once my offer's reviews improved,
I'm unable to change, to introduce a new price,
I can create a new level and or delete any existing.
Deleting a level will cancel existing memberships if it happens.
Okay, submit for review.
Yes, my tier, my freaking membership streams do not have...
Sorry, I'm like straight up talking when there's a thing.
No, it does not come...
Right, your peric is being sent for review, it said...
$5.99!
That's so expensive, I'm going to have to stream way more than...
I'm going to have to stream more to earn that,
because $5.99 is really getting expensive.
Does it even display the damn thing?
I don't think so.
Right, it doesn't display it,
because it's not been approved by YouTube, question mark.
It's $1.
So like, all the tier twos will be reset.
So the tier twos can upgrade via $1.99.
You already stream more than most, it's no problem.
We can buy one less candy per month.
You already stream every day.
Yeah, well you're ready for multiple streams in one day of different things?
Yeah.
Am I losing my membership tier?
Maybe.
Why does it not work?
So what does it say? Is it there?
No, it's not been approved, so you can't see it.
Elliebot, thank you for the membership upgrade.
Why does it specify you upgraded?
That's so specific.
Oh no, more streams, oh no.
Thank you for fixing that.
Yes, so we need to wait for YouTube to approve the new tier,
and then that's the actual tier.
I guess, but I don't know how long it takes to get it approved.
I wonder, actually, I wonder if YouTube is going to be able to see
that it's so similar to the second one,
and they're going to be like, yeah, you're dumb.
You praised it wrong, didn't you?
And I'm like, yes, I praised it wrong, please forgive me.
I'm sorry.
And then YouTube will be like, I will have mercy on your soul.
Your levels are approved, published.
Wait, what? I already got approved?
Wait.
Hello, YouTube? Are you watching me right now?
I promise I'm not doing anything bad.
Feet are a natural part of the body.
Thank you for monetizing me, YouTube.
Please don't take it away.
Is YouTube actually here right now?
Why did it just get approved?
Is it approved? Is it live?
Wait, hold on, let me try it.
Oh, okay. Wow, it is.
Okay, right.
I'm going to delete the other tier.
Okay, thank you for upgrading.
Did I delete it now?
And then, oh my God, everyone's upgrading.
Thank you so much.
I'm so sorry, Mifflins.
I'm so, so sorry.
I've completely messed this.
I've absolutely balled this one up.
Right, I will delete the...
How do I delete it?
I do.
I will delete it.
Delete this level.
If you delete a level, members of that level will lose their membership.
Consider notifying them before deleting,
encouraging them to change levels.
Any member that purchases this level this month will be reimbursed.
Okay, that's good.
Any member that purchased this level this month will be reimbursed.
Okay, YouTube, I'm reading that myself.
Once you submit your changes, they'll get approved.
Delete.
Next, submit and review.
I understand that once my offer is reviewed and approved,
all members of deleted levels will lose their membership
and will be reimbursed for the last month.
Okay, submit for review.
We're doing it live.
Okay, we're doing it live.
Do it live.
Publish.
Did that work?
What does it say now?
Wait, hold on, let me refresh.
Hold on, I think we did it.
Hold on, pause.
I think we did it.
We did it.
Okay, I will not mess up with the girls,
but I will...
Okay, there we go.
I believe it's fully working now.
If you do gift memberships, it will only go to refling emotes,
which I need to add a sugar ton to
because it was like, you're only allowed to add four emotes
until you get more members,
so I'll add to the rest and I'll commission a ton more
because with that amount of membership,
I think there's quite more than 10 slots that I have.
Thank you so much for your patience for me doing this.
Thank you everyone who's upgrading to the new tier.
I do apologize for the mistake.
I really severely wanted membership gifting to be on emotes only
because I didn't want to charge more than $5.99.
No, $4.99.
Thank you everyone who's upgrading.
Can I see your upgrades?
Nope.
Stream Ellen's just really doesn't like it.
That's very curious.
Very curious indeed.
But I won't mess up for the girls when I enable it.
I don't know if and when.
I don't know if she's doing hers right now.
If she is, it's a surprise.
I don't know if I'm the only one who's currently doing the membership member.
Oh my god, I don't think.
Wait, it's not telling me the upgrades?
No.
It's not telling me when you've upgraded.
Like on my screen, on any screen.
I'm so sorry.
I don't think I can keep up with the upgrades.
Thank you everyone who's upgrading.
I appreciate it.
I'm so sorry.
I suck.
I suck as a streamer.
My apologies for such an unprofessional start.
But then again, is it really me if it's not unprofessional?
It's so over.
No.
We will support the cut for this regard.
Thank you.
I think it's not an upgrade now because the tier is gone.
So it's just a new membership.
It's not registered.
Oh wait, is it registered?
Oh no.
This can't be.
Wait, how am I supposed to...
Oh wow, so it's not even telling me if it's an upgrade now.
Okay, this is good.
Membership note showing in your stream elements is a bug with your stream elements account.
I've contacted their support about it.
I wonder if the stream elements is for Twitch really.
But thank you so much everyone for upgrading or becoming a member of the tier.
I actually can't remember if I've said it wrong.
We can just send it.
You're more professional than many streamers.
You treat us like humans.
Who streams and doesn't treat you like a human?
What?
Please tell me there's not actually streamers like that.
I remember when you guys taught me that people get actually jealous.
Like if they see you in someone else's chat and I'm like, huh?
That's real?
Because I thought you guys were memeing on me, like teaching me this.
And I'm like, wait, some VTubers expect you to solely watch them and only them.
It was very eye-opening.
Very eye-opening.
Boy, thank you for the tip.
Alert this.
For some reason, I can see that on stream elements, but nothing else.
I can see if someone gifts membership on stream elements as well.
But that's it.
This bit was off.
Some people are a bit cray-cray about it.
I used to be sweating right now.
That was slightly different.
I understand where she said that.
Yeah, it's a lot more common than you think.
I'm only going to have time for you to try.
It's a lot more than 12 hours streams, yeah.
Oh, thank you for the gifted membership.
iPor, thank you.
Oh, you need to allow gifts.
There may be a prompt in chat right now to allow gifts.
Make sure you click it.
Thank you.
It will say that you can receive gifts.
I don't know how it works.
My membership just got refunded.
Did I miss something?
Yes, I had to change the price because gifted membership was the wrong price.
So thank you, everyone, who's resubbing.
I believe you got a refund question mark question mark, which is really good.
It's so sweet.
Yeah, we all got refunded.
That was really quick.
Honestly, shout out to YouTube if everyone literally got refunded.
That was so quick.
Where is the join button on mobile?
Get right, you're on mobile.
There is no join button.
It's just a mystery.
The join button is more of a suggestion than actual rules.
Thank you, everyone, for resubbing.
I'm so sorry.
T.W., thank you for resubbing.
Giving Kitsuny, Consulus, Lolliwika, Conrad, Asterix.
I'm like pretty sure I've said all these names before.
I'm so sorry to anyone whose name I haven't said before.
The join button is on the YouTube page.
Oh, if you want my YouTube page, apparently.
Cookie Fumplur.
You guys have such funny gamer tags, honestly.
Sorry, I meant 21 Bibboots over 21 days.
Not all at once.
I was in a rush to get a brain rot.
I was about to clarify.
Okay, I was going to say that was quite the length.
Being inspired by the 21 days of brushing me.
The microplastics will be purged.
Oh, that's a good, I like that.
I subscribed on desktop with PayPal on the old 4.99.
So what now?
YouTube should have already refunded you apparently.
Apparently everyone already got refunded like within seconds.
So the new tier is $1 more due to the fact that Gifted Membership will go to Emote Tier,
which was what I wanted.
But I was so stubborn and like, oh yeah, YouTube.
I'm sure YouTube will make sure that you can't donate streams at that price.
But no, no.
YouTube insisted.
PayPal learned me what's pending.
It should.
VTuber Foot Connoisseur, thank you.
What a name.
What a name to show up in this stream with.
Thank you for becoming a member.
That's hilarious.
Mika's biggest fan.
I'm thinking Mika, Mika, Uwe.
Art Bomb Biscuit, thank you.
What a name.
Honestly, you like the French tip?
Is this dinner for you?
That's right.
Where other VTubers don't provide, I come sweeping in on week one.
Week one, I give you what you seek.
He really is a connoisseur.
How's the winded tour doing?
I had to take painkillers because it's getting a bit sore.
I may or may not be making a doctor's appointment about my toe.
Because something...
I'm going to see what happens.
I'm going to go for a bath after the stream and let it sweat it out, like in the hot water.
In Vulcan, Black Blood, Zafarian, Jacob of Thru.
I still forgot this is week one.
I mean technical, well, we're just entered week two, I guess.
But if YouTube stats updated immediately, we would have been monetized day one.
But it took a whole week for it to thingy.
This is week two, my apology.
Fee.
Yes.
I'm so sorry if you don't like immersion breaking.
Although I am literally as white as night.
I'm actually, I'm so white, I'm transparent.
What the heck did I just move there?
You can literally see my veins in the blue.
You didn't know veins are blue.
They carry deoxygenated blood back to your heart.
They also have back blow valves, which are really good.
It stops the blood from going backwards in your system.
Because if your blood ever goes backwards, that's very, very, very bad.
Yeah, you're probably not going to make it if your blood starts going backwards.
Strunnies, paralysis and everything.
Yes.
And then your arteries are what the little red veins are.
All the redness.
That's pushing oxygenated blood to where it's needed.
And then your circulatory system takes care of the rest.
It's really quite fascinating.
You could also talk about the heart.
If you like.
Today, thank you for signing up.
Oh, you've got a banding of Isaac.
This, what's that, X?
The fucking laser one.
That's a...
Sass and frizz.
That's swine up.
You guys really Pokemon and video game pictures.
That's quite cool.
Thank you for signing up.
Your feet are beautiful.
Don't worry.
Theans, yeah.
You like seeing the deoxygenated blood pumping through these veins?
I can't wait for you to play Binding of Isaac.
November, I'm just warning you all right now.
November is when Binding of Isaac's 10-year anniversary is
and Molly Player is unlocked.
I am not going to be off that from...
You can see my hands in the shadow.
I am instructing you.
I am not going to be off that game for a very long time.
Okay?
Do you understand?
Refling.
And then you all say I understand.
Mame in unison.
Okay?
We're going to be playing multiplayer Isaac all day long.
Multiple days.
Am I even...
Am I even commit to a week and alienate more people with my Binding of Isaac?
Just so you understand.
But thank you all for signing off.
I understand.
I understand, Mame.
Yes.
Good reflings.
You will be rewarded for your...
Sorry, I didn't realize how much my shadow was casting over.
You will be rewarded.
Wait, if you can see my shadow...
No, we'll do that in a membership.
That was a very bad idea.
That was a terrible idea.
I don't want any of your little ears cleaned.
Let me pick up this Q-tip or this ear cleaner.
Let me just pick up this ear cleaner.
I understand.
Right, over here you go.
Just need to hold it like a bit.
Oh, I dropped it.
It's not very good.
It's actually quite hard to utilize this.
Put it...
There we go.
Right, you ready for some ear cleaning?
Oh, poor you.
See, if you get trapped water in your ear, don't worry too much.
Your ear can expel it at a later time.
Some people actually find that expelling of the water in your ear quite...
Oh wait, you can't even see me touch the thing.
This is...
Right, I'm going to do a basic 101.
Sorry, I'm a whisper.
I need a whisper.
I'm getting too passionate.
I'm going to show you a basic 101 for any ASMR artist that's watching right now.
Okay?
And I know this is very hypocritical because I've just bashed the ear about...
I'm going to teach you this right now live.
Okay?
You see this ear?
Inside this ear?
This black section?
This is what you don't do, okay?
This is what you don't do.
No ASMRs.
You go around the microphone.
Around gently, okay?
Don't ever touch this bit here.
That's the microphone, okay?
But go around the ear.
Gentle strokes.
Gentle, gentle, gentle, gentle, okay?
That's all you need.
Just gentle movements.
Gentle, gentle.
Okay?
There, 101 ASMR.
That's all you need to know.
This, I'm going to try and avoid doing with the toe.
Just around the ear.
You don't need to go inside.
No, no, no, no.
I know.
I know you guys like to rush into it, okay?
Why are you covered in band-aids?
I caught myself making food.
I hurt myself on my fingy.
So I have to put a band-aid on.
I'm a bit of, which is known as a clutch.
Thank you.
I had nothing.
I drank my karma.
The ceremony, or Bubba the Great.
I appreciate it.
Wait.
Does that mean you were making food with your foot?
No, this, I got all my toes done at the same time.
But this part, so when you get your toes done,
they take clippers and they take this like push thing.
They like pushed all my, like, toe skin back and stuff.
But this section on this toe, she has cut,
I was actually kind of sore touching that.
I'm not even going to lie,
she cut and sliced into it as she was cutting my toenail.
And it's quite sore and I'm not really sure what to do.
I've not really experienced such a problem before,
but we will, we'll be fine.
I think we'll be okay.
Thank you, Star Killer, for becoming a member.
Do you guys want me to flip you instead?
Wait a minute, I got a freaking tiny...
Seems like you forgot her pronounce my name from yesterday.
Spain-ee, lol.
Spain-ee, that's what I said.
Anyway, I'm off to work, see you later and congrats on monetization.
Thank you for the tip and yes, thank you.
Spain-ee, you could literally hear me like be scared to say it
because I say it wrong all the time.
Starny, do you have a stethoscope?
No, I don't.
That would be quite the prop for ASMR, honestly,
having a stethoscope.
You push back the cuticle, the nail bit cleaner,
but the actual tool lining is not a cuticle.
You should probably get it right, Muckers.
This is great, but I have class now.
Okay, enjoy class.
Get educated, get educated, get educated, get through will.
Epsom salt foot bath, yeah.
I think I'd make just something like that,
because it's a wee bit sore.
I heard someone say use it for heartbeat ASMR.
Oh, would that even work?
I don't know, we tried.
I wouldn't mind buying that prop.
I will buy that prop with my membership money.
Thank you, wonderful members.
I hope we're full of heels, yeah.
I think we'll be fine, right?
Sorry, let me look at the Q and A questions on marshmallow.
Congrats on the membership.
You're the goodest girl around.
What is your favourite meal to eat?
Savery, something savory.
Hello, will Patreon subs get to see the membership streams on Patreon?
Nope, they are two different subscriptions.
Patreon and YouTube activity are two separate things.
So, if you're interested in seeing your girl,
your Oshidevs live, then that is more YouTube orientated.
If you're interested in the alternative content
that any member of Veiler offers, that is what is on Patreon.
Thank you for your question.
You have big feet for a woman.
Okay, wow.
I don't know what you want me to do with that.
You may sign up for basketball.
Right, sorry, let me just end the stream.
I'm going to contact NBA.
Big feet?
You think I have big feet?
Are you sure it's not perspective,
because you have nothing else to judge?
Literally, what?
Big feet is good.
Your feet are great.
Literally, everyone's been saying my feet are cute and stuff,
and then you come to me and you're like, yeah, your feet are massive.
I'm sorry, do you want me to bind them?
Like, we're in fucking China or something?
Like, back when they used to bind the lowest feet?
Is that what you want?
You want a little fucking lowest feet?
Get out of here with that shit.
I don't know anything about feet, but they're normal feet.
Yeah, I'm just like...
Like, oh, sorry, excuse me.
Oh, I see.
When I spawned in, when I spawned in,
I actually picked the foot size manually.
You know, there's a little slider bar and everything.
Banana for scale.
I don't even have bananas.
Oh, do you want my stoop waffle that I ate yesterday for scale?
There, there's your scale.
Your stoop waffle.
Your fear.
Thank you.
No sense of permanence.
I'm just going to assume you're a talking pair of feet, honestly.
Who said that?
Who?
I don't know.
What feet size are you?
I actually don't know.
I've not bought...
I bought...
When did I buy a new pair of shoes?
I completely forgot.
I had to get measured for them actually when I got a new pair of shoes
because I didn't know what my shoe size was.
I don't know what to say here, to be honest,
but I'm glad for Shibi Dome Momaya.
She's really cute and the gap was really nice.
Sorry, Stroney.
And the year-long wait was worth it.
Aw, I'm glad to think so.
Yeah.
Some people were asking, like,
weren't you worried about, like,
everyone being disappointed after a year's wait?
And I'm like, I'm sorry,
but if you're, if you're a wifelin',
you knew what, you knew we were mean men.
You knew I was rambling.
You knew exactly what was going on.
Merci.
When are you doing your membership stream
for no particular reason?
Star Killer, thank you.
Nayudi Julie, thank you.
Swirly Lexa 6.
You have...
Thank you for signing up.
Your profile picture around me,
I could have bought a frickin' hypno thing
and put it on the floor and hypnotise people to my feet.
My feet?
They're gonna be so funny though.
I can't put it off.
Jesus.
Fuckin'...
Okay, that's a bit too hard.
We're squishing the ball.
We're going back to squishing the ball.
It's so easy to squish a ball.
Feet cam...
Feet stream Q&A.
Will you ever beat the Peeler Alligator?
I don't think so.
So when the girls started posting it for free,
I was like,
oh, I was gonna do a donut-on-reward
where I wrap my 3D weapon like a poly bag,
like a plastic bag,
hypnotising the reefing through your feet
to convince them I worshipped the feet, honestly.
Goes in a straw knee stream.
Your feet are big, good for gathering produce all day.
So, literally, I was like,
I've never seen you in my life.
And now you want to do it for free?
Yeah.
I was gonna make it a fun donut-on-reward
because I was gonna do it on 3D all night.
But I need to wrap it up to make sure it doesn't,
you know, short circuit.
What is this about being in a bag?
Might need that stream.
Hey.
Oh, reefing.
Oh, what a pee.
Peas on you.
You still can.
Wow.
3D MoMA?
That's terrible, honestly.
Oh, my, like, donut-on-plans are absolutely outrageous.
Someone says,
hi, love you.
That's all.
Love you, reefing.
Someone says, Pokemon or Digimon?
I only saw Pokemon.
I never got into Digimon.
Because wasn't the Digimon meme
that's literally, like,
this, like, cute adorable thing
ends up developing, like, an AK-47.
And, like, a galeel on one arm,
a Famous on the other.
The only big thing Strenny has
is her...
her...
her heart.
She has a really big heart.
Hearing your feet sweat
stick to the ball
reminds me of ear coughing
when the hand leaves the ear.
Oh, stop.
Wait, I think my feet are sweating
off to do your Pokemon vlog.
What does this sound like?
Oh, that's great.
Oh, you actually like it?
Thank you, Destiny, to enjoy your cave.
It sounds nice.
Pokemon vlog.
Can I do two at...
Can I do both?
Hold on.
I think I can do the Joe-Wheeled ear cupping.
Oh, sorry, I just peaked the audio.
It's a bit more difficult this way.
It sounds good.
Wait, there really are sticking to the ear.
Did you miss the Pop Rock segment
where I proved how sweaty my feet are
via Pop Rocking?
I just realized the mic is swapped.
Is it?
Oh, no.
Is it on the wrong side?
I can swap it out manually if you want.
Peaking the audio just means you're peeking.
You want to hear my heartbeat from my foot?
I don't know if I can do that.
I don't think you can hear it.
I go here 10 minutes ago.
Yeah, the start of the stream.
I may or may not have opened up Pop Rocks
and put them on the soles of my feet
to prove how sweaty my feet are.
And they popped.
No outside influence necessary.
So I have proven that I do have hyperhydrolysis.
Not that anyone needed proof.
I don't know why you would make up such an accusation
in all honesty.
Why would anyone want it?
Thank you, glacial soles.
Yeah.
Oh, tapping ASMR.
So fancy.
I get sweaty feet too, yeah.
Just as a mild warning to anyone who's listening,
if you have permanent sweaty hands and feet,
please do consider autism.
That's all, that's my note.
Can we do toe tapping ASMR?
Oh, yes.
Yes, it's actually a very common satrate
of having autism
by having permanently sweaty hands and feet.
What if you have hairy palms?
I don't actually know.
Maybe you're Italian, because aren't Italians hairy?
I am acoustic.
Oh, that explains a lot actually.
Yeah.
We have strong autism though.
Little toe tapping ASMR, that's right.
That's right.
Average VTuber will recharge thousands for this
in a donor phone.
Me, you get it for free.
I never noticed it until you actually mentioned it,
but yeah, I do have autism and sweaty hands and feet.
Yeah, it's a very common trait.
If you are...
Depending on the scale, however you want to scale,
you can do it different ways,
but if you are on the high need side of autism,
if you do toe walking only,
that is a massive indicator, a humongous indicator
that you are kind of on the upper scale
of the present needs.
Thank you, Jin Azuru channel.
And thank you, Krax.
Krax.
I used to have...
I have to use antiperspirant on my feet anytime I had,
otherwise it's blistering.
Huh, I never noticed that before,
but you're right about the sweaty feet.
Yeah.
The toe walking is too real.
Toe walking is a humongous indicator
that the child, that normally it's noticed in childhood,
you can unlearn it as you get older,
but it's a massive indicator.
I used to toe walk all the time.
Yes, it is one of the biggest giveaways
of a child's autistic,
basically, if they toe walk.
Got used to some powers for goods.
Literally, well, like, without mine,
like, I had...
I stopped at VTubers, I've been stroking my ego.
They're like, I don't know how you do it.
I don't know how you stream.
I'm like, do I tell them the truth
and the reason I can stream all the time
is because I have to?
Or am I just like, oh, I'm just really passionate.
I just really like what I get to do.
For me, it's always sitting in weird ways
that put so much pressure on my feet
that I keep getting callused feet.
I toe run, is that similar?
Toe running, maybe isn't the biggest indicator
in children, but then like,
you can start getting stimulated.
She's unstoppable.
I walked on toes as a child
and then my feet are...
Don't be shy, you can finish the rest of your sentence.
We don't bite here.
We don't bite from around these folks.
I got...
Do you remember that South Park episode about us?
This is enough toe tapping.
What else can I do?
I freaking...
I've brought this stick in.
Some people, like, wouldn't stick ASMR.
I've never particularly found it easy to record it.
So the only thing I can do really is just tapping,
like, on the ear.
Any other major indications of tism?
There's time.
I don't know.
Any other major indications of tism?
There's tons, like,
stimming with hands, lack of eye contact is a big one.
My biggest question to you,
if you're sitting here and you're like,
hold on a minute, she's starting to...
she's spitting the truth.
My biggest question, if you genuinely are like,
huh, is how different would the world look
if everyone thought like you?
How different would the world look
And before you're like,
that's not an indication,
just think about it a bit more.
Okay, just think a little bit deeper into that question.
Okay?
Anyway, gifts are messed up.
Everyone's getting tier two, one dollar
for something we really wanted, so why?
One more dollar for something we really wanted, so why?
Wait, was that because...
Oh wait, is this an old...
Sorry, this might be an old message.
Hold on.
Sorry, I'm reading...
I'm so happy to have you back.
I miss you so much.
I miss you too a lot recently.
Okay, yeah, sorry.
Those were old ones talking about the tier.
Thank you for anyone's info about the tiers.
World ends up addicted to watching VLM.
That's how we take over.
You guys thought my hypnosis was to drown you all?
No, it was to...
I don't know.
Oh my god, my feet are sometimes so dirty.
I'm gonna put your mops on to protect you
because I'm probably gonna mess up shortly.
I can get a bit of a mint.
Right, let's see where we are.
What?
You're the strongest, at least mentally,
I don't know about physically,
like me who struggled to open a can of fizzy juice
on the hand-cam stream.
Eep.
Can I buy or use Band-Aids to put on an alt-art?
This one literally has gunk on it.
I don't know what's going on with this toe,
but we'll figure it out.
Girl I've ever known.
But someone like you should never mess with infections,
get that toe-checked ace up.
Oh, Monka Ace, okay.
If you had to take painkillers, you can go to the ER,
but I know you'll never do it because you're a sweetheart,
but somebody else could sue that pedicure.
Oh no, she didn't mean it.
You should at least show them the medical papers
you get from the hospital.
Monka Ace, am I going to the hospital because of my toe?
I'll tell you what, I'll update you some Twitter after my bath.
I'll do a salt plingy and see what happens,
because salt normally makes up.
Would you be interested in playing Omega Strikers on stream?
It's a 3v3 mob-style air hockey that's free to play.
Oh my god, that sounds fun.
Omega Strikers.
Thank you, whoa, and thank you, Panopetition.
Oh my god, Omega Strikers looks so cool.
All their waifus are cute.
Isn't this free to play?
Oh no, it's Nintendo.
Oh no.
It's Nintendo.
Nintendo's so expensive.
Is it Nintendo?
Oh yeah.
Oh no, this can't be.
This can't be, it can't be Nintendo.
Why does it say Nintendo on the top now?
It's on PC.
Oh okay, it's on PC.
Right, whoa, okay, okay, it's fine, it's fine, it's fine.
If it's on PC, it can't be overcharged that much.
If anything is specifically published by Nintendo,
just know you're going to get rinsed out ours for the price.
It's absolutely ridiculous.
Wait, I can see that.
It showed up.
Panoptition.
Panoption, thank you so much for, oh my goodness,
all those gifted memberships.
Whoa, wait a minute.
Stream Elements is assigning your gifts in real time.
I can see who's been gifted your gifts.
Thank you so much.
Congrats to everyone who managed to catch that.
You do have to enable it in chat.
I'm so sorry, I can hardly say the name.
Panoptition, surely it's Panoptition.
Panoptition, thank you so much for the 20 gifted, thank you.
And congrats to everyone who caught up with their face.
It's all coming together.
Yes, you'll have to like, I think you have to talk in chat
or even if you just say a simple message like hi
and then it'll be like you could have got this, enable it.
I love you.
Will you go on a date with me?
You better come to the convention.
I'm giving everyone roses.
I think if we ever did like an actual convention,
I'd love to buy like single roses so I can give it out
and I'll be like, ha, that's right.
You have beat all the odds of a man never receiving a flower
before he is.
Hold on, let me hydrate, let me hydrate.
Well, convention where?
No, there's been no picked convention,
but I really want to try it once in my life.
I've never been to a convention before.
I've never been to like a location that has been
self-identified for nerds and dorks like us.
So it would be a very unique experience.
Wow, that is like literally real-time assigning gifted
memberships.
That's crazy.
That's so cool.
Viola Conta.
Well, the only thing is I have absolutely crippling,
traveling anxiety, which is a bit of a problem.
There's a big convention in California, I think,
and a lot of the girls would actually be able to make it
manually, I think, if we all went.
But I don't want to let the team down.
There's a lot of issues about getting on a plane.
And I get violently motion sick as well.
This is why I just want to farm with a U-reflink,
because I can't travel anywhere.
I get so sick, like I had to get a taxi.
I get a taxi to my dentist appointment.
And it's not even that far away from me.
I was violently ill.
I was like, ooh.
I was like, can I just put the window down?
And the guy's like, yeah, yeah.
He's like on his phone talking to his pal and all that.
I'm getting scared.
Oh.
I would use thank you, Nero, for becoming a member.
I can see that.
Get drunk and pass out on the plane, honestly.
I would be so high on medication.
See, the problem is I don't want to be like,
I'm definitely going to a convention,
because I have A-bomb.
And A-bomb really messes up things that happen in real life.
And I don't want to be like, oh, you should go to this convention
in Melbourne on this day at this time.
I'll be here, because I don't want anyone to spend money
to come out on the sole reason to come see me type thing.
Because if my freaking A-bomb gets in the way,
I, oh wait, I'll tell it in another stream, okay?
But I have a really freaking, it's really frustrating,
but it's quite humorous at the same time.
But yeah, you could be the one of those robots that meet up.
Yeah, that's possible.
First Mercy next round.
Do all the girls have motion sickness?
Oh no, I can still play video games.
I have like travel motion sickness.
Like a parent.
Oh wait, no.
She put those goofy goggles on her eyes.
I'm pretty sure she did.
No, you're right about Mercy.
She put those funny goggles on her eyes.
What is A-bomb?
A-bomb stands for anxiety,
because people are sick of hearing about it,
like the word anxiety.
So I just call it A-bomb as a substitute.
It's ear problems?
Oh, well I can fix your ear problems with my sweaty feet.
Oh yes, oh yes, you can hear that.
There's a little tool rubbing ASMR.
Yeah, that's right, a little rubber.
Maybe you don't see that on airport.
Oh no, yeah, we're not going to use that terminology.
I think Johnny can fix their ear problems on his Patreon.
I mean your motion sickness, sorry.
Do you take game suggestions?
I do, I have absolutely no issues.
A lot of streamers kind of don't...
No, that's not nice.
I will not generalise.
Please don't be afraid to...
Dap your bucket, thank you for becoming a member.
Please don't be afraid to, you know, ask me questions,
or game suggestions are perfectly fine with me,
I have no problems.
Is that how many people use A-bomb as a word
for being mildly introverted?
Yes, I kind of generally touch up on the subject
just because I am very thankful to be where I am
versus where I was,
but I feel like people are so tired
and burned out hearing about it and like,
oh everyone's got it.
And I'm like, yeah, I wonder everyone's got it.
Have you seen society today?
We live in a society, I wonder everyone's got it.
Anyway, we can do that.
I can talk about that in another stream.
This stream is supposed to be me celebrating monetisation
and yet again I'm talking about
how we need the downfall of society.
It's terrible.
It's shocking.
I've got his DEMPA in here,
no way DEMPA is in here staring at my toes right now.
Oh, gorgeous.
Hi DEMPA, I have no idea what size my feet are.
I bought like new shoes last year
and they had to measure them
and I already forgot my shoes aren't in this room.
Sorry DEMPA, I had to be this way.
I literally am, I had to be this way.
Yeah DEMPA, you should do foot cam ASMR with me.
You want to come over?
I feel like you would have smaller toes than me.
I've never had a pedicure before.
Oh, well if you ever get one,
just make sure they don't mess up your toe by the way
because mine's an agony.
You definitely need to be careful with that.
Here's my beefling heart.
The world is, there's no surprise.
I have a broken pinky toe,
can you like spread your little,
look at my pinky toe, it's a little dance.
I don't want someone to touch my feet.
Getting a massage is very unique sensation.
Very, very unique sensation.
DEMPA, I've got a strange feeling somewhere.
Poor DEMPA's pinky toe.
Are there any game genres you want to avoid?
I don't like, oh this is going to be controversial.
I might filter some people with this one.
The reason, I do not like games like Resident Evil
where you give me ammunition,
but it does not perish the enemy.
Do not give me enemies that cannot be perished.
What is the point in having an ammunition resource management section
if it does not perish the big bad enemy?
Please do not suggest these kinds of games.
It will turn into a rage stream real quick
and I will become so scots you will not actually be able to understand them.
I'm sorry, but do not give me ammunition if it does not perish then.
Simple as.
I mean, that's fair.
Preach.
Did you put hydrogen peroxide on it?
No, I'm going to take a bath.
I'm going to take this off and go for a bath
and do salt in the bath.
You mean like that 30 bullets to kill that one enemy?
Yeah.
I'm sure the Resident Evil games are good.
However, I have fantastic news.
I have five gen mates that are more than likely to play that kind of genre.
I've never played Resident Evil.
I watched my dad play Resident Evil
and it started off in Africa,
but he couldn't even get through it
and we were both watching it and we were like,
well, I was watching him play it
and both of us were looking at each other like,
what is this?
He couldn't get through it.
I couldn't get through it.
Oh, Res Fat.
Yeah, it was like set in Africa or something.
It was like super hot Savannah type thing.
And both of us were just staring at each other like,
this is the biggest piece that we've ever bought.
Because normally we play games together,
share games together type thing.
You watch your dad play the second worst one.
Oh, well, there you go.
Literally, I think we've got 20 minutes into it
and both of us were looking at each other like,
yeah, that game's going back.
We're going to hand it in for a different game.
Is there something you've always wanted to try
that you've made for 100% games that you've never wanted to try?
I've wanted to play Civ 6.
I have done one run on it
and I enjoyed it, but I was very dumb.
I don't want to play Baldur's Gate.
I definitely want to try that for the first time.
But I think it will be a patience testing stream
because I get worried about playing a game for the first time.
Five and six are some of the best solve ones, regardless.
Wow, feet for free.
Congrats on monetization.
Ding!
Let's just make sure I didn't lose anything.
Right, I think I won.
This one says, I think your feet are very beautiful and hot.
Thanks. Do you have my toes?
I got my toes done.
Look at that step piece.
Look at that side profile on the toe spread.
Can I just get a zoom in and appreciation
for the side profile of the toe spread?
Yeah.
I mean, look at that.
You already know. You're welcome.
Yeah, you're welcome. You owe me one membership.
You're welcome.
The new Baldur's Gate?
Yeah, I've never played the Baldur's Gate, apparently.
Yeah, someone says it's cool, but apparently it's cool.
Delicious.
You played any RTS?
Starcraft?
No, my dad played it.
Age of Empires? No.
Civ 6 is a dumpster fire.
Is that actually?
Didn't they not announce there's a new Civ 6 border?
Yeah, a new Civ coming out.
Long toes.
Wait, they actually have long toes.
Stop. Do I have long toes?
There you go. I'm going to start again.
Hold on. I'm going to get that really right.
Hold on.
I don't know.
I feel like I have the toe...
Because you can have...
Some people have toes that...
Oh, wait. Sorry. You can't see any of them.
Hold on. Let's try it again.
Some people have toes where they are all the same size.
They are all the same length.
They come across like that.
Mainly the...
That shape?
I don't know if that makes any sense.
You feel cute.
Your toes are cute.
I'm going to start getting a complex about my freaking toes.
You don't...
Right. How long are my toes?
We'll do it in inches because you're all American.
You said 2.5 inches is...
Wait, hold on.
I'm trying to show you and do it at the same time.
Where is 2.5?
Where...
I am...
My index toe is just bigger than an inch.
Up there.
Sorry. I just hit the mic.
Oh, you're not American.
I'm sorry.
Hold on.
Okay.
Roughly...
3 centimeter toe.
I got 3 centimeter toe.
I am offended.
Long toe equals more than joy.
Well, fuck is an inch.
3 of these, baby.
Measure the entire foot.
Oh, no.
But then you will know that I've got big feet.
My foot's bigger than the ruler.
If the ruler goes there, it's like way bigger.
If this ruler is 15 centimeters...
Wait, hold on.
Let me put it as a thing.
Okay. Put it on my heel.
And it's there on my toe.
So I'm like 16 centimeter feet.
Yeah.
Sorry. That was like the most known way to do it.
But I did it.
Big feet are good.
I'm glad you like them.
But you have not big feet.
The mic is low.
I don't know.
I might have...
I genuinely thought I was like average on everything.
But then when I did the sweet-eating cam,
and everyone saw my hands,
they were like,
oh, your hands are so small.
But when we started measuring it together,
I was like, oh, okay.
Imagine if this is popped right now,
because I'm a sweetie.
Can you measure how wide you can spread your big toe?
And the one next to...
Wait, how wide?
I don't know.
Like, because you could...
Like this?
Is that what you wanted?
Hold on.
Okay.
Thank you, Snowberry sweetie.
Like that?
Or do you mean like the actual width?
I don't know.
It depends.
It has to be malleable.
This is course measurement.
Like it has to be...
Because I can grip stuff like...
Hold on.
Let me just...
Try moving it a little bit.
There you go.
Just pop it there.
Good boy.
Tap.
Headpats.
This.
It depends,
because like that is...
You know.
I can put it in between my toes.
In the culture,
she would have nice grippers
down her renders and chat.
I guess your feet are small,
but it makes your toes
really long and compact.
No!
I'm going to get
a freaking complex after this dream.
I just thought my feet
were really normal.
Oh, my cat's meowing.
Did you hear him?
Do you want in?
Did you hear that?
Hold on.
Let me get him.
Baby boy.
You want in?
Vigo.
You can't just...
Oh.
Gimli.
Gimli,
do you want to come on stream?
She's so confused right now.
She's like,
what are you doing?
Gimli, come here.
Gimli,
come right here.
Come right here.
Show the people
how adorable you are.
No, that's the wrong way.
Gimli, what's this?
Gimli.
Yes.
Okay,
just gently don't knock
over the webcam
or I'll cry.
Gimli.
Don't knock over it.
Right.
Out.
You're going to knock over the webcam.
Gimli.
I'm sure.
I've only got 10 more minutes.
I'll be out in a minute, Gimli.
You can't go.
Give me 10 minutes,
Gimli.
Just 10 minutes is all I need.
Sorry.
My tree was sweet to hear that.
Mommy Gimli.
She was so going to knock over
that webcam,
so I was like,
get out, Gimli.
I can tell.
Oh.
Oh, I've done it now.
I haven't off.
Gimli, 10 minutes.
And I'm out.
Stop it.
Your dog is very cute.
Thank you.
I've been in...
I've certified for eight years
for your perfect.
Thank you.
Literally,
I shouldn't have brought her in
because now she's going to
want the attention.
And I was like,
I'm not finished.
Give me 10 minutes, girls.
10 minutes of getting
screamed at by a cat.
Literally,
a cat does not understand
the feed type.
She doesn't have a cat.
She has 10 doves.
And that was my Gimli.
I thought it was my baby boy,
Vigo.
Thank you very much.
Votams.
And thank you for Rono.
I appreciate the gifts
and membership.
I could...
Cats and the Feet.
Yes.
I picked up.
Thank you.
Caleb Harris as well.
I adopted Vigo
and Gimli.
And their starting situations
are actually really sad,
but it's a really happy ending.
So I
I messaged a shelter
and I was like,
hey,
I work from home.
I would love to
open up my home
to two cats
that cannot be separated.
If you didn't know
for adoption agencies
and all that kind of thing,
it's really hard
to be home doubles
that are inseparable.
So I messaged them
and they came back
and they were like,
we have these two ruffians.
They have come from
an hoarder's home,
which makes them un...
They cannot be
with any other animal,
but each other.
So I went
and visited them
and they were these
poor, scaredy cats.
They genuinely were
so terrified of any humans.
Thank you, yummy,
for the memba.
Thank you for just like
remembering as well
for the correct tier.
I do apologize
about messing up that tier.
Yes, they're a bonded pair
and they can't be separated.
But I just want to say
the universe works
in mysterious ways.
Sorry, I know I'm supposed
to be doing ASMR,
but I'm just trying
to call them right now
without the mic on the floor.
The world will work
in mysterious ways.
Now I do not believe
in supporting certain
cat breeds,
which are bad for their health.
An example of that
is the munchkin breed.
Vigo is mixed tabby
and munchkin breed.
The universe
will fight
and the universe
will find ways
to laugh in your face.
Because I am a big believer
and like completely
no longer breeding them
and not letting them
be a genetic line
any further
because it's so bad
for their health.
San Baroli,
thank you very much.
And then the universe
laughed in my face
and said,
guess what?
Your baby boy
is a half-foot
and I'm like,
okay.
Both of them,
thank you for the upgrade.
So yeah,
if you ever think
the universe doesn't
have a little joke for you,
oh, I assure you,
the universe is going to,
it's got a joke for you.
Yeah, like pugs,
yes, I am a bit of a
please don't support,
but this was just me,
like Scottish fold cats.
As adorable as they look,
absolutely not.
Hairless cats,
A lot of people
will say,
but I can look after them.
It's not about you looking after them.
It's about the general population
looking after them.
Does the general population
going to do all these steps
about looking after their cat
and the hairless ones
getting out of bath
and removing the dirt cells
because it's not got
freaking fur?
No, it's not.
Think of the bigger picture.
It's selfish.
Anyway,
don't get me started
on animal breeding
because a lot of it
is just absolutely insane.
I'm waiting until you get started
and learn about
what pedigree dogs are.
Pedigree dogs are just certified.
You'll literally get a certificate
saying, yes, this dog
has been produced via
freaking insane amounts of
zest.
And it was like,
why is pedigree even a thing?
Get a mutt.
Muts are the healthiest kind of dog
you can even get.
Ah, and mixed breed cats,
they're the healthiest kind
you can get.
Don't support the little munchkins
that have freaking stilts for legs.
It's actually so freaking sad.
And a canny,
oh, oh, I could really start
fucking beating my back.
Right, can, can, can, can, can.
Anyway, yeah,
the universe will always
have a joke for you.
So, yeah,
I despise munchkins.
I don't,
for the, for the kindness
of the poor cat,
they shouldn't be a thing.
And then the universe said,
oh, by the way,
Vigo is a half mix
of Tabby and munchkin.
And yeah,
he has saucer eyeballs.
I should actually post
a picture of my baby
but yeah,
Vigo has saucer eyeballs.
He's so adorable.
And the universe won
after that.
Hey,
do you do rabble and
dress streams where you
just go down a bunch of
rabbit holes?
Oh, absolutely.
I did it in my
Skyrim one.
I started talking about
the needy streamer
overload ending
where she becomes a god
and starts a new
religion type thing
or like,
starts a new society.
And like,
I started talking
about conspiracy theories
and stuff,
but I don't like going too
deep into it
because I know it like
really just like
people didn't like it.
So I was like,
okay,
I will maybe do it too much
and so does me.
My mom used to read
Labrador's
but regarding cats,
McTess, yeah.
Vigo is just a small rock.
Every scrawny rage
makes me a lover
even more awe.
Vigo,
yeah,
my cat sings Vigo after
the guy,
did you know
and darted the rings
in the scene
where he kicks the helmet,
he was screaming for real.
Do you want to know
why he screamed out
for real like that?
Because
because he actually
booked his poop.
And yeah,
and yes,
did you name
your cats
after the Lord of the Rings?
Of course I named my cats
after the Lord of the Rings.
Well,
would I name them
freaking Bill and Ben,
the flower pot men?
No,
I wouldn't.
So yeah,
my baby boy,
my baby girl.
And yes,
I gave
Gimli,
well yeah,
I gave Gimli a boy's name
technically.
But Gimli's got
ginger on her butt.
So,
Gimli,
my homie now.
Yeah,
yeah,
name them,
Bill and Ben,
the flower pot men,
honestly.
Holy crap,
you just maybe remember
Bill and Ben.
I remember Bill and Ben.
JJ,
you've got a picture of me.
Thank you for the membership,
JJ.
I appreciate it.
Just for all members
who are watching,
the membership stream
start next week,
but I promise you,
I will throw you into
the thick of it
and we'll
have a lot of fun from there.
We'll take it from there
because this week
is kind of locked
in a little bit.
We do have a collab
again
with me
and all my girls.
You are
an adorable girl.
We love it.
Yes.
What's next?
Was it a gym?
Cute.
Yeah,
I'm not going to get
any more
putters
after Vigo
and
Gimli.
I think
I will probably
have the biggest
mental breakdown
of my life
once they pass.
Thankfully,
I have them very young.
They,
I think they're
three years old.
Unfortunately,
due to the hoarder situation,
they actually don't know
what age
my baby boy and baby girl are.
Like,
I was trying to get
as much information
that they had,
but they were just very honest
and said,
like, look,
we don't,
we don't actually
have information
on these babies.
Strani,
do you know
if you get a cut
of YouTube Premium membership
watchers?
I absolutely do.
If you pay for YouTube,
oh, it used to be called
YouTube Red,
but if you do
YouTube Premium,
forever,
however long you watch it,
like, I get a percentage.
So say you 100%
watched me.
I get 100%
of what you
generate
for content creators.
Does that make sense?
It's the only percentage
base to the best they can.
I've noticed my
favorite troopers dabble
in theories.
Must be one of those jokes
from the universe.
Honestly, the universe
is a little funny joke for you.
Like, please,
if you're ever, like,
thinking,
oh, there's nothing
interesting's gonna happen
in my life,
I assure you,
the universe is cooking something.
Because I,
I am the biggest,
like,
don't support,
pugs,
don't support
French Bulldogs,
like,
don't support
munchkin cats,
don't do this or that.
And then the universe goes,
oh, by the way,
here's a half munchkin.
I'm like,
oh, okay,
I see how it is.
This squishy thing
is kind of hypnotic.
Yeah, you can, like,
see the balls move around in it.
It's just quite nice.
I quite like it.
It's, like,
really therapeutic
to, like,
squish down into it,
honestly.
I'm not being,
like, I genuinely
wholeheartedly mean it.
Like, it feels very nice
to, like, squish something
under my feet.
Got to go.
Have fun with the rest
of the game.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
Yes, please don't worry.
Can you go?
I'm going to redirect
into the sheebie.
Actually,
is she up right now?
Hold on.
I'm leaning over.
She's live right now
with another crab's treasure.
Oh, yeah.
Apparently,
the music in that game
is, like, so good.
But it's a Dark Souls crab.
I thought it was, like,
a fun little crab game.
I was going to play it
and someone said it was, like,
it's like Dark Souls
and I'm like, bro,
if I can't,
if I can't tag in
the reflins to help me,
then that game,
there's a fight.
I will most likely do
a Talking Stream membership
one for next week,
just because there's
so many marshmallows
I can't really say,
but we can see
in another time.
But yeah,
I hope you enjoy this
role-play, role-play,
it's not even role-play.
Literally, it wasn't even
ASMR.
I'm talking to you
at normal levels.
I normally do it for streams,
so it's all fake.
It's a Souls crab game,
honestly.
Adjust the ears, boy.
Thanks for the stream, Sonny.
It's what's Sonny.
Strawny.
Thank you, not Alessandro,
for the two.
I appreciate it.
I really hope
I've managed to say
everyone's names.
Thank you so much
for your patience as well
as I completely messed
that stream up
and wholeheartedly
just, like,
yapping in tone.
That's all we're doing here.
Best stream I had
feet and a kitty.
What more could I ask for?
Yeah, that was gimme.
Love this.
Thank you, Strawny.
Thank you, my stream.
Thank you so much, yes.
I will go now,
but thank you so much
to everyone who
membershiped
and gifted
and download, etc.
The membership streams
start next week
because this week's schedule
had already kind of been
locked in
and I didn't actually know
what I was going to do
with the monetization.
Thank you, Dufus.
Dufedoff
for the member.
And again,
if you can't membership,
please do not worry.
I always have
free streams coming.
I always have free content
coming out.
You just need to
give me a little patience.
But the dust
is definitely starting
to settle from debut,
which means I can, like,
fully focus on
everything I want to do.
Legs!
Thank you for the five gifts.
I appreciate it.
Congrats on those
who caught it
with your face.
And all the music.
Thank you very much.
That was very kind of you.
But yes, the dust
is starting to settle,
which is good
because it means
I can start focusing
on the free content
I want to do
and all the stuff
I want to
think about.
But yes,
please say hi to Shipee
for me.
I will type a few
messages in her chat
and then I am going
to go soak
this little tub
and see what happens.
Yeah,
my purr tub
isn't doing
so good.
But we'll see.
We'll see.
Okay.
Right.
Bye-bye for now,
reeflings.
I would do
my little kissy,
but this is the
microphone.
Can I kiss you
with my tub?
Right.
This is
my kisses.
Mmm.
Bye-bye, reeflings.
Bye-bye.
Look,
I'm waving you goodbye.
Bye-bye.
Oh,
this is like really hard
and like doing on an axis here.
Bye-bye.
Actually,
I can shake this
foot really fast.
Bye-bye.
Okay.
Bye-bye, reeflings.
I'm going to
say hi to Shipee.
Okay.
Bye-bye.
reeflings.
Be good.
Bye-bye.