I'm trying my ankle.
Wah.
It's up.
I think it's up.
I've just built this freaking game and the music.
Oh my gosh.
Are you there?
Hopefully I'm live.
I know I've started like nine minutes early,
but I'm just sitting here and I'm like,
I don't want to wait the nine minutes
for when I'm supposed to start my stream time.
I just want to start now.
So I'm starting now.
I just need to make sure I can see I'm live
and then I can close my stream.
Okay, yeah, it says I'm live.
I'm so sorry I've been boozled.
Yes, I put in the wrong day.
I put in the wrong hour.
Shocking behavior.
I have the most kind of like saddest start
to a stream so far.
I got on Marshmallow, but sadly due to text,
I cannot see what the tone is behind
and I've read the Marshmallow as like a veiled threat
or something, but I just want to say
to the person who sent me a cat picture link,
like an actual picture of a cat.
I don't know how to break this to you.
I got my payloads in March after a very rough time
where I realized that life was too short.
I've not owned a pet, okay, since then
and my payloads came into my life in March.
So please, like, I don't know if it was like
a weird threat thing going on
and I know for literally everyone else,
this makes no sense.
But I can't read tone in a text
and it looked like a weird veiled threat
and I just like, I got my payloads in March.
And yeah, I don't know what to tell you.
Like I've visited America as a child at nine years old.
I don't live in America.
I don't know what's going on.
So you identified yourself as not a reefling.
So if it's all good, I'm just gonna, you know,
stream here with my reeflings and we're gonna do our thing.
Hopefully it wasn't actually a threat,
but if it was, then hey-ho, I've addressed it
and I've negated what your evidence was purely
on the basis that I got Gimli and Vigo in March
and that's when I got my payloads.
So yeah, I apologize for that
making absolutely no sense to literally everyone else,
but good morning, good evening, and good afternoon.
It is a wild ride.
You play two games of Assassin's Creed Brotherhood.
I'm literally not even on my third game stream.
I've never done a second game stream variation.
And it's like, oh, I don't think it's a threat,
but at the same time, my brain's telling me
it's a veiled threat, so I'm just gonna address it that way.
If you didn't mean it, sure, but as I said,
I don't live in America.
I have two cats that I got in March.
They were adopted and yeah, I don't know what else
to tell you, bro.
I'd just appreciate if you left me alone
and I'll just be having fun with my reeflings.
So thanks.
Don't do that again.
Yes, anyway, now that we've got that part over, Jesus.
A little bit of a restless sleep.
May or may not have had diarrhea
because I can't tell context.
However, we're gonna be playing a game
called Needy Streamer Overload.
I just opened it up and it gave me a kind of Windows XP thing.
Windows Vista was like before me.
I'm like, oh, 99% sure.
Wait, Windows Vista.
Like, I don't think I even had, like, wait, when, when,
wait, this is Windows Vista, no, I think Windows Vista
when released it.
Oh, would my dad have had that on the console?
Well, let's give it a Windows Vista or Windows 98.
I don't know what version of Windows, okay?
So we're gonna have a shot at this game.
I don't know what to expect.
Now, a few reflings told me yesterday that for a factoid,
this game apparently has over 500 different endings
or I made that number up
because someone said the game had a ton of endings.
Now, this is gonna be a shorter stream today,
but the good news with it being a shorter stream
is I might be able to release my first ASMR,
like 1K thank you audio, like today,
but I need to go edit it, but it's gonna be, like, fun
and it's clean, it's, like, clean ASMR.
Like, it's literally me just rambling
and, like, tapping away on stuff
and all that kind of thing, so it's cute.
Oh, just, yeah, just a short nine hour stream today.
I'm sure you can strap in the lads and lasses,
don't you worry.
Yeah, only seven are, yeah, easy peasy lemme squeeze there.
I was actually thinking Skyrim,
I've put down Skyrim as two, 12 back to back.
I don't know if I should purposely wake up
right before stream for the Skyrim
and then make a second room
and then we'll do, like, 12 hours
and then in the second room another four hours
and then I think the following day, that 12 hour stream,
I can complete the full achievements.
I'm not 100% sure.
I do have a honey tea with me, though,
so hopefully you have some water, some snackies.
And all that jazz.
But, yes, next week our endurance stream
is going to be Skyrim
and we're also doing an endurance runescape,
old school runescape.
I will tell you what world to be in.
I am going to start on a fresh account.
I am going to buy premium in runescape
but we'll get to that when we get to that, you know what I mean?
So let's stream into it.
Yeah, I'm a bit of a fiend for streaming.
I really enjoy it.
Like, some people, like, due to their circumstances,
like, they can't stream every day
or they find it a bit harder,
like, and mentally it takes its toll.
Me?
Like, I'm about to freaking try out this crazy game
for the first time.
I don't know much about it.
Apparently you can do implied scenes in it,
so I'm like, all right, all right, here we go, here we go.
So I'm interested.
I don't know if it should just get straight into it.
You guys can hear it, it's not too loud.
I was worried about the music being too loud.
I can almost turn it off on my end, but yeah.
Yeah, some streamers, like, kinda just do it circumstances
but I just seem to have the perfect mesh
of, like, missing brain cells here,
a bit of a smooth brain here,
a bit more of a complex surface area
at the section of my brain.
Music's actually a bit quiet, right?
Okay, it's just loud in my headset.
Okay.
I've turned off a bit.
I'm a wee bit close to my mic, but, right.
Oh, it's got a little love heart.
See that, so Mersey was theorized that her heart,
right, this is what I theorized when Mersey thingied.
Mersey's pupils are normal
before her first experience as a yandere occurred
and then her pupils broke
and she can no longer love appropriately.
Like, the concept doesn't exist for her.
If you look back in Amy's lore video,
you'll notice she, her pupils are normal
until she picks up that book.
They have little small details.
Obviously my pupils have always been
a little cuddle fishes.
She's broken.
I started to think that if someone is a beacher
within the entire brain, it's just soup.
Honestly, I would happily join the study data group thing.
You can hook me up because I can prove that I'm pretty dumb.
Like, yeah.
I didn't think to pay attention.
No, there's like little small details
like in everyone's lore.
Like, you know,
AC has scars from the polar bear that she destroyed
and then she raised Feral
and like kind of like all kind of plays back into it.
Like for AC's audio work, she's actually,
hey, this is gonna sound terrible.
I'm so sorry.
This is gonna sound terrible.
In my experience, if there is ever an audio produced
where you the listener may or may not be taking,
have been taken by the band page of,
by the female performer, it always goes down really well.
And I consented AC with the idea
that she doesn't know what Bincent is.
She doesn't know what Bincent is.
So she just jumps on you basically.
No prior warning because she was raised Feral.
So it's not a thing.
Like if you're a bear, you grab what you want instantly.
You wanna eat?
Okay, let's go down to the river.
You wanna climb this tree?
Heck yeah, let's climb this tree.
So yeah, and I kind of made her like that.
I've not made her do anything like that,
but it's just kind of like a small detail
because everyone's like,
oh, this brat needs correction,
or like, oh, G-San, you can't keep up.
And it's kind of interesting to see that dynamic form
because the dynamic in my head was like,
she completely has you wrapped around her claw type thing
and she does what she wants to do, which is so terrible.
But look, this is a fun thing about like going from concept
to actually what's happening now.
Like as I said, girls, I've full control type thing going on.
My update for YouTube monetization,
my statistics have updated and we've been told,
like I can see on my YouTube that I've met the watch hour,
but if I go to apply for monetization,
it says I've only got 88 hours watch time
and I'm like, right, it's been four days.
I would like to apply for it now.
Like I don't have no idea why it's taken
so long to update, it's crazy.
I'm going to take a sipping tin of my tea
and then we'll see what this game provides.
So I am warning you, it is a shorter stream today.
However, I do think Shibi is coming on in two hours.
I think AC is having a rest day.
Shibi and me, is it a rest day for Azura?
I think Azura does double back rest days.
What kind of tea?
It's always the same tea.
But Ash, like I think it's called black tea
or English breakfast tea, either variation with honey.
For once having a tough time sleeping is a good thing.
No, Azura is an ASMR.
Oh my gosh, she's an ASMR today.
Oh, I'm so excited for Azura's ASMR.
Please give her lots of tips unironically.
Oh well, in three ways.
Monetary, your advice, and the other.
She's so nervous, but I know she's going to do perfect.
Like imagine listening, I can hear it now.
Imagine that voice going from ear to ear and her kisses.
Oh, and I hope she hugs me.
I need to, I've not told her to,
like I don't tell anyone what to do,
but if she hugs the mic, heart beat, Azura, heart beat.
Heartbeat and kisses ASMR from Azura.
Yeah, I'm there, I'm already on cloud nine,
I don't know what to tell you.
Also, I may have infected Azura and Shibi.
They said they might play Assassin's Creed Brotherhood
at a later time, because I've inspired them
and they've read my mind about playing the games.
I'm going to be fangirling so hard
if I get to watch them play Brotherhood.
But good morning, good evening, good afternoon,
or good time zone, like that one we fling said.
No better feeling than chilling your childhood game.
Bro, literally, I feel like I didn't know
Azura played that game,
because she spoke a lot of like watching anime in her 2.0.
So I was like, oh okay, like on a scale of gamer to weave,
I'd say she was weave type thing, and yeah.
We aren't real we flings, YouTube is telling on us.
Evening, let's spread the AC love.
Oh yeah, spreads my AC all over your face.
So Johnny, you've made me want to re-play Ezio.
Oh, it's so good, oh.
We are going to revisit in Octogre,
but my morning has been good,
my pants have been shat successfully.
Oh, I never got Marshmallow from a fart in the toilet, Anon.
I don't think he's here anymore,
I think we lost him in the great cryo chamber, unfortunately.
But literally, I think Amy started her stream yesterday,
and she was like, I shoulda dida dida dida,
and I shoulda dida dida this morning,
because I got a really weird Marshmallow,
and I'm like, I don't want to freaking upset
or offend anyone or anything like that.
And I'm like, I can't read context,
so my brain's like, is someone threatening me?
Ah, I don't know.
But yeah, bizarre, bizarre.
Rip to every one, pants shitted.
Honestly, it was fucking weak again,
I'm not being funny, but it was absolutely,
you know what, you know what,
it's a British word that I don't use often at all,
but I saw it in a TikTok recently.
That's Pongin, like P-O-N-G-E-D,
Pongin, Pongin, Pong, so smells.
It's such a bizarre word.
I don't say that, I'm just like, I just,
that's Rikin, we say Rikin, R-E-E-K-I-N-G.
Rikin, Pongin, oh, honestly, that sounds Dutch.
Pongin, junga, alo, yay, mooroo.
Mengen, oh yeah, Mengen, Rikin.
I say Rikin for smell, I think Mengen's like,
more disgust, but Rikin is for smell.
And British, you've never heard that, Pongin,
like when it Pongs, I wonder if it's an older word.
My gran, my gran, I think she said, oh, that's Pongin.
Although she made me laugh one time,
she calls farts Windy Pops, and I was like,
and I burst out laughing, I've never heard of any
like refer to as Windy Pops before,
and I'm like, oh, okay.
I was like, it's so polite and so British,
like if we end up getting a British fridge in too,
I'm making her say like, ooh, Windy Pops,
like in our wee English accent.
I was saying that we could get a Welsh,
or a Northern Irish, Irish, but sometimes Northern Irish
don't really wanna be referred to as British, you know,
and in which I completely respect and understand,
like let's not get into it, wait until you learn,
wait until we do the history stream
of why the Irish famine, potato famine,
wasn't actually real, thanks to the British Empire, yahoo.
It's ridiculous, but yes, if you didn't know,
a lot of Irish migrated to America,
a lot of Irish migrated to Scotland,
to different parts, to in search of working food,
which is why a lot of you are like,
I'm one eighth Scottish, I'm one eighth Irish type thing.
Heck yeah you are,
because that's how mass migration works,
so you know that one eighth Scottish in you,
that's right, I'm in you right now,
I'm in your blood supply, I'm beating around there,
I'm seeking things in your body,
because you're like one sixteenth Scots.
As a British person, a lot of things were up for.
Well England, with its sanctions on Scotland.
Please don't take the strunnies in me, oh yeah.
I thought it was meant to be the other way around,
look it works both ways here, that's all I'm saying,
look some people didn't like it, I respect that, okay?
All I'm saying, if I had some sort of sensory organ,
it would give me more of a reason to explore even more.
One fourth Scottish, let's move, actually.
What percent campfire will we tolerate?
I see the most common.
I have three percent strunnie in me, there we go.
The potato famine was not fun for Ireland.
Well wait until you learn even more about the issues.
Maybe we can do an education stream about it,
but I don't want it to be like hate,
because I assure you any English twat the day
did not have any bearing on the famine, many a minute ago.
But I don't mind doing historical education streams,
and the reason why Ireland kentatized them with Scotland
is because there was mass migration due to that,
so I don't mind a cheeky education stream once in a while.
I've actually really always enjoyed academics,
sadly the social sides of academics,
I may have failed that part, but I've always enjoyed it.
I'm actually going back to college soon,
which I'm excited to talk about.
Not now though, man's trying to run a business,
you know what I'm saying?
Well, I say that, I'm actually passing off it,
so it's everyone else's problem, but man.
But I am thinking of doing beauty school,
beauty school, but listen, hear me out,
beauty school dropout, that's a grease thing.
The reason why I'm doing beauty school
is because I want to get a certificate
to possibly open up a little, so you might not know this,
you know in salons, they have a spare room,
these rooms can be rented out for whatever you want,
and I was just thinking on the idea,
when time progresses, things do their thing,
I might have a pop up at a little ASMR shop,
but it's just a little bed in the room,
and it would just be so fun, and I love it,
because I am genuinely passionate about ASMR.
I love the stuff about it,
I've tried to research some of the psychology,
I've came up with my own theories,
not everyone agrees with my theories,
but that's because it's just what it is,
but I think it would be a lot better.
V sucky salon, right, you're done, you're done, you're done.
Honestly, the skills you've learned
running a business is worth a lot,
much more than the MBA.
Well, you see skills, but literally,
I'm at the process where I'm about to hand
everything off now, like I'm so freaking happy,
and the only thing I need to worry about is clippers,
and there's the possibility, for those of you
who have an oh-she-desk and editing skills of the girls,
I am 100% open, like once things settle,
because I know it takes a while to kind of settle
on an oh-she-desk and be like, oh yeah, shit,
yeah, I'm gonna watch her consistently.
If you have the time, and if you're an editor,
I am very open, if you wanted to be a dedicated clipper
or highlight editor for that girl,
you're welcome to email the website.
Just to tell you right now, no,
you do not get a open communication with a girl,
everything is done through IWL messages,
but yeah, if you really enjoy one of the girls
and you wanna clip them, or do highlight streams,
or funny moments type thing, and wanna get paid for it,
hit the website up, because it saves me even more time,
because right now I'm, today after the short stream,
I'm going to edit my 1K, thank you ASMR,
and then upload that, and then I'm gonna send away
a few more clips for editing, because the second guy
we've got, poor guy, I've left him on red
for like six days now, and I'm like, oops, but yeah.
I'm definitely gonna have to find a few more clippers,
I probably wanna try two more clippers, but yeah.
You don't like Vsucky, so you'd say that Vsucky blows,
honestly, shawty, shawty.
But yes, there's opportunities,
please don't think that this is a super closed off thing,
I'm happy to tell you about what the process is like
when it comes to clips, the reason why
subtitles kinda jump at you in clips,
is because that's what gets the monkey side of your brain
to like keep watching.
The editor for Mercy's recent clip,
I forgot to put credit in the blonde one,
you can edit credit in the description.
Right, I need to do that,
Mercy has a new short coming out,
and the editing style is just,
captures the ADHD perfectly,
it has insider knowledge about VTubers,
like I'm just really happy with it,
so if you can edit what Mercy's recently published clips
are like, feel free to hit the website up,
I'm needing a few more clippers.
I'm needing to get,
Sheeby needs clips very badly, I need to put up.
However,
there's like so many little notes I'm like,
so I've told the girls to cover up your
for now, like as you can see,
you can only see my deckliotage at the moment,
because I'm a bit worried about
what the heck's going on with YouTube right now.
I feel like there's still policy updates going,
but that's just me.
But right, let me finish this team,
we'll actually jump into the game,
because I have been yapping for 20 minutes,
I'm not even, oh that's ridiculous, sorry, I'm so sorry.
Goodness gravy, once I get started,
I can't even stop, 20 freaking two minutes.
That is terrible.
Are you looking for clippers?
Mm, if you look on Mercy's most recent short,
if you can do clips like that, that's pre-made stuff,
where I just send you the model and the audio,
and then you do the subtitling and all the other fancy,
like,
then yes, definitely apply.
If you mean clipping highlight sections in general,
again, I'm gonna see what happens after Gelt's stream.
Ah, okay, I finished my tea.
I came for the yapping, honestly.
Don't worry, there was two points,
I was like half yapping, but it was so fun.
Yes.
Okay, what is this game about?
Good question, I actually don't know.
So all I know is it's called Needy Streamer Overload.
I believe it is one girl,
and there's a ton of different endings
that we can potentially get,
so we're gonna check it out, see how it is.
I believe it's a click simulator,
so I can't get annoyed at the gameplay,
because this is my kind of thing,
like, nice chill, doing my thing.
Vealur, where the company competition
is actually just who's the biggest yapper, honestly.
20 minute talking, no gameplay, if you can show me.
Honestly, this game is a feature for Life Simulator.
Is it actually?
Okay, that's good, that's good.
I was gonna play YouTube Simulator,
and then I was gonna call it like, well, Vealur fail.
Okay, okay, so there's day progressions, okay?
Okay, you ready?
Welcome, day one of five.
Man, wait, no.
Got the stream account, time to log in and get ready.
Click on stream and log in with my,
thank you for the tip, Joshua Jones, 22.
Oh, there's a cat, oh my god.
Meow, meow.
Click on stream and log in with the password
angelkawaii2, log in.
Oh, wait, like angelkawaii2.
Sorry, I do things phonetically.
I see, you've logged in, this is it, we're,
this is where, oh no, everyone knows I can't read now.
Ah, it's got to fast.
We'll be together no matter what happens online,
whether I die or I get arrested or I break,
or I get stabbed or I get flamed,
or I become god or go crazy.
But Jenga, thank you for the tip as well.
That's got to happen,
the main reason I'm here for overall,
thank you for the tip.
We'll be together no matter what happens.
The internet is truly the festering cesspool of heck,
born from modern society.
But even so, I have nowhere else to turn to.
You're squidding me right now.
Doctor Resurgence, thank you for the tip.
Okay, you're awesome and I love your accent.
Thank you so much for the tip, I appreciate it.
Cause I have trouble getting out of bed in the morning.
I don't want to get out.
I don't want to get a proper job.
No, she's a need, no.
I'm scared of other people, adults pee me off
and I'm bum bum, I'm dum dum.
And I still want everyone to fawn over me.
She wants to be an idol and streamers get fawned over
and the most, over the most right now.
Oh God, everyone knows I can't read.
So that's why I want to be one.
Thanks for sizing up all my gear
and getting my streams off while you're running.
Peach and, my name's Pete.
Heck yeah, my name's Pete.
When I send you a DM,
you can sometimes fix your own reply.
When the time comes,
make sure you think long and hard what to say.
Peach and.
Peach on.
Yep, you're my Peach and cause you're so.
Oh, wait, we're the manager.
We're the manager.
I mean, you're the only,
this is the people that have been emailing the website.
That's all I'm going to say when they're like,
I want to be a talent manager and have no Thanks.
I mean, you're the only person in the world
who understands and supports me
and you're my one true love and you're also
like my producer, so fit,
oh, this is the freaking scar.
Okay, you're super smart.
No, you're super smart for naming them unlike me.
So you can gave me, you can tell me or anything and I'll do it.
Let's do this, let's do this, let's do this, let's do this,
let's do this, let's do this, let's do this, let's do this.
Oh, it's almost time.
My makeup looks good, got my wig.
Perfect.
Here we go.
Here we go, it's time for my first and go.
Wait, this is late.
Wait, this is good though.
That would not have been cheap to...
During each stream, you can delete the annoying comments and choose two coloured comments.
Super chat.
Keep your cursor in the comment section.
What?
Keeping your cursor in the comment section will slow the game down a little to make things a bit easier.
Kawaii ne.
Ohai wo gozaimasu.
Nice, cheery.
Cute.
What?
Stream as usual.
As usual.
God, you're so cute, cute.
Kawaii ne.
Alright, so we're playing Mod Simulator on Ironical.
Wait, YouTube Mod Simulator.
Choosing comments.
Weird name.
Kei Angel.
Kanjo?
Weird name.
Parish!
Array of light, illuminating the chaotic internet of today.
Bringing happiness to the nerds, floating in this electronic sea.
Can I type myself?
Wait, so she gets stressed if I miss stuff?
Oh boy, here come the nerds in the comment.
We're all here just to vibe?
So don't be mean.
We're all just here to vibe.
There's no point in starting calling each other nerds.
We're all just trying to enjoy ourselves.
A promise of future peace.
I'm a little manic and moody, but that's alright.
Don't go depression on us.
Does that mean?
I don't know if it's mean or not.
I wouldn't care.
I feel like I'm deleting all the comments.
Go get therapy.
No, right.
No, don't be mean so hard.
The internet angel has descended.
Thank you for gracing us.
Cheers.
Yeah, read it.
Oh, I can tell her to read it.
Okay, okay, okay.
Let's go.
We got a little Minecraft.
Wait, wait, wait, get out of here.
No, don't read it.
Delete it.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, delete it.
You silly sausage.
No, don't delete it.
Why?
What was that?
Or do I tailor to...
Okay, I don't...
For goodness sake.
I'm a rubbish mod, honestly.
So when are you going to show us...
See, I would leave that in because I've been like...
I've got bikini models.
I'm the terrible mod.
I feel like...
I don't mind.
If it's a way for you to get your stuff out, then sure.
And while I'm at it, I'm going to be the biggest streamer on YouTube.
That's a threat and a promise.
Oh my God, threaten us more Kangol.
Is it Kangol or K-Angel?
I feel like Kangol sounds like Kigo.
Right, group Kigo exercises replaying.
You've got my support.
Go big or go home.
So I'm going to shoot for a million.
Jesus, lady.
You've got my support.
Yeah.
K-Angel.
Kawaii Angel.
Oh, Pepega.
She literally...
An interesting newbie has appeared.
No one even freaking types newbie like that.
That's ridiculous.
Show us what you've got, baby.
Anyway, there's still a lot I have to...
Anyway, there's still a lot I have to learn.
But I'm still going to be here.
I can't wait to meet you all.
I think that's what she sounds like.
Nice to meet you.
To meet you nice.
Time for a challenge.
Thank you for greeting us.
I'm K-Angel.
Go home.
Get out of here.
Oops.
I don't think I was supposed to do it.
You get out of here.
Oh, and if you're a backseat gamer, do me a favor and stay away please.
Well, what's wrong with freaking getting your hand held?
They're games.
Nice to meet you.
Subscribbled.
The birth of a legend.
First stream complete.
At the end of the stream, I will respond to the comments you choose.
The fans love that, so...
Aren't I so kind and generous?
I guess.
Tweeter.
Hi, everyone.
Wow, this is my first...
This is my first time meeting all of you.
Oh my god.
You're an internet angel.
What did you guys think of my first meet?
I hope you're right.
Oh, I can't read that fast.
Oh my god.
Oh my god, I'm still shaking.
Did you like my performance on stream though?
So when she...
Her voice is deep here.
Kate Angel finally descended upon the world after we spent so long mulling over it.
We've got a thousand more subscribers, huh?
But that's not enough.
I want more people to fawn over me.
We're only just getting started.
I like that bunches.
Best design.
I need at least one million fans to satisfy my desperate need for approval.
That's crazy dialogue.
I wonder what dev team made this.
We got to get that.
We got to...
We got to get to that within our month.
That's the most motivation I've got.
Oh, she's done it in a month!
So let's make this month count.
Okay, we have 30 days.
We can make Kate Angel the biggest streamer in the world if we work together, right?
Yeah.
Yup.
I love you so much.
Oh my god.
I really hope we can pull this off.
We're counting on you, pizza!
We're going to make it happen.
It's her dream.
We have to make it happen.
I might break if you push me too hard,
but when that happens, we can just destroy the internet.
And anyway, I'll be counting on you tomorrow too.
Good night.
Okay, so it's a 30-day sim.
Okay, okay.
Day two.
Good morning.
It's my first morning as an official streamer.
Wait, it's already noon.
I'm just not a morning person at all.
I was a bit too slow on that.
Anyway, since we're aiming for 1 million subscribers,
we still need 9,000 more.
But first, let's start small and go for 10k first.
We'll get there in no time.
And as you know, I'm completely useless on my own.
So you need to tell me what to do every day.
I know you'll make the right...
Is this terrible of me to say?
But as a manager point of view,
it's actually super easy to direct people like this.
Just tell me what to do and I'll do it.
So I'll do everything you tell me.
Really, I have complete faith in you, pizza.
I'll follow all your orders perfectly.
And I promise I'll become the best streamer.
Literally, I feel so bad.
But this is the perfect employee.
Because if not, I think I'll break and fall apart.
Or I could break you.
I don't want to be...
Oh, fuck it, I'm fucking her.
Or I could break you myself.
Yeah, you could.
Oh my...
Wait, she reciprocates.
Oh my god.
Oh my god, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, my penis typed that on the keyboard.
I'm sorry, I couldn't...
Gum in the side.
I'm sorry.
Please don't be creeped out by a manager like that.
Right, how do I tell her?
Are we done?
Hang out.
Oh!
Okay, okay, hang out.
New idea incoming.
Sleep.
New...
I...
Medication!
Oh dear, that's not good.
Oh, she feels okay.
So I'm definitely...
Mental darkness.
Wow, okay.
Oh wait, what does that say?
Collect ideas.
Okay!
I comprehend.
To collect ideas,
I want you to search the internet
for the current Twitter trend
of a VTuber model.
Social media.
Puts her stress up.
Pre-streamer.
Vanity search.
No, don't do that.
Video streaming?
No.
What's ST?
I don't know.
Dender.
No, you don't need dender, hen.
Go follow the latest VTuber trend.
I don't care what it is,
but go do it for me, darling.
Someone I met for the first time today
told me you look like you would be
really into underground male idols.
Do I really?
The task manager will show you...
Oh, I'm learning, I'm learning.
Conspiracy theories are always so interesting to read about.
It's so funny seeing people argue about
whether they are real or absolute BS.
I never get tired of it.
Okay, okay.
You're actually...
so smart?
I don't...
idea gotten.
But you know, I feel like if you go deep enough,
you'll end up buying into it.
Sooner or later, curiosity killed the cat kind of deal.
Well, I'm fine though.
I never let that happen to me.
I'm the most rational and logical girl in the world,
and the only thing that drives me crazy is you.
Okay, if it's reciprocated love,
then I don't feel bad about being weird.
But anyway, I figured that conspiracy theories
would make for great content,
so let's start this off with a banger.
Okay, okay.
We can only stream once for the idea we get
from commands marked with an exclamation mark.
If we stream with a low level idea,
we'll be able to find another idea on the next level up.
Comprehend, yes.
Go to dust.
Is that my only choice?
I don't really want to cross her out.
Okay, it's making me go to dust.
I think I messed up your mediflicks recommendation,
because I was using your account to watch stuff.
I'm sorry, that's fine.
Wait, you can't stream...
Do you actually need to go to bed?
Is she tired already?
Do you need to sweep, little one?
Or do you need to go again?
Does she...
Do you want to do internet again?
Pre-stream alert goes up, but her stress...
It will change time tonight.
Okay, okay.
I wanted to buy myself a super comfy couch,
but if I did that, I think I would never leave it.
I think it would turn into a blob.
Go to night, and then she can stream.
So she can stream at night.
Can I want to dye my hair pink something?
I think even more people would love me if I did that.
Pink is definitely an idol hair.
Colour for VTubers is very common.
I actually didn't want pink VTuber,
but I think purple would have a pink one.
In general, let's be honest.
Right, chat and chill, all hail the internet.
I think that's it.
So this is her doing her 2.0, so we'll do that.
So, begin.
Transform!
Honestly?
I'm digging this so far.
This is already blooming out of expectation.
Out of the war.
Okay, very, very, very.
Stream speed as usual.
Hi cuties!
I'm the internet angel.
I kind of sound like...
What the heck, the rabbit from Sonic Heroes?
Why does she always say bless or whatever?
Clearly because she's...
You're blessed to have her in our life.
You're so quiet. You're super cute.
Feeling a bit blue so I'll be lurking?
Lurk away.
More than welcome.
Hopefully feel a bit better soon.
I love the internet because all of the lovely people
are willing to listen to you alone
and other intentional...
Parish!
Why, angel?
Thank you for your super chat.
I love you.
I keep reading that.
It's Kigo.
I'm not even gonna pretend otherwise.
My biggest fear is sentiment.
I can imagine living a life not being needed by anyone.
No, this is too real.
Oh no, we're about to put on Mr. Kitty.
As the hours pass on, you'll live to know.
She sure is bold for a new streamer.
Did I need to speed this up?
Uh-huh.
I love you guys for hearing me out.
I'll keep working my hearts for all of you.
She says she loves me.
She loves me?
I don't know about the rest of you,
but your face sure is cute.
Okay.
Well, I love it.
This is the true mod experience.
Honestly.
Can I speed this up?
No, I can.
I guess.
No takebacks now.
Chin hands.
Oh, this is chin hands?
This pose?
I got Mercy have chin hands toggle.
Because it's all over if you get bored of me.
And I don't want to die yet.
Let's go.
I'm gonna need more so quickly if I'm done.
I didn't bring any more.
Please don't die.
Oh no.
I'm bored.
Why would you super tip I'm bored?
Let's have a look see.
Why Angel?
I kind of messed up the super chats, but.
I've always been an Angel since I was born.
Because I'm just too kawaii.
Please don't die.
People die.
And whether I live or die is all up to my bet.
Whoa, steady on.
Oh well.
What a stream.
Thanks to everyone who came along to stream today.
Sorry I haven't spent all of my plays.
I'm so new to this.
Love you all.
I never caught on days when Kegel streams.
I'm so good.
I can't read it.
Right.
Oh.
Dear P-chan.
This is Saito from Little Bet Creations.
As per our last phone call,
your rent is still outstanding and you will have to pay.
You have until the 10th to pay for-
Oh my god, I'm going to get kicked out.
Please forward your payment to the account details below
and contact me when you've done so with regards.
Please reply to this email with any concerns.
I'm sorry.
What is this?
Does this mean we need to pay all our rent by day 10?
We're broke as heck.
We need to be able to monetize our content ASAP.
We need to get more than 10k followers first.
Easy peasy for us.
Let's go.
Yes, yes, yes.
Oh my god, you're such a hard worker.
What the heck is that though?
That little bear thing.
Right.
I need you to-
Your stress is really high.
How do I de-stress you?
Hang out.
Play game.
Stress goes down by five-
No, that's number four.
That's four.
Affection goes up between us.
I don't want her to have to-
What's this?
Spend time together.
Her affection goes up and her stress goes down by six units though.
I think we'll do that.
No, she needs-
Wait.
Wait, hold on.
It says dot, dot, dot.
Love is in the air.
Stress goes down significantly but mental darkness-
Mental darkness goes down.
Affection goes up and stress goes down.
This is a win-win.
This is the most po-
This is the best thing to make her feel better.
Sorry, but...
Is that that game where it's like 120 levels?
I promised to never portray you guys, so please keep on showing me all your love.
Oh!
Noory.
Noory Nelly.
What taking?
No, what?
This shows how much pressure I'm feeling.
I might start acting weird if I get too high, so watch out.
I may even become more scared of the internet by the day.
This displays how much I love you.
I'd be sad if I don't love you enough, but if I love you too much,
it might be hard to handle to try and strike a good balance.
This lets you know how I'm doing mentally.
How well I cope with reality will change.
Depending on the numbers, it might have a bigger influence over my future,
rather than in your future.
Show me one hater who bothers to wear clothes that fit them properly.
That's the most bizarre thing I've ever read.
We're definitely gonna have to research tomorrow.
We'll do conspiracies.
Why are you here now?
Transform!
Time for her voice to go like this.
Oh, way up there.
Men here have each other similar?
Is that how it goes?
I know there's lots of end-ends, but...
Thank you, ladies.
It's okay, you two.
We're a fixer who controls them.
The fixer who controls them?
What does that even mean?
First time here.
Oh, yeah.
Is that streaming on TV?
Oh, wait. No, sorry.
I'm reading parts in the voice.
I'm not supposed to.
Do you think I can conspiracy theories?
I do.
Have I read about them?
But why?
Young nerds love these.
That's American viewer-spotted.
Annihilate this man.
Is this supposed to go faster than this?
Oh, I love conspiracy theories.
I'm excited.
Yes.
Okay.
Do you like conspiracy?
So, my company...
I can...
Please go again.
Oh, that's going too fast.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Today, I'll be talking about their culture in conspiracy theories.
Like, the fricking...
Is it the ET game that's currently...
dug into a ditch
and it's like 40,000 worth of games or something?
Some people say that...
They develop organically.
Oh, this is going too fast.
They wanted to do the Japanese masses
into nerds to numb them.
Sounds wacky.
But what if it did happen?
I'm not a nerd.
I think we'll do a nicer super chat.
I think we could do a super chat
that makes her happier than that.
But then people get mad if you don't read them out.
Everyone watching now would be dancing
to the tune of three minds on...
Feels like you're going to eventually
go off the deep end if you...
What, talking about conspiracies?
But it's okay, because even if you...
We're all...
This...
I can't even moderate it.
I'm not a nerd.
I...
That's what a nerd says.
And she's gone.
Just like that.
Jeez, right.
I'm not clicking that speed up option.
My goodness.
What was that?
You upped the stream speed,
but I've tried to lower it.
Did I not?
Wait, is this her alt?
I will...
Shatalki Mushroom Yoll on my Privilege
and will...
As long as one finds that they can
stay blissfully unaware.
And even if someone does find it,
it's not like I'm committing a crime.
Even though it does feel like real, just...
Wait, so this is her alt.
Oh, and this is her mane.
Oh, that's a shame.
She doesn't even enjoy streaming.
Then you do it then.
So, but you didn't have to stream
if you didn't like it.
I don't know why we're...
Can you write some good stuff about...
Thingy on ST for me?
I think it'll be too obvious
if I do it myself, so please.
Please.
Medication gives her an idea.
Diazipam?
One milligram Diazipam
makes her floppy.
Brof.
It's five milligrams
that'll make you floppy, hen.
It's not one milligram.
One milligram does nothing.
That's a tiddly wink of Diazipam.
It's someone who's got the anxiety
made, so I assure you, it's five milligrams
is when you're gonna feel it.
Right, I am going to let her
get a new idea by playing games.
She used to play some games.
She's a lightweight, literally.
All you need is a beat a blocker
and you're good to go.
And if you're really not good to go,
Diazipam.
I hit my gacha a bunch of all right.
We just paid money for that!
Did you just spend money
when we have to pay rent?
Nothing beats a good games.
Humans were born to play
and I'm getting the hang of this streaming thing,
so I want to do a let's play.
Let's do this.
Yeah, that's exactly what you're supposed to do.
Why are these reactions so scuffed?
You have a new idea for stream.
Let's play throwback stream.
Hey, that's what I did!
Go to dusk, go to dusk.
Right, you can play again.
I want you.
I need you.
I love you.
Atama no naka.
I don't know what the tune is,
but I've probably heard it
if it's that popular Japanese.
I'll let her play twice
so she can get two game things.
Need to grind, need to grind,
need to grind, need to grind, grind.
So I put a stress by four
and affection up,
but I didn't do anything.
I just remembered this game I played
where you become a big shot
who has a global influence
or whatever I actually got
so into it, I ended up skipping it.
What game is that a reference to?
I just remembered this game
becomes some big shot
who has global influence.
What game?
That must be a reference,
but it's so generic.
But anyway, I know it's recently
a lot of people these days
like to play games where you have to
rule, power to rule the world
and even reduce population and stuff.
What are these references to?
There must be references to.
Is the game,
is referencing itself?
Oh, Papaga.
That's very plausible.
And some people also truly believe
that's what's happening in our world
and make up these wild boogie men
to direct their rage at.
Wait.
Is this because I looked up
that conspiracy stuff she's saying this?
I don't blame them though.
I think considering the times we live in
it's not so strange that people want
someone or something to be angry at.
Not as, not as dissect
in human nature.
Hold on, this game is,
I love it already.
What the heck, we're like human nature.
But we should all be working together.
Please, this is my only wish
as an internet angel.
Wait, but I'm,
I'm eating this up for breakfast.
Like, I love the intricate
like one human nature, like you need something to
sounds good, doesn't it?
Well, I'm gonna say that
and see how the
Schumer's React, they are my li-
Girl.
Do not bite the hand that feeds.
My goodness.
Oh no, she was talking about theories.
I didn't, only one cover.
Wait, am I gonna turn her into a politician?
Can I turn her into anti-Margaret Thatcher?
Please, can I turn her into our
Margaret Thatcher?
Stop.
Stop, anti-Margaret Thatcher.
Let's go.
E-girl, anti-Margaret Thatcher.
We believe in the public
owning the fricking things
and the private sector does not
own or have stakes.
And that the people do not buy out mistakes,
buy out companies that go bust
because it's not the people's problems
for the private companies.
Oh my God, yes!
Revolution, yes!
Oh my God, this game's amazing.
Hi guys, it's Chloe Angel,
the Napoleon of the Streaming Wall.
Who's Napoleon?
Right, not you.
That's a terrible super chat
and you should be embarrassed,
but we'll put it in
because we can take it out.
No way we can do this.
In 30 years, our world could be
ruled by one body.
Also, oh, we're too late for that.
Conglomerates are screaming
to create...
Wait, I can't turn it off.
What's a conglomerate?
I've done another rabbit hole.
The division has already begun.
Oh, I haven't long ago.
Conglomerates are scheming.
They're even trying to reduce
the world population to one billion.
That's scary.
I want to live in an equal society.
I'll put it in because it's super chat,
but we'll see if we can replace it with something else.
What would the world be like
ruled by one government?
I don't know how I feel about
worshiping a fallen angel
being an angel myself.
Lucifer, hold that guy.
You can be my...
You can be my fallen angel.
Sorry, this is a chat.
Keep freaking doing it wrong.
I'm already taking action.
Your frowny face is so cute.
Is there any mean comments?
I don't think I've seen any mean comments.
Literally, we're playing
the binding number Isaac right now.
We've got biblical references.
I'm kind of curious about
that kind of world.
Okay, we'll put that in.
Wow.
I assume if I don't...
Like, if I skip this,
I'll miss out on, like,
she might get stressed.
I'll have a peek at the comments.
That's scary.
I want to live in an equal society.
Yeah, but then just sitting around
and complaining,
I'm going to change everything.
Wait, I'm spying.
No way!
We're freaking starting a revolution
as an e-girl, please!
Yes, you can...
I shall be the new...
I'll be the new god of this world!
Yes!
Oh, my God!
How do I make her do more of this?
This is amazing.
Oh, my God.
Oh, no, it makes her shaky, though.
Oh, I don't want her to be upset.
No matter what you're doing,
you're always bound to end up fighting
one way or another.
Those who do not fight will not survive.
Look at my DM and stop ignoring me.
I'm sorry!
Where's your webcam?
Oh, sorry.
Oh, I thought I can head-patter.
Can I?
Obviously, the first thing you've got to check
is that you can touch next to this section,
but hey, ho...
Oh, I can head-patter!
Take that!
You like that?
Head-patter.
Okay.
I don't think I can talk to you right now.
I've just been focusing on your career,
so it's fine.
It's fine.
Ah.
Alex Jones feature for art!
I want her to, like, take over the world!
I'm going to make an Amazon wish list.
What should I put in it?
Bath bomb costume and expensive mic.
I have to do that.
Expensive mic.
The people need to hear your words!
All right, that's it.
Yes!
The people need to hear you!
So not Kawaii, Nate.
Oh, my God.
You're so Kawaii.
Oh, she's blushing.
You're so not cute.
Okay.
If this is you complaining about me not interacting with you,
my lady,
I have to say this is the most rubbish interaction
I've ever seen before.
We are sending each other emojis,
and that's it.
You're done.
How do I make you do that thing again?
How is...
What was the one that made her get that row?
I want her to do that right more.
Her stress go-
Oh, her stress is 61?
Oh, that's so high.
Her mental darkness goes up on social media.
I don't want that.
Daisling stops call.
It makes you feel a streamer's voice is a lifeline,
but it'll take too many,
and stuff will happen.
Okay.
Everything just feels more manageable,
and it makes you feel kind of floaty.
Do we pop one?
Fuck it.
We'll pop it.
What happens to her stress levels?
Eh.
Madame.
Madame,
you did not have to post that on the main account.
So her stress went-
Wait, that was it?
The stress went down by one?
That was pathetic.
Don't ever do that again.
That was rubbish.
Oh, my God.
She's high as a kite.
You are in no state.
Is this a jump scare here as well?
You're in no state to stream.
Yeah, you're in no straight.
That was useless.
You're not looking at my DMs as quickly as you used to.
You don't care about my girlfriend.
We got rent to make, honey!
Get them yiddies out!
I love you, but get them yiddies out.
What are you talking about?
Right, how did I get her to do that?
Come on, become a politician!
Go on social media!
Oh, wait.
I think you just put her stress up more.
Oh, I'm really bad at this game.
Feels like everyone is a little on edge.
Is it because of something they did?
Also, please remember the streamer and people too.
Oh, my God.
I see that tweet all the time.
Honestly, this game's pretty mad.
I have to admit.
I don't know.
But then, wait, so how'd I progress?
I want more of this one.
Take a dive into conspiracy world.
I'm not allowed to do it.
Or am I allowed to do it?
No.
I think it regurgitates the stream.
So you can't do that.
The next idea for conspiracy is on internet video streaming.
Okay.
Let's do a throwback to a game.
I needed her stress.
It's getting pretty bad.
We're over 50%.
We're at 56% stress levels.
Oh, I didn't mean to skip that.
But I did.
You got a lot more stream ideas.
Hey, cuties!
I'm finding time for me to come.
NICE never gets old.
As usual.
We're going to check out some truly ancient artifacts today.
What, like Assassin's Creed Brotherhood?
Goodness, gravy.
I love games.
I'm excited.
What games are you playing?
The chat would like to know.
Hey, I'm just doing my algebra while listening to she's background music.
It's such a good adaptation.
See, this is so slow.
But the next thing is so fast.
Can I make her...
Gamers, let's go.
That's right.
Gamers are in the most press.
And play some flash games.
Oh, I don't even remember any flash games, to be honest.
Fancy pants.
I think it's the only flash game I remember playing.
It had like a mohawk.
And it was just like a 2D.
You look like you suck at games.
And you look like you swallow at games.
You're nasty.
Thanks for the fives.
Going to a rent.
Don't know what's going on, but I like it.
Yes.
As long as you're enjoying yourself.
What a lovely freaking chat she's got already.
Although her design is like, oh, wow.
Wow, this takes me back.
This site should be the one.
Wait, huh?
Don't TOS yourself.
Don't TOS.
What are you opening?
Are you all right?
What's wrong?
Oh, it's so old that support has ended and we can't play.
Girl, you're supposed to pre-open the game before stream for this reason.
Of course, literally.
That's actually in one of my rule books for the girls.
I gave them a document and it said,
please open the game before stream to make sure you know it works
and have backup games immediately.
Yep, there is folks.
No, that was rude, I think.
You're so silly.
That's cute.
Lol, this is...
This was more interesting, actually.
Okay, okay.
Literally in the document, I'm like, please open.
I'm like, don't cry.
Stop pandering to the old fucks on the internet.
Are we ages out here?
Hold on a minute.
I'm not.
You're not reading that.
That's not nice.
Or should I put it in there and then she'll address it?
Possibly.
I'll put it in so she addresses it and she's like,
we're not ages out here.
We're just here having a good time, you know what I'm saying?
It's okay, there's always next time.
You're lucky you're so pretty.
You're lucky?
No.
Yeah, you spawned in, okay?
You didn't pick the coordinates.
You didn't pick what's going on.
Alright, maybe I shouldn't have done that one.
Oh, I don't know.
Don't cry.
There are only three situations
where it is appropriate for a woman to cry.
Alright.
When you get dumped, when you lose your wallet,
and when your childhood flash games get discontinued.
Sorry, I've got warrable if you can hear me rubbing that.
Stop entering to the old folks on the internet.
Shut up, I love all of this.
That's a cool way.
Doesn't matter what age and gender.
Okay, yeah, she's sure I'm done.
That's what I'm talking about.
So much for our first game stream.
That's all for today, I guess.
Blaze.
Welcome to the house of Blaze.
Okay.
Well, that's it.
What can you do?
Things are only just getting started,
so I have to try even harder from now.
Come on, I said stop ignoring me.
I'm 500 times more needed.
Can I like like these so she knows I'm not ignoring her?
I don't know.
My fiction 50.
Our stress is so high.
We need to do something about that.
We need to do something about our stress today.
I'm getting nervous.
I'm getting shaky.
Right.
For your stress, go and...
Our stress goes way down.
And the fiction goes way up.
But the thing is, the stress goes down by like...
What number of difference is that?
Eight.
Whereas the stress goes down by six on that one.
I'm sorry, but a wee...
Oh wait, I need to talk to her.
Sorry.
My new microphone's here.
People have been calling about the sense.
So this is really good.
Maybe I should take it with me to karaoke.
Oh my God, yeah, I wanna hear you sing, baby girl.
It's lovely time.
Oh my God, you're so cute.
I'm dead.
This is so cute.
We'll be together in our next...
Oh, are we doing afterlife?
Yeah, yeah, together in our afterlife.
You believe in that stuff?
Okay, right.
To bed you go.
Go do your thing, baby girl.
Let's get that stress level done.
Cause I'm getting nervous.
I'm getting shaky.
Wow, some...
What's something you guys are really into these days?
Minus.
I love everything about...
I feel like my brain's gonna leak out of my head from how good it feels.
I wanna have...
Right, we're at night.
Wait, we're at night already?
Oh, for goodness sake.
One day we'll be one of those couples that can afford to call a taxi to go wherever we want.
That is so specific.
Yeah, oh my God, I would love that.
I'm afraid you need to stream.
But her stress is so high.
And I never even got her to get a new...
I never got...
Are you sure you want to proceed?
You'll miss out on streaming at night, but I can't.
I'm out of idea.
Wait, she actually can't just do a zatsu off the top of her head.
Wait, what am I supposed to do? Am I to send her to bed?
What's going on?
I already forgot what I told her to do.
Is she doing something?
Hold on, Danny.
What are you...
What are you doing?
Are you doing something?
Is she doing something?
You can give her head pads.
Okay.
Oh, wow, I didn't know that.
What on earth?
I'm kind of tired.
Thanks for always being so nice to me.
Yeah.
I should carry on your spirit and be nice to my little nerds every once in a while.
Okay.
How do I reduce your stress?
Sexy stream.
Her first ASMR stream.
Let's go.
Go two to one.
So we can't do anything because we're, like, out of time.
Can I, like, head pat her until, like, some of the stats go down?
I think she was doing something sexy.
Honestly, I was like, what's going on?
Oh, we're on day seven.
Rent's due soon.
Hey, what color should I paint my nails?
Light blue, purple, rainbow, black.
I want to say purple because of her hair streaks and her alternative outfit.
Light blue and red for her actual natural self, though.
Light blue matches her natural self more.
I know black is, like, the thing, but she is going to have to dress up for her stream.
Aw, she's actually doing as I say.
You're actually such a good girl.
You're so clever.
Good girl.
I did my nails.
Aren't they pretty?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, that's what I was thinking.
Like, it kind of matches.
Jake, it's not even me that likes the color.
Well, I knew black.
Found a new girl.
I like more than you.
I mean, yeah, you get new Oshis all the time.
You're allowed a new Oshie.
You don't have to say it.
I've allowed, though.
You know, some...
Right.
Stress?
Oh, forget the sleep.
If she sleeps, sleep until tomorrow.
A new idea if I sleep until tomorrow.
Aw.
Okay.
I'm just going to send her a bed.
We have an ASMR stream planned for tonight.
She's going to sleep.
Okay.
Let her sleep.
Right.
ASMR time.
Get the mic out.
Get licking it, young lady.
Okay.
Did I make myself clear?
I want to get ha...
Oh.
I don't think we...
I don't think we're allowed to condone that.
Sorry, but no, you're about to do an ASMR stream.
And we need to make sure it's YouTube terms of service safe.
Okay?
So, no, you're not allowed.
Go do ASMR.
Right now.
Hold on.
I'm going to reach for a water ball from yesterday.
Because I forgot to get a new water ball.
Sub-squibble.
Any sub-squibblers?
First time.
Hi, cuties.
I hope all of you nerds are going through it today, too.
Going through it?
Like...
The Mr. K is the always best.
I want to die!
Whoa!
I don't think I can allow that.
Sorry, I put my hand over my mouth in shock.
Because I didn't want to...
Like, to...
I'm not a nerd.
But...
So much...
Die show food.
You're also good for always trying so hard.
It's okay if you're chocolate-er.
You can lie to someone.
Honestly, I'm starting to agree with her.
Hold on a minute.
She's actually kind of starting to make sense.
Like, sorry, but you actually have been told by the capitalist cogs
that you need to be productive for every...
Here comes the most jobless of them all.
Eh!
You have been told that you need to be productive
for every second of your life.
That's not true.
You try harder than any of us.
But personally, I hate being told
that just being alive is enough.
Eh!
It's just such an empty-ass compliment.
No!
Sorry, I'm disagreeing.
Hold on a minute.
K Angel, you're starting to lose it.
Get back on the politician bandwagon.
I want you to take over Earth right now.
I feel that.
Tell him.
I feel worse now.
Uh, not for...
I feel like that's cathartic.
Is it cathartic?
If someone, like, kind of just gets to vent and chat?
I feel like that'll put her stress up, though.
But it's, like, cathartic to, like, put it out there
to be like, you know what?
I'm feeling it!
You know?
I have a really good pick-me-up for you guys today.
ASMR!
Here we go.
What is it?
Yo!
I'll be your team yell.
Smooch!
Is that what I'm supposed to say?
I don't know if I'm supposed to go muah or smooch.
You're my real life Angel.
Love you.
I've always wanted to try that.
But now that I have, I'm so embarrassed I could die.
May I stop keeping going?
No, I'm not going to stop.
I need to stop.
Can you take it off?
Yeah, we're gonna...
I'll give it an A+.
My first kiss.
I'm so happy.
Then die.
Thank you for the tip.
But no, I'm not gonna...
This pandering feels forced.
It's weird.
Is that gonna stress her out?
I think because we know she's role-playing, it will.
Thank you for the tip.
Okay, that's much nicer.
I don't want her to get stressed out
because I'm already struggling with her stress at the moment.
She looks like Monka.
Do it again, please.
You're too cute.
Yes.
Ratchets in a way.
I don't know if we're gonna make rent.
I'm gonna make you my girlfriend.
This is...
I always send the girls these little symbols
all the time in my messages.
And they're just surrounding me.
Love.
Love and thank you for the super chat, too.
I love a man who can send me both love and money.
Love and money.
And thank you kiss for you.
And I'll thank you kiss for you more.
Thanks.
Please go down.
Why did you say that?
Are you squidding me right now?
Beryl, I thank you kiss for you more.
Why did she say that at the end of the stream?
Why did you say go die at the end of a super chat?
What?
I was so confused why she randomly came over that.
Did you see her?
Hey, did you all like what you saw the date?
If you did, let's play again tomorrow.
Did some basic ass pandering in my stats or skyroll?
Oh, wow.
I actually did.
Oh, her stress is so high after that.
But the longest way around is the shortest way home, right?
I can't just ignore the groves.
One new Twitter.
I missed it.
You guys are having...
You guys are having a really tough time in life.
When you're in life, things are doing overwhelming.
But shut up, everyone.
As long as you're not falling forward,
you'll find me waiting for you on the internet.
Is that the end?
Do you need a head part?
Is there a secret to the stress level thing?
I think I'm not achieving whatever it is.
I don't want her to break.
I reached 10.
I want to do a celebration stream,
but you know, 10k is a nice number,
but that's about it.
Yeah, go for it.
It's very...
I was actually speaking to the girls about this.
The first step I'm taking is a legendary angel,
but I'm going to get everyone to celebrate it.
No takes back.
You will love me for...
I don't know about you, Andrea.
You have a new idea.
Internet Angel, the internet and me.
Thanks for 10k.
Okay.
That happened naturally,
so I can fully de-stress her today
without needing to come up with ideas.
Wait, she's going to get an idea
if I do this to her?
It drops her...
Wait, what does this do?
Wait, two gaming...
Oh, but she gets a new idea if I do this.
I don't know what the thing is, though.
Rest and touching grass,
like a real streamer stress management.
Literally, we need to take her out
and go meet Gami.
So when she meets Gami,
things just even out, you know?
Thank God they didn't introduce you
to demonetising.
I'm not even monetised yet.
They won't update my stats,
so I can't even get my stats.
She gets a new stream idea
if I do this, though.
And she doesn't, if we do play stress
and things, internet.
Her stress goes up exponentially.
Mental darkness.
Cine...
Video streaming.
Watch a movie.
It takes her to dust.
You know what?
She's not actually sat and watched something.
Oh, no, she's crying!
Wait, you didn't want to watch that?
I'm sorry.
Were we supposed to do something?
Oops.
I think so, didn't I?
I keep looking up there.
I'm rattling the channel page
for the prison door screen monetised story.
They just won't update the stats.
I don't know why.
The streaming site I use updated.
I've got, like, idle anime, truly.
And the best ones are the kids' idle anime.
It's not idle.
I'm glad you love it.
Well, I guess that's why the page on the TV
is my best though.
Right!
For any TV shows,
really good inspiration for my streams.
If there's anything you guys would like me to do,
let me know in the replies
and maybe I could do something
that we could always have somewhere.
A girl's idle journey in a kid's anime.
Okay, okay, okay.
Shake a prompt.
Uh, stress is still faking high.
Mmm.
I'll miss...
Yeah, I'll miss stream if I do that.
Is there an internet?
It only puts it down by four,
but it gives her another...
This doesn't do anything?
I don't know, it's dindered.
I don't know why.
That puts her stress down by four
and gives her a new news stream idea.
That takes her to the next date.
No, I think we're just going to have
to do spend time together
and put affection up.
Oh, sorry, I'm sorry.
Apparently with this credit card thing,
we can...
No!
Credit cards are bad.
They're not real credit...
No!
Don't...
I'll punch you.
I don't care,
you can beat me up
and spit in my mouth.
Do whatever you want.
You will not know peace.
Oh my God,
this is literally what I'm asking for.
I love it.
I love you so much.
Oh my God,
you just read my mind?
Oh, it says read when she reads it.
Oh, that's kind of scary, actually.
Right, what?
Wait, what is this?
Affection goes up during game.
Game or girl goes up.
But experience goes up.
Ah, maybe...
Does make stress 67s better.
Are we going for the end ending?
I don't know what endings there are.
I've not played the game before.
Click anywhere to give a head pat.
More.
Spend the whole day lasering.
Oh wait, did I just skip stream?
Oh, no.
Maybe?
No, no.
It's time to stream.
Okay, my apologies.
Let's celebrate your 10k milestone,
because that's fantastic.
As I was saying before,
I got interrupted by my own thoughts.
I actually said to the girls,
like, unfortunately,
like, you kind of have to celebrate numbers
as they come through
to like make the tripper news or whatever.
And like, it's really annoying.
I don't like playing that game,
but you do have to play that angle
as a Vtuber,
and it's like a bit like...
I don't like it at all.
You gotta do what you gotta do.
Hi, here we go.
Hey cuties, it's me,
Angel...
Wait.
You're not reading comments for the stream.
Hey cuties, it's me,
Angel, Cypher, CypherSpace.
You're crossing over my fingers.
This stream is one to celebrate.
Celebrate?
What do you ask?
Well, did you not read the title?
Don't know how to make things for that game.
I can't do anything actually.
Um...
Take your top off.
Wait, I can't.
This is nothing for you, I'm sure.
I guess just skip ahead,
honestly, because...
no.
That's right.
Hi, King Angel!
Have received 10,000 subscribers!
You're such a...
You could get away with...
You could get way more subscribers.
Oh, I can...
I'm only gonna get bigger and bigger.
I'm just gonna shine brighter than ever.
Just watch.
Everyone, subscribe.
We need to blow...
up.
Celebrate with something tasty.
Well, let's talk about the internet today.
I bet you guys are...
I can't read the path.
You know, I really hated adults.
They're all so fake.
Adults?
Girl, aren't you 18 plus?
I'm getting nervous.
Are you 18?
I'm getting swayed.
What's going on here?
There's always a lot of adults on the internet,
but they're all...
But they were all true to themselves.
Why do I find you being a dropout cute?
Pat-pat-pats.
They weren't ashamed of being into anime or manga.
They were so free, so natural.
I thought to myself,
I want to live like that.
I want to live on the internet and be my drizzle.
I guess I wasn't too interested,
but I'm glad I could share with you guys less.
She said,
you talk too fast for me when I put you on this mode.
Jeez, the stream's already over.
I'm gonna do a dang thing.
Hello, you are all pure cinnamon world...
Nerds.
Thanks for celebrating 10k with me.
I'm going to keep working so hard
that everyone in the world knows my name.
Please use that in a year's work.
Look, I draw some fan art.
Oh, that's so cool.
That's so cool.
Getting fan art is honestly crazy.
I have to admit.
Can I save it or send it to her
so she can see it just so she knows?
Oh, the night time trim is actually really nice.
It reminds me of that Russian song
that goes la la la la la la la la la la la la la.
Best of me.
She's 17!
Am I ignoring her DMs again?
How do I ignore them by accident?
I'm sorry, I love you.
I'm sorry.
Can you get an achievement
for clicking her head 100 times in a row?
Okay, that's as fast as I can click.
If I didn't make her happy, I wouldn't have won.
I can hear that in the chat.
Shit! Wait, she's actually 17.
I very strongly think that any content creator
should be at least 18 years old.
Sponsorships, trying out new drinks?
I got DM...
Oh, sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Oh my god, that's amazing.
Oh my god, love you.
Oh my god, you're so cool.
She's gonna know I haven't...
Are you sure?
Yeah!
Yeah, this, I'm so sure.
Wait, what did she ask?
I don't pay attention.
I got DM'd about sponsorship.
Sponsorships, we're entering the big leagues.
Let's see what it says.
We'd like for you to review
of our new...
Natto?
Wait, Natto is that fermented soybeans?
Flavoured cola?
And they said they'll pay me a year's supply.
No!
You have to accept US dollars for payment.
You do not ever, ever entertain a sponsorship
that say, we'll pay you with our product.
No!
Hard-earned, cold cash.
Do not entertain, respond, reply.
Okay?
This is true.
Yeah, why not?
A job's a job.
No, we are not doing that stream.
Absolute waste of time.
I'm going to send you to do that internet thing
because I want you to become a politician.
But her stress goes up.
Her mental darkness goes up.
But her stress goes down?
No, her affection goes down.
We will do...
Is ST going to give me the fricking politician angle?
I want her to take over the world.
This takes me to dusk?
Congrats on getting monetised.
Why are they happy about that?
So they can be her paper already down.
Wait, what's this?
This bottom book.
POST!
Oh no, her stress goes up.
No, we ain't doing that.
Your stress goes up.
You go watch some cinema.
I've been streaming a lot of anime by myself.
Let me know in the replies if you have recommendations.
Lying around and watching anime.
Late...
Late night anime is probably my favourite thing ever.
Maybe I'll talk about conspir-
YES!
Absolutely.
Do it.
But you know I'm a little scared to-
No, keep talking about it.
You're going to rule the world.
You will rule the world.
You must.
I don't think I have to do it.
No, you have to do it.
But I don't think I have to duel too much on that.
Plus, I guess believing in them is kind of like its own brand of happiness.
Please!
But I think I'll talk about microchip snakes.
Those are one of my favourites.
YES!
Your PCs can scan the layout of your house.
I remember watching a talk show once in the sky.
He was talking about an urban legend and another guest.
It's like you got microchipped into you and then the guy was like,
I could tell you but then I'd have to kill you.
It was the most dead pan face ever.
That was what made me look into this whole microchip business.
In the first place, I guess I want to talk about it because of how plausible it is.
YES!
I want her to be like I'm a conspiracy nut.
I've been falling asleep with my eyes open so if you see me doing that, please close
your eyes.
Please close my eyes for me.
What the heck?
Yeah, I will.
Oh my god.
Right, I'm just going to de-stress her because we already know what she's going to do.
I put her stress up to post on social media which is such a shame.
Video streaming seems like such a safe thing to make her less stressed.
I'll do that and then we'll stream conspiracy theory.
Oh tiny spiny, thank you for the tip.
It's work time for me against Ronnie but enjoy the game.
You'll probably all find I'm done but I'll catch up later.
Yes, thank you so much.
Unfortunately, it is a shorter stream but yes, have fun at work and thank you so very
much for the kind tip.
I appreciate it.
I love videos where the person just talks about what they like even better if you learn
something new from it.
YES!
Agreed.
I may be dumb dumb with mental issues and a horrific academic record.
Wait, hold on a minute.
Hold on a minute.
This is a henabit too close to home.
But I still want to share all the things I've turned up researching these things.
Wait, wait a minute.
Hold on a minute.
She wants to do education streams.
Oh, wait a minute.
Hold on, hold on, hold on.
I'm getting mental Illinois.
I'm going to do a stream talking about things I like and I like and my darling little nerds
like and to do that, I guess I'll have to start at the very beginning with nerds themselves
and I've already done plenty of research on them.
Let's do it.
Okay.
Why are these?
Oh my God.
Yeah.
You're so smart for coming up with these ideas baby girls.
I can't even see you.
Oh my God.
You're so cute.
Head pat.
Right.
Okay.
Let's go to the night and the moment I get a single wrinkle, I think I'll end things.
She's hitting the wall.
Oh my God.
I'm orb.
Is she okay?
I feel like these are just like such random emotions like as long as she's happy.
Were you even paying attention?
Yes.
Oh my God.
You're so needed.
Right.
Let's do it.
Oh, stress goes up so much talking about these though.
Her mental darkness goes up.
But communication and rabbit hole go up so much though.
Take a deep dive into the conspiracy of the world but don't go too deep.
But I want her to do it.
Right.
She's definitely going to be on stress management but we're doing it.
Wait.
Yeah.
We're doing it.
She's spain.
She's an orb.
She's orbudes.
Wow.
Look at them nails.
Hey.
You changed your nails already.
They're supposed to be blue like your hair color and there's little things.
Subscribble on ear.
As technology improves by leaps and bounds perhaps one day we will all be bankrupt.
Oh wait.
Turn it down.
Okay.
K angel.
Hey.
Hello.
Hi.
And you come and you come.
What would her fan base K angel fan base name be?
If she's an angel and you follow an angel I guess so you're a worshipper really.
Yeah.
You just be fan name would be worshipper.
K goals.
Okay.
Well I can't.
Yeah.
She's a streamer.
She's needy.
And now we need to the overload of weekend rule credits.
Their name is nerds.
That's what she said.
Oh okay.
Okay.
Call member.
Let's go.
See it's so slow.
If you don't it's literally so slow.
If I don't speed this up but it's like far too fast.
I don't know maybe nothing's bugging out.
I don't know the game seems pretty like the game seems pretty put well together.
Do I need clicker?
No.
Nothing's happening.
Imagine cities of people being controlled by microchips embedded from birth.
Going into the deep end.
Yeah.
I'm barely doing work with work I can watch a game now.
We're doing the politician route question mark or the conspiracy not route concert.
I see you're also enlightened.
Yeah.
That's so scary.
I got one in my arm.
What?
I've just noticed the music gets quieter when I tab over to do moderation stuff and then.
That's a really good detail.
I've got a microchip too.
Is she going to?
I feel like that's going to spur her on to do more microchip to do more of these types of streams.
Another government conspiracy.
Wait until you learn about that time.
The ruling class could manipulate our brainwaves as we like.
We'd all use our puppets.
Oh my god.
I don't want to be main controlled.
No way.
You mean I could be brainwashed right now?
Oh wait.
Where's my tinfoil hat?
Exactly.
We're going to be the tinfoil hat gang.
Maybe just maybe we already have those chips in our arms.
You could not be suggesting such a thing my innocent VTuber.
Idol Angel.
Kate Angel.
Was that a scream?
How did you find out about this?
Take that instead of the microchip thing.
We'll be living under a dictatorship soon mark my words.
We are all on a watch list right now.
Kate Angel branded tinfoil hat.
Hat marriage win honestly.
I'm not going to be able to sleep after this.
The music is so good.
I don't know who crafted it but.
As if that technology could exist.
Relax people.
Thank god.
Phew.
Stronecottle's branded tinfoil.
Literally just get tinfoil out of the cupboard.
That was scary.
For now anyway.
Oh her eyes are starting to change.
Am I noticing that?
I'm actually going to leave that one.
I'll leave the dystopia one.
But yeah.
Her eyes are changing or have I just made that up?
Please talk about this forever Kate Angel.
She's going.
Oh my god I'm loving this route.
Is the music going up because she's going this route?
Because I don't remember.
You're not like the other girls.
Yeah she ain't.
I'm going to make sure of it.
I feel like I'm going to fall really hard for Kate Angel.
That click mouse button sounds like the
Legend of Zelda Minish Cap raindroplets
or slime droplets.
Let's have a look see.
I don't want to be mind controlled.
Scary isn't it?
It'd be scary if I were real though.
How did you find out about this?
Um, why do you ask?
Am I being interrogated?
The government must have sent you to kill me.
Wait.
Girl.
Bless.
Amen.
Amen in the chat.
Why are you guys saying bless or whatever?
Because we're a cult though.
Bless.
We're a cult.
Literally get them hand emojis out there.
Bless.
Couldn't come up with a better greeting.
Greeting.
We're about to be out.
The cult is forming.
What have I done?
I should have really like a scream being incorporated into the music.
Ah, look at you.
Bless.
She did it.
We do have to maintain.
Help me.
The microchip in my arm is controlling what I post.
Microchips are like whatever because even without them,
you still can't prove that we actually have free will.
Oh, she's at breaking point.
She's at breaking point.
Definitely de-stressed day today.
Hello, pumpkin spice.
I believe this is the biggest de-stresser I can do to you right now.
It does take me all the way.
If we miss a day of streaming, it takes it to 65.
Or if we do that, it's 71.
Oh, it's still quite high.
I don't want her on edge though.
These didn't do anything.
If she takes a third one, it gives her an idea,
like a psychedelic route you can maybe do.
No, right.
We'll do...
We'll just do this.
I know it takes us tonight,
but I really want her to do...
Oh, I keep ignoring her messages.
I'm sorry.
I keep forgetting.
I'm super like manager in this right now.
I'm not like VTuber manager groomer.
I'm like proper manager.
Like I'm going to make you successful.
I get some blue DMs from guys.
Oh, my God.
On Marshmallow.
I don't think I haven't been seeing what I've been getting.
But let me just...
Let me just say that this is not okay.
Wait, what?
But that's the best part.
Okay, we're doing ASMR.
I never thought about doing it
in my k-angel outfit profile.
Oh, hi, wait.
Oh, wait.
My clothes are finding crumpled.
Do you think that I'll be fine to go on camera?
Oh, well, if I can't leave...
Oh, wait.
No, this is a regular...
Oh, well, if I can't leave...
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
I mean...
I mean, true.
But like...
You do get suspended and stuff,
but a little head pat because you don't...
Who's a good swag?
You're my good swag, aren't you?
Oh, who's my good swag?
Not click-bleat.
Not to collect the eight.
Jesus.
Lying down and...
Is it super comfy?
I think I need to get a water and a cola.
The words are mashing together.
And now I can't get up.
Come, please help me.
Yes.
I'm freaking...
I think I have to get a cola and a water,
unironically.
The words start mashing together if I read for too long.
Oh, our stress goes round and round.
Is there any stream that doesn't put your stress up?
Like, I don't feel stressed when I stream.
Is that bad?
Do we have to skip?
Honestly, do we have to skip?
I think we skip and do ASMR tomorrow.
Um, no.
Not the medication.
I don't think that's a good route for you, darling,
because if you start relying on it...
67 to watch something.
65 to play together or...
59.
Yeah, no stream.
We'll do ASMR tomorrow.
No stream.
Let her take a day off, yes.
Can't really.
I stream every single day,
so I'm not really sure what the issue is, hen.
If I ever find my special someone,
I want to go to the amusement park
with them.
We can scream together.
Scream together?
Eat ice cream together?
Rape the Ferris wheel?
Why would you scream?
Oh, an amusement park!
Sorry.
I thought it meant a park park, like,
that one in New York City or something.
Why would you scream there?
Uh, I made up with Peachhan.
I made up with Peachhan,
and then things got a bit...
What?
Wait, you made up?
You fell out?
Is she, like, super lovey-and-dovey?
Monetization.
Oh, she got monetization!
Congrats!
That's perfect.
You're amazing.
Ignoring you.
No, you're not.
You're literally freaking sending me emojis.
We won't get convicted
because those online nerds
can pay for our rent, Jesus.
Dodged a bullet there.
I don't want to have us
to stream out on the streets.
I really need a cola.
I need a freaking...
I'm gonna go grab a cola in a war.
I'll literally be a second.
I'm like...
Oh, my God, I can't.
There's so many words to word.
I don't know if you guys get this,
but if you read for too long,
all the letters start merging together,
and it's really hard to think of.
Like, a context,
a view of one heritage.
The actual word is...
It's not over all my feelings.
I don't know how you do it,
but maybe you're a bit different...
And yes, I did just keep talking
while I walked into the room.
I probably didn't even hear anything.
I got my cola in a war.
I'm gonna take a little sipping tin.
Put my blanket around me again.
I'm actually wearing underwear today.
I can't believe it.
It's a Christmas miracle,
But I'm not wearing a hoodie, I've just got my blanket like a poncho, like a poncho.
These streams are always a blast to watch, yeah?
Are you ready for the rabbit hole route ending?
I actually kind of, I'm interested to see what the other endings are.
I don't think I'm going to do the other endings, so please don't get excited for a strapped in big long stream or anything like that.
I think I will happily watch what the other endings look like.
Let's take a little water sipping tin.
If you are remaining seated, please do wiggle, move your foot up and down.
And if you feel your calf muscles flex, then that's good because that is helping the circulation in your legs.
Just do a few of those and then you're good to go.
See you later, bye bye, thanks for hanging, I appreciate it.
Shibi cotton bum, 30 minutes.
I will redirect into her though, so don't worry about 30 minutes.
That's right, you better wiggle.
We're increasing that blood circulation for you.
Oh, I just realized I can't hear any game sound at all right now.
Is it because of that tab out?
No, I guess it's the end of the day, so to symbolize it's the end of the day the music stops.
I was like, where is it?
You know, some things may be cliche, but they're cliche for a reason like this.
Welcome home darling, would you like to have dinner first or a bath or me?
Wait, is this cause affection is so high?
I think so.
The music is different as well and she's animated different.
Okay, I like this kind of detail, like these subtle things.
Oh wow, I'm like appreciating this game.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, did we just, we were supposed to do an ASMR?
Oh no, she's gonna be crazy for me, she's gonna go frickin' yandere.
Oh my god, I don't want her to go yandere, I need to like ignore her a little bit.
I don't want her to go yandere, I want her to go politicization.
No, no, you have to, you have to stream, you have to stream.
Oh no, I'm, I'm, I'm frickin', I, I successfully gripped my feature for talent, but I didn't want to.
Right, go stream ASMR please.
Okay, it drops affection dramatically doing ASMR, that's good.
We'll do that.
Go be unaffectionate for your frickin' manager, cause that was highly inappropriate.
She's like yandere on me, she's called Mercy Mode, honestly.
You're too good, I'm too good in this sheet, she can't, suffering from success literally.
Wow.
Oh, her eyes are different, am I going crazy or am I just makin' up that the eyes are different?
Hi cuties, is your favorite Indian, sorry I just drank a cola, so.
Is your favorite Indian Angel, Angel?
I love you.
Oh wait, no, that's a chat, I love you.
Okay, we can do super chats today, I can see it now.
Get the hole.
What should we talk about today?
Oh I know, I've got a bit of a trivia about the corned beef I ate yesterday, what are you talking about?
Is this relevant to the ASMR?
Is this relevant to the ASMR stream?
I don't, oh yeah, corned beef trivia, I've never been so interested in corned beef before.
Wait, please talk every day about corned beef.
Okay, her chat's actually really funny, I'm gonna give it to him.
Corned beef ASMR literally, did you know that corned beef is shaped so because of old canning methods, which would?
Is her heart pounding?
No.
Is her heart pounding because she's so in love at the moment?
Good stream, but that's all it was, just good.
That's a backhanded comment, so we will remove it because that's not very pleasant.
Does this game have scenes that I need to be nervous about?
A subbing for sure, omega lol.
I did not know that was gonna happen, hey don't look, you can't.
I didn't know, okay the game's safe, it's safe, okay it's safe.
I didn't know if it was gonna go any further.
You've just got yourself a new fan.
Oh my god, I suppose I could give you a smaller one.
Oh my god, that's so mean when the bikini freaking toggle came on and I'm just meanin' about typing.
I didn't even notice.
Thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you.
Okay this game, this game, I know it's early days because we haven't finished our route
but I wanna say this is 10 out of 10 already for me.
This game, highly enjoying it, highly.
Literally flush emoji, flush emoji momento.
This is so good.
You're gonna get big I can feel it, yes okay, I thought I read that.
Thank you mother for having me, thank you for spawning me in on the same timeline as you stream.
You just made me smile for the rest of my life.
I suppose as a nicer compliment then I give you a reward.
But if she needs to pay rent and get more equipment, cause we got that microphone.
I will never forget the stream for as long as I live.
Don't worry it's already been archived eight times over, you don't got to worry.
Can you do a workout stream?
Oh, is there like a fitness route?
That would actually be kind of cool, you can like make her boss.
I feel like you're trying too hard.
You're out.
You will not hurt my streamer's feelings.
Guess this makes you an arch angel for now.
Wait, wait, wait, let me read that again.
Guess that makes you an arch angel now.
Oh, that didn't work.
Oh no, did that work?
No, my freaking thing doesn't work.
My freaking brooms doesn't work.
I'm so sad.
No, stop, stop giving me money for something so small.
You feel, wait, take my memory wipe beam.
Oh, my freaking sand board's dead.
I don't know why it's dead.
Come on guys.
Oh, someone's message me.
Oh, Amy is such a fucking hard worker, you know that.
Hold on, hold on, game, game.
Did I accidentally go a little overboard?
Yeah, you're just popped it.
Hmm, I got way better numbers showing a bit.
Hmm, I wonder how that worked.
Hmm, I truly am a mystery.
Can I talk to her?
Oh, wait, we got our goal.
She wanted 100k.
She did it.
Wait, we've won already?
That's not right.
Did she not want 100k?
This isn't the first time reaching so many.
I don't know what's going to happen for you.
I'm a bit nervous.
She wanted a milk.
Oh, Hen, that's greedy.
Hen, Hen, you're supposed to take down the capitalist cog of greediness.
Okay.
I need to thank them for their devotion.
Yeah, I think she's going to get, yeah, yeah, yeah, definitely do a thank you stream
because that's like insane.
What we will do is nothing affection wise.
Definitely stress though.
Yeah, we'll just make her watch two videos in a row, I think.
Who goes there?
Identify yourself.
As long as the fiction doesn't go up, then I'm happy.
I was watching this idol video and they were all eating popsicles for some reason.
I already know where.
Oh, ASMR.
Oh, she's wanting the ASMR route, but I'm wanting the different route.
I don't know how to get the fricking politician.
I want the politician route.
Is she okay?
You look so annoyed there.
Here, Jester asked me what I do and I was like, lol, I'm just a voice.
That's what I was saying.
If someone ever makes small talk with me, I'm just like, I'm just a voice actor.
It's so much easier to explain than be like, I'm an anime woman on Das Interwebs, yeah?
I'm just like, oh yeah, the Scottish voice is in demand all the time.
You know, I get to play big strong women in my audios.
Meanwhile, my audios are like, yeah, take it!
Oh, can't she go outside for stress relief possibly?
I'm dead, that's so cute.
That's so cute, I'm dead.
So not cute.
Oh my god, I'm so sorry.
Love forever.
Did I just do that and then she's happy?
Is she like talking to herself when she does that?
Or is that a reflection on...
If I sleep until night, her mental dark...
Okay, so sleep gets rid of mental darkness.
I think we will do that, that's lovely.
Yes, just have a wee nap, hen.
You've deserved it, we rest.
Okay, mental darkness.
I hate this.
Shaky.
I wouldn't say...
Are you okay?
Why are you looking at me like that?
I woke up on record time this morning, please...
This morning is night time.
Selfie time.
You're such a girl, honestly.
Selfie time, I mean...
Wait, so why is that highlighted?
Give me this!
How do I unlock this?
Does it tell you how to progress or is it just it happens?
I want rabbit holes so badly.
But don't go too deep.
No.
Right, we'll do...
Thank you for 100k, because that is very...
Special milestone to celebrate and it's fantastic.
Just got to look around the ideals.
You have to find it, oh...
Okay, I think...
Conspiracies would be...
Not in a video.
Okay, we can do this...
I need to play that Russian song...
La la la la la la la la...
I can never remember it.
Having my...
Coca-Cola, he's too mad.
Don't politicians usually have high stress and high mental darkness?
I'm very greedy.
I thought she said she wanted to become like some sort of...
What's Socrates?
Like a philosopher to rebuild a new world.
I thought that's the kind of route that that angle took.
That's what I'm trying to get.
Well, that's what I think anyway, I don't actually know.
Because I was kind of like, oh, let's be anti-Margaret Fatcher.
And like, public...
The resources of the nation need to be in the hands of the public and all that kind of thing.
Yeah, yeah, I want to make her a god!
Yes!
Andrei, you've grown so much as an angel.
Wow, that's...
Your channel grows so fast.
Our super, super popular.
I'm an angel that came down from Earth from heaven to save everyone on the internet.
Default setting too strong.
I feel like you've said something similar before.
Oh, I can't believe it.
I can't believe Streamer repeated one sentence.
We're not reading comments for the stream.
Thank you for coming to bless us.
I like how she's...
That's so gross down here, you should go back to heaven.
Oh...
The internet is oversaturated with users and content, but it's hard to tell what to believe in.
Yes, you should do more conspiracies.
Whenever you feel lost, I want you to know that you can believe in me.
All right.
Save us, my angel.
And all believers will be...
Whoa, we're doing the rapture.
All believers will be saved.
You just need to have a little fight.
As the internet angel, I will always be by your side.
It says exactly like that one Russian song.
Beginning of a cult, cult, cult, cult, cult.
Give me a cult, give me a cult.
I want cult ending.
I'm so glad we got tinfoil, foil, hat, merch.
I wear it all the time when I watch your streams, Kate Angel.
That's actually really nice.
I think that's a good sentiment.
Your smile is bright enough to illuminate the hearts of all 100K of us.
Change 100K.
Does she not say she eats these?
Am I going to fail if I don't get her the numbers sometime?
I'd like, do you always get the numbers and it's like a unique ending to whoever?
Strongly blessing us with ink in this universe.
This game gives Valhalla.
I've never played that game.
Oh, is this simple?
Obviously, thank you.
I skipped school a lot so I didn't have any friends.
I don't like when she gets a bit real.
Only the people online cared about what I had to fuck it up with.
I used to sit on Xbox and skip school because I had a rough time.
Hold on a minute, hold on a minute, hold on a minute.
I feel like a lot of v-tubers probably had a rough time socializing
and that's how they've got the internet culture to be a v-tuber in the first place.
Or is she idle?
She's not v-tubers, she's just idle.
I didn't know angels had to go to school too.
Valhalla is a great experience.
How many ever?
Big game, weak game, endurance game?
She's v-tuber coded.
I was bullied a lot, it's good for being so cute and pretty too.
Jealousy is it?
Try and stay humble, try and stay humble.
Hold on a minute, hold on a minute.
Can't relate to that part of it anyway.
Did I ever tell you at my job, I actually didn't know it was polite to say good morning to people.
That's how socially inept I was.
I had to learn to say good morning, which is why I like saying good morning, good evening, good afternoon to you guys
because I think that hopefully you do get to learn things with me over time.
As long as you have faith in me, I will find you within the darkness.
I literally didn't know I was like, you say good morning to your cool workers like a dumbass
and I didn't know that that was socializing and really common.
Guess that makes you an archangel now.
Oh, that's strange.
Or is it just to signify,
Remember, you're never alone.
Bless.
We are joining the call, the bless call, bless call, bless call.
Kate Angel having 20 concurrent 100k followers to create a part of the game.
Oh, unbelievable.
I can't promise to save everyone because that would be a lie, but if there's just one person to be saved, where's my person?
Can I just say something?
Oh, she got found her.
Oh, she's greeting.
No, didn't cry.
We didn't need to cry.
Why didn't you draw a cry in?
Only thing really to draw me crying is because I'm just so happy with that we did previously.
If my smile can grant soul salvation, then I will keep smiling for all the viewers on there.
Are we changing her personality as well to become a god?
I can't play a game, do Q&A, rate a gigantic turtle around Shinjuku.
No, I want her to do the conspiracy theory.
None of these are conspiracy theory for later.
Yeah, okay, okay.
I hate this.
Wait, did her stress go up there?
Her affection's still too high for us.
She's like doing this weird thing.
How do I find...
Do I find the idea here?
I put her stress up her affection down and mental.
But maybe it'll give us the fricking...
I want the fricking politician.
Oh.
What?
I just found out an author that I've liked ever since I was a kid watches the stream.
It's like a dream come true.
Someone looks like they'd make me so glad to start streaming.
I'm happy that one of my favourites would miss me.
But when I replied, he was like, do you want a video called The Disappointment?
I fell out of that for the video.
I thought this was a real start for the mental.
Who says that anymore?
Conspiracy?
Conspiracy, please?
Oh my god, what did you think?
Do you ever get curious about what cringy things people have done online in the past?
I reckon I could turn my past cringy into content or something.
That's like watching your debut stream.
Definitely VTubers watching their debut stream for the first time.
Over again after a while has passed.
I do agree that that's good content.
I wouldn't mind showing our mock streams.
I wouldn't show the girls' mock streams but my mock stream.
I actually did better in my second mock stream attempt than I did in my debut.
And that's fact.
I'm happy to show it at a later time.
It's a good idea, but to be honest, I just don't really want to do it.
Oh, I just need to think.
And it makes people want to die, but the suffering is what makes it interesting.
So I guess I got...
Being a streamer is so hard, girl.
Being a streamer.
I'm not putting you in any way.
But then again, maybe the stars have aligned for someone like me.
I know it's not.
Can we not stream today?
Day off, day off, day off.
I need to blow some steam off.
Right, if you're genuinely not wanting a day off, that's fine with me.
I'm going to drug you up and see if that...
Oh, she's going to get so messed up.
She's going to get so messed up.
And it puts her mental darkness up to 32.
Are you sure?
Yeah.
You wanted a break.
Pass out on these drugs.
Have a good time, hen.
Enjoy yourself.
Three milligrams of the Azepam.
We'll not do this here.
Oh, no.
I thought you were going to go to sleep.
More than the sweet release of death,
I crave the sweet, sweet follow account,
but still, why is living so hard?
I guess I'll pop a few pills before going live.
Breakdown stream.
No.
Uh-uh.
Get off lying.
Get a break.
No.
You're getting closed.
You asked for a day off.
I gave you one and you give me break downstream?
When I woke up, the sun was already setting.
I still feel so lazy after sleeping so much.
Can I just sleep forever?
You're probably feeling what's known as the side effects.
I'm sorry.
Can I just sleep forever?
Rest for a turn eight?
No.
Sure.
Do you want to sleep again?
That means I don't have to bother living in it.
Is she off on or not?
I think she may be off on or not.
Is she okay?
I don't think we should have done that one.
Oh, she can go out!
Oh, but who's fricking affectionate?
Wait, Akihabara.
Let's visit nerd culture, popular with young people.
Young people?
Oh, this is actually really cool.
So can we map?
Disneyland?
Akihabara?
Shinjuku?
Wait, so it says Shinjuku, but I can't...
Alright, okay, okay, okay.
Maybe that's where our politician...
I forgot sick women!
Give me politician!
Just go to sleep!
Just go...
Give me politician!
Just sleep one more time.
We're going to stream you absolutely to...
It fails tomorrow.
The moment I go to bed,
all these horrible memories come flooding back to me.
Oh, because you're on 28A, darkness?
Oh, God, I'm so sorry.
Oh, that's so sad.
Oh, no, you can't...
Oh, wait!
There actually is an Ace of Arc category!
Oh, that's so cool.
Okay, that's really cool.
How cool is it tomorrow?
My silver award is getting for your fur.
That's amazing.
Okay, that's really good.
Wait, but there's actually Ace of Arc.
Oh, you're so fantastic.
Oh, my God!
You need to reach 80 mental darkness to prove...
Aww!
How...
I need to make her mentally...
You want mental darkness?
80?
That's so bad.
How do I do that?
That's terrible.
Is it this one?
Oh, I really wanted to do the fricking...
I wanted her to be a God.
But all these...
I'm going to run out of time in order to...
Oh, sugar.
I didn't read that in time.
Aww.
Mental darkness?
Okay, that's so cool.
Love it.
Bye.
Netlord.
No.
Wait, ego searching.
Ego searching, does it?
Yeah, yeah.
Love you.
This is amazing.
Oh, yay.
Shaky.
A is so high.
Check if any of your streams increase mental darkness.
Good call.
Okay, that one.
ASMR increases mental...
Mental darkness goes to 39.
Okay, okay.
I don't know if anyone's gonna watch a breakdown stream though 39 39 for sex
streams well yes if they both do it we'll do that one no breakdown time
we'll do it with the ice cream looking or something this is such a good
animation honestly well done as a dead team who goes this identify yourself what
me eating ice cream honestly hey hey hey the negative comments increase mental
darkness oh you're right no increases stress hi thank you for joining we are
currently trying to make her a god oh my god wait they actually animated it they
bolder time to me to I didn't I didn't think they were gonna do that you know
what else is creamy and trips over reef links are you in her chat right now
that sense like something you would say I wouldn't make her the god of ASMR yeah
this is where it brings mental darkness I'm not sure about that one she said hey
cuties I brought some ice cream today I am
with that bring mental darkness or stress I'm gonna leave that to see if
that brings a mental darkness I can't wait I can't wait to like I'll speed up
because girl you take it too long
ASMR reduces stress through should lower mental but yeah I'm gonna say like I'm
a smart stranger just like bing ching danger man okay I remember it's like
what are you eating it's a milk popsicle I've been expecting this what are
freaking Star Wars quoting right now I've been expecting you I also love ice
cream well wholesome super chat
and the fact that you skip most things you love to see
hey yo reef blends that's when you use super chat and that I bet it was I love
you wipes a tear away I don't think it's that kind of tear but you will need a
tissue after that stream I know about the rest of you but that face sure is cute
yeah or play buttons in the background oh that's such good detail that's like
really good detail that these small things that's good I like I like this
small details really mentioned something and then sudden changes let's see what
you guys thought please be careful my popsicle
how about you eat this ban but I hold on a minute I was a super chat thank you
angel huh you don't have to thank me in fact I'd love to put it in my mouth again
sometime bless bless amen amen we follow the cult of key angel bless bless this
was awesome oh stress is high I want mental darkness squat but stress low the
more that go the more and it feels so good oh my god it's such a mercy thank
god this is just the game huh the bond between us is finally broken wait a flat
land
hey what happened wait no my friend wait because I she just perished wait
seriously if you ignore her messages no wait she doesn't want me to be your
manager I got you a hundred K freakin subscribers and you don't want me to be
your manager anymore because we didn't cuz that freaking was tell I want my
politician and but seems like it's actually quite hot whoa whoa whoa one
two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen
fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen ninety twenty one two three four twenty four
endings bro yeah I'm not throwing up a freaking emojis are clearly you stop
talking to her when you hit under key you literally four days without answering
look I'm trying to get to help her achiever goes she said she wanted a
million I'm getting her a million okay if that means P Chan has to go a wee bit
quiet I'll go a wee bit quiet and you're in stream to get them all of I do not
think so there's no way wait this is who made the game one two three four five
six seven seven people came together to make this game honestly that's fantastic
seven people came together to make this game shout out to them I am blown away
by this game first time I played it I didn't really know what to expect but I
have to admit this is like 10 out of 10 experience I understand a flatline and I
didn't even get any end in all really this is the worst ending that is that's
fantastic I'm not even like mad or anything click anywhere to proceed the
end oh wait it's real fan art no way they used real fan art in the game that's
absolutely amazing that is so lovely holy crap that's real fan art I can't
click around to see what these bottom ones are for some reason but main that
is blown away absolutely blown away yeah see this is what I saw when I put it up
and I think this is Windows Vista that is actually love that's so lovely what a
lovely game like I know the yeah this is open to open I was like what kind of
game am I getting into the warning this game is set in a place sort of like
modern day Japan but also not any resemblance to real places entities
living are dead is just coincidental do not try any of the more extreme or
depressing action so I don't know what I haven't unlocked like action wise but
she's this game is big okay it is like you've read the warming properly right
yeah okay wow oh at least you're back in
oh I give it do you love me I love you I love love love you unhappy end world
or maybe I don't want to spoil it I'm gonna watch someone do all the endings
because this is fantastic I love this good game shout out to the day I'm I'm
so impressed with this game I think it's a 10 out of 10 I love met us met a
gameplay as well it kind of VTuber orientated ask type things and I very
I love the manager like VTuber manager like fucking grooming route that's
hilarious and wow oh so I've not unlocked all the fan arts as well they're all
zipped up in credits oh there's few I was gonna say there's no me seven oh wait
no producing staff one two producing staff one two three four five six seven
eight nine ten eleven twelve and wow published by playground I'm gonna have
to look I'm 10 out of 10 game I'll see if they've got anything else to play
because that was like so good such a good game it's she be live I could easily
watch you 12 more hours of this they said port and stuff oh my apologies my
apologies I'm a dumb dumb can read yes she is okay I will redirect into she be
is a shorter date today but I'm sorting out some clip stuff and I'm getting a
freaking new manager in place and I need to set that up and once I've done it I
have like hardly any responsibilities and I love it I don't want any
responsibility anymore right let me ensure that we successfully redirect
into sheepsters that was so good I did not expect that oh she be playing a
horror game mr. Hopes Playhouse is that a horror game as Bunny really it's all
wow I'm such a thoroughly enjoyed that thoroughly enjoyed that I know I know I
got I didn't even get a successful ending but that was good thank you for
the stream 10 out of 10 that was fun I had a lot of fun as well and freaking
hilarious I enjoyed my state I'm glad you did I do apologize it's shorter
tomorrow I believe we're playing James Cameron's avatar which is an eight hour
campaign and or maybe six hour actually if I zoom through it and then our
multiplayer game of this week is none other than old-school RuneScape that
will be an endurance stream as well so you can pop in at any time if you want
to make a fresh character you're more than welcome to I will tell you what
world we are on we will pick a server that is not populated so we can all fit
in because I'm not sure how many old-school RuneScapers there are I will
be doing a fresh account myself and I will also be getting premium but again I
will warn you tomorrow on James Cameron's avatar but just so you know if
you are interested in playing multiplayer games with me a old-school RuneScape I
will say the server and we can do a questing together I do recommend a new
account because I wanted to do some questing and then we'll get into the
meat of trying to do 99 cooking is my first ever 99 so I would love to do that
together okay right thank you so so much please enjoy she be she be weebie and
she's playing a horror game I think and thank you so so much for hanging and I'll
see you tomorrow won't I refling I better hmm needy needy streamer needs to
see you tomorrow and thank you so much let she be takeover okay let let she be
entertaining you okay