I'm sorry.
Bruh.
Everything is breaking right now.
Holy crap.
Everything has broken.
I can't even hear in-game sound.
I'm pretty sure I'm supposed to be here in the music right now.
Hold on.
I'm so sorry.
Everything broke from yesterday.
And my headset isn't registering sound at all.
I knew it wasn't.
You're lying to me.
Oh, the scuff isn't working.
Oh, here we go.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
No, I just had to test it with some music.
Okay.
I can now hear the title music?
Yes, I can.
And you can hear it too.
I don't know how loud it's going to be though.
Oh my god.
Anything that can break will.
Well, I didn't change a single thing from yesterday's drum.
Oh, I apologize for being late.
Little refunds.
That was horrific.
I haven't even been able to watch yesterday's words.
I know the next stream is starting.
How are we meant to keep up with your strongy?
That's the fun part.
I have endless stamina.
See, those details come really good later on.
Right, I don't, I need to, I mean,
I'll tell you what world we're in.
Right now I'm entering world 424.
But I want tutorial island.
So please don't worry.
What was that first song?
It was called Music Makes You Lose Control.
Music makes you lose control.
Let's go.
Please don't worry if you've not actually got your character
outside good ol' Lummi Castle, Lumbridge Castle.
I've not even done the tutorial part.
I do.
I'm playing with a plugin called Runelight.
But we're just going through tutorial island super quick.
I'm not.
Oh no, I just liked it a brand new.
Oh, we're doing an indepth in tutorial island then.
Ah.
I've actually been smart and I've prepared a whole meal.
It was absolutely chaos getting, like,
I was trying to get Runelight to work on screen
and I was trying to cook fricking my,
well, technically my breakfast, but I call it dinner.
But, and I actually have, like, the world's saddest fricking rose,
I think it's called, like, rosemary sauce when you have it with shrimp.
And, ah.
So, I do have membership.
As is in the finalized world, please,
I've not even got through this tutorial.
Right, let me just skip through this fricking tutorial.
Oh, my phone's in the way.
Oh, my God, no.
I can't skip this.
This is going to take so long.
Oh, right.
Yes, we'll talk to the survival specialist.
Look, that's what I'm eating right now.
Unironically, I'm eating that right now.
I'm good.
Wait a minute.
This game's based on real life.
How cool is that?
We're going fishing.
Would you fish me up?
Huh?
But anyway, good morning.
Good evening.
Good afternoon.
I apologize.
It's been fricking chaos.
Since there is no work tomorrow,
I'm commit to catch the full stream today.
No way.
Thank you for the tip, Virginia.
There is no way.
Literally.
Oh, ace the con, Snow Bear June, as well.
Thank you for the tip.
I'm about to munch on.
I've got bex, pate, oh.
Right.
And then I've got shrimp.
And then I've got a rose, a sauce,
while I've not made it correctly,
because I didn't fricking squeeze the water
out of the prawns.
Hi, ready?
Hi, acey and Snowberry Raiders.
But if you put all those words together,
it becomes reading.
Are you splitting me right now?
Strony.
You're eating marshmallows last night
inspired me to try to write something
to make your heart flutter,
because I think it's adorable.
Are you going to read more tonight?
I can definitely read more.
Thank you very much, Gramble, for the tip.
Yeah, I can definitely read more.
Oh, I'm sorry to...
Trying to eat and beat and vape
and do everything all at once.
Hi, we're playing RuneScape,
an old-school RuneScape.
We're going to play multiplayer
and do quests together.
I am called Scottlefish,
because I totally did not steal that from a roofling.
Thank you very much.
But yeah,
we're going to do good.
I am not...
I'm going to move to a free world,
but if you want to make a new account,
we are going to do, like, the free quest,
like, Cook's Assistant and that.
Where the heck am I supposed to go?
I don't know.
I'm not paying attention.
Now that you have logged, it's time to light fire.
Oh, okay, pardon me.
Pardon me, excuse me.
I'm going to take a bite.
Ah.
Hi, it's Trombone.
What a nickname.
I should have thrown it that bad.
See?
So I've got this plugin
called RuneLight.
And, at least, it's really good.
I think it's really good.
If the game needs to be louder,
please do tell me.
I actually think it does need to be louder.
Because I'm, like,
screaming over all the things.
What next?
Moving on.
Well done.
I've completely forgotten how
the tutorial goes,
because it's been so long.
I'ma take another bite of my food.
But, yeah, if you want to join in,
don't worry, you can literally
make a character right now
and be faster than me.
I will tell you what world we're on.
We're all going to meet outside
of Lumbridge Castle.
So whenever what world we'll get,
we will do a Chicky Lumbridge Castle.
And then we'll take it one by one
and we'll quest.
Right?
Let's start with Cook's Assistant,
because, obviously, this is a bit squished.
And my goal is to get 99 cooking live.
Like, not in this one stream.
Okay, not in this one stream.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
I don't know how to do that.
Although, I think of Fletching.
If you have, like, a ton of GP,
you can actually get 99 Fletching
in one day or something like that.
I can't remember.
I think it's Fletching.
You can kind of smurf of it,
smurf of the cheese of it.
All in one stream, crazy.
No, no, stop getting hype.
It's not happening in one stream.
Okay, quest journal.
Yep, you're going to do the free quest first
as best as we can.
And then we might move on to membership quest,
but I do want to give Beefling the chance
to come hang at Lummi Castle, the glum castle.
Any, any lummers?
Any hashtag, a lummer?
I'm taking a little bit.
It's super expensive for a member.
Yeah, it's really expensive, actually,
to do the thing, but, um,
membership in this game is so expensive.
I remember
I asked my mum
to buy me membership when I was away,
and it was, like,
cheap as anything, and she never got me it,
because she didn't understand what the game was,
and she was like, why do you need it?
Why do you need it?
I'm like, mum!
I want membership!
Ryan!
No way!
Are you...
You must have been so many iron reaper
that I managed to get an eight hour sleep
after that stream.
I don't know how long the endurance stream...
It was, like, three quid the last time I got it.
Honestly, I remember, like, begging my mum,
I was like, mum!
I want membership, but she never understood my games.
And then that's when I go to Dad.
See, Dad, Dad knew.
Dad knew what was going on. He knew the games.
Mum and Dad!
What were we doing?
I'm not talking, I'm right.
Hello, my name is Skullfish!
I still live.
I usually sleep four or five.
You guys all insomniacs, I got four hours.
Good enough for me.
Bro, that's not healthy, honestly.
I woke up and I felt sick today,
and I was like,
is that because
you will be told to equip items later?
You don't have access to the interface for equipment items?
Oh, okay, one more, thank you.
Right, shovel on now.
Oh, okay.
Are you squiddin' me right now?
Brian!
No!
Oh, I actually quite like that sentiment.
Thank you, Tim Shortle.
I think Tim Shortle's the way I'm supposed to say it,
because there's no way it's like any other way.
Right, let's go.
Combat interface, right?
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Oh, beautiful, let's stab.
Give him a little stabby stab.
Damn rats.
All right, hold on, hold on.
Nope, too far, too far.
Inbought, inbought.
I...
Whenever I've watched RuneScape Streamers,
they're always super zoomed in.
They're like, oh yeah, look at that.
And I'm like, bro,
I need to be able to see what I'm looking at.
I can see the health bar,
I can see everything,
and we battle down the area.
I'm not setting anything up
before anyone complains.
Chat sleep.
Chat needs to rest as much as me.
I've got absolutely no sleep at all.
Are you all insomniacs?
You're all...
Literally all holding on for the ASMR stream.
I'm getting my nails done
after the ASMR stream.
So I hope you're all ready.
Wait, what am I supposed to do?
Oh no, wait, sorry.
I'm supposed to do range weaponry.
Can I do it from through the gate?
Oh, I can.
It's cheating.
Didn't realize old-school room shape...
Oh, didn't realize old-school RuneScape membership is 8'9".
No!
Bro, the inflation has hands.
I'm sorry, but...
All these things being like,
oh no, cost of living.
Well, you're not paying your pay...
You're not paying your employees more.
So I don't know why we're pretending
the cost of living is a thing
for these companies.
That's it also.
You're doing your nails
for the sweet-eating stream.
Uh, yeah.
How else are you going to, you know,
do my hands?
You need to be able to imagine
my hand wrapped around...
That's terrible.
We're just started.
I was doing a lot of food filming.
Oh my god, I'm rich!
I'm rich!
We're rich!
I've got 25 coins.
Are you squeezing me right now?
Brian!
That's because I had problems sleeping.
Thank you for the tip, Tharya.
Oh my god.
Right, so you can do voting.
Like, if you're like hardcore,
well, it's not really actually,
but it's actually quite quick to get the...
Oh, I've just skipped past the bit that tells you.
Oh, what should we vote on?
Should Firelight a new level 77 demon bait?
Bro, I...
I've not...
Whoa, these are like the same question,
but different.
I have not...
I have not played enough RuneScape.
I'm like the basic RuneScape part, okay?
Before you think I'm going to start getting prayer pots out,
I'm going to start, uh,
what is it called?
Like, PKN.
No, I'm not PKN.
I'm not doing that.
I'm not happening.
No, I'm called Squatfish.
I've got membership 30 days left.
Oh, no, you can't see it because I'm a big ass, hey.
Who's grabbing this?
What world?
Okay, world can hold 2,000 members.
Okay.
We're very lucky,
but I don't think there's 2,000 recently
available at StreamSnipe.
So, uh, the good thing...
Oh god, it's probably a bit too heavy.
Please don't show my email and password.
That would kind of suck.
But then again, let's just throw away the purpose.
On the way to victory, to victory, to victory.
I'm on the way to victory.
So, into the church I go.
Hello, mister...
Hello, Mr. Brace.
Any bracers?
What is PKN?
Player killing.
It's when you attack players
and you sell the goods that they drop, basically.
But, uh, before anyone thinks I'm going to turn into PKN,
yeah, good luck, mate.
That's what happens.
I'm doing this tutorial right now.
I'm going to eat my food outside Lumbridge
so everyone can get a chance to group up
if you want to start on a new account
if you can go questing together.
So please don't panic if you think, like,
oh no, I've not got enough time to join in.
You absolutely do.
I am going to make it so.
I eat my foodies.
I've got a cola and two bottles of water with me.
Um, as for those of you interested,
if this is, uh, an...
Where the heck?
Oh, it's...
Where the heck am I supposed to go?
It's not blinking anything.
I'm grabbing the booze.
You will be shown how to cast spells.
When you get there, just talk to the magic instructor.
I assume you can hear them.
Oh, of course it pops up.
What are we doing?
I'll hop on.
We're going to just do basic questing
because I've started a fresh account
and we're going to try and get 99 Kooten.
However, open up your final menu.
Ah!
Am I done?
Okay, not yet.
We're about to teleport to Lummi
and then I'll pick a free-to-play server.
Um, and...
Oh my god, I'm casting the chicken.
You wouldn't cast the chicken, would you?
Would you?
Who goes there?
Everyone has some when you trust a lure into the world, eh?
Can I?
I'm so sorry, but I'm going to confess
my biggest sin,
and you guys honestly aren't ready for it.
I used to be double in money
and take people's money.
The biggest amount I ever took was 100K gold
and then I stopped.
I don't know how I didn't get banned.
I think because I did it in such low increments.
Um...
Right, send me to the mainland.
I'm so sorry.
I used to be the one at the Grand Exchange.
I was like a little kid
because what happened was
I got fricking scammed.
Hey, Scottfish, come over here.
Adventure or John?
Um, I got scammed
and then I realized, wait,
I can just scam other people
to get my money back!
Double in gold!
And I'm like, I got all the money I lost back.
It's time.
Officers, it's her.
Literally, I was like a little
nine-year-old hustler, like,
like, oh, it's terrible.
So if you ever got done at the Grand Exchange
because you were a silly, silly McGee,
guess what?
It was probably me!
We're gonna hang out at this fountain
at Lummi Castle right here.
We're gonna hang out at the little fountain.
I am going to Swap World.
Wait, why is it flashing?
It's...
Why it's flashing?
Right, what world are we gonna go to?
I'll make it a free-to-play world.
Where...
How do I...
Change worlds?
Whoa!
Oh, wait, wait, wait.
I think World Shifter's up here.
Okay!
Um...
Free-to-play trade?
No, it's got 900 people in it already.
Do we want free-to-play trade?
There's 900 people in it?
Jagex is watching you now.
They better not be!
I'm in trouble.
We're gonna hang out at Lummi Castle
until I've finished my dinner.
I'm trying to eat it on my breakfast.
Everything's set.
What world do we want?
Free-to-play is good.
Right, we'll just do the classic
free-to-play trade-free world 301.
There's 900 folk in it,
so we've got all the room in the world.
Take me...
Are you sure you wish to go to World 301?
Yes, sir!
Let's...
Let's cycle!
Okay.
I don't know where the heck the reef ones are,
so we'll come a little over to the fountain.
Oh, no!
What are they used?
I don't know.
We might need to...
I don't want...
Are these reeflings in game?
Wait, wait, wait.
We're gonna go over to the tree
to make sure these are reeflings.
Holy crap, are they?
Brian!
Evening, Alessandro.
Thank you for the tip.
Oh, my God!
They're reeflings!
Oh, my God.
Oh, you're looking at...
Wait, you guys are actual...
Some of you are actual players, though.
Oh, why are you so high level?
Oh, someone's got tiny cuttles.
That's funny.
Wait, you guys are like actual...
I miss Fauna.
It's such a good name.
Oh, my God.
Just yummy.
Hello, hello.
Oh, my God.
You guys are like actual skillers and stuff.
Good morning, reeflings.
They're saying,
Oh, that's crazy.
Strony surprise attack gamers.
I know, but I didn't know if you guys were going...
Oh, my God.
You stole my drip.
You look like me.
Oh, you guys...
You get stood on.
I see a Strony.
You guys are like so high level.
That's amazing.
You guys should probably teach me how to play the game.
Unfortunately, we can't...
What is that?
Why is he standing like that?
What does it mean?
Am I to raid him like a pony?
Oh, the guy's got the magma cape.
I've never done the magma cape before.
I have a stupid snowflake account.
So I won't join.
What does that mean?
I have a snowflake account.
Steals her legs.
Snowflake, by the way.
What does that mean?
Oh, my God.
Look at your fit.
Your outfit's so unique.
You're holding a puppy.
And you've got like little things going on on you.
Right.
A lot of you are like over leveled like heck.
What is this in his hand?
A fish.
Is that me in his hand?
Come on, guys.
Oh, why is your name that?
Oh, no.
Why would you rename yourself?
Trick or treat.
Let me take.
I don't think I get...
We want to see what you got, Sans.
Show us what you got whilst I eat my dinner.
Where did he go?
Wait, did he just disappear because I looked down for one second?
It says you guys want to trade me,
but I don't think I can trade because I'm a new account.
I don't think it works.
I think I need to go quest and to like unlock trade.
If you guys are wanting to give me anything.
Is it in the stream to trade?
Yeah, like I don't think you guys can trade me anything.
So don't worry.
We're going to go quest and RIP, yeah.
Wait, I'm getting the fish.
There's so many riblings.
Hello, riblings.
Thank you, everyone that can join.
Yo, we're deforestation out here.
Oh, they leveled up. Let's go.
Okay.
Trick it is.
Jeez.
Yeah, look.
Accept trade.
I don't think you can trade because I'm a new, new, new account.
What?
Are you giving me?
A rope and a fish?
Are you telling me?
Are you doing that?
No way.
You can trade that.
I have a fricking rope in my inventory right now.
Wait, can you only give me like World 301?
Yeah, this world is full sad.
Why?
Oh, the world is full.
Okay.
Wait, wait, hold on.
Right, we're going to move to...
We're not doing...
I don't know what these are.
The regular bought items can't be traded.
Okay, we're learning.
Right.
The world is full, so we're going to go to an emptier one.
Everyone get ready.
High risk world.
Yeah, no thanks.
I have a bow.
Is there like a really easy one we can get inside?
Clan Wars?
I don't know.
Do we get grouped on?
Are we technically a clan?
No.
These are just dead Oz servers apparently?
Are these American?
380.
Someone says 380.
Hold on.
380.
Right.
World 380.
And we're going to Brit Bungland.
Right, let's go 380.
World 380.
Wait, I'm double clicking.
Let me go.
380.
Grand exchanges limited to until you do quests or play for a while.
Now you have the fish.
You're canonically strong.
Okay, okay.
Oh, look at the replays.
Okay.
World 380.
How do you dance?
Oh my God.
It's been so long.
How do you dance?
I want to dance too.
I can dance.
I'm sure I can dance.
Hold on.
Let's go.
Grand.
Little dance.
Look at that.
What?
I'm stunning on them.
Look at them.
Whoa.
What in the pivot axis was that?
That was awful.
Don't ever do that again.
Right, we're clapping.
Okay, now dance honestly.
Grand exchanges limited to 8.
That's not a clan.
That's an army.
Oh yeah?
Will we do the refland clan and we'll go pk'ing like other clans or something?
As if I know how the combat works.
This only world where the text matters is PvP, high-risk, total and demo.
Right.
Are you ready to do the first official quest?
Or I say that as if I've even hardly eaten any of my dinner.
Hold on.
I'm trying to eat but I'm such a blabbermouth.
Honestly.
I can't stop.
I'm glad the refland's not stacking into one space.
Astroni can appreciate them each.
Yeah.
I'm still convinced that guy wants me to ride him.
Because he's like a horse, literally.
I'm so cute.
Still got people doing tutorials.
Yeah, don't worry if you're still doing tutorial island.
I'm gonna inhale my dinner really quickly.
I'm gonna try my best.
What is that noise?
You're all making noises.
I can't believe it.
I'm driving the bug.
I'm still trying to log in.
You're not giving people time to do the tutorial.
Only the players flexing their heads.
How many?
Oh my god.
Oh, that's just an MBC hand.
Oh, someone just leveled up.
Look at how high level you guys are.
Literally got the pepper, the frog over there.
I love mummy.
Oh my god.
Sad.
Like you're your name.
Just Yome.
You guys are like actual gamers.
Oh my god.
You're much better than me.
I'm like scared to play the game.
I'm like you guys are gonna show me off.
Quality player is determined by their agility and rune crafting level.
Yeah, yeah.
No one likes rune crafting.
You're not selling it here.
Get your propaganda useless out of here because you're not.
Rune crafting is the worst.
Unless you literally have an entire army behind you to help.
It ain't happening.
At the end of the stream you'll be that high level.
Ah, I think not.
Yeah, I need to have agility.
89.
You're really good at going in a circle then.
Jeez.
My brother was a Rinscape essence slaver for years.
Do you pay to like carry the thing?
Just don't please tell me.
Banks are for squares.
Are you an iron man?
Oh, so there's different types of players you can be.
If you're an iron man it means you don't have access to bank or something like that.
Guardians of the Rift is experienced also.
It's also experienced.
So will this be a 28 hour marathon?
No, no, I don't think it's a marathon.
I said yesterday I thought it was a marathon but I woke up and I don't actually feel that well today.
I can't believe it.
I can't believe streaming for 12 hours making me feel a bit wonky.
I don't know why because essentially I would sit at the PC and work on like it and for like ASMR or something like that.
But why is it when a streamer feels sick?
Like it doesn't make sense.
I feel weak in stream height honestly.
Free cuttlefish mustache rights here.
That's awful.
Oh, how did you...
What?
Ah, are you just cuttlefish right in front of us?
I didn't know Rinscape had emotes like this.
More active for streaming.
Maybe because you did it three times this week.
Me?
Isn't every strong stream technically a marathon honestly?
Damn, how does one become an essence run slave?
That's good money for that hour.
The members emotes go hard.
Strong party.
Heck yeah.
There's so many reflings.
The servers are like who on earth are all these people?
D refling.
I'll read out your name if it's refling related,
but I was trying not to accidentally say anything.
Who is leveling up there?
Freaking...
I can hear someone leveling up and it's always going doot doot doot doot doot doot.
Hello?
Jack the Ripper's coming to get us lads.
We're done for.
Maybe it was your screaming yesterday, bro.
I was so annoyed.
I listened back.
I didn't realise how angry I got.
Like I got angry.
Wow.
Oh, it's a skill cape or more?
Oh my god, he's got the fishing skill cape.
Ah, jacquem prongs.
Jacquem prongs, wee wee.
What is this freaking UFO over here?
What is that?
Oh, is that prey?
Is that questing?
You've done all quests.
Oh, you've got all the jelly.
Oh my god.
Wait, what's the cooking one?
Does anyone have 99 cooking?
What's the cooking or more?
Oh, I can't wait to get it.
Oh, look at us all.
Well, binchinning.
Binchinning.
How do I change servers?
Um...
I'm on the runelight, so it's plug-in, so it's up here.
But if you're not on the runelight plug-in,
it's...
Down the bottom somewhere.
Smile.
It's on the cog, I think.
I have two baked potatoes.
I've not even finished the first one,
and it's frickin' totey.
Like, it's so small.
I'm trying so I can't eat and talk,
and it'd be entertaining at the same time.
Quest cape, quest cape.
Ah.
Max capers shaming us all.
Click the top right eggs, then you'll see worlds switcher on the bottom.
The door icon to hop worlds is what they're saying.
Refillins are so MLG pro, honestly.
Like, we're not even gay people.
Oh, you're so green!
This refilling's, like, literally so green.
That's amazing.
Maybe we should...
Amala to tell us to all go buy green capes.
For strawney.
And then we all just walk around with green capes,
and, like, whenever we pass someone, they'll be like,
huh, what's going on over there?
Why are they all doing their thing?
Wishes to trade with you.
So, I can't accept anything outside of, like, regular trades.
I know.
You get...
You're giving me your crusty cum sock.
No!
Wait.
I have a crusty cum sock on my inventory.
How did you even get that?
Okay.
Gently used.
Literally gently used.
Right.
I'm gonna eat.
I'm gonna save maybe a five-minute countdown,
and then we're gonna start with Cook's insistent,
and we'll take it from there.
So, for those of you who haven't made an account,
we are on World 380.
And we're outside Lung Bridge Castle.
When you spawn in, we are literally just...
You'll spawn in this way, and we're the left of the castle.
We're just hanging out here,
because we don't want to bother anyone
that might be spawning in over here.
But I'm starting with the character's pink hair,
or my same pink.
Mine has ginger hair.
Like, I'm a junior.
Which thing?
And then I've got green top,
and then pink...
I think...
Prepared to get billied nerds!
I'm trying to eat so fast.
It's hard.
Honestly.
I hope you guys have got hydration and eating.
I don't know if it's an endurance stream yet.
Okay.
But...
Ginger hair, cute outfit, and a rope.
Yeah, yeah.
You can get at me.
380.
Yeah, 380.
The refling in the game, of course, is gonna be...
Don't stop until you get 99.
Bro, you think I can stream until 99?
Cooking?
I don't even know how to, like,
maximise cooking.
The closest I ever got was, like, 80,
but I'd rather do it live with you guys.
Buying girlfriend 50 gold.
What happened to party hats?
I don't remember people were, like,
renting party hats in quotation marks.
I don't know what that means at all.
Delicious coke.
I say delicious as if...
it's just not a regular fizzy juice.
Well, actually, it's, like, one of the most popular fizzy juices, so...
They decided not to have exclusive one-time items.
Oh, even though they're tradable?
I guess they didn't, like, give enough out?
Possible?
They can...
They became common.
Oh!
They made it common.
You go to a good place for cooking
and you cook till the number says 99,
or you run out of money.
With some of the fish.
Okay, you're done.
Oh, people are getting, uh...
minigames.
I was, like, I'm saying,
come along with me, Miss...
I Miss Fauna.
Wakey-wakey, I Miss Fauna.
Max Capers.
How much playtime?
232 days says one.
314 says another.
I can't believe my little...
My little reeflings are adorable little nerds!
I can't believe it!
You can do just a feckin' adorable!
Any language game?
That's so precious.
I'm glad you found a game
that you really enjoy
and can, uh, throw yourself inside.
It's... When you find that game,
it's really nice.
Anyway, Assassin's Creed Brotherhood,
let's get started.
Mmm.
Yesterday, Avatar,
No Capitalist Simulator.
This is all really a trust.
Someone says 63 days,
and I haven't even left this area,
uh, someone says 1,650 hours
for a total of 1,800...
I can't read numbers.
Uh, big number.
Big hours for big number.
Thank you.
Mmm.
Well, more reeflings?
Have we got more reeflings joining us?
Yeah?
Someone's got...
Oh, someone literally is called Swiss Oak.
A snowflake among snowflakes.
Wait, what am I missing?
What is this?
Is this, like, super runescape terms
that I don't know about yet?
Or is this literally, uh,
take the word heart
and remove the H and replace...
Remove the H and E
and replace it with an F.
Relax, snowflake.
It's called Dark Humor.
Is that the joke?
Or am I missing Platinum?
Respect for the Iron Man.
Snowflake accounts are accounts
that have extremely restrictive stipulations.
What does that even mean?
You've somehow...
You can't...
Snowflake is a special account.
Wait, the Venezuelans are the snowflakes?
Game is not degen enough.
We need to make it harder.
What the heck?
Honestly.
I think this girl in crossbones
means this guy's a p-care over here.
I'm okay.
Can only do content in a region.
Jeez.
One guy's playing the game
where if he takes damage,
all...
Oh, I know!
Uh, the...
Swamplet X guy.
Yeah.
I've not actually watched that series.
The No Hits run series,
but, yeah.
Region locked.
Oh, settle!
That's his name, not Swamplet X.
I have still not finished
the first fucking potato.
I'm actually getting annoyed now.
Why is the food not getting away
off my plate?
I'm inhaling it.
I'm so sorry.
I'm just gonna have to send it.
I can't.
I'm getting too distracted
trying to, like, talk into this.
I'm sending it.
This is the fastest freaking
eating you'll ever hear of me.
I'm chewing.
I've got another bit of potato.
I've never done this.
And, um...
Okay, I've had enough of eating.
I'm already bored of it.
I should weigh myself, honestly,
just so I don't lose too much weight,
because I stream too much.
I was actually wondering about that,
because I've not had a proper meal.
I'm, like, ages...
Ow.
I'll cut, I'll cut.
Done.
I'm a finger blade for my fucking plate.
I've tried to eat it.
It's taken too long.
Right.
Okay.
I was trying to eat a baked potato
in prawns, and it was just taken forever.
Oh, I've had enough.
Right.
Is this everyone who wants to show up?
Um, can chat, talk to me,
and tell me, is everyone here
that wants to be here?
Talking with your mouth full,
ASMR's running really...
It's fine.
Stop!
If that counts as ASMR,
then I've got a ton of content for you.
Okay, is everyone who wants to be
questing, is in the game right now?
Is anyone in Tutorial Island?
Someone says they're late.
Okay, we'll wait.
We'll wait.
We'll get a few more minutes.
Right.
If we've got a few more minutes,
it's time to start telling jokes.
Why did Ernest the chicken
cross the road?
To get to the other side.
Oh, thank you.
Thank you.
If you didn't know there's a quest
called Ernest the chicken.
Thank you.
I feel your pain.
Yes, do re-log in on your questing account
to render the other side.
I'm here.
I've never opened this game before.
Okay.
We'll stand outside the castle this time.
We're just gonna be right outside the castle.
If you want to start on a new quest
on the account just to have the shizz and giggles,
we are going to do a main quest.
Oh my god, there's so many reflings.
It's over.
Thank you so much for joining me.
I'm being the law.
I'm like so fucking happy.
Like, I don't realize that like,
oh my god, that's a lot of this playing.
Right.
Don't forget the riveting tale of
lily pad labor dispute, honestly.
I'm down for some shingles.
Okay.
Why is his name erinist?
I honestly didn't know.
I can't even remember.
I hardly remember.
I'm here, but I've never opened this game before.
What world?
I am on world 388.
Do mods have pinning?
Can mods pin?
World 388.
Free questing.
I might work some unable to participate,
but have fun, Strony reflings.
Oh, thank you.
We will.
I don't think mods can pin.
Okay.
Can I pin?
Hold on.
Ow, don't, don't, don't.
Where's YouTube?
Can you open up one stream?
Strony, cartels.
Tape it in.
Oh, I'm live.
I'm live right now.
Tape it in.
Oh my gosh, I'm live right now.
Pin message.
There we go.
Beautiful.
Strony, after the bloke completion,
what do you think about the bad jokes completion?
Honestly, we should.
Wish us to treat.
I'll take anything.
I've got a crusty sock in my inventory right now.
Oh, should I?
You're giving me a chef's hat because I want cooking.
Yes.
Yes, put the hat on me.
Please, please, please, please, please, please.
I want the hat.
Check it out.
You can even see my bunches around.
Oh, look at it.
Cool.
Thank you so much.
Look at the hat.
Oh my God, check it.
Check it.
Check out the drip lads.
Yeah.
Yeah, I'll show you.
Check it out.
Oh, I'm going to.
I'm going to stale on them.
You ready?
We're going to stale on them.
I got that stale.
Stale.
Hey, hey, hey.
Hit them with the dab.
Oh, put it away.
Put it away.
Wee.
Level one cooking.
Level nine cooking.
Here we go.
Everyone here that would like to be here.
This is him.
I drink za.
The thingy.
She's cooking.
Very snazzy.
Drip check.
Certified cooking stream.
Okay.
First quest.
Open up our little quest adventure menu.
Where the heck is that?
I can't see because the iPhone's in the way.
Excuse me, iPhone.
I'm here to do something.
Right.
The quest is called.
Cook's assistant.
Oh, oh, here it is.
I'll read it out for you as for those of you that are blind.
Cook's assistant.
I can start this quest by talking to the Cook Lumberge Castle.
Difficulty novice.
Very short.
Release 2001.
Jeez.
Storyline.
Stand alone.
No requirements and no none.
Wait, someone else wishes to trade.
I don't, you guys can't give me like main stuff.
I am.
I'm going to head to bed early.
And I'll use the stream as a sleep bed.
I hope I don't wake you.
No way.
I've got a penny.
No.
I have a penny as well.
Oh my God.
Wait.
Sorry.
Hold on.
Camera angle.
Oh my God.
I'm a real freaking woman.
Oh, let's go.
I look so good.
Thank you for the penny.
Thank you for the chess hat.
If you want to gift you games, how do we do that?
You don't.
I buy them with my hard earned cash.
Cold hard cash.
Right.
Let's go.
Cooks assistant.
I'll turn off running.
We'll just walk.
Right.
You ready?
Lumberge castle.
Do you mind?
I don't know.
Come reflings.
You can follow me if you want.
Wait.
Who are we fighting?
Why are you fighting that per man?
Right.
Oh my God.
Women's simulator.
Time to head to the kitchen.
Oh my God.
There's so many.
Right.
This cook is like, why are all you people in my kitchen right now?
Yes.
Cook.
What's wrong, Mr. Cook?
Oh dear.
I'm in terrible trouble with mess.
It's the Duke's birthday today and I should be making him a big, lovely birthday cake.
I've forgotten to buy the ingredients.
I'll never get them now.
He'll sack me.
What will I do?
I have four children and I go look after.
Honestly.
Me with the...
What?
I have five babies but one of them is a goat.
He has four babies and a goat.
What are the odds?
Yes.
We're going to help Cook's assistant.
I'll help you.
Oh great.
Oh.
My little quest helper just popped up.
Where do I find these ingredients?
I think I remember where they are so I think we can just walk away.
Do I need to pick up a pit?
I think...
Do we need this jug?
Wait.
Are we all going to be fighting over the same jug?
Do we not need a jug for this quest to put the milk in?
Save yourself and run.
Buy eggs here.
100 cold coins.
Sell an egg.
No.
Do we not have to pick up the big egg and the milk from the dairy?
Am I going crazy?
Isn't that like one special big egg and one special thing?
I've got 25.
Best I can offer.
Real cheap.
People are thinking you are doing a drop party or something.
All the folk following.
Oh.
No idea.
I'm like...
Yo.
You guys have money?
I can go get some jugs and drop them.
Man's running a scheme.
I respect it honestly.
Are you guys grabbing all his equipment?
Okay.
Right.
We can take off and get the egg.
Go to the front of the castello.
If everyone has accepted that quest, we'll go to the front.
I think they changed it.
Okay.
Right.
Oh no.
It does look like we're a drop party.
I'm broke so I can't afford any eggs.
Don't worry.
I'm going to take you to the egg factory.
It's me.
Plop.
Okay.
Oh my God.
We look like a drop party so badly.
Right.
We're going to the river.
The chickens aren't going to stand a chance.
Yeah.
So the cow milk and the eggs are across the river.
If you follow me...
Oh my God.
Strongly lays eggs.
I was going to do ovate deposit.
I'm not even going to pretend otherwise.
We call these people hurting the goblins.
Il goblina village.
We're going to milk a cow.
Milk the cow.
We need it straight from the teeth.
You know?
A normal egg works just fine.
Yes.
Has YouTube ceased the culling?
I think so.
We actually are submitting for monetization today.
Can I milk your cow or do I need a bucket?
Oh, I milked it.
But that's because I had a jug?
Wait.
Did I milk it or am I going crazy?
She goes, Teehee, you've never milked a cow before.
How could you tell?
Because you're spilling milk.
What a waste.
You need something to hold the milk.
Oh.
Oh, no.
Where'd you get a bucket in this game?
Right.
We'll go get the eggs then.
Eggs first.
We'll deal with a bucket problem in a minute.
Buckets are from the tutorial.
Worked for me.
I don't have a bucket.
Oh, no.
I already have a bucket of milk.
What the heck?
I already have a bucket.
I've already got a bucket of milk in my inventory.
I don't know why she said that to me.
Cheeky rat, honestly.
Egg time.
We go get the eggs.
That's the only thing about the RuneScape plugin.
I can see the price of everything.
You guys want to watch me beat up a chicken?
That's right.
Violence.
Rage against the machine.
Take this.
Oh, I just killed it with Kung Fu.
That's right.
And I know three other dangerous ones.
I didn't drop an egg.
All right.
Okay.
Let's all beat up the chickens and get eggs.
Beat the chickens up.
We're going to gang violence these chickens.
Literally the whole gang of us coming.
Someone's casting Shadow Wizard Money Gang.
We love casting spells on chickens.
Oh, my God.
There's like so much.
It's just hard to see anything.
Oh, my God.
I need to like zoom right in.
Beat that chicken up.
No, you stole my chicken.
Wait.
I'm going to take this egg.
Right.
I have an egg.
So I'm going to stand here because I've got one.
But make sure you get an egg before you move away from this section.
Have a good day.
Hey, I'm me, man.
We play and if you have an egg and you have milk, you're allowed to stand at the gate
with me.
Come on, you succeeded.
Beat them, beat them chicken up they're level one show me whose boss show me his boss.
Oh, oh, oh, Hidden The Grady hidden the grady.
Oh show him again, dude.
Do it again.
Do it once.
This dude again.
We just got some funny, we use caps.
We enormous needs were down to their own Cass, the other oh, oh.
it's a chicken massacre this date will go down in history is the chicken
hey he jumped in for joy or is he jumping for joy
I made it to where you are said hi and left oh do you need to go work show that
chicken with boss be more be more right oh no the gates close sorry we need to
open the gate to let the reasons come in and out there they're a bit slow like
me how many so what I think we've still got a few refunds behind that are
getting eggs he had got a few stragglers that's okay that's okay you guys
gonna get them eggs jugs ahead hey yo oh you dropped jugs oh for the refunds
that skip tutorial island there's a bucket in the house by the way
got a few more oh his heads just straight up off okay I don't even know
RuneScape did cosmetics like this I guess because of RuneScape 3 cosmetics
like this I've got egg and milk good good that's what be that in pop gang violence
on that and be a be that in pop that's what you get that's what you get for
coming around these parts when we're doing cooks assistant is there any more
stragglers or is that everyone these I think these are just actual I can't
believe it I think these are just actual players is that all my rooflings is
anyone behind I don't think anyone's behind it sir I need head oh I shouldn't
stretch it I love it here everything your level 3 you might be everything that's
coming along I love women right I think that's everyone okay next we need to go
to the flower mill we are gonna cross this lovely little bridge okay you're
welcome to follow if you click on me you could follow and you don't even have to
think I'll take charge we don't take that can be arranged there is another
chicken pan near the windmill oh I didn't realize oh no he got caught in the
bridge I'm sorry she doesn't know the bridge lore it's an evil bridge is it
oh no we are walking and the windmills up here oh there is a chicken farm
outside the windmill good crap by myself I couldn't make a new camp but my
can't stop pretty fish what you never done cook system before we like it when
you take charge story did you like my post yesterday I was actually kind of
hard to shove together we're gonna grab some of the I have I just real playing
them doing it yeah it was amazing we'd love to join but jog eggs locked your
well thankfully there are gonna be more multiplayer right everyone pick up
some wheat yankers make sure you've got one bit of wheat go on reeflings I will
teach you the how good it is to look at all harvest and oh my god I've got you
use look like slaves oh no this isn't good you you look like I'm like running
like a factory or something is everyone got a bit of flour are we a wee bit
green are we it does not look good that does not look good honestly instead of
a like people are like no no reflet no no you're not seven I read that in game
oh close the door on the refling who did that right everyone climb ladder we
need to go up to the top we are not caught we promise literally people
thinking it's a drop party and we're all just like harvesting right drop your
wheat into the hopper and then you pull on the lever at the top of this wait are
we pulling it for each other okay I think that I think it's still in
yeah okay and then if we go down to the bottom yay it's waiting for us and now
we have everything we need wait wasn't the point to have an army of slay oh why
do you walk like that that's actually really freaky I'm sorry but why do you
walk like that honestly is that like a thing why do you walk like that oh that's
so creepy I don't like it feels like something that's changed like chasing
yeah wrong lever crunk how do you increase render distance I can't see
anything I have no idea I'm using runelite plug-in so I can see like this
far but I don't need to like focus on this really wait do we need to pay this
to be slaves no we do it for free I think to the he wants you to mount him
ah he's scary it's thanks to the banana they're wielding the banana makes your
legs open up oh okay okay when I said it out loud it makes sense that his legs
do that is everyone got their wheat I think so
there's slaves and then there's like I think everyone's got their wheat just
to make sure all the reeflings are following yeah okay we're gonna make it
back to the castello
you're strong independent man chat
mmm when do you drown them in the sea I don't want to do that I know it's a part
of my lore wheat or weed oh it's not another word that sounds the same wheat
I'd like to harvest some wheat I'm gonna smoke some wheat
when you're drowning we should go port sarum and vade the sea shanty at some
point yeah we should but we'll literally just blast the music on film she's
taking them to the river I know we're going to the castello to hand in the
quest items I'm not only strong but I'm also fat and ugly hell yeah we are not
hive mind I promise what is that what is that what is that cosmetic what is on
your heat you look bizarre right everyone let's totally not freak out
unfortunately corners are a bit rough for the follow mechanic so you might get
caught on a corner it's very plausible here's the a bunch a bucket of milk
here's a pot of flour and here's some fresh eggs oh you brought me everything
I need I'm saved thank you so did I get to go to the juke's party I'm afraid not
only the big cheeses get to dine with the juke well maybe one day I'll be
important enough to sit on the juke's table maybe but I wouldn't be holding my
breath oh stay on congratulations you have completed Cook's assistant you
are awarded one quest point and 300 Cook next P total quest points one oh
we're actually we are so MLG we don't even know it oh let off cooking level
four you see that juicy juicy juicy call it juicy jay cuz we doing it
everyone handed in the quest right next quest hmm what's a really easy quest
that's free it's earnest to chicken easy level four that's like halfway already
exactly we're almost there like I'm not reffing the gear for nothing oh what's
the easiest next quest X marks the spot someone says oh sheep shearer definitely
sheep shearer right let's do sheep shearer next we can start this quest by
talking to Fred at his farm in northern Lumbridge so we are we're actually just
there I'm like that's me okay that's Fred so literally we just need to go up
again okay we're going to do sheep shearer not to be confused with what the
Welsh are associated and actually I could talk about that the reason why the
Welsh are associated with that because it wasn't it's illegal to steal someone's
sheep but it wasn't illegal at the time to mm-hmm a sheep I'll wait outside to
get everyone all you need 23 inventory slots pause pause pause pause hold the
line hold the line what's going on we need 20 inventory space right get to the
top of that castle and shove everything in your bank we are not letting a gold
coin go to waste in this operation get up them stairs right now we are going to
the bank if you check if you click on the quest the plug intrusion what you
need for the quest me who was ignoring it wait why why is quest helper open wait
did I oh it's cuz we've not accepted the question right get upstairs twice and
then everyone get to the bank and empty your inventory we need sheep shears for
this quest so you can probably just drop everything I'm not even getting bank
that bank man's like who's Sunday lunch at Sunday lunch oh no no I don't want to
set a pen in front of everyone everyone can do my pen yes yes I already did the
tutorial I don't know why you're telling me this take a hydration check if you
haven't had it yes yes yes yes yes mr. bank or mrs. bank one or the other do
not make me set a pin right in front cuz I can't right there right we're just
shoving everything inside oh like that boom
do I need to hold anything I don't know we can always come back if we need more
quest items say Nate a banking the English later redefined it by taking it
to you Dizzler wishes to alright what were you what were you showing us how
you're gonna flakes on us what you've got what I am you got dragon claws be
honest what I am oh no you you can't give me that I'm a new account you can get
me that wait why would you trust me with that kind of no oh my god that's
going to the cooking fun get that in the bank we can get interest on that right
now oh my god that's going to the cooking fun get in get in the bank put
them all on the bank oh my god oh my call payment thank you for the money oh
my god well when we when we do our finisher question and we actually start
leveling up cooking I'll I'm gonna take a look at a guide if you're finished at
the bank I'll wait for you outside Lumbridge okay outside the castle we'll
just stand and wait outside the castle as long as your inventory is empty and
we're gonna do sheep shear quest he was communicating on Morse code with a
emotes on the screen already actually and oh my god that's going to the money
fund I don't know what the fastest way to do cooking is I think it's sharks I
want to say it's sharks but sharks are so expensive because they're hard to run
okay let's make sure all the reeflings that I still tell it terrifies me to this
day um cooking is wines I thought pay to play is it really wines and then but it
costs money okay okay okay we're learning we're learning I really hope that guy
gives us shears or I'm gonna cry wait why do I have no weapon drew on me
probably gonna get rolled in battle if we have to do a battle thing you can
proc it you can profit if you do cook thingy except trade were you were you
gonna flex on his dragon claws next a wizards ha candles ha oh you wouldn't
give me candles how me when my stream is late wait hold on me when my stream is
late a streamer is never late or early he arrives precisely when he means that
we're doing the cooking I think cooking looks better with the bunches yeah you
can't even see my eyes Gandalf bought cringe what
dairy oh Gandalf bought cringe okay okay all right I think that's all my
reeflings my little reefy reeflers why why take the banana off it just
literally hunting around killing rats are your legs higher no right we were
gonna make our way to sheep shears let's go we'll walk cuz I don't want anyone to
get left behind I don't know how many quest points I need and in order to do
like to be unblocked strong either blue would that would I be strong even
green surprise exam oh someone's got an NPC a NPC event oh the farmers in here
it should be here the quest starts surprise exam oh this reeflings so
tired oh no he's like behind refling oh no he's going for the tree right talk to
the farmer first shears 100k no that's terrible there's shears in here shears
100k talk who's closing the door in the reeflings wait who did I talk talk to Fred
the farmer Fred's in the second room here that's price go jig I'm looking for
a quest okay yes we can share your sheep we're to avoid the thing because there's
one sheep that's not like the other is okay I can do that good now that's one
oh we do need shears hold on a minute oh oh no Fred gives your shears okay the
farmer will give you shears see that see that refling out there that's done that
hustle for a hundred K he just gives you it for free okay okay we need to spin
wool back it oh we need all the way back to Lumbridge Lumbridge Castle after
this anyway right everyone hop over this little thing here make sure the
whale shark doing this quick guess to that do you see the thing in the pen
we're gonna look for there is there's the thing it's like a person role-playing
oh it's a penguin hello can I shear or does it just back off oh why is it just
around the thing no don't hurt the sheep you can shear sheep for free you don't
need to perish the sheep in order to shear on refunds you're so you're so
aggressive right I've got one you need we all need 20 so we're gonna be here for
a hot second we're all gonna like streams we're gonna be sniping sheep shearing
I'm getting stream sniped on shearing sheep and runescape go they're not gonna
grow back quick quick quick we need to do it I need to be the first one to get
all 20 okay there's another one there's another one get right get right I'm
gonna hug him I'm gonna hug him by doing two at once no no no no I need these
first I need these first if you've got 20 you need to stand outside the pen so
we know the first person did it is I'm getting a lot I'm getting a lot I'm
getting them oh I'm getting them come on I'm at your first I'm at your first
oh I don't know if you guys are like starting faster than me you're right
you're right was a one two three four five six seven eight nine two I'm on ten
I'm on ten I've got ten more no you guys are sniping the sheep too fast oh my god
you guys have ping advantage stop your chin I didn't even there's a way you can
get in the pen from there I know the reflux are gonna beat me oh god no one
get right get right oh this is so dumb but I love it
literally all of us are chasing these perches she the sheep are like I've just
grown that rude oh oh I'm will wars literally forget like Gellinore games
forget winter is it hot winter taught or taught or something we're literally
stream sniping sheep she ran I can't wait for the cow grinding honestly we'll
probably need to get levels up together like so we're not like in danger of
dying stop you saved me I can't believe we forget stipend these sheep per sheep
were forced to be stripped over no who is perishing the sheep you don't need
person to harvest the will the penguins are part of the fun members quest oh
aren't they I didn't know that one two three four five six seven eight nine ten
eleven twelve thirty forty fifty sixty seventeen what seventeen I'm actually
just gonna do full inventory I think guess night guess night I was before I
was before I'm actually so much better than you guys at runescape even hardly
even played this game who's levelling up their combat you're really being these
poor things up get right guess night guess night guess night I got it guess
night literally I saw you I saw the way you were walking over to that that sheep
life is hard in runescape world honestly but wouldn't it be fun like this is
imagine if all you had to do was like share sheep and then you get paid coins
for a grand exchange you can go like get food and stuff I'm actually camping the
sheep right now I'm like camping it wait you guys are cheating you're right
behind me I'm like camping the sheep come on I have faith oh this what oh I must
have 20 no the refling one someone's already outside and you're outside as
well or did you not do the quest pretty sure it's a real job to be a sheep sure
I mean yeah where do I sign up to do that right I have got it so I it's no
longer highlighted for me I think so I just need to wait until you guys are
already and you've got your 20 and then we're gonna waddle our way back to
Lumberge Castle if only there was a job in real life that involves shooting
sheep some sort someone should coffee runescape honestly I think we're getting
there we're getting a few more refling joining in I think you guys are getting
close to being you are getting beaten up someone is half health over here I mean
you got a little more what's that oh you got boxing gloves check them out oh my
god you got necko ears oh my god it's discord kitten oh oh oh him with a fake
out him with a fake out oh oh oh oh flow like a butterfly stinging like a bee
peon peon peon I'm looking for his father again chest but what a $5 per hour
to shear sheet oh first rough I think some of us are still shearing we're still
shearing away don't worry we're still call us Ed Sheeran cuz when your legs
any work like they used to about for war we're still ed sheeran these sheeps
wishes to trade what you're gonna have you're just gonna have a load of cotton
you're giving me cabbage and and goblin mail I don't think I can put got a
goblin a male on why are you just giving me stuff cuz you can wait it's too small
yeah the armors too small for a human but I've got kebab oh I got giving a
kebab let's go being on and out necko ears boxing gloves and programmer socks
oh did we spot a femboy in the world can I offer you an egg in these trying
oh what's this wait what is that why is it called 10 oh eight one oh it's an
Easter egg oh I thought his name was actually the number femboys and my
escape more likely than you think what on earth is great why what are you
planning with our legs that's dangerous why what the what do you do with the egg
it says I don't want to eat it examine the egg it just says happy Easter grand
exchange average it's worth 10 okay toast macaroni right I am going to stand
outside the pen so if you're finished stand outside the pen with your
gatherings I'll go back to walking speed but we'll see if the reeflings are all
finished shearing we've got our little seller of our was I was it called
investor we could charge us as far too much money there's a few more reeflings
so we'll hang fire as a five-two guy I basically have to become a femboy so
there's a that's that's a whale sentence as a five-two guy I basically have to
become a femboy to have it what and that statement is whale that's the state
but that is way old say that why would you say that we're literally the same
hey oh you give me pissy oh don't mind if I do what is it it's a tuna oh we can
cook it later when we have enough for cooking who we've got a reefling reefling
and another reefling and four reeflings that we're waiting on oh look I'm
sheared away look up sheared way Brian hey strongy got a dip out now for work
have fun at work still gaming once I'm out I'll try and catch up if not I'll
try and catch up off-screen thank you so much thank you for the tip and yeah don't
worry I don't know how long we're going for today I need to figure out I don't
know if but you're a girl I got a booty hole and hold on a minute I don't know
I mean it what's going on here 80 to over stream do you honestly think I'm
capable going 82 hours I mean if you try
wonder how far I could eat strong he's in strong because she's short honestly
true here we go um ever ever I am snaper isn't moving I'm not sure if they're
playing or if they're doing something their character hasn't moved so I don't
know I think we might very slowly move on strongy more like shorty how do you
shot is like a melody in the morning that I can't keep from me sing this way
oh he just logged out all right I think we can progress reeflings we're on the
move to Lumberge Castle you can follow me and it should automatically follow you
up there are headless we fling sir gold foot running sailing sheep shears 50k
shorty more like shouty you making will like this damn girl what does I even
mean someone says holiday event no I don't know it's not a holiday event I
don't think it's like winter tall or anything like that oh sorry on the
corner sorry on the corner I should maybe wait okay we need to go up the
stairs once and then we have access to the spinning thing that you ain't
Cinderella being sure it was average then recent generations came and everyone
suddenly became six foot I think because of malnutrition I believe it
there's an event and old school runes keep going on right now right everyone
spin your will and get that craft an XP spin that will spin it's close oh my
reeflings are we all in the bedroom together we couldn't possibly be so
dastardly oh it's okay schools it's close at the door on the reeflings
be you're literally the door closer right you need to spin all of the will
you go on this little thing over here dips going first so much white string
oh my gosh what's gonna happen I wish can you like sit on the bed like in
Sims nah you can't do none of that someone's done press up next to that no
wait is press up some more how we how we do our thing which ones press up that
have it I don't have it locked whoa there's like tons I've premiered oh no
and everyone knows that I paid money to be premiering alright oh no I can do a
kiss in the bedroom there I can do a little kiss I can spit I'm spending on
the tip right now you just don't know I'm spinning we well I'm jumping on I'm
jumping on that shit get it yeah yeah yeah this is worth a garden in 99 how
have you got garden in 99 I see oh is it why is there a dagger at the bedside
table I'm getting nervous I'm gonna shake it everyone fight and laugh at the
preem you can make a peep in RuneScape chat if you type a QPW but I've never
I don't know what that is yes and we're not gonna leave until we're all finance
is this Emmy's bedroom what because it's medieval or mercy why am there's
nothing that really indicates honestly it looks like a dungeon so wouldn't it be
sheepsters you don't keep a knife in your oh the knife next to the bed oopsies
Emmy always has a knife on right as everyone spun their will they better
have I'll wait outside the castle but everyone needs to spin that will you
need to spin that will K bedroom ERP sessions over time to spin that will
right well it's out the castello we'll wait for you outside the castello don't
worry everyone point Phil which do not tempt those innocent refilling may your
will rot in your hands I say such such things who is a cow oh my gosh who I hope
that's no refund that can't be I think it's just a thinking that's an
incredibly incredibly unique
BRB a scream truck is here I'm gonna take a drink of water some of their snowballs
don't get no balls no balls no balls thrown at me how do you throw snowballs
how do I do that I don't have it I can only bow please wait are you hurt me no
oh it looks like you're hurting my goodness it's too bad known ball is
members what's known ball I've never played it before now is this all the
leaflings I'm gonna I'm gonna beat it I'm gonna beat it up take this yeah we're
definitely gonna have to level our combat so we're a bit more efficient it's like
American football okay okay can I be a cheerleader you remember no man people
you can do that in game stop I'm gonna take a knife I'm gonna not a good
I think that's everyone right there's no way that anyone is still spinning will
at this point we're moving on to the farm going back on to the farm come on
replaying so what the plan is is we're gonna do the easiest free quests first
and then we're actually gonna take a proper stab at leveling up cooking okay
thank you you can tempt me all you want my body is ready man's ghost pyro is
true we're like ducklings following the mother duck because my voice is horse
that's actually perfect for making that noise a little echo going strongy
teaching us to cook so we can survive no I'm gonna cook for you I need night
night cooking so all my rooflings can have really healthy meals every night
okay that sounds like a plan right open that door Fred farmer open that door to
what are you doing on my land I need to talk about sharing these sheets oh how
are you getting on with the balls of wool I have some give them here then that's
the last of them I guess I better pay you then just don't be too friendly now
congratulations you complete sheep shearer you've got quest point 150
crafting and two quest points we're getting so emily oh everyone's leveling up
their their craft and I can hear all the noises members can now craft cups and
polish buttons I too am a button polisher I'm actually have many years of
experience in polishing my button it is absolutely atrocious and far too easy
our next quest what's the easiest quest
someone said X marks the spots easy actually don't storyline it's very short
I can start this quest by talking to Vios and share drum that's a very someone
who's a demon slayer yeah I'm starting demon slayer okay if we go back where
we came from we can do X marks the spot I actually don't recall doing that quest
so let's get phone we're gonna do X marks the spot
are you level 99 yet we've not even started I'm level four hello today this
is the new bot form literally do you think Jack X is watching over us like
what on earth is going on like why is this event happening where am I
him him okay in the corner we're like literally sorry I completely forgotten
could go vibe in ports around bar for 10 hours all we cannot just get drunk and
start like sharing stories forbidden right it's right here okay let's see what
X marks the spots all about I don't actually know I'm just beating up a man
I don't have any I'm like literally oh no oh I don't really want to be up a man
oh no am I gonna win I might die here I don't I'm gonna drop my Easter egg if I
die oh no I think I'm okay there's a pub fight immediately literally such a true
Scott oh his bones are just hanging out oh that's a shame let's bury them sorry
mate so I'll bury you in the pub he died exactly where he loved it right who am
talking to the man in robes hello there I'm looking for a quest hmm well now that
you mention it I could do with some help the names be off I'm a treasure hunter
from the wondrous king of great current great current where's that across the
sea to the far west it's truly magnificent place interesting so what
brings you to Lumbridge I am here on a bit of a hunt the hunters treasure back
in my home of great me I came across a scroll I believe it'll lead me to
something of great value alas I've hit a bit of a blocker the scroll has led me
but here but as I don't really know the area I'm not sure what to do next maybe
you can help with this sure we need a spade take the scroll it should lead you
to the treasure I seek once you've found it meet me at my ship it's docked near
ports of rem all we're gonna go to ports of rem anyway anything else I need to
know you probably want to spade I find they're pretty much always needed when
it comes to treasure hunting check the general store if you don't have one I'll
be sticking around a little longer okay thank you right everyone to the general
store I have 63 gold so I can share it out the general stores just this from
across the street just go across the street I do have I do have 63 coins so
I could probably buy right let's talk to him can I help you yes what are you
selling I would like one oh no wait my cost wait can I buy it bye oh no is this
limited is there only two spades left for you guys it's not looking good brother
you need to buy spade off that guy but I snore can grow that would you be not the
bouncer shit a certain dominant 99 prayer yeah good luck with that unless you
guys are gonna be my bodyguards and like feed me dragon bones which I don't even
have the money for yeah 99 prayer ain't happening oh no there's no more
speeds right I will trade the speeds okay don't worry we're all gonna share a
speed okay we'll share the speed so don't worry if you've not got a speed
just come outside and we will share the speed my map is telling me I need to go
down I don't know where sorry I'm new to the quiz
within the town of Lumbridge lives a new a man named Bob who walks out of his
door and takes one step east seven steps north five steps west and one south
once he writes he digs a hole where he buried his treasure yeah
hi mom right I'm back what did I miss we're currently doing X marks a spot so
reeflings don't worry we're gonna share spades I'll share spades with you oh
okay this is why we like the rune like plug-in all the the reeflings are already
telling us where it is and they've got cat where did you pick that cat right
we are going to talk to evil Bob no we're not evil Bob's in the way how did I
dig here I don't need to select it with a spade oh wait what
behind the back of the castle right who needs a spade how do I how do I treat
someone a speed who wants to spade trade me if you need a spade I'm I'm called
Skullfish trade me if you need a spade I'm just a dwarf but I'm digging a hole
diggy diggy hole okay we fling ah okay if you if you need a spade but we're gonna
we're gonna pass it around okay we're gonna trade spade okay if you are a
reefling that has a spade go to the... can I not trade that?
waiting for other player other yoke deigo the community spade literally if you
need a spade please stand by the church and a reefling will trade you if you need
a spade stand by this church and a reefling will trade you okay if you need
a spade stand by the church stand at the wall at the church if you need a spade
okay any reeflings that have a spade can you pick on someone who's at the church
wall and trade them your spade please and we can share the spade
take me to church I'm just a reefling pick on them that's so evil yeah if you
have a spade pass it over and then they can dig the spot there and then we'll
just keep doing that until everyone's picked up the scroll just lined us up
against the wall that's right who am I touching first that's the only reason
I'd be doing a lie a lineup on my account it's restricted for trading the
speed is restricted for trading I think I'm about to get a spade back maybe we
drop the spades instead okay okay I wonder if it's because I bought
membership I'm spared right reefling you're getting traded how do I trade
like that I never I just read the word trade right can I give you this and we
literally share in like three three right now okay that's one more reefling
with the go to the dig spot it's still it's just over there at the we house if
you buy membership then you skip tree oh like they're digging look at the
reeflings go they're so smart they're digging okay once you finish where you
spade give it to the other one yeah the ones who are lined up at the church need
a spade so just just trade them when you have a spade on your person and we'll
just share it the communal spade this is like herding kids honestly we're not
doing too bad oh no no no they're refling by the wall yeah yeah by the
wall no no but the wall yeah yeah yeah where that one is oh oh did we but did
we bet that after refunds but it's okay yeah yeah yeah they're where the one in
red is that's where it is where the one in red is that's where you dig yeah no
no no green one one forward green one no no yeah yeah yeah the rent yeah yeah
that's where it is that's where you should pick up all the call the spades
like like like someone drop spade someone says one million someone says one
million for spades okay you're done you're done spade drop party okay I'm
picking up a spade as well because I need it for the next section there's so
many spades right everyone pick up a spade pick up a spade there's lots of
spades on that we love spades thank you for dropping the spade I'm a dwarf and
herding the reeflings to their demise I mean happy lovely cuttlefish love
seeing strong experience my diction for the last 16 years as everyone got a
spade like there's so many spades on the ground now we shouldn't we don't need to
share there's three more by the church all right if everyone's got a spade and
everyone has killed is so you have to open the closed girl first and then dig
for it in this little dig site here and then open it up again and then it'll
reveal that the this is Lumbridge Castle and this is behind the castle this is
where we were hanging out at the start of the stream someone's lit okay if
everyone's got a spade we're gonna go behind the castle now if you've all dug
it up there'll be like one briefing that like I have no clue what I'm doing right
now I'm just happy to be here so we're gonna go behind the castle the
castle so can you explain all real escape to me as if I was a general
manager explaining to a new hire incremental game oh look the reeflings
already here to tell us what's up you know what what happens behind the
castle now we just dig up with your spade and what did I get I got a
mysterious what I feel mysterious orb examine an orb I found well treasure
hunting for views okay now where do we go solve the clue scroll dig dig behind
the castle just outside the kitchen door dig northwest of dry nor village jail
just by the wheat farm wait there's more I thought we were done wait are we
about to go like really I think we have to go through here if you've dug up the
orb then we need to know quest halfway across the map we need to go where
drying our village wow okay we have to go a little bit right who knows right is
everyone following no we've got not that's an embassy we've got stuff on the
wall you're refling then fire stuff right where you definitely want to follow
me for this next section unless we're fall can I just follow the refling and
the refling will take me there honestly out of pure laziness yes if you guys
follow me I'll follow the refling and it's just one big conga line all the
way to join our village are we gonna all we're gonna get so caught in these
trees there's no way can't they get freaky in the castle I think I do it
behind the door I think it did I've got a few scripts that are like that for the
girls coming out it's like actually mercy has won this month I don't want to
take us to the Dixie I don't know where it is you taking us to it taxi to drink
drink or anyone taxi she's gonna get all we're locking music tracks as well
conga conga conga can you do the conga but we're making this this is the
world's worst drop party we're dropping speeds out here oh look there is because
I'm not paying for this the navigation is horrible
we're at the unsatisfactory unsatisfactory thing in my bubble that
sorry I mentioned my eyeball I was into itch my eyeball you've picked up a
treasure skull we're gonna open it we know this Uber's been a one out of five
have you guys taken over I'm just I would be so scared to do it where the heck
do we need to go now can't see it oh it's only over there it's fine it's
literally right over here in the market it's not big deal it's literally straight
over here oh yeah let's just go for it fun fact click on the map for the shortest
route to your destination
idea for ASMR wait eyeball itching oh my eyes I can make my eyes make noise like
make it like it's pretty gross okay let's see talk to the zero no you're not
an NPC we need to we're digging in in piggy kaka use the space please why you're
not working is it cuz there's spade oh I'm spading I'm literally hitting you
with a spade right now okay everyone at the space I need to take you away so we
can so I can dig this freaking pan use spade on why it says use spade on I love
mommy why is it not I'm up in them you have to dig not use oh almost oh right I
got it got it got it got it got it it says talk to views I'm sorry I'm so
dumb using dig should be the same thing it's a verb it's a doing word right we
are gonna go to port southern to go talk to the guy which we just need to
basically do a u-turn like a okay you turn time you turn time so we just need
to go up here cuz none of us have agility so we can't use this underworld
tunnel literally you pay membership so you can have shortcuts only that you have
the grain to get the shortcut
might as well be an mpc
uh taxi we've got taxi I know some of the reflinks are left behind yeah come
around the wall do a u-turn around the wall and it's literally right here sorry
I know you some guys render distance might not be able to see it all but we
their third question
oh we all celebrate
Okay, we can finish our quest. How's the treasure hunt going? I found the treasure. Excellent.
Oh, I've got an ancient casket.
Ah! I have no clue. I've got three total quest points. We've got an antique lamp, 200 coal. Oh, we've got a closed scroll.
Do we all get the same closed scroll?
Near the open desert, I reside to get past me, you must abide. Go forward if you dare for when you pass me.
You'll be sweating by your hair.
No.
Dungeon master. Is that an easy quest?
Was our next easy free to play quest? Hmm.
That was...dark.
I've got one about an anagram of how I need to speak tonight. Oh my god, this music is so good. It's so good.
Someone did a base remix of Sea Shanty 2 and it's so good, I love it.
What's the easiest mission quest that we could do? I'm not sure.
Absolute banger. I'm going to rub my...BRB, I'm going to go rub my...
Someone said rune no treasure. What are you going to quest for? You're trolling me, that's not quest.
Pirate's treasure? I don't know. I'm sure there's this headless quest.
The restless ghost, I think that's it. Yeah, the restless ghost. Let's do the restless ghost because I'm pretty sure.
Okay, we need...okay, just teleport back to Lumberge.
So open up your magic book and you should have a teleport. It should say Lumberge home teleport.
You open up your little magic page. I don't know if you can see it over my hair.
Oh, my hair's so big. I can hardly see my inventory.
But just teleport back to Lummi. We're going to do it. We're going to draw it in the ground.
Who put a cow over here? I don't even know how you did that.
Yeah, teleport to Lumberge. Open up your magic spell book and it's the very first one.
It should be on cooldown because we've been mucking about.
Okay, I'll stand here and I'll wait for my lonely thing to come.
Oh, no, I know another one. No. Get away. Get away with your stance.
Okay. Yes, your hair is big.
It is. I'm covering up my queen. My big A3.
Oh, no more silly songs. I love the way you say cow. A cow.
A cow. How do you say cow? Who? Oh, you can also say a highland cow. That's true.
Wishes to trade with you. Hmm, what do you offer me? What do you offer me?
Tomato and cheese. Can I cook that?
What do I do with a tomato and cheese sandwich? Yeah.
Oh, there's the cow again. Absolutely stunning on them.
Good food. I'll eat it the next time I get into a bar fight by accident.
Okay, hopefully all the reeflings made it to the teleport.
That was your first time teleporting. Who is doing a snowball fight?
Okay, let me take us to the next question. Pretty sure it's over here.
Sorry, I was bumping my desk. Have you heard that? That cow? A literal woman.
I think they heal one. That's all I need in a bar fight. One cheeky bit of health.
He he he. Right. Oh, no, it's in here. Sorry, it's in the church.
I'm sorry, I'm such a fake gamer. It's inside the church. I apologize.
Father Eric.
Here, Father, who art in heaven, hallowed be thy name. I'm seeking a quest.
I'm looking for a quest. I'm looking for a quest.
That's lucky. I need someone to do a quest for me.
Before starting this quest, be aware that your combat level is lower than the recommended of time.
I'm pretty sure you don't have to fight, so we're going to send it, okay?
We're going to send it.
Accept the graveyard through the south gate and reach the swamp.
I'm sure if you told him that, I sent you. He'd be willing to help.
My name is Father Eric, by the way. Please come in, yeah.
Blackwax. Take her traveling through the swamps. I've heard like a good thing for us.
Okay, the stronger reeflings are literally going to have to pick on the animals that pick on the weaker reeflings, okay?
Because I'm going to get picked on as well.
I need what? Get a ghost speak amulet.
Where though? Fuck.
Is that from? In the shack up here?
We need to go down to the shack. So let's go through the graveyard.
Reeflings together strong. Literally. Why is he Father Ted?
No, because all like, all prayer men are like ire's.
I've forgotten the name of them. The prayer man.
I'm not sure if I want to go through the swamp.
I think we might need to go around. Unless we've run through the swamp.
I don't know. The music's getting different.
I'm just a small weak reefling. Yeah, if anyone gets attacked on the way, you're going to have to like help them out and stuff.
I'm getting attacked, basically. Because we're too weak for this. Get with me, swamp.
What are you doing? Let my swamp.
Oh, a priest. Aye, that's the name. It's a priest prayer man. Completely. I've forgotten that word.
The music. And this game's set up.
It's not highly included either. Adorable youth.
I actually had an extended family member that owned one.
And it was like the gentlest giant ever. I never got to meet her. It was like a female Highland cow.
God, that's the most Scottish thing I could see. I had a family member that owned a Scottish cow.
That Highland cow, which is, you know, Scottish.
Father Eric sent me to talk to you. I suppose I'd rather talk to you then.
What problems have you got himself into this time? It's got a ghost haunting his graveyard.
Oh, that silly fool. I leave town for just five months and you already can't manage.
Sorry. Well, I can't go back and exercise it. I vowed not to leave this life until I've done a full two years of prayer and meditation.
Two years to sit on your own, bro. Right, we need to go talk to the ghost. We now have an amulet.
So we're going to, you'll get given an amulet. Make sure you put it on your person.
Okay, make sure you do not waste your sprint weaker leaflings because we need to run away, like, from this fight immediately.
Two years without internet? I'd be absolutely losing it. I'm sorry.
I'd be. I'd just be...
Are you squiddin' me right now?
Oh, Brian!
Hey, Stroney, if I wanted to share a interesting prompt for you to read, but it was too long for Marshmallow.
How would you like me to share it with you?
I don't think I'll have any other way.
Are all the leaflings coming?
Leafling, you're so, you're so behind. I'm going to have to wait for them to spawn on the other one.
But I don't want us to get attacked by the big routes.
I'm not sure. Thank you for the tip, Anon.
If it's big?
I think Pastebin is a safe website.
Right, let's get the heck out here for these rat scouts.
Are the frogs at the swamp?
Hey, Stroney. Hi, hi. Thanks for joining.
Two years of isolation is wild.
Literally, like, I'm sorry, but if I was isolated, I'd just straight up day and night.
No stop and say, I'm sorry, but I gotta do something to pass the time.
Gotta do something to pass the time, so...
I do not know how that brings anyone closer to meditation.
Could a Pastebin link work?
Yeah, I think Pastebin's probably the only thing.
Right, I think we need to be ready to run away, so get ready to turn these running boots on, okay?
But talk to the restless ghost.
Hello, ghost. How are you?
Not very good, actually.
What's the problem then?
Did you just understand what I said?
Yeah, no, tell me what the problem is.
Woo, this is incredible.
I didn't even expect anyone to ever understand me again.
Okay, okay, I can understand you.
But do you have any idea why you're doomed to be a ghost?
Well, to be honest, I'm not sure.
I've been told a certain task may need to be completed, so you can rest in peace.
I should think it is probably because a warlock has come along and stolen my skull.
If you look inside my coffin, it's no there...
A wreathling just closed the coffin as soon as he said that.
Okay, okay, he's missing his head. We can see he's missing his head.
He clearly needs some head.
Oh yeah, that would be such great relief.
Okay, return the ghost's skull.
Where do we need...
What?
What? We need to go to the wizard's tower?
What the hell?
I don't remember that.
No way.
I don't remember.
It's actually quite far away.
A wreathling was to show me something.
What do you want to show me, wreathling?
Other player has accepted.
Oh, you're giving me fish to cook?
Wait, you're giving me this now?
Wait, I think you might need to hold on to it.
Because if I die in this quest, you need to hold on to this.
Okay, hold on to it. Thank you, but you need to hold on to that.
Because if I die, I'm going to drop all of that.
We'll do a few more quests and then we're going to actually start levelling up cooking like for real, for real, okay?
But thank you so much.
But do hold on to that because I'm going to end up perishing.
Looks in coffin.
So no head.
Right, are we all here?
I think so.
When you guys stack, it's really hard to see like if we're all here.
Hey, it's the Praise Gocher!
Bro, I feel like I'm getting lured.
Do you trust me? Do you trust where we're going?
It'd be such a shame if you got lured to me.
Oh, someone sent me a marshmallow and they're like, I'm going to be mind broken by you.
And I'm like...
Soon, soon.
Wait, is this not where the mage tower is?
Oh no, there's enemies ahead that attack us, okay?
Everyone get ready to sprint.
There's wizards and robes here that are getting ready to attack us.
At these trees up here, there's you trees.
Please get ready to run if you're a weaker reefling.
We're going to get absolutely wrecked.
I'll tell you when to run, okay?
But it should be coming up.
It should be coming up.
Wait, isn't there not you logs here?
Am I too late?
Eh?
Isn't there not you logs here and wizards that beat you up here?
I guess I must be misremembering.
I'm such a fake landscape gamer.
That's Viroc.
Oh, should be safe.
Meet you guys at the mage bank.
Take the bridge.
Let's go.
We're not...
We're north of the...
Okay.
Everyone's following.
Sorry, little reefling.
You need to come around.
Jump up, jump up, and get down.
You shall not pass.
Excuse me, pardon me.
Come through.
Pardon me.
Oh my god.
Well fought.
Right.
Be careful, weaker reeflings.
We must run away when we do this, okay?
Put your gold on in a minute.
Hold on, hold on.
Get ready for Friday.
Search, alter, and run.
Run like your little life depends on it.
Run on your retentacles.
Search the allers.
Search the aller, reeflings.
Reeflings scare once he spawns in.
Run away, reeflings.
Run away, run away, run away.
Go up the ladder, weaker ones.
Go up the ladder, go up the ladder, go up the ladder.
As soon as you get the score, you need to go up the ladder.
There's so many reeflings.
That skeleton's getting absolutely wrecked.
We made it, reeflings.
We made it, we're safe.
We did it.
We didn't get wrecked.
I'll wait for you outside the mage castello.
We did it today, reeflings.
We cheated death.
It wasn't a match for us.
Yeah.
Oh my god.
So many of us.
The scaly didn't know what hit him, literally.
It's closing doors.
You've been so mean to the reeflings.
Not only are you jacking up prices artificially,
but you're closing doors.
Oh my god.
There's so many of us.
Oh, he's beating up that wizard.
Oh, shadow wizard money gang.
They love casting spells.
Death by dark wizard is a rinscape right of passage.
Honestly though, no troll under the bridge.
Yeah.
It's normal.
Is that all my reeflings?
Did we all make it?
Hopefully no one perished.
Sailing head.
What?
That's a good girl's trying.
You thought.
Ain't that kind of stream?
I think if I'm feeling better,
maybe the ASMR stream,
I give permission for you to give it a try.
Right.
Okay, reeflings.
All the way back to the ghost.
Oh, unless, wait, follow the rabbit.
Follow the rabbit.
The rabbit will take us to where we need to go.
Honestly, that rabbit outfit, not going to lie.
I'm digging it.
I'm actually digging that rabbit.
Like, I mean, you can see the hips definition.
You can see the yiddies.
It's all looking pretty good.
And then headless refilling.
You're at my render distance.
Whoever's back there had this refilling.
Look at the size of them grippers.
Oh, we're up.
What is that?
Someone's got like a thing on their back.
I honestly didn't know how many cosmetics there was in the game.
If you get us beaten up by baddies,
because you've taken this path.
Okay, I think we're safe.
Reefling just hovering in the background.
Hey, it's constantly coming in and out of render distance.
Okay, hydration check.
I hope this taxi is better than the last.
Oh, wow.
Oh, no.
Rad attack.
Walking us to the Edgeville dungeon.
Wait, there is a place called Edgeville.
Oh my gosh, that's where we should make the home.
Oh, I was going to play hide and seek.
And if I touch you, then you're out.
Right, where do we need to go?
Oh, we need to go to the graveyard, guys.
Yeah, there's literally a place called Edgeville in this game.
There's a plugin for hide and seek.
Is there actually?
That's so smart.
Maybe next stream I'll get the plugin and we'll see how it works.
I don't know.
Hide and seek.
I'd rather lose.
But every time I find you, all you hear is plop, plop, plop.
And then move on to the next refund.
Plop, plop, plop.
It's over.
Okay.
We need to put the hedge on the coffin.
And all is good.
We're going to use the skull on the coffin.
Use it on the coffin.
It's not a...
Oh, cut scene.
Release.
Thank you, stranger.
Yeah.
Oh, he's away.
Oh, he's in the water.
Oh, he's had enough.
He's in the water.
Whoa, we got one cave prayer for that.
That was actually pretty big.
Right, we've got four quest points now.
Jeez, we've got nine prayers.
What?
And I'm level four combat currently.
I didn't fight anything, though.
Hide and plop.
Yes, hide and plop.
I want to find hide and plop.
Good.
Release.
Oh, that's a lot.
Everyone's leveling up.
Rep sleeping viewers.
Yeah, sorry.
Hopefully no one actually uses this to sleep, too.
I wonder if there's also a kumbor.
Right, what's the easiest quest next?
Or are we actually going to have to level up?
I think we might have to get stronger because everything's like...
Maybe Goblin Village?
If we buy everything in advance for that Goblin quest,
I forgot the name of it.
Romeo and Juliet is good.
Should we try Romeo and Juliet?
Romeo and Juliet.
Also an amulet that's useful for the future, right?
Stronghold of security time?
I've never done that one.
Romeo and Juliet is no needed stats.
Okay, we're going to do that one then.
I can start this quest by talking to Romeo and Varrock Square.
Who the heck?
Oh, that's a big walk.
Not going to lie.
That's like really far away.
Okay, we cross the bridge,
and then we just keep going all the way up to Varrock.
I've already lost where Romeo is.
Oh, he's literally in the square of Varrock.
Well, we don't have teleport stone,
so we're going to have to do it the old fashioned way.
I heard it drops the goal in the amulet.
I don't know what that is.
Follow, someone says follow.
Just...
Oh, oh, taxi!
Okay, follow the guy with the magma cape.
Wait, make sure we get out of the graveyard first
because we might actually get stuck on the gravestones.
Yeah, you'll get...
Careful, you'll get stuck on the gravestones.
Okay, if you're going to tax sales,
can I make a cup of tea?
Am I allowed to make a cup of tea?
That little voice is getting sore.
This is a magma cape, winky.
It is!
Isn't that a magma cape?
Whoa, what is that?
Wait, you got a special accolade?
Is that a special accolade to this thing?
Oh, it's a fire cape.
I mean, it looks like magma lava,
so whoever named it is wrong.
We...
We must go directly into the dark mages.
Oh, wait, I can't make a cup of tea
because I'm going to get hurt by the mages.
For the weaker reeflings,
we're about to pass some wizards
outside of a rock that will attack us.
We need to be ready to run.
Go west near the farm.
Oh, he says he's going to go around.
I think we have enough people to kill the dark wizards.
Oh, can I go quickly make a cup of tea, then?
Watching strongy stream?
Whenever I read the last thingy,
you know the love heart?
You can put a love heart on stream.
Tap that love heart thing.
It's in the way if I read the most bottom thing.
It says, watching strongy stream is the type of accolade.
Yeah, if you tap that heart,
I can see when you tap it,
but it blocks the last message.
I'll be doing nothing but laughing if anyone dies.
Oh, we'll also be at the bank,
so is that reefling still there to trade the fish?
Plenty more fish.
I can only see it on mobile.
Yeah, I can see someone make a flush face smiley reaction.
It's in the way for everyone.
Okay, right.
I was going to say, because it's in the way.
Whenever I read the most bottom message,
it's in the way.
That cape requires you to kill a level 700 monster.
Unless you guys can carry me through that monster,
I don't think we can do that.
I've never done it before.
Yeah, I had to nuke the heart with an edlocker.
I think you can toggle it away.
Yeah, I have to scroll around it.
It's a solo fight?
Well, I'm never getting that.
I am here with the fish.
Okay, we will be going next to the bank,
so we should be okay.
I think.
Is there any?
Hopefully, there's not too many.
Oh, yeah.
Good idea to go to the bushes first.
Oh, no, these reeflings.
Oh, no, don't get stuck on the wall, reefling.
These are reeflings.
Oh, no, I don't know if that's everything.
I might just be someone.
There's three dots at the top of chat.
No, no, I think it's okay.
I think it's there.
Fire cape would be fun.
Oh, no, I don't even know how to do that.
I don't even know how prayer pots work in, like,
strength potions and all of that work,
and it's, like, all temporary,
but they're, like, a thousand, and it's so expensive.
Watch out now.
All right, weaker reeflings.
Get ready.
Get ready, weaker reeflings.
Stronger reeflings.
Beat them up.
Show those wizards.
We mean freaking...
We mean business.
Beat them up, stronger reeflings.
We'll be...
The weaker reeflings are going to stick together.
This is the best we can do under the circumstances.
Cut off, Boudin.
Run into the circle reefling.
No, do not go in that circle.
These wizards are stinky.
They're no good, guys.
He's telling you fevers.
He's telling you the Fibonacci sequence,
because those are fevers.
Okay, I think the reeflings, like,
literally eradicate all the wizards for us in a way.
Thank you.
They're all dead.
Literally just absolutely eradicated them.
I think the funniest thing ever.
Wow.
How can I tell?
Whoa, how many quests is there?
I don't know if we can do all the quests in just a little while.
Right, we're looking for R for Romeo.
Uh-oh.
Okay.
We're here.
Right, who's Romeo?
Oh, Romeo's inside the shop.
Inside the shop with the green windows.
Inside the shop is where Romeo is.
He thought he could hide from us.
Right, talk to Romeo.
Romeo.
What?
What is to become of me and my darling Juliet?
I cannot find her anywhere.
Have you seen her?
Yes, I have seen her, actually.
At least, I think it was her.
Blonde, a bit stressed.
Golly, yes, yes.
You make a sense of very interesting.
And I'll bet she's a bit of a fox around.
Well, I guess she could be considered attractive.
I'll bet she is.
Woo-hoo.
Sorry, all that jubilation has made me forget what we were talking about.
You were asking me about Juliet.
You seem to know her.
Oh, yes, Juliet.
That fox.
Could you tell her that she is the love of my long?
What?
She is the love of my long?
Rinse, jagged.
She's the love of my long and that I love to be with her.
What?
Surely you mean she is the love of your life and that you long to be with her?
Oh, yes, what you said.
Tell her that, it sounds much better.
Oh, you're so good at this.
Start the Romeo and Juliet quest.
Yeah, okay, I'll let her know.
Oh, great, and tell her that I want to kiss her a give.
You mean you want to give her a kiss?
Oh, you are good, you are good.
I see I've picked a true professional.
Is he drunk?
Okay, thanks.
Yay!
Okay, has everyone got the quest?
We now need to...
Actually, we're going to very quickly go to the bank
and I'm going to young call the fish from your juicy, juicy donations to me.
Okay.
Oh, wait, sorry, sorry, wait, wait, wait.
Pause, pause.
I'm in the square, I'm in the square.
Sorry, I didn't mean to run away so quickly.
We're going to very quickly go to the Grand Exchange
because I'm going to empty my inventory
and if you want to give me anything, you can, okay?
But I'll...
Uh, no, don't give me a bond.
I've already bought premium, thank you so much.
Don't give me a bond though, I bought premium.
Right, Reflings, if you want to follow me,
we're going to go to the Grand Exchange.
So if you want to give me anything, you can.
Get your scam messages ready.
Oh no, I need to mute public chat whilst we're here.
I might need to mute public chat.
I don't know how bad the bots are going to be.
I have no idea how bad the bots are going to be.
I might have to mute public chat until we go away.
Buying girlfriend through...
Oh, there's like the bots aren't talking.
Okay, nothing's happening.
Right, I'm going to put...
I'm literally...
Oh no, no, I don't want to sell them.
I'm just literally going to shove everything in the bank.
Uh, I think I'll just drop the clue scroll.
Ah, you know what?
I'll just put it in the bank.
It doesn't make a difference.
Put all my coins in.
I've got an antique lamp.
I don't know what that does.
Oh, I can't put it away.
Uh, I'll rub the antique lamp.
Oh!
Um, into kicking please.
Hey, 300 XP in kicking.
Yay!
Okay, I'm level 7.
Cooking now feels good, man.
Stand over here.
If you want to trade me, you're more than welcome to.
I'm literally starting a farm for, uh...
How do I accept, accept?
Okay, there we go.
Sorry, sorry, I'm dumb.
Oh my gosh, that's a lot of fish.
Oh, a 10 million?
Are you crazy?
Isn't that a lot of money?
Are you sure?
That's a lot of money.
Oh wait, did I just accept you as a friend by accident?
Whoops.
10 million reeflings.
Is this account going to get shot down?
Because, like, Jagex are going to be like,
you're clearly, like, paying for these?
I got lobster!
I'm cake!
Yes!
Thank you for the lobster!
Oopsie.
The weapon is 1.2 billion?
That's crazy.
Sorry, I think I accidentally added a frame.
10 million?
Isn't that not, like, a...
How much, how much ink?
How much ink?
1,000 crusty socks?
Why did Jagex make that item?
They knew exactly what they were doing.
Doubling money!
This shmuck just made 10 million.
Doubling money, doubling money.
That's ridiculous.
On the contrary, we play here.
Oh, it's a ring!
Oh, can I wear it?
Am I allowed to put it on?
It's a diamond reefling!
Oh, my God.
Wait, wait.
Can I see it on my finger if I put it on?
No, I didn't change my persons.
I'm married to the reeflings.
He he he he he.
Okay, what do we do on the wedding then?
What's the honeymoon?
I want to know about the honeymoon.
Fishies!
Oh, we are going to be, like, exploding.
Oh, my God, that's so much.
We are going to be exploding once we cook all these.
Thank you, reeflings.
Oh, my gosh.
Okay, I'm going to put it all in the bank,
and then we get to come back.
Come back.
There's not one single bot here.
That's pretty thingy.
Okay, we are doing Romeo and Juliet.
Do we need to do anything?
We actually don't need any items at all.
Wow.
Oh, sorry.
Sorry, there's a few more that wish to trade.
My apologies.
Fishies!
Look at all the fishies.
You can bank note these, by the way.
But thank you for the fishies.
We're getting so much fish.
Yes, thank you.
Okay, how do I accept this?
Oh, I'm getting grapes.
Hey, yo, you want to grape me?
Hold on a minute.
Oh, no, sorry.
The cut of our berries.
My apologies.
It's a wedding gift.
Who did I not accept the trade from?
Is it you?
Did I accept the trade from you?
God, great.
Wait, does Johnny come in tax fraud and runescape?
Honestly?
Oopsie, sorry.
Oh, wait, hold on.
I accidentally added a reefling.
I apologize.
Sorry.
It's just because it was show.
What's the dress going to look like?
Someone called Sweaty Socks.
Are you role-playing as my Sweaty Socks?
I actually have socks on.
Oh, it's a necklace.
It's so pretty.
Oh, they get to put it on.
Amulet of power.
Oh, check me out.
Oh, look at that little thing.
This puppet that you get to hurry.
When we celebrate in the wedding
on my alternative Twitter.
Eat cuttlefish.
Whatever, you name yourself like that.
Unless you mean the other way.
What, you got to show me what you've got?
Eat cuttlefish.
You know what?
Are you just going to...
Hi, Johnny, sounding beautiful as ever.
Are you declined it?
Right, I will put this away in the bank.
And then we will finish
Gnotic and Elf and Gnotic and Oblin.
Wait, why is that not doing all...
There we go.
Oh, that's all I needed to do.
Speaking of alt-Twitters.
What was your reaction to them blown up?
So, Mercy stumbled upon the algorithm.
And then Sheebie did it.
But I did mine too late, Rip.
But, I mean, the video did really well.
It got like a hundred and...
A thousand likes on it.
And you're really good.
Wait, are you trying again?
Did you get stage fright?
Or is that the other one?
Ah, okay, okay, okay.
Right, Gnome, Gnotic and Elf and Gnotic and Oblin.
We need to Gnotic and Elf to over to Gnor.
To Faldor, I think.
I think she's somewhere here.
I don't know where she is.
Talk to Romeo, I did.
Did I not accept?
Talk to Juliet in the house west of Viroc.
Oh wait, they're both in Viroc?
Why did I think she was in Faldor?
And where is Gnotic and Oblin?
I'm analising.
Oh!
Eh?
She's here?
Why would you be in there?
Okay.
Alright, let's go to the front of the Grand Exchange
for my little refillings, front of the Grand Exchange,
front centre.
After this quest, I am going to...
Faldor?
I hardly even know her.
Thank you, thank you.
I came up with that myself, thank you.
Refillings, I'm at the front of the Grand Exchange.
You can find me over here.
So we're making a clan.
Can you make a clan?
Like, can anyone make a clan?
That video was amazing.
All per eco fish just wanted to feel included in it.
It got none to thingy.
A luring clan, he even knows.
Okay, is this all my refillings?
We're at the front?
Okay, this looks like great.
Ready?
Atten!
Up!
Two, three, four.
How do I get in this house?
It looks like I get in this door here.
Unless there's another door.
No, there's a door here.
Okay, we just used this door.
Literally right over there.
Hut!
Two, three, four.
Hit!
Mine is too bad joke, literally.
Just going down ten aura, sorry.
Okay, open the door.
Hello, we would like to come inside your house.
Don't mind us, we're just...
How have I come the hardest way to get around this house?
There's no way!
I literally picked the most awkward door.
I'm so sorry!
We literally have trailed through the entire house, but the one door.
Stop pranking each other with the door!
You're pranking me with the door!
Why is there a fisherman?
It's a true draw party!
Get your truck, get your truck, get your truck.
We're going to need it.
We're going to need all the XP.
I got three, four, five, six.
I don't know how I managed to do the worst.
Right, go up the stairs.
Up the stairs.
It smells fishy in here.
It does.
Right, where's Juliet?
Oh, her room's all pink.
Oh my God, you're such a girl.
How do we know Juliet's a girl?
Hmm, it's a mystery.
Hi Juliet.
Juliet, I've come from Romeo.
He begs me to tell you that he cares still.
Oh how my heart soars for hearing this news.
Please take this message to him with great haste.
Well, I hope it's good news.
He was quite upset when I left him.
He's quite often upset at the poor sensitive soul,
but I don't think he's going to take this news very well.
However, all is not lost.
Everything is explained in the letter.
Would you be so kind to deliver it to him, please?
Certainly, I'll do so straight away.
Many thanks.
Oh, I'm so very grateful.
You may be our only hope.
Help me, Obi-Wan Kenobi.
You're my only hope.
Okay, as everyone spoke to Juliet,
Romeo and Juliet, we're just literally passing
sextant messages, honestly.
What's going on here?
If you have spoken to Juliet,
we can go back doing the stairs,
and we're going to go back to Romeo.
Oh, Romeo, where are for thou art Romeo?
Oi, who closed that door?
I literally just smacked my face.
My, I freaking, you closed that door,
and now I'm tracking outside backwards.
Stop it.
Don't, don't close the door.
You made me whack my face into it.
Stop it.
Let me out of this house.
It keeps trying to make me go.
Right, I'm out.
I'm out.
Okay, we're safe.
We're safe.
You don't want to go through the five doors instead, honestly.
Forget doing agility training.
It's hard enough to get out of a door
that someone else is closing.
What?
How did that pop up?
I didn't even accept.
Okay, our all reflings here.
We're going to go back to Romeo.
He's this way.
Hardest boss in the game, pathing.
Yeah.
Are we refling back there?
Dear Mario, please come to the castle.
Oh, did I tell you I really like this meme?
Dear Mario, please don't come to the castle.
I've baked a cake.
It's absolutely dark shit.
I love that meme so much.
Okay, we go talk to Romeo back in the green shop.
Why is that green?
Oh, cloth right.
Which one did that?
Stop.
Stop it.
Right, I'm in.
Who did that?
Was that you?
You're the one who's right behind the door.
I love Mummy.
Am I accusing you live?
Was that you?
I don't know who did that.
Talk to Romeo.
Romeo, great news.
I've been in touch with Big Juliet.
She's written a message for you.
You hand over the message.
Oh, a message.
A message.
I've never had a message before.
Really?
No, no, no.
Not one.
Well, except for the occasional court summon.
But the really, really nice message.
Not like this one.
I'm sure this message will be lovely.
Yes, yes.
Where are you?
Well, are you going to open it or not?
Oh, yes.
Yes, of course.
Affection.
She thinks I'm deceased.
Oh, affliction.
Oh, I can't read.
Sorry.
I'm not going to get my glasses on.
It says affliction.
Affection.
Oh, wait.
No, I got it right.
Affection.
Oh, yes.
Still hold affection for me.
I still feel great affection for you.
Unfortunately, my father opposes our marriage.
Oh, dear.
That doesn't sound too good at all.
I want great affection for you.
Father opposes our marriage.
And well, we'll kill you if he sees you again.
I'm going to be honest.
It's not getting any better, me.
Our only hope is that the father Lawrence, a long time confidant,
can help us in some way.
Romeo folds the message away.
Well, that's it then.
We haven't got a chance.
What about Father Lawrence?
Our love is over the great romance that'll life of my love.
Or you could speak to Father Lawrence.
Oh, my aching, breaking heart.
Oh, how useless the situation is now.
I've got no one to turn to.
Father Lawrence.
Oh, yes, Father Lawrence.
He's a long time confidant.
He might have a solution.
Yes, yes.
You have to go and talk to Father Lawrence for once
and ask him if he's got any suggestion for a predicament.
Where can I feign Father Lawrence?
Lawrence, Father Lawrence.
Oh, you know, he's not my real father, don't you?
I think I suspected that he wasn't.
Did he get hit on the head?
Well, anyway, he tells his songs,
luring bare moans and keep these here.
What? I can't even read that.
Yeah, okay, thanks.
Okay, thanks.
Yeah, thanks mate.
Nice try on the English, but even I can't read that.
Where the heck are we going? Somewhere over here.
He's just a, and then dot, dot, dot.
I don't know what you typed, Reefling.
Are you trying to say he's one of us?
For that word, he's one of us.
No one slammed the door.
I slammed my piece.
Okay, Reeflings, we're going a little to the left
outside that shop.
Any Reeflings left behind?
There's one Reefling.
Yay.
I don't think these are all NPCs.
I love Reefling there.
I didn't close the door, but I'm ready to accept
any punishment you do with it.
Captain Jack Thornbare.
Okay, let's go.
We are just following the path.
I see the blue marker because of rune light,
so we're just following that.
But, oh no!
Oh no, I'm going to get you strapped on the fence.
I'm sorry.
I was a bit, I was a bit preemptive.
Okay, okay, that was lucky.
Easy, take it easy, easy.
Let's not get any Reeflings caught on a fence.
Come on.
We can do it.
I have no idea how.
Oh, here's the church.
Right, we're going to go to the steps over here.
Rare correct path, I think, honestly.
Going to Wildy Ditch.
Should we start attacking each other?
Should we do fisty cuffs?
Should we do fisty cuffs in Wildy
and just start beating each other up
until there's a crowned Reefling at the end?
And then I give you a rose as a favour
because you're the knight that stood against all Reeflings.
And...
And lutes are domain, like the way for you.
Oh, I was in the middle of a ceremony.
But Romeo sent me.
But I'm busy delivering in a ceremony to my congregation.
Ah, yes.
It certainly seems like you have a captive audience.
Okay, okay, what do you want?
So I can get rid of you and continue with my ceremony.
Romeo sent me?
He says you've been able to help?
Ah, Romeo, yes.
A fine land, but he's a wee bit confused.
Very confused.
Anyway, Romeo wishes to be married to Julia.
She must be rescued from her father's control.
I agree, and I think I have an idea.
A potion to make her dad...
Oh, to appear passed away.
Dead!
Sounds a bit creepy to me, but please continue.
The potion will only make Julia yet appear dead.
Then she will be taken to the crypt.
Crypt!
Again, we're getting a bit creepy, mate.
You must have some strange hobbies.
That's what the berries someone gave me.
Apart from...
Did that refling want me to be asleep?
Or did you want to be asleep?
Okay, reflings!
Once you have...
Why does someone have a...
Someone has a prayer on?
Don't leave it on.
You've got a prayer on.
You're going to run out of prayer.
Also, someone get fond of the potion!
That's terrible.
Guys, you're putting your prayer on.
You're going to run out of prayer.
Literally, I only have nine prayer points.
Right, everyone outside the church.
Con-
Mass is over.
Congrats on finishing Mass.
You just have a lot of fun.
Where are we going?
Oh, that's cool.
Oh, you can't see because of my hair.
All right, you can kind of see it.
See how the bar is like...
Oh, you're getting close to being finished.
That's new.
I don't remember that.
Where are we heading?
Whoa!
Where am I?
No?
Can I please go back to the surface?
Thank you.
Where do we need to go?
I'm looking...
Oh, there is...
Still in the same town.
Thank goodness.
Okay.
I'll just follow the HUD for the most part.
Oh, you wished to trade with me.
I will accept your trade.
What do you offer me?
Oh!
You've rejected!
How dare you!
Oh, no.
I had to do with a friend.
Sorry.
I keep freaking adding people as a friend by accident.
Oh, wait.
Hold on.
I need to remove you.
I'm dying.
Delete.
Rip.
One tick.
Player.
Flick.
One tick flicking on Romeo and Juliet Quest.
True gamers here, honestly.
I wish I understood the tick mechanic.
I've heard it explained so many times to me.
I don't get it.
I'm practicing.
Literally.
Oh, there's like little birds making noises in the game.
Is this the actual priestess...
Crickets, please.
What?
You want me to just play?
I'll just play crickets right now, even though you asked for it like five minutes ago.
Oh, it's this shop.
Okay.
What are we doing over here?
I thought it was only in the day that I remember Scotland.
I'm like, I can be out until like 9.
It's summer.
When it's summer in Scotland, the sun doesn't go away until like 9.
It's pretty bright.
Oh, no.
I'm closing the door.
Okay.
I thought I was closing the door, but I'm not.
Let's talk.
I am apocrity.
I broke potions.
Do you need anything?
Yes.
I do need something very specific about Romeo and Juliet.
Wait.
Wasn't there a movie called Romeo and Juliet?
And it was about nose.
What do these berries look like?
Wait.
We need berries.
Oh, no.
Someone gave me berries.
Okay.
I guess we will get the berries.
Um, to the Grand Exchange Reeflings, we will go obtain some berries.
Oh, I can't get out because someone closed the door.
I clicked on the map to get out.
Someone's closing the door.
I can't get out of that room.
I'm not stuck in there.
Yeah.
My hand hurts after a few minutes of it.
Oh, you can only last a few minutes now?
One handed?
Right.
Let's go get some berries.
Secret berries.
I thought it said I didn't need anything.
It said recommended items.
None.
It says bring.
You can pick some from the bushes.
Oh, we're to pick them from the bushes.
I'm sorry.
I apologize.
Where's the bushes?
Bring.
Talk.
I've just read it.
Bring.
Nope.
I just read where I can pick the bushes.
You can pick some bushes southeast of Iraq.
Wait.
Where am I supposed to go then?
What's southeast?
Southeast?
Like over here?
Feels like I can get stabbed in these back alleys.
You can pick my dingo, but...
Send!
We're trying to find a freaking bush.
Yeah, done.
I didn't tell you my short caller arrived for our streaming app.
Where are the berries?
Pass the dark wizard.
Okay.
Strong reeflings, please go ahead and beat the absolute crap out of those dark wizards.
For weaker reeflings, get ready.
Prepare thyself.
Where are these berries?
I'm looking.
Oh my god, the reeflings are just absolutely going to town on them.
All the magic noises.
Oh!
Yes!
The bushes are ahead.
Fragile and weak, please handle me with care.
Trying to find strongies bushes then.
Right.
I'm going to say something.
I'm going to say something controversial.
I was going to make a here ASMR, like here sounds, but it was rather, rather different.
Okay.
Right.
I've got berries.
Everyone, everyone collect your berries off the bushes.
Has everyone got a berry?
It looks like they're infinite spawn bushes actually, so.
Wait, did bots run these berries?
Wait, it's cost 400 GP for these berries?
Have we just stumbled on a money maker?
Here ASMR, not controversial.
How would that even work?
I would place the microphone at hips level.
I've been here for two seconds and you're already getting controversial.
I can't.
You show up in it.
Right.
I think everyone's got it.
Yeah.
These berries are bought and free to play world smothers with your hair.
Next winning strat in GG.
Okay.
Let's go past the wizards again.
Stronger leaflings.
You know the drill.
Has everyone got a berry?
400 GP.
Oh my God.
That's huge.
Interest on the 10 million GP.
True.
10 million GP investment.
Beat them up.
Show them who's boss.
Oh, that red bead is worth so much money.
Oh, that refling got it.
Oh, no.
Take this bead.
I got it.
Wow.
Wizard hats are 1,000 money.
Why is it so much money?
We should be killing these wizards over and over again.
Okay.
I'm going to get out of here before we're getting trouble.
I don't want the wizards to spawn and start getting us.
Stronger leaf, we're doing this one.
Can we have a reward that lets us see the stream stingers?
Stop.
I've literally not even put them on.
I just realized I've not even shown you what my stream stingers look like.
That's terrible.
Literally like, what did reflings look like?
And I'm like, what do you mean?
I've already shown you what reflings look like in the artwork.
We've got stingers either.
And I don't even use my loading screen.
And I spent like 600 US dollars on it.
I'm like, genuinely such a bad vtuber.
But I just want to jump in the game.
Who did that?
I managed to somehow get past.
Alright, Romeo and Juliet.
Well done.
You have the berries.
I do.
Okay.
Oh, he's apocratizing.
He's apocratizing all over the place.
I'm going to smack the plan.
Bring the potion to Juliet.
Okay.
I'm going to stand outside and wait for everyone to get out.
Because you already know what's going to happen.
And you're always going to freaking smack everyone's face.
Strongest seat is a moneymaker.
Who said that?
Oh.
Okay, wait until the other reflings are ready.
I'm mousin' all over the refling.
I'm mousin' all over you.
Are you like that?
Oh, I got that.
Mousin' all over me.
I'm just mousin' all over you.
Watch out for Viralt Guards.
No, Virat.
Doubt these potions are illegal.
I haven't made any money though.
Drink the potion for a funny thing.
Oh, I don't want to drink it.
I'd have to go get another thing again.
Does it make you pass out?
Viralt Guards don't get paid enough to care about that.
Honestly, $1 million donation reward.
Use stream startin' screen once for 10 seconds.
Bravo, honestly.
It's been $600, $800-ish.
Okay, is that one more refling?
Oh, we're all level six now or something?
Whoa, that's a lot of refling.
Well, no, refling.
Or are you not done the quest properly?
Or is this...
You've got a chef's hat on, which makes me think you're a refler.
What are the odds that someone just happens to be doing the quest at the same time?
When are we going to winter town?
I've literally never done any event in RuneScape
because I'm just so bad at it and I don't understand.
I know that because I had to hunt it down
to get a refler shop for the fan art.
Oh, watch it mostly shine.
I didn't even know stingers were a thing.
So everyone got a logo stinger
and everyone got an artwork stinger.
I need a moment of time.
Oh, someone wants to trade.
Except your trade.
What do you offer me?
Ah!
Okay.
I'll accept.
I did say I wanted your ink, okay?
I got you.
Yeah.
Right, we're going to hand over the potion to Julia.
Winter tot is where the yarrow...
Literally, that's why I'm like winter fell in Skyrim.
That's where the yarrow live.
Right, we're going to open the door for everyone.
Yarrow ballroom.
These here.
Oh, I'm going to close the door back.
Okay, let's get inside the house, please.
Get inside the house.
Get up the stairs.
Anyway, if I catch any refling closing doors...
Something bad's going to happen.
I don't know.
I'm not decided on the punishment yet.
Your stream starting soon is very beautiful.
Yes, but it's very...
As well.
Oh, sorry.
I have a Kandava potion here.
Suggested by Father Lawrence, if you...
Oh, wait, that's me.
Excuse me, sorry, I don't know where that voice came from.
Have a Kandava potion here. Suggested by Father Lawrence.
If you drink it, it will make you appear dead.
Yes?
And when you appear dead,
you're still in lifeless corpse will be removed from the crypt.
Oh, a cold, dark, creepy crypt.
Sounds just peachy.
Then Romeo can steal...
And...
Let's just steal into the crypt and rescue you just as you wake up.
And this is a great idea for getting me out of here.
To be fair, I can't take all the credit.
In fact, it was all Father Lawrence's suggestion.
Okay, if this is the best we can do, then hand over that potion.
You pass the suspicion potion to Juliet.
Wonderful.
Wonderful, I just thought Romeo could remember to get me from the crypt.
Why do I feel like we're about to bust her out of the crypt?
Please go to Romeo and make sure you understand the lie of his...
His gormless, love-lorn, soppy ways.
He can be a bit dense sometimes and I don't want to wake...
And I want to wake up in the crypt on my own.
Yeah, we're definitely picking up the crypt.
Here it is.
Oh, he...
Here's Philippine, my cousin, she's in...
She's in on the plot too.
She's going to make it seem like it's more convincing.
Yes, I'm quick.
Ah.
What's a British boy?
He's quick, British, quick.
Nick-a-car.
Yes, I'm quite an actress.
Good luck, dear cousin.
Right, bottoms up.
Oh, she's Paris.
Oh, no.
Juliet has died.
You may be more believable if you're not smiling when you see it.
Oh, yeah.
You might be right.
Oh, no, no, no.
Let's try that again.
Try that again.
Oh, no.
Juliet's dead.
I can't do, like, three different accents at one time.
Perhaps a bit louder, like, you're upset, you know, that your cousin just died.
Right, yeah, okay.
Nick-a-car.
Okay, I think I'm getting the motivation now.
Okay, let's just try this again.
Oh, no.
Juliet's dead.
Juliet, my poor dead cousin.
Oh, this was not a lot of screaming.
Oh, you cunt, she's dead.
Oh, poor Juliet.
I made preparations for her body to be blessed with the crypt.
This is terrible.
I don't know where that came from.
Right, okay.
Where do we go next?
Bring...
Talk to Romeo and Varric Square to finish the quest.
All right.
That man was Cornel Sanders.
How am I getting door blocked?
How have they not figured out this freaking door block, honestly?
Stop!
Right, I just went through that door.
That's how strong I am.
I just went through that door.
Okay.
Let's go to Romeo.
Where everyone...
Right, I'll wait outside.
Father noticed that a random person handed her a potion and she perished, literally.
Oh, no.
Juliet.
You're dead.
No.
I say no.
Follow the cute face.
Any cute fishers?
Any cute fishermen coming to hook her?
Yee.
Quite the hooker.
Hey.
Yeah.
Oh.
Yo-ho.
I assume everyone got out.
Yeah, the door's been left open.
That's how I know all the reeflings are available.
Oh, there's two doors to this place.
Okay, we'll go in this room.
Oh, I now understand people are in their angular gear.
I saw that.
Who's that shadowed guy?
You literally are making us walk all the way around because you closed that fecking door.
I saw that.
I literally saw that in 4K.
It's you.
It's the freaking shadow one.
Who's your name?
Identify yourself.
Bye.
More like slamming to a door.
Romeo, it's all set.
Juliet has dropped the potion.
Ah, great.
The potion.
Great.
What potion would that be then?
The kind of a potion.
You know, the one which will make her appear dead.
She's in the crepe.
Pop along and clean your true love.
But I'm scared.
Will you come with me?
Yeah, I knew we were going to come with you.
Oh, come on.
I just saw the entrance when I visited there last.
Stranny, you have hooked me.
What voice did I give him?
Oh, this is pretty scary.
I would be quiet.
Oh, he's got flowers.
Oh my god, cut scene.
Look, we're here.
Look, Juliet's over there.
Oh, there she is.
I don't remember doing this quest, honestly.
I think I'll confuse it with Goblin Mail one.
Go over to her and I'll go wait over here.
Okay, then.
Yeah, just go.
She's fine.
Hey, Juliet.
Juliet.
Oh, dear.
You seem to be dead.
What voice did I give her?
Oh, Romeo.
I'm Philippa.
Oh, wow.
You're a fox.
It's a shame about Juliet, but perhaps we can meet up later.
Who's Juliet?
Wait, what?
That's it?
What?
Hello?
I didn't wait, so she's actually dead.
Did we actually kill her?
Oh, no.
That's really sad.
I actually feel really bad.
I don't remember that.
Father Lawrence messed it all up.
We just poisoned an innocent woman.
Wait, we're go check.
Wait, we'll go to her house to see if she's there because what?
That was a method.
Right, we're going back to the house because what?
Juliet in shambles, literally.
She's selling her stonks.
That was crazy.
Right, the door's still open.
Surely.
Surely there will be no shenanigans at this door.
She's fine.
Is she actually?
Let's get inside.
Let's inside.
Inside.
There we go.
You got there in the end.
You just need a little guidance.
I suppose you're quite pleased with yourself now.
Wait, why?
Juliet?
She's literally getting ran through about yourself.
What did she say?
I sat in that cold crib for ages waiting on Romeo.
That useless fool never showed up.
And all I got was indigestion.
I'm done with men like him.
Now go away before I call my father.
Oh, can I play piano?
Oh, I wish you could play piano.
That'd be kind of cool though.
That's so bad.
Wait, why can't I go through that door?
That's actually really sad.
I feel kind of bad though.
Sorry, Juliet.
We didn't mean that.
I'm sorry.
Stop!
I'm getting locked in again.
Actually getting soft locked in my video game.
Okay, I am going to make a cup of tea and call a pee break.
And then we're...
Are we got enough level, like enough skill level now that anyone can like trade?
Is nine quest points enough?
I think we were going to do some quick fissure.
Fissure on.
Pee break, finally.
Let's just name a preview.
All of yous have been needing a pee for ages.
A wee break.
A piddle break, if you will.
Oh my god.
Yeah, what do you want to give me?
Oh, a beer and a kebab.
Are you asking for a drunk stream soon?
Because don't think I won't do that.
Don't think I won't give the people what they want.
Thank you very much.
Okay.
Oh wait, is that going to log me out and then you can all see what my freaking email is?
I will turn...
I will hide the game off a screen.
But I might have to log back in again.
No, let's game audio.
Hold on.
Game chat, donations.
In game?
No.
Right.
I'm going to do that just in case because I don't know if it's going to show.
You can set it to 25 minutes.
Oh, I've not set it.
Okay.
Give me like three minutes.
I'm going to pee.
I'm going to make a cup of tea.
I do recommend you get up, stretch your legs, get some water and then we are going to do
actual cooking.
We're going to do actual cooking now, I think.
Because we've hit the quest point thing.
I don't know.
But okay.
Give me...
Let me cook for like three minutes and by cook, I mean let me boil a freaking a kettle.
Okay.
Right.
I will be a moment.
Okay.
Three minutes.
Go for a go for a tinkle-winkle.
Okay.
it put me back in so rude sorry the stream just dead silent
she doesn't know that we know her email already though oh no you did not know the email that was
used oh you're all here welcome back oh he's playing the wrong back I've got me copper tea
so if you hear that with my meow and my cupboards hi I just wanted to say it's very likely that she
be caught in button button bum is online right now because it's very likely that she's online right now
what tea honey tea honey um honey every day egg eggglish break for three you want to trade with me
sure I'll I'll trade oh wait I'm not gonna show on the freaking screen you've been such a silly
being sorry ever you given me what is this what is it what is it oh jug of white are you trying to
get us all sozled are we having our first drunk get together no I mean the flavor uh it's like
every day in ghoulish breakfast I think it's just called black tea quick hate the fish what are you
what are you doing it's unironically a good healing item Wayne I mean I'll get drunk with you guys
anything if we ever do a convention like after after the end of the convention can we do a pub
crawl I've never done it before but I want to I want to participate never done that's part of
the British culture right but it lowers your attack level oh my god can we do a drunk brawling
in the wildies we'll do that at the end of the stream we'll all get drunk and and go into the
wildies and have a brawl and whoever's the last man standing I'll give you can you can you buy a
rose in this game I'll give a single I caught what she did with her stream it was so beautiful
she was like lying on us POV stream I'm like damn these girls were like so they've put so much
effort into it because um I literally was just gonna sit there and be like you know get drunk
melee more powerful eat cuttlefish which okay what do you wish to offer me eat cuttlefish
what are you offering making offering you must you must impress me from the last time you didn't
offer or are you new to the game and you don't know how to put an item in the slot wait so you
add milk to your tea yeah honey milk and everyday tea I'm not supposed to have date right you have
taken too long we're quick shots around here okay right we have nine quest points so I think all
our accounts should be unrestricted by now or something so we are officially gonna start
our fishing level and what we're going to do can it right okay we're going to do it the way I
did it in my childhood and then we'll change to whatever the most like fastest method is okay
so everyone teleport to Lumbridge we are doing it the way this is how I used to do it as a child
everyone go to Lumbridge use your open up your spellcasting book and take us to Lumbridge
I'm on ancient what does that mean Strony it's not their fault they don't know where to put it
oh you can't fit okay and now I'm gonna quickly go up to the bank and we're all gonna take the
fishing nets that we put into the bank because we're gonna catch crawfish so everyone up them
stairs up them stairs it's gonna be rush hour inside the bank okay so empty your inventory
like everything in on your person's empty and then I will take the small fishing net okay and then
I'm also going to bring an axe and a tinderbox and I'll make the fire if I had a tinderbox I do
tinderbox uh there we go so all you need to bring is that small fishing net and we're going to do it
we're going to do it baby Strony style because this is what I used to do okay so drop all your items
up here in the bank reflings drop drop drop oh it was a refling the cow was a refling I remember
when everyone thought a zero was a cow and I was like eh think again cow has been done to death
think again this guy says wtf he has no idea where we flings okay make sure you dropped everything
you got your fishing net and then we'll go back to the front of the castle okay let's go as long as
you have a small fishing net we can get leveled up I will be outside the front of the castle waiting
for you hats never fit I'm on ancients my home telly goes to edgeville I have to hop
world to teleport there I'm gonna pretend like I know what that means okay look at all my refling
is that everyone there's a little refling there is there anyone else coming down the stairs
give it a few more minutes I want to give you fish you want to give me fish no we're going fishing
we're going to go cook we're going to level up my cooking we're currently level
seven on cooking so first we're going to what's going on
brainwashing mostly
what was that putting me those guys like what's going on it's like what's brainwashing mostly
okay true ah he goes ah I understand not called brain right okay take a little left
outside the castle make sure all my reflings are here a little bit of a left doesn't work on me
don't have a brain oh bless you okay okay please follow me reflings I don't want to leave anyone
behind I want to make sure you're my reflings no okay we are now going to go to the fishing spot
that is past the graveyard not a cult if we're hypnotized maybe technically oh no sorry I lost
some reflings that were following oh no they're stuck behind at the church I'm so sorry okay
everyone get to the fishing spot over here this is where I used to fish as a child
mama and her ducklings main break we're gonna be up and then look wait these reflings
no maybe not really but we can fish everyone can fish on the same tail doesn't make a
difference how many bots we got all these bars you can boss shrimp who's buying shrimp for hell
starting leading the refling around like a big school field trip we are all individuals
yeah we're gonna fish and then we're gonna get like cooking level what is happening
beep beep does not compute 101 oh 101 oh 101 we're pretending we're bots
oh are such shows shrimp locked hardcore pre-vp bronze man market sunk by bots
this is going to be fun to do without access to my bank oh no I don't even thought hello fellow human
hello fellow flesh humans how are you doing fish shrimp cook many big level keep cook keep get
yes that's a plan so we're just starting with this everything that lives is designed to end
what is that refling doing that oh my god that bot just ran off so we're gonna fish until
our inventories fill and then I'm gonna chop down one of those trees and we're all gonna
cook around the fire together and we're all gonna share little stories when we cook our food like
like what people do in communities and stuff so who's gonna be the I'll be the fire master okay
and this batch of fish we're gonna talk I forgot the net I told you to bring it now the only thing
about fishing is that it all expires so you have to move to the next tail this is to prevent
and hashtag and quotation marks this is to prevent oh hold on I'm calibrating
did it calibrate yeah calibrate I'm level fishing too
oh the the trainer guy should give you a free net hopefully what is that
so we're yeah we just doing this and we're gonna cook the fishy and then
when our cooking goes up we can start cooking other stuff and making other stuff
that brings even more hardcore bro watch out oh no the the tail expires give me give me
never seen so many real players oh oh that's crazy can we cook scrawny don't cook the cuttlefish
oh I put it in all caps but it didn't work we're all both don't cook the cuttlefish
calamari no let's see if they know the secret roofing handshake
I'm a bot hooked up to jet chat GPT scrawny cooks in her own way pretending to be a human right
now I'm behind a paywall oh it's fine chat GPT nine was breathing amazing they're like what on earth
is going on okay we're actually doing really well run fishing.exe honestly I'm character AI
oh you want to you want to what you don't want to kick the cuttlefish no you don't
oh we're leveling up I can hear reeflings getting levels I'm gonna go grab a net yes
we're gonna be here for a little while until we stop burning the shrimpies oh wait that
doesn't that fishing tutor give you a net wait come back and that's like you can hear me anymore
okay I think that fishing tutor might give a net can I head pat you can head pat the cuttlefish
a bunch of randies yeah oh we're oh we're randy all right are you sure yeah
this random guy's like oh
we're a bunch of randy andies instructor unclear stuck in there oh no who's making the fire I'm
making the fire are you already full of inventory I'm not even full
I feel so much more fishing to do just run to the baby no no I'll make a fire I'll be a moment
oh someone made a fire there's a fire there if you need to cook
I'm wondering I'm actually gonna do something mildly controversial I'm gonna move myself here
so you can see my inventory there so now you can see my inventory as well
yeah that's better isn't it and look I'm touching text
okay I will go here so then you can see my thing oh runelight just made me take a screenshot
wow runelight that's just gonna go for that I'm level 3 fishing see that's how much I've hardly
fished up anything taken so long new twitter audio licking chat I mean that audio I made yesterday
was pretty cool is she's now Ian reeflings I I saw I see over you'd let me bite me there was an
error generating a response oh my god are you guys trolling this guy it's like I'm seven again
they're fishing levels oh my god level level three level three fishing bestie I'm just so good
I'm actually just so good at fishing I say that as a fishing spot disappears right in front of me
astronomy if we eat shrimps are are we kind of accountable you're in for a rude awakening when
you learn what fish eat
so true but it's a silly oh my god I'm level three fishing too to win
wait you can share your fishing rank like that how do you do that
what the what is going on I'm scared what happens if we tell them what happens if they're like oh
we hate each other's uh some I don't know if you can read that because I was quite far away
uh we're shrimp maxing shrimp maxing gang
well I'm hopping gross oh no so gross oh we out here shrimp maxing literally shrimp maxing gang
he couldn't handle the odor look we are smelling quite fermenting
average mmo player when he sees other players yeah I'm getting out of here and then and then he'll
come play but oh this is all bots and dead and then finally meets like a gang of folk and uh yeah
900 xp an hour one take shrimping for real for real what a sloot
strongy's fish an error not that you are one might say it smells quite fishy drop drop the
strap for one chicken for real for real um if you're new to runescape if you hold shift you
can drop your inventory once you click I am a beep beep bop please contact strongy if broken
honestly that do you think the jagex team are like one ass is going on over here
we never see this kind of a god it takes so long I still don't have a full inventory
my my inventory inventory I'm not feeling it wait you beep the beeps I beep the boops beep boop
is social interaction how much okay uh oh you guys are making fires right let's see what level
we get once we have a full inventory 500 I I boop the boot I boop the boop
okay we're almost there I just need to pick up two more shrimp do it pick up two more shrimp
check out that long pick up them shrimp
dropping is faster I threw them on the ground I want the xp for fishing as well
so I say that as if it's not like 10 xp for a net honestly
it's strong a slang term too oh I'm strong in myself right now honestly I think it works
any stronger my inventory is fully f I'm literally missing one fish like please just
fish it up oh my gosh finally you can't carry any more fish just click the raw anchovies or fishies
and then let's see how many we burn we burnt the first one cook the same burnt the next
yeah inventory full begin walking sequence find nearest fire honestly
I'm at work right now I feel like my boss is you're on RuneScape at work isn't that dangerous can't
you not get fired for that like please don't get fired because you're watching a RuneScape stream
I'm literally going to be online for quite a while I don't know how long but work from home gang
okay okay okay I was going to say imagine your boss like walks past your cubicle and all they see
is me typing in chat I'm strong in myself right now like getting fired for a visa but worth it
I hope no wait oh no the fire disappeared sorry I wasn't cooking that entire time sorry I wasn't
paying attention look I just get so distracted there's some of your feelings around how am I
how am I supposed to not get distracted oh are we gonna level eight cooking only another
91 to go because it's 99
oh is it technically are you feeling a bit better I am I think I needed that food and
just to kind of wake up um I'm not sure why I felt so rough when I woke up I feel better
I've got food in my tum tum I've got a honey tea that can't wait getting a promotion from
each of our boss calls in on the office you're all she is based technically you're also playing
runescape at work off I wouldn't he say streamings work honestly I'd say the only time it feels
like work is if I have to prepare like maybe like for the game shows and stuff level nine by the way
that's right read him and wait for level nine boss calls you in the office and says he's watching
scrawny too runescape takes no focus though okay and now I am going to hold shift and drop all
these freaking wait hello wait no why isn't it working I thought it was shift is another shift
to drop stop is that am I going crazy I'm good sorry oh just seems everywhere oh pardon me wait I
could have sworn it was shift to drop things far oh my god oh no you guys are gonna have to watch me
manually draw bless you bless you I'm manually dropping please don't look I'm so embarrassed right
now okay it's setting oh it's a certain is it actually why would they not have it on like
the pens the pens all sentence but I did all sense it's not gonna like just show my IP address is
that controls drop gameplay oh this is too much I won't drop I won't drop click shift to drop
I am beautiful I actually got that that was so good right hopefully my email address didn't show up
I hate that's just how it is right oh there we go got it right and then we go back to fishing
because we're only level 99 I'm gonna check the chart view cooking gates we can do meat chicken
and all that trout is 15 which is a big start upgrade so I guess we're doing this until 15
and we're going fishing elsewhere but as we level up we get closer and closer
oh my god level four fishing not to brag or anything but level four all of us
I'm pretty close level fishing
wait what are you doing a command he's tapping a command well got run you catch the shrimp and
burn them I'll burn them thanks for hanging see when you come back I just I don't know I've not
decided if it's an endurance right now we're just memeing and dreaming and streaming and fishing
and then we're fishing and we're cooking and we're cooking and we're fishing
my mind not working you just gotta trust me for real for real don't worry I do this all the time
don't worry did you see it what what did I see the toenail wait what did I miss was there
something on stream I don't see it I see you guys we're all just hanging out
sorry I've got gains to get bye bye I don't think I was a roofland I was
someone that was interested in what we're doing see how you feel like four is going from there
she literally at the start was no this will not be an endurance human after a few hours she
doesn't know anymore it's hard just the bots hanging out doing a lot of bot things he wants to
talk about his cars extended warranty I literally I do not want to talk to you leave me alone old
man he's getting harassed by an NPC shadow wizard and when you get how how purple are those anchovies
are shrimpies oh wait anchovies and shrimp are different
hmm just tip some money for another four hours I'm like a receipt a reciprocal
a reciprocal Danny you put Danny put text behind my screen
okay there text doesn't go over me anymore
oh my god leveling up we're getting them gains I did not realize how slow fishing was to get
my goodness
she doesn't want to leave us honestly I like after the so I can apply for monetization I'm
going to apply after the stream and see what happens I don't know how long it's going to take
but um tomorrow's ASMR so that's short and then the taste test and stream is short as well
however it might work out better because if I get monetized then I'm doing my pop-up
monetization stream surprise thing um I know I'm fishing but there's no fishy
I wish you good luck on the month yeah basically YouTube just reviews the account and goes yeah
good to go oh man my bank is locked can you hit me up again in three days
I don't know what that means back to fishing we're just fishing uh but yes um we're just
going to level up as much as we can do right now um any ringfoot adventure streams yeah
100% I absolutely adore love ring uh ringfoot adventure
and it was really fun as long as it's not dangerous for my car but I'm pretty sure I got
pretty high last time do you have an idea of how many more watch hours you need oh I made
watchers the problem was YouTube wasn't updating our stats for one week like the stats are now
behind one week like it doesn't make sense um so only now I can apply even though after debut
we had watch time like it's just a bit it's a bit silly but um we're submitting we also think now
that we have one confirmed like week of stats the culling stops here so you might be unsubscribed
if you're watching in right now I don't know but don't be afraid to like and subscribe to the stream
helps out you know that jazz but um we think the culling has stopped so a few ASMR group collabs
and all that are gonna come out shortly after monetization because the girls some dummy used
my email to make an account and one of the passwords I use that's just like as great
names ring fit my blood please don't push yourself too hard like that one time I don't I just really
enjoyed it but I can't do like subscribe and send your bank card details hell yeah um just thumbs
up right now thank you I don't know why but haven't been subbed on once um maybe it's because I got
YouTube premium I don't know what caused it because I did get marshmallows that are like no I like
I straight up gotten subbed by like three of the girls or did this or whatever I don't know if it's
also related to if you don't watch the girls like shorts or if you don't watch any content but
subscribe and then peace out then YouTube don't like that and see it as bot activity rather than
someone subscribing and being like I'll come back later and watch this like not everyone watches YouTube
shorts um which reminds me I should have sent two shorts to Emmy to review because the editor had
finished those shorts I'm going to do that after stream and solve by watching everyone
literally if you put if you watch their shorts or puts like some minutes and a watch time into them
then I think YouTube doesn't um take you I got unsubbed from some other VTubers pre-davio but
not from any of the girls good good that's what I like to hear so me subscribing just to support
is pointless oh no like actual YouTube subscribe is not pointless what happened was the accounts
were getting called because they were new and for bot protection we were getting wrecked but we
think now because there's one week of confirmed stats it's over like I don't think we got called
at all recently like today or when I was asleep so yeah so I think it's only going up from here
now thankfully I like check the stats of everyone's accounts and we should have been at 5k right now
but it's okay we'll we'll work back up towards it um yes it's weird I know it's bot protection
I had never experienced it before and me oh my it was aggressive on us very aggressive but I do
think it's I genuinely do believe it's over especially once the girls get monetized I don't
think you experience it as a monetized channel because that just seems a bit odd because they
know if you're being watched by bots or not so oh my god my mind's are cracking okay I'm gonna
slip my slip I'm gonna sip my tea please don't do anything to the slit okay
delicious
but yes I have a very fun collapse coming out soon TM
I can't wait YouTube stopped in oh literally it's such a shame I felt so bad for the girls
because we were like in the discord like oh my god we're at 3000 subscribers oh my god oh my god
like getting ready to make but like all of us held back from doing a celebration post because it
just wasn't happening and it was such a shame I do have a special like congrats on 5k for everyone
posting a 10k and then I don't know what's happening after that if I should order more artwork or not
the 10k artwork is absolutely gorgeous so I can't wait for everyone to react to it
but I can't I can't let anyone know what it is I don't want to ruin the surprise
level 10 cooking we did it we did it are you squidding me right now
Brian can't wait my wallet is ready pachinga thank you very much for the tip again you can't wait
for what the 10k it's already it's free it's free to subscribe young Uber
how do you mean the onion my fishy my fire keeps the fires pranking me it keeps disappearing as
soon as I go get it I'm on level 11 it stops you cooking every every time it's selling oh I'm in
the fire now I'm sacrificing myself for nothing interesting happens use it on the fire I think
they mean the soup with the membership oh sorry sorry my bad apologies apologies me um no that's
smart okay uh I'm like kneeling out of the fire to cook these
she uh honestly when I said I was cooking making veal or I wasn't kidding okay I'm cooking by gas
okay who's making that noise
sounds like someone's building something building something
back to the fishing we're getting oh pardon me sorry maybe we should be doing the cows you know
that so we can get um uh how to say it so we can get combat and maybe we can do a few more quests
that require a tiny bit of combat before so we don't get too wrecked is there a timetable for
super membership or is it still soon it's still soon um basically it's gonna pop up once it happens
so we need to submit ourselves and youtube takes this sweet time to review that and all that and
once it's accepted it's up to the girls whoop by the pope brian brian speak and on you didn't put
anything in the box thank you for the tip and on I appreciate it I'm not gonna call you out for
not putting nothing in the box hmm but brian didn't say anything and congrats if your name's brian
you're gonna love these streams oh my god wait you must get startled I just go brian I don't know where
hmm what's in the box nothing wasn't me in the donal but still a little little yeah
if your name's brian you'll look nice maybe that should be my mom oh
brian nothing you ordered miss stop no I purposely didn't say anything so you went
tiff again I purposely didn't say anything add on so you wouldn't do that you goofy goober stop it
here's that nothing you ordered me yeah you think you're so smart you'll smile you you'll
you set another desk right now huh you twirl you twirling your hair you flicking your feet about
the arm so smart yeah I'm such a smart you're such a smart alec you're not you're not smart
you know couldn't on an anonymous you're such a smart al anonymous instead of smart alec oh you
know I tried I tried okay I tried I don't know something something brian brian
brian brian said nothing thank you brian brian brian brian brian the one brian in the chat right
now his face is like so red it's a smart fling oh yeah when reeflings are smart I'm gonna call them
smartlings I wasn't even a joke to be honest I wasn't even a joke I just said what someone said in chat
don't mind me I just got here
he says I just got here
it's not as terrible I didn't add any more sound effects I was busy it's busy I need to think
of what's a terrible joke that no one likes what's the difference between a legume and a chick pea
I've never had a legume on my face before
thank you thank you I'll be here all week
get it do you get actually ac should probably tell that joke
why was the pony taking cough medicine
because he was a little horse
oh oh sorry I thought that was that was a good one my bad my bad
a horse goes to the bar the bar man asks why the long face
okay no more no more no more no more jokes sorry guys sorry sorry
two blondes walk into a bar you think one of them would have seen it
it's like the goofiest gimmick ever okay someone says hey strongy guess what
what that's right we're talking in chat and in stream at the same time I chuckled chicken butt
someone said they chuckled
we should level up jokes instead of cooking oh god are we that bad
how are we joked she be slander wait how
no comedian opens a comedy date are you all right okay okay hold on
are you all right no you're all left
we're getting like five eggs be per hour with these jokes honestly
oh
are you guys are just giving me jokes to say
two fish are in a tank one turns to the other and asks how are you do you drive this thing
I'm just stealing your jokes I'm not even I'm not even delivering them the way a comedian should
do
oh my gosh oh level 12 cooking we can do trout soon
I feel like I'm taking damage of the emotional can listen
getting your material these are terrible a guy walks in a bar and says oh that was the blonde
joke two blondes walk into a bar you think one of them would have seen it
mm I'm not burning too much
we're doing all right we're doing all right oh level 13 we're really not burning that much
then if we're getting this fast I don't know what level you stop burning shrimp but yeah
reading the black ops will give me pts flashbacks to second chance honestly that perk was so annoying
and I remember being Tizmo enough that I remembered if people were using it in
snd so I would keep freaking spraying until they were they were dust
I could tell you the best knock knock joke if you want to go on then I ain't got a song
bored for none where do cows go on days the movies
ah did you already hear that one okay sorry god you guys are you get a tough crowd tough
crowd to do honestly tough crowd some of you guys okay two muffins are baking in an oven one
muffin says boy it sure is hot in here the other says oh my god a talking muffin
oh didn't like that one you guys are really two hydrogen atoms we're walking down the street
when one turns to the other oh dear I've lost an electron really are you sure I'm positive
oh oh you guys know your you guys know your uh your physics you paid attention in physics class
lovely lovely what do you do when you cross a cow in an octopus cow amari
I think I'm gonna get I'm gonna get kicked off stage I'm getting I'm getting
on please I am he goes please stop I'm dying right right we'll give that break we'll give
that break we'll give that break no more no more because I don't know much about real physics
well studied vtuber physics oh did you hear twitch updated its terms of service and a vtuber's
have to be held to the same standard as flesh tubers and everyone like why why did you pick youtube
I've told many times and I'll tell again you cannot run a manager account on twitch as well
well matters
strongy's good joke drop rate is one out of five thousand oh that's rough that's a rough drop rate
brian what is the difference between the sea and strongy strongy always tastes like fish
brian you got the wait what did I understand that iron reaper thank you for the tip what's
the difference oh wait I don't even think what's the difference between the sea and strongy strongy
always tastes like fish the sea doesn't taste like fish what like saltwater I don't get it oh you want
brian to do jokes more than me you'd rather freaking tts brian make the jokes than me okay okay I see
who is she kept telling us to be positive it's hard without oh wait sorry I'm gonna start your
joke I think I just read the end of your joke oops I just read the punchline of a joke
brian has some real comedic timing to be fair
why brian is better at delivering the joke sorry strongy no fair yeah I'm gonna fucking oh when
I went for a pee a hardly peed so I'm gonna force myself to hydrate quite a lot in the next few
moments because I'm gonna forget how many tickles does it take to make a squid laugh
tentacles oh that's a cute one I like that one I like that one that's a good name
miss strongy this is my first stream of yours and I find it extra uncanny that you're actually
funny saying my real name so much oh it's because the the tts the text to speech if someone don't
his name is brian so I always scream brian because he interrupts me when I'm talking because I talk
so much I don't think the tts has ever interrupted me when I'm not talking I don't even think that's
possible brian that announced her yes sorry I'm really trying to finish this bottle of water
hmm what's brian's oh she mark will we make brian a visa for
we'll get instead of neurosama we've got brian samos
two eggs in a pan one says to the other it's boiling in here the other says wait until you
get out here and smack you in the head I need to add you're making me wanting to add like
wham wham wham wham yeah scott scott's are want to talk uh after all an Irish man true true
I have a lot of jokes about unemployment sadly none of them work oh who goes there how does a
squid go into battle well armed get it because squids have eight arms not eight legs people
think it's eight legs but it's not but it's because it's a like a misconception that octopi have eight
legs add a boo you suck honestly I probably should I want to add the wham wham wham you suck
are you squidding me right now brian a bear walks into a bar and asks for a gin and tonic
the bartender serves them and asks why the big pause the bear holds up its front legs and says
because I'm a bear
are you squidding me right now that was terrible reluctantly saying impossible to not interrupt you
when you're always yapping that helped me out here I was quiet for once because I was like
brian tell his little joke thank you reluctantly saying for the tip and the terrible joke um
oh I get the joke now oh no the joke's actually pretty smart I'm sorry there was like three little
dots it says a bear walks into the bar and asks for a gin and tonic the bartender serves them and
says why the big pause as in pause in your sentence and he says I'm a bear as in big pause I'm sorry
I never got that the first time I'm sorry or if on biscuit impossible not interrupt you
I'm sorry I wasn't thinking I'm sorry
did you hear about the guy who got connected why OBS my OBS just is connected but I'm still in game
I'm still here why does OBS do that it just connects me for a millisecond and it gives
me a heart attack why why did they do that I said I disconnected for a second I really dislike
when OBS keeps doing it I don't know if it's my internet or OBS we are so back yeah literally
back on stream lots strutting we're strutting I'm back I'm back I'm back I've been sabotaged
by the beastie boys it's time for sabotage do you like when I pretend to be a guitar
do you remember that Star Wars movie
where that was how they defeated the enemies I thought it was the coolest thing ever I loved it
and I cried at the other Star Trek movie that came out that's the Star Wars I meant Star Trek sorry
pardon if I said Star Wars the Star Trek movie and then sabotage
how do you call cow with no legs ground beef
thank you thank you came up with myself totally didn't read it from
from our reef on indian karaoke where you just provide the guitar sense
I just heard the cat
the jokes are too much for the server I am I I think I'm killing you guys with the sound board
now I think we need to maybe give up a bit of a rest
you got me so confused where you said the Star Wars movie that became Star Trek yes sorry sorry
I used to see DJ stream with you girls make an instrument noises Brian what do you call
account of his seizures beef jerky
yeah that's what you get that's what you get on
thank you for the tip honestly that wasn't that bad
I'm level 14 over oh the fire the fire playing a little prank on me hold on the fire is playing a
prank on me thanks for the tip it was actually not a bad joke I'll give you
everyone knows that Star Wars and Star Trek is the same thing no it's me I missed
I really like I really I cried at the Star Trek movie I'm like a little baby
at the was it the radiation scene where he goes inside the chamber
and Spock is like and if you've not seen the Star Trek movie cover your ears you got the
original frickin was it leaner Leonard Hoffman the leaner Hoffman oh I can't remember his name
Sunlin I can't remember you know what I mean you know what I mean he was in the original he was
the original Spock got to meet Spock in the movie and it's crazy
Leonard Nimoy any Leonard Nimoyers
right are we staying here until level 20 are we moving on to trout what do we
what's the plans refill and you guys are kind of in charge here as much as I like to pretend
that I'm the one in charge you guys are actually in charge here do we let's just take a little
look at the cooking gate hmm yes yes a bit of uh let's see what we're looking at for the the meats
no the fish okay I guess fish is under meat uh we've unlocked trout so we could go a barbarian
village I believe they dropped trout and salmon over there
oh what do you call cow with one leg steak
uh what do you call a cow with two legs limby yeah what do you call a cow with three legs
try tip try tip
you can see if the crash occurs because the internet would be us itself oh
true
Leonard Nimoy yes the famous voice of old zi hard north from combat kh I don't know
I don't want to say more about combat I still look like civilization for just to hear his voice
over barb village the classic we're in charge huh can I tell a dark joke as long as it's not gonna
be offensive
my password had to be eight characters so I picked snow white in the seven dwarves
oh that's good I like that one don't challenge death to a pillow fight unless you're ready for
repercussions my plan is full story okay we are gonna head to barbarian village
so drop all your fishy fishies we are gonna rely on oh wait
wait can we even fish I don't know if we can even flesh I think we need uh I think we need a
fishing rod and we can't even fish because we're too low level uh we're too low level
for fishing the fish oh we need 20 fish okay it doesn't matter we're gonna stay here you don't
have a rod oh yeah okay doesn't change the plan sorry I reached overall level 150 let's go
actual MLG MLG you can borrow mine she be and the harem not to be confused with harem
how is the harem and the sheepsters going on how did the stream go
got a rod right here for you um pants crap
okay I guess we're like just gonna be fishing and going for it because we can't even do fly
fishing to get our own but we are literally we started on seven and we're like level 15 already
and that's without getting the like big stuff she be read hi here here um I was gonna say
harambe but rip harambe buddy read hello hi guys today I am playing old school runescape
which you are more than welcome to join in on we are uh achieving uh level 99 cooking we are just
at the bottom of lumbridge castle near the mines and we I know I know harambe my brain because of
the spell and we are currently just fishing to cook and then we're gonna move on shortly uh
merce um who's online who's online today I actually can't remember everyone's schedule
mercy normally comes online in quite a bit um I wanted to play with you but my internet is
absolutely oh well we are at the bottom of lummy if you ever wanted to join but if you're
internet it's crap in the bed is it not in me is emmy emmy is coming on in an hour that's correct
brian why are snails bad at racing they're sluggish
oh so when brian makes a joke you all laugh but when I make a joke I don't get nothing
thank you sherm tank for the don't know freaking everyone's laughing at brian's jokes but when I
make the joke it's terrible emmy emmy coffin game oh we're stream sniping emmy hold on she's
playing the coffin game I want to see a reaction to it I was gonna get a highlight real made of
that stream I'm sorry stroney brian is funny and you're a woman you're not supposed to say that
part out loud that's an insane thought that's an insane thought I'm because it's actually
witty right right you're done you're done brian stream stroney stream oh shocking behavior
oh there's an uncut emerald why did you drop it you can use that for crafting later I'm yonking
it I mean now sorry that emerald's mine now I'm keeping a hold of that you can craft it
she sniped it wait do you want it do you want it back I can give you a back
you can um she went for the uncut one oh you're done you're done oh you're already 99 what the
heck level are you 125 what does that mean you might literally green and shiny I'll take it
come on it's me it's stroney green and shiny oh what is that is that shield
no that's awful I can't look at it properly because of the way the camera angle is working this game
look at that shield can't give up stroney what do you call man with no arms no legs and limbs
in the tiger cage clawed plowed
what did you hear the joke about stroney it was incredible
okay I can fish for herring but I don't want to do that I'm gonna be able to fish out
Emmy playing the coffin game so on current yeah I'm interested to see what her reaction is I don't
know what it's going that joke fell a little short oh this is incredible it's a pun punny
gonna walk my dog lurk time walk you look hi stroney here's the runescaping we are level 15
and 99 on the road to 99 cooking we took her sweet time but we did some questing which was a
bag of fun aim I have no idea how long we're streaming for today jokes about stroney usually
sure full shoot oh and I'm starting okay I just got annihilated because I started I'm sorry I can't
even make a comeback to it now if I wanted oh if I wanted to come back and scrape it off your most
teeth
oh wait maybe I should have done that
I probably should have done that one don't forget level 92 is halfway oh we're getting
close to 92 I can feel it in my bones are you actually going for 99 yeah I want to do it live
with you guys I think it'd be so fun if we all do and literally brieflings gave me a boat load of
fish um to cook so once I stop burning fish I'm gonna like use them and I think that's gonna
propel me quite a lot I want to do it all live on stream and like it's not gonna be behind a
member stream or anything you guys can like we're gonna need a bigger boat I know you guys can
literally come and join me at any point as well when we do these like kind of stream snipe things
I also give you a boat load of money yes a reefling gave me 10 million GP I'm like
Jagex is looking at the account like she's clearly bought right now I have zero wait you want to do
it with us live yeah ASMR I have zero idea how RuneScape plays my friends just post images
of the animal models in the game and they look very funny oh can I get a reefling pet I don't
know how to get a pet in the game oh my god oh my god is there like a pet that looks like a reefling
gold laundering literally Jagex is staring at my account right now could you imagine if I got
banning at the at Jagex and be like hey my account named scottlesfish I know it looks I got banned
because you guys thought I was like money buying like GP or something uh I'm actually just a
beater burn we're all hanging out please I'm banned is there a pet cracking oh I can't oh
Ali I just got a shock on my arm there that wasn't supposed to happen I don't know how I did that I
think I accidentally jammed my elbow in the nerve crack there's nine pets how did you even get those
emotes on screen
gold laundering if they ban you it's because they hate they heard the jokes
cracking these nevermind please don't
look all hail the fire all hail the fire
oh I'm getting close to the next level I keep burning look how much I'm still burning I'm
like burning massive amounts I wonder when you stop burning shrimpies maybe level 20 I feel
like that's like over leveled further fire
let's go maybe a pet slug slugs are close to cut off it yeah
she is not cooking literally everything's burning I'm like missing out on so much HP XP
there hopefully the fishing gets a bit faster because seriously this is like taken forever at
this fishing berth
juke pet is closest to a slug
what do you call a man with no arms and no legs on your front porch matt
oh congrats if your name's matt shout out to matt
oh you guys are going to start sending puns where like the finishing line is like actual names
I got true I got true you can start cooking at 15 oh you got me true
uh my inventory whoa
riflin that's so much oh my god thank you oh my god this will definitely go uh
we're probably gonna artificially inflate thank you riflin I appreciate that uh I think when we
get cooking level 20 we'll take off and see if we can snipe some fishies uh um how you uh
barbarian village there's normally bots always running a barbarian village and we can literally
pick up the fish that's on the floor my only worry is that it might be quiet and we might have to
swap to a different server who owns this hill we don't know we're ten and we're ten aunts okay
yeah you're done you're done get out here
I asked the riveting gameplay the other ones get rivet and literally just clicking points
similar but look how many reeflings there are seriously this little chillin well bing chining
hydration check I'm really needing a hydra oh that was like bats coming out of him
Barb barbarian fishing spot on world through one is one of the greatest free to play areas
okay we'll probably do that next hmm oh do you want me to be reactive
oh that really didn't yeah that doesn't look like it yeah okay maybe not reactive today
maybe another day you'll have to hate the chat though oh because it's thoughts oh the one squid
mirror brian straw me want to do mommy roll play but can't even cock brian that's inappropriate
thank you iron river for the tip I can so cook some pains okay I'm getting there you know
go let me go let me get a bit more experienced
jesus walked into a hotel and tossed three nails on the counter and said put me up for the next
I'm not sure we're going to do a sound reaction to that one
one wait the cuttlefish cooking fish this is kind of no fishy it's the circle of life for fishes
they eat each other no no no no oh my god is the fishing going faster I literally caught two
in a row there I need one more and I level up hmm ah I went away
wait does that mean you eat reeflings only the ones that want board
I can bring you back up again if you want
oh like a cat it's it's it's all these jokes are really cracking me up
oh shucks guys I love the way you hate me up you're so good
you're so good
hello hi hi we're playing old school brisk game and we're leveling up who's driving this thing
my only concern cooking trout right now even though I'm leveled is I'm just gonna burn
it all which is such a waste I don't want it to be a waste
it's a gang gang gang gang it's our new reefling identified
that reefling's beating up that row there
key
my son had been eating electrical cords what did I do grand and mentally conducts himself right
right you know what sound effect I need oh if I got 4k did I finally reach 4k subscribers
but we didn't get called this time a christmas miracle thank you for everyone who has subscribed
I appreciate it greatly uh I will start to uh once I get monetized I will start to slip out
um the 1000 subscriber thank you ASMR videos very shortly uh but thank you so much don't
jinx it I don't know now that we've got our youtube stats updated like I'm gonna apply for
monetization and then I think the culling just stops after that I did the same to shebe and
nothing happened I think it's over I do think it's over did you know that in every five years the
red deer in Scotland have to be culled or they'd overrun the forest because wolves used to be a
natural uh predator in uh the united kingdom but then once they were eradicated basically
the deer obviously their population just like went crazy
man he used to play with my cousin and friend after school when I was younger my name was
hey yo don't put your gamer tie
what do you call a sportsman who is standing in the doorway hey man
what do you call a sportsman who's standing in his oh home okay you're done you're done
heme is slang for home in my bit means my house in scots
yeah I struggle with no roman numerals until I get to 159 then I just click oh then it just clicks
oh okay okay okay I'm gonna I'm gonna open up marshmallows in a minute I forget any more puns
you're all done I tell you more puns but I'm not feeling very punny okay okay I get it I get it
you all just want Brian whoa I'm actually not burnt oh I took this uh I jinxed it I was gonna say
I'm actually not burning that much I burned two so far do you take part in the deer calling I do not
I just know I just remember reading it in a book and I was like yeah that makes sense
need some marshmallows for the campfire why is Jesus the worst teammate in an online
shirt it takes him three days okay you're done you're done no more puns we love Brian yeah clearly
Brian you'll laugh when it's his joke but when it's my joke oh crickets
wow cooking best I can do is burnt meat literally I'm burning so much still I'm like
getting pretty high level I feel like all things considered hold on let me check um yeah I'm 17
cooking and I'm still burning shrimp I feel like 15 should have been the shrimp cut off
if shrimp is a one level one um like cut off I feel like burnt shrimp is a lot
Emmy's going live in five minutes playing the coffin of her lore video um
and before anyone says did your development team just copy that game no actually no one in the
development team had played the game at the point she was conceptualized she was conceptualized
in my image because kind of bro is the best and I don't care why no one says
don't be jealous of Brian only because he makes better jokes I mean yes true but you have other
quality yeah yeah yeah Andy and Lily where should you go if you can't stop reciting
Scottish poetry the burns you know then no one's gonna get that Rabbie Burns is one of her famous
poet it would come with talk to me oh someone wants to trade with me sorry I missed it sorry I
don't know who's sending me a tradeover I apologize what what is that
reflin is that gold it's gold
no way no way I'm literally what in freaking literally level 17 cooking and I'm dripped out
in the gold refling whoa thank you oh my god I'm starting on hold on I need a little dance I need
I need to show it off I need to show it wait let me go in the hill so you can all see me okay
all right I need to face you from the hill so I'm on the hill and you face there are ready
ready we go stun on them we were stunned hey that's right hey a little pair away see from the
back see from the back hey yeah that's right do a little dance do a little dance that's right
that's right stun on them dancing that's right gold gold gold baby yeah we love I love the head
bang a more it's absolutely awful that is awful that more oh my god yeah we love gold playing
are you proud over here thanks god you are cute Brian oh oh no TTS didn't meet that out oh no oh did
it did I talk over it I'm sorry Brian iron thank you for the tip again you can't cook you can't make
jokes thank you thank god you are cute so the thing I got for me we're starting out and we
blown them a kiss like nah you want to beat me oh you want to beat me because I've got that gold
oh yeah you do panic oh look at the hey hey hit it with the knees hey hey hey hit it with the knees
hit it with the knees oh my god that's so good okay fashion shows over folk straight back to the
sleeve mill over again so again the prawns oh my god we hit with the knees oh that was so good
the drip is so good thank you so much replaying you are throwing everything into that head bang
honestly blowing out your back what blowing out your back you want to blow my back out oh my god
I love the gold it so doesn't match my green or purple but I don't care I don't care it's so good
I don't even know you could get golden chef's hat and stuff the fact that I'm level 17 and
cooking makes it even funnier that I'm dripped out in like golden chef stuff honestly you're
damn straight the richest the most popular cooking rinse scape honestly wait hold on
no it's emmy is it real emmy are you guys are you guys freaking throwing is emmy
except trade is emmy here or is emmy doing this right before her stream
emmy is that you emmy is that her emmy she's giving me her coins from starter island
her 25 coins emmy is it imposter if it's emmy would be like no way it's a new account she
gave me her she gave me the coins from tutorial island little sister say two oh I need to give
her bad french oh thank you for the bond offer I've bought membership for a month thank you so
much please keep that bond for yourself I have membership for a month I think we're going to
try and do 99 cooking in a month thank you so much for that offer though I really appreciate that
reflin really do em keep that bond is that emmy do we know if it's emmy she's gonna she's gonna
build upstream and she's either gonna be all cheeky and like of course that was me or she's
gonna be like what rinse what rinse game I've ever played rinse game before
I've never played that game before
oh my god strong is why are you quoted
scaling costume homie is probably in there third wait what are we getting billy's are we
bullying each other we better not be
she's
hope on her can't wait for the night and then kicking your fish dates will be fantastic
oh that's actually pretty good
who wants to trade who who's yummy I thought it said who's emmy I've got emmy on my mind now
oh oh whoa whoa whoa
reflin's how are you also reflin bro we need to take this to the bank like right now I cannot
be standing with this bunch of money on me uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh what on air how are you
also rich in this game
oh you can't be telling your ages acy's gonna be happy that you're all ojisans
she's gonna be in an extra smug about it
ag nature how are you also rich in this game how do you make money in this game honestly
maybe we should maybe we should do like the winter oh i'm about to level up what level
I said I'm about to level up okay there we go 18 kooten okay that's good we're so close to 20 maybe
we should stick around oh my god look how much oh look at the fat stacks like oh my gosh oh my gosh
how
gosh right we'll do that we'll do this
they make money selling the food you cook oh my god cooked fish runs
it was my non-iron man account oh since I can't trade on that oh it's your problem yeah I get it
I get it is this an original couple
all right so emi is on her loading screen who knows what she's doing behind that screen
I'd buy food from strawney yeah where's ya would you buy my homemade ink
or would you like it for free
right if emi's on her loading screen mods may you please post emicles is link and can you
guys please interrogate her and say is she on runescape or is someone is someone
larping as my little sister I'm with my real little sister emi's life story that's awful
who named that I wasn't me that's not it's music so nice and chill but yes emi is going live
with the coffin of Andy and Laylee it is a bit of a reading simulator just warning for those
um make sure you tell her to hydrate through it if she's going to be reading absolutely everything
because oh my gosh
hmm
she said nah
oh who is larping as my little sister giving me 25 coins is that my 20% cut that you give me
what color is the ink uh it's been described as glippy
someone actually I said this other day whoever said it's like a male jar you're done
I don't know who said that hello reeflings oh and you really reefling joined the fray
yes we're on world 388 and we're at the bottom of we're south of lumbridge castle at the mining
slash fishing tutorial area or to the east of the swamp under lumbridge to take the castle
if she knows nothing she's gonna like it for sure
Andy and Laylee is a mess of game it has very unique story plot yes oh please keep going
you cast your net we're almost 20 cooking when we're 20 cooking we're gonna move on to the next
place which is barbarian village I don't know if there's gonna be bot spam in there I could have
sworn I came across a religion bot before that was spamming and it and I was like there is no way
someone's paying for that it was the most bizarre thing this place has got to smell terrifying
literally rotten fish on the floor everywhere burnt fish cooked fish like the whole of gellinore
can smell our operation front over here
wow hydration hydration hydration
how is our fishing level so low what is that our fishing is 12 but our cooking is all the way up at 18
oh
they did not have to go so hard on the music in this game but so good
oh my god we're getting flexed on someone's got a fishing rod
actually getting flexed on hold on is that how you pick up anchovies by the fishing rod
well it means gonna force chat to get her done
there's only all I'm gonna say is there's only one way to finish that game there's only one real
way to finish that game you should work in the seafood business
imagine getting followed by Jehovah's Witnesses even in old-school runes game honestly
there's boss like and it's like why you get more exp for cooking rather than yeah
there's only one real ending to that game and I will accept no other
any food by strongy seafood if I see it I eat it oh that's good I like that
could I interest you in our lordency yeah have you heard of our lordency for Brian
honestly I think I can't remember if I said this or not I thought they're just shouting out like
randomly I would just shout like the most common like boy names and like a chance for someone to
hear their name just like jack and then just freak you out and then we just go back to the
gameplay and I played nothing happened what's another popular boy name I have no idea
Jacob so there we go okay and then we just go back to gameplay I played nothing
just to like freak out whoever's listening and just be like oh my god that's my name
most popular okay fill inventory okay now you just pin your own oh John's a comment John
andrew wake up
hey oh joseph there's a lot of J names j-j-j-j on j-j-j-j joseph j-j-j-j the fire is tricking me again
I don't know I'll see what I can do I don't know I find it fun like kind of trolling a bit like that
and you just like secretly add on yeah see I wanted I'm actually gonna um I'll
I'll spoil this I want to do a hypnosis themed audio where I get you to forget your name and
respond to refling I think that'd be pretty cool pretty cool but I will put like a it wears off
after like 30 minutes type thing I don't want anyone panicking thinking they're they're gonna
like pair them up forget their name if you say Brian three times in front of a mirror you can
summon him and he tells us a pun 19 oh we're so close we're so close maybe like one more rack of
fish and then we're done if I don't burn any actually they're really starting not to get burnt
I'm really happy with that oh that's someone cutting down a tree that's what that noise is
ripped to all those with this obscure yeah like that's the only reason I was like oh it's probably
not that fun for those who have like obscure name type thing going on no strongy make it so it
never wears up no I have to make aware all I'm not really into perma effect hypnosis it's just not
for me um rather a bit a bit scared of it are you with me right now Brian Anakin stark panicking I
don't have a planakin banana and anakin thank you for the tip iron we pour what there was a really
popular um meme about anakin and it was like bananakin and that was it that was the meme
and it had everyone in hysterics had them in a chokehold for years absolutely shawng behavior
shawng they go thanks for the tip anakin start panicking I don't have a planakin that sounds
like that song here comes michael finnegan he had whiskers on his chin again something something
back to the begin again
the best you're getting at me is twinkle twinkle little star you'll either take it or leave it
maybe vader someday later oh I don't remember that part I remember the yoda song where it goes
like oh someone dropped a party hat oh we can put oh I've got my chef's hat look we flings
look look look there's party hats if you want to put them on because it's a party oh look at the
box coming over from the main look oh there's a Santa hat there's a red party hat oh there's a white
party hat and there's burnt fish oh there's one over there and there's a Santa hat
thank you to ever drop them oh look you're open your party hats on look at your party
it's a party in the south of lumbridge yeah
the little party hat oh look at your fancy party hats look at you
what's up party people can we ask the chat to speak german I don't know if the ball
fillers uh non-english words because I'm set up as an english thing why can't mickey miss flying
his plane to scotland at disneyland
you didn't know just say does not in scott's you say does me I don't know why
if I have to explain the joke because of flying how are Santa hats 16k I don't know that this thing
can't speak german it can't speak dutch okay these puns were not I wanted I need a refund
he he he that was good actually I'm gonna be that one I'm giving you that one
yeah I don't know what the bot doesn't doesn't like in terms of TTS at the moment okay we're
definitely fishing a lot uh where is my riefling for sexy fire making
I would like to summon one fire please I'm gonna dance until the fire appears okay let's
dance hey him with a spin him with a spin he's a little bit a little Irish jig hello dance hey
hey hey stop stop stop head back hey hey hey get him with a yawn that is not like a yawn
rish strongy you are my leader schmetaling
a little schmetaling but is that schmetaling in english what is the schmetaling is that
caught a fish in is that caught a fish in german is that what it means thank you for the tip iron
report a butterfly
where's fire right I'll go get a fire don't worry guys I'm on the fire oh wait I found the fire
I'm blind I'm just blind I need my glasses on sorry sorry there's a fire down here sorry
hey strongy do you have a party hat I have an extra one uh I have uh I sorry uh to you know
kind of flex on the peasants but on my head is gold in crusted chef's hat I must stick to my
golden crusted chef's hat thank you very much for your offer super kind you know I don't want to
flex on them peasants below me but I'm kind of styling with the the combo of gold apron and gold
hat wouldn't be like super awesome if the player entered the group and discovered the
shroom thingy to come here if I play oh like someone just joins along well we I don't know if you
uh we told some they were like what's going on and I was like oh some cringe vtuber's shroom
in and they were like I'm world hopping and I was like okay thanks for an incident and
literally no one cares thanks um am I level I don't am I level 19 so
oh I am like two fishies away from 20 and then we're gonna move to barbarian village which
is west of the grand exchange um strongy has power to actually do eh crusted chef's hat weird flex
that happened to me in final fantasy our marshmallow is anonymous yes um if you have firefox it
might be able to translate the screen automatically sometimes a thousand why
um I am going to make another cup of tea hop on stride is a yo
um I'm gonna make another cup of tea because my voice is absolutely feeling it what do you
mean doing multiple 12 or streams back to back is straining on the throat oh it says 10 is that
like a runescape like congrats 10 balloon I saw that wait hold on let me make it look oh my god
he's getting performance anxiety making that fire look it's a 10 he must have got it for 10 oh you
don't look at your shirt what is it's like the logo let me zoom out a little bit it was the 10th
anniversary how old is this game there's too many people well another cup of tea you mean a cup
of tea for the non endurance stream right yeah surely as I say hold on the four hour mark and
we're not even like level 20 and cooking yeah not an endurance stream at all
oh google chrome apparently translates marshmallow as well but now if I send the marshmallow you'll
know it's me no actually because I'm not opening them up right now and for some reason marshmallow
puts like five questions from like loads of different times together at once it doesn't make
any sense send the most horrendous cringe marshmallow and sign your name at the bottom
like a gigatab I played when I was five on my older brother's account oh did he like force you
to go questing that's funniest anything this isn't runescape huh it's old school runescape
oh no we're getting corrections
oh wow doing bot run on your brother's account for him oh I said Lamalle twice in the same
sense oh my god cringe so cringe give it here you're in a level 14 fishing I mean we're getting
somewhere oh no I think I might need pee pee bye bye time as well actually yeah a tea and a pee
might but not a tea not the pee in the pee but I need a pee in the pee in general
key quest is how often are these old school rooms I was gonna do a few endurance streams I have no
idea how long cooking takes so I was gonna do a few endurance streams of it I was gonna try and
finish it in one month but I don't know if that's just being like far too crazy cut off fish wrapper
needs the tea and a pee on runescape with the refunds doing nothing hunting for shrimp I can't
rhyme can't do it I don't know how people do it at the same time
you can reasonably get night night cooking less than 30 hours okay I know currently we're not
maxing but it'll do it'll do I'm gonna do that we did it 30 hours of one tick clicking
level 20 cooking do we still burn shrimp on 20 with carab
one this carab one's a real thing it might be in print oh I don't think you burn after level 20
a reefling check for those of you who are on a fresh account what level are we looking at 20 as well
you guys 20 carambuas or oh she sees okay you're done
I've got 21 I've got 23 how are you all faster than me okay we'll go a little reefling
okay what I'm gonna do is I'm gonna do a pee and a tea a classic um and we will be back
hi how's runescaping we're doing good uh if you ever wanted to join in we're in world 3a
top right there uh why is my latest tip we're not working it should be rotating right now
sorry latest and uh and then we're gonna move to barbarian village next and we're gonna see what
happens if there's oh wait no we can hmm the problem is I don't want to mute the in-game chat
because of the bots I'm gonna go to bed have fun cooking oh well thank you for everything thank you
for the extortionate prices for the shearers and all that um I just realized we would probably have
to fat fly fish the fish ourselves unless we went to the grand exchange but only I have
access to all the fish in my inventory so it's not like we can share it out equally hmm the
bots on this world won't speak I mean I can't I just ignore them if we have to fly fish I think
we need like level 20 fishing so we would be here for a bit longer hmm but rest well there's
reeflings that do need to sleep yeah we would need 20 for the trout hmm oh sorry I just like we need
fish and wine maybe we should pray but how can fish fly are you telling me this fish flies
hmm I'm thinking I'm thinking I'm not sure you guys want to be held here for another
what it were until we get like the actual level needed
hmm I'm thinking but my brain isn't really coming up with any solutions it's either
no there is no solution we have to keep being here until level 20 fishing
and then we can move on it's gonna be a long road either well yeah literally if it takes 30 hours of
like are you telling me a shrimp right this way are you telling me I've cuddled this fish
yeah um if it's going to be a 30 hour stream anyway congrats on 20
no questing for airy levels suck hmm yeah we're also pretty low on combat for fresh
starts as well which is a bit hmm I don't know what we should do are you telling me I cuddled
exactly you can do
miss the mystery well here that quest is right here oh do we need okay how about that
we go for a T and a P and we're gonna do some more questing just to break up the the fishing
because that was quite a few levels we've got with fishing so we'll go do some questing and
and then it can be broken up a little bit because I don't want to like hurt you too much
just doing it over and over oh no you mean we have to stay here and keep chatting forever
I would hate that oh wow oh that would suck yeah I'm glad I'm glad you enjoy my rambles
but just as a reminder Emmy is live playing uh the coffin of Andy congrats a few names Andy
and Lele congrats a few names Ashley or Lele nicknames Lele um then we are going to do a few
more quests free quest just to break it up a little bit because I don't want you guys being
bored out or not but we will start the cooking grind soon another German name for cuttlefish is
Tintin fish a a Tintin fish a Tintin fish oh my gosh okay thank you for the tip iron report
the German name for cuttlefish is Tintin fish I did it in a German at hallo leutard
a Tintin fish a Tintin fish I can't do it I am a big Tintin fish then I mean
um level congratulations you reach a total level of 75 oh I'm flexing on other RuneScape players
right now with that flexing Tintin fish equals an ink fish oh that's such a cool translation so Tintin
Tint as in tint of a color and it's ink tint and so it means tinted fish the tint of the ink oh that's
so cool wow why did I stop cooking I wish I was that high level sad face he says no one feel well
he's probably like billions of levels higher than us tint and ink oh my god ich liebe ich liebe
ich liebe Deutschland yeah okay I am going to go make a tea and pee whilst I fish
hopefully this fishing spot doesn't despawn and then we're going to do a quest okay so I'll be back
in like three minutes now okay give me three three oh excuse me that was a mcdonald's bag from
yesterday I do apologize if you heard that picked up in mic okay I'll be right back I'll be three
minutes pee in a tea please get up and stretch and get some water or hydration or anything of
course that freaking despawns how dare you disrespect I've been shown by this fishing spot you got
Mickey D's yesterday oh well okay right I very quickly go I'll be as quick as I can okay wait
do I need to cover the screen I don't know I don't think I have to but yeah just in case so you
see my email I'll be three minutes okay I was
you
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
I will sing the actual this song
this song can probably just leave the screen on
okay
I can give me the on when I sing
pe-peeeeeeeeeeee
wait
why is he greeting
Wait, what do you mean disconnected? I'm not disconnected! Wait, why are you
greeting? What are you saying? She loves us. What? I never said that, didn't I?
Because I went for a tinkle. You have 30 days. She's back quick, hide the memes.
What were you doing while I was away? I've been away for a few minutes. How was the
pee? It was not a lot of liquid again and I've literally finished up all the
water. So, and I had a tea, and I finished a can of cola. I've got another bottle of
water here. I don't know if you can hear my nails kind of against it. I'm gonna
try and finish that and the tea. I'm not really sure what's going on.
I'm being pranked. I've been pranked by my body. Wait, why does someone say she
doesn't love us hard eyes? What? By the way, reeflings are the best. You say
Coca-Cola. I hear burps. Cola burps. Cola burps. We did kiss the homies. Don't tell
Amy that, she'll be jealous. I'm freaking, wait, I just caught an anchovy.
What does it do? Oh wait, I'm now catching an anchovy because I'm a level? Oh, maybe
that'll speed up the fishing level gain. Okay, I didn't know that. You put
anchovies on a pizza. I don't think I've ever tasted that before. Burps. Oh, I was
so proud when Shabee started burping in her streams. I was like, oh my god. My
literal daughter. Oh my god. With all the tea she drinks, Johnny will be really
sophisticated. That's not bad. The burps are hot. I don't understand the appeal of it,
but then someone said, think of it about the aftermath. Give your run air back, I
believe. We get to rate more mouth pranks. Why do you keep on firing? That's why
there's a freaking fire. I'm getting pranked by the spine. Oh, I'm still burning
stuff. I'm not level. I'm literally cooking level 22 and I'm still burning. That's pretty
rough after this. This is taking us a hot second. Right, so what fishing level do we need?
We need fishing level 20. Shabee made a burp speed. She's indeed cheaper. Exactly. That's what
I thought. Tea bag in the fire. It's running, I kneel. I get so many things like, oh, I kneel
for all the choices. The barbed village spot has a permanent fire to cook on. Oh, right,
I'll put my tinderbox and axe away. And then we will buy fishing gear. We farm until 20
fishing. I did know that. Yeah, we're going to do 20 fishing and then we're going to buy
rods because some of us don't have that attachment. And then we get to go to Barbarian Village and we
fish and we just keep doing that for a while. I think maybe we could get 40 doing that because
salmon. However, the problem is the cost of feathers, but the problem's already been solved
thanks to reeflings literally giving me an insane amount of in-game currency. Oh no,
we're doing a quest. I completely forgot. I apologize. We are fishing level 20 fishing and
then we're going to do a quest that's right here that begins with M. We're going to do maybe three
quests just to break up the little fishing segment a little bit. It's called Mythilene Mystery.
Mythilene Mystery. Burps are saying you ever like come through around someone. I am like, yeah.
Some people like get taught it's really rude manners. Like obviously it's rude,
like you wouldn't be in a job interview and burp in there. Actually speaking of burping in job
interviews, I'm like 90% sure I accidentally burped when I was interviewing one of the girls
revealer now that I think about it. Absolutely mortified. I think it might have been in me.
You know that? No, it couldn't have been in me. I think it might have been Mercy. Someone
had burped and I was like, oh my God, I'm so sorry.
Did you hear about the Talon chef who died? He passed away.
Oh, that didn't go, that didn't go down well.
32, I think to stop burping, burning shrimp. Level 32, you stop burning shrimp. That's insane.
Brian. Stronny, I hope you're proud. I was reading a comic earlier and all I heard was your
voice. I'm so cooked. Oh, did that actually happen? Am I in your head? Thank you,
Senpai. Am I in your head? Is my accent in your head?
Okay, hopefully that hypno's off, that reverbs off on the mic because I actually
I didn't say a thing that tells me if it's on or not.
Always in your head. Soon, world domination. Soon, the first 99 cooking, okay. It's more
attractive if someone doesn't care about it. Giving my wood the sort of group. What? Who is
Riefling is this? Come get your Riefling. You've been in my head for a long time, Stronny.
Cryo Freeze, Momento. See, Stronny, that's why I didn't want the undo button.
Want an undo button. Right, I'm definitely cooking fish a heck of a lot faster now.
Catching fish, my apologies, not cooking.
We need to video game OST ranking. Okay, that slightly slows down progress now that we're
also getting anchovies as well. I keep accidentally trying to use fish on people. I've literally
slapped so many Rieflings with shrimp right now and feel really bad. Hopefully touching
your legs with my shrimp. I'm like, please take my raw shrimp. At 21, I can finally turn cream.
But we all turn cream together at the same time.
If you look at it, it's kind of like a cute little fishing campsite. Riefling's on.
There's a place to turn cream and lump. Wait, we can actually do it?
Hey, I thought we had to wait for another time for doing that. Honestly, right by Farmer
I didn't even know you can turn by. Take it, take my raw shrimp.
I'm really happy that you said you love Germany. It's the first time we've worn something.
Deutschland Uber alles! Deutschland Uber alles! There you go. That's like all the German I could
come up with. Just Deutschland Uber alles. Thank you for the tip, Iron Reaver.
Wait, I don't know why. Nope, that wasn't it. Don't do that again. Why?
Hold on. I'm going to try, I don't know why it doesn't like that.
I don't know why it's frozen.
I'm so sorry, my little scroll and don't know things frozen. I'm gonna have to fix that next thing.
Well, no way you can say that. Wait, what does Deutschland Uber alles means?
Wait, if I just said something really bad, I thought it meant like Germany number one.
Like China number one. What did I just say in German?
Did I just say something really bad?
I thought it meant China number one, but German number one. What did I just say?
Did I just say something really bad? It sounds like...
No, it's fine, but it can be associated with other stuff. I am so sorry,
bitter. I am so sorry.
I thought it meant China number one. Let's just forget about it. I am so sorry. I genuinely
thought it meant China number one, but Germany number one.
When you learned your German from Call of Duty, unironically, like...
Oh my God, idiot, absolute idiot. I'm so sorry. I do apologize for that.
It's the first line of a national anthem. Oh wait, it's the first line of the national...
German national anthem?
It's only problematic if you use in a specific contact. Oh, okay.
Shawnee, tomorrow will start to pop out strange fan art of you in a strange and nostalgic outfit.
Just remember, I don't own rights to previous things. That's what you're gonna...
Like, I might not be able to interact with it if you're maybe getting a bit too cheeky.
Yeah, their national anthem from 1930s. Wait, not... I'm sorry, I really didn't...
Which Germany... Oh God, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Oh, genuinely thought it meant China number one. Like, I don't know if you guys ever played
pub G or something, pub Newgrounds or whatever. But everyone used to come in and go China number
one. And that was it. That's basically what I thought I just said, but I did not say that at all.
Don't worry, I'm new here. How do I find where you are on the map?
So when you open up map, you will start here right outside of Lumberge.
And you just take a... Or maybe you started at the quest guy. He's like literally right here.
You want to go south. You can always use this cross here and click it and it will make everything
like north point north. And then just come south through a graveyard and we are literally all here.
So south through a graveyard and south again.
Brian!
I'm so sorry. I didn't... I genuinely didn't know what it meant. I do apologize.
I thought like... I thought everyone was like yay because I said Germany number one.
And there's a few German watchers and no, I'm just an idiot. So yep, there's that. Apologies.
Sorry. Thank you for the tip. I do apologize.
Ah, cringing at myself. I'm like, oh, maybe I should cut that segment out of the void honestly.
I don't want anything happening. Like anything weird happening. Don't stress about it.
Okay, I'll try to get there.
I can't stop laughing. No, I don't laugh at me. I literally... Anyone got a fire?
Yeah, probably take that out. I want to ask, how are you already so good at this?
I watched someone else try and they only have two quests left in FTP but still need attack.
Oh, I'm not good at the game. What? You were literally in it with us. I'm rubbish at the game.
Well, actually we have one, two, three, four and five. We have five quests done.
Oh wait, are you memeing? I watched someone try and they only have two quests left in FTP
but still need a taxi to Viroc. Oh right, because I actually threw the game.
What's the timestamp? Hold on. Four hours and like 38 minutes.
Hold on, I need to make more of that. Four hours, 48 minutes.
Oh, be on my... Right, there we go, wrote a note.
Time to get this board chopped up.
We have other... Another 90 levels of cooking in front of us.
Don't let your... Your not... Sorry, the love heart's in the freaking way.
In fact, it's in the way again. You're not Dutch knowledge, so...
Hello, I am a Dutchman. I know how to speak Dutch.
Yes, I know how to speak Dutch.
Only 13 million XP to go. No, no, no cuttles, we're laughing with you. I was laughing at you.
Okay, okay.
Relaxing stream. Okay, I'm glad you find it chill like that.
I'm sorry, I'm at the stage where I'm now cringing at myself thinking
I thought that meant Germany number one in all the contexts that I'd ever seen that phrase.
Anyway, I'm going to drink my tea and I'm probably going to cringe myself to sleep tonight.
Have you declared... Have you declared war to something with that sentence or opened a bakery?
Good people. Hopefully the bakery.
You're fine. Oh no, is there fire maker going offline? I will make us a fire, don't you worry.
Come, let me go get a tree. I think there's a tree in the swamp or something.
Is there not a dead tree in here? Am I going crazy?
I could have sworn there's like a dead tree in the swamp that you can... Oh, there is.
I'm going to get jumped by a frog, but I'm going to be so quick with froggy and got time to attack me.
Oh, I'm full. All right, drop, take the tree, and then run all the way back to the tree.
Oh, you made fire. Sorry. Oh my god, my woodcutting is so bad. It's going to take forever to cut this tree.
Okay, we did it, we did it, we did it. I have 50, not to brag or anything, but I've got 50 XP in woodcutting.
Let's see. Okay, okay, we're back, we're back, we're back.
Just so you know, Germany number one means Deutschland of dying irons. Maybe next time. Yeah.
Deutschland, Deutschland of dying irons.
We're learning who said streams and educate your man, huh? Get that on fire.
A whole 50, literally, not to brag.
What if you moved on to higher tier fish? So we're currently trying to get fishing level 20,
and then we're going to do some questing just to get over all XP,
and then we're going to move on to higher level fish, just to kind of break it up with a bit of fun
questing in between. I hope I don't pass out too early to the confidence of this company and me so hard.
Learning that a Scottish cut official of Germany, yes, this is educational content you've chosen one for.
Are you squidding me right now?
If it's for you, then we'll start the third world.
Thank you for the tip, iron reefer, hardy har har. No, no, bad Brian. Don't read that out loud, Brian.
That's naughty. There'll be no world wars. If anything, I'm actually a field medic,
so I'm here to stitch you up and give you all negative blood when you're perishing from blood loss.
I'm literally a bad boy, Brian, bad boy. Don't say that out loud. Oh my gosh.
No AI, the AI uprising. What's going on here? Oh, I'm itching my little schnozer. I'm going to
take a sip of my tea and see if it's, oh my god, it's the perfect sipping temperature,
truly a British moment when you enjoy, when you appreciate the temperature of the tea.
What are we on for fishing? Oh wait, I'm on 18 fishing. What are you guys on for fishing? We
must be getting close. We can do the quest very shortly. I'm going to put all of this in my bank
though. I am not questing with all of this money on me. Sorry, don't kill some of the money. I'm
zero negative life. The perfect cup of the perfect time, perfect dunking. Oh, what are they called?
Apparently custard cream's got named the best dunkable biscuit. Oh, you're like, how are you
guys higher level than me, honestly? Yeah, are you cheesy, don't run.
Did the Scott have a British moment?
Unfortunately, I do seem to share some traits. Can I even light logs or is it going to take forever?
Because I'm such a low level in fire like making three, four. Oh, it took me four times.
Honestly, that wasn't that bad. 15, but I had to step away a few times. Ah.
Oh, you had to step away because my, my soundboard jokes were just too good.
Remember the one time when Facebook released an AI on the internet and learned from the
community that turned into the biggest thing going wrong?
Oh, it's four men in uniform to carry my little souls through home.
What should he do? Should have been a musician, but he didn't have the money for a guitar.
What should he do? Should have been a politician, but he didn't have a property. This is not the
song that was. Did we do it? We're almost there. We flings. We're so close to 20.
We're so close. By the way, do you have a plan for stages of cooking levels that would do it
chilling spot until 99? I absolutely have no plan whatsoever. I've returned with logs for my fire duty.
I honestly have no plan whatsoever. We're going to move on to Salmon and Trout at
Barbarian Village after we do some questing. And then after that, I think it's just jugs of wine.
And we're literally going to be hanging out like maybe at the Grand Exchange on like a very quiet
server. Oh, level 19 fishing. There might be a quest we're going to do.
Sorry for letting my inner German out, my guess. By the way, do you, oh no, the fact that she didn't
correct the message does mean that she already chose to go straight to level 99.
Yeah, that's the plan anyway. We're going to do some questing just to break it up.
And then we are going to jump back into it. I want to see if maybe we could do level 40 today.
I don't think I'm going to do a full endurance stream as much as I love to harass you guys
and destroy your sleep pattern. I don't think we're going to do a full 12 hour stream today.
Also, my freaking VOD broke. Apparently the VODs break on 11 hours and 55 minutes,
not on the 12th hour. So the end of my VOD got chopped away and it just cuts off.
15 trout, 20 is and 25 is salmon. Oh, we can make apple pies. Oh, I have a muffin.
I have an apple muffin. I forgot to eat it yesterday.
Yeah, something's like not really...
YouTube VODs are almost especially the longer ones. Yeah.
Oh, is it displaying again correctly? Maybe it changed. Yeah, they told us.
That is a sad and frightening, so speaking super fast.
M&M's got nothing on me when I'm saying bioreflums. Okay, I'm like,
eh, that explains why all the other VJubers stopped 10 minutes before the 12 hour mark.
Yeah, so unfortunately, we are having to bend the knee to the VOD overlords. I wonder,
I suppose they had to give a number, like it doesn't matter.
Circum... wait, I thought it said circumstance. Sure, you're not a mumble rat. Oh, I'm a mumble
rat. I can assure you that much. I'm annunciating the words right now. I'm annunciating. Any annunciators?
Oh, come on, catch that last one.
Anything to do with this inventory full of shrimp? Drop them. If you go, you cook them on the fire
and then you drop them once they're all cooked. It sounds like a decision made for some technical
reason over at you. Yeah, like, I assumed they had to put like a number on it, but they couldn't
just infinitely do it. Although there's those accounts that used to infinitely stream music,
was it lo-fi girl or something like that? They just like constantly like keep going.
I'll chug them all. If you go into sentence, you can hit, I think it's like controls or something,
and it's like use shift to drop, and then if you hold shift, you can drop your full inventory stack
really quickly. Okay, level 25 cooking. I'll take it, like we're getting there. It's if I could stop
burning this stuff, if we stop burning, we'd be like literally flying through the levels.
Right, 20 is maybe one more deck officially. Lo-fi girl never saved vods and didn't let you
rewind, so that could be why. We are learning. Okay, more of my tea. I keep forgetting.
And these fishes are hiding from me.
So I assume it costs money to get some of these hysterics costumes, because
these are like total costumes. I have to go in 10 minutes. I can't stay on Firejoy forever.
Yes, that's okay. Don't worry, we can take over. We're probably doing by Quest next.
But thank you for your service. Wait, hold on, 07. Thank you for your service on Firejoy. 07,
we salute. Yeah, Wi-Fi, low-fi girl is more like a follower radio channel.
Yeah. The only MTX in old-school RuneScape is Bond.
You can stream non-stop, but when you end the VOD, it will only save the foot 11.55.
Hmm. Well, I'll need to know that for the Donathons, because Azuras is first.
20! I'm finally fishing level 20. That took so long.
I can drop them. Okay, we're level 20. We're gonna do questing once I finish this batch that I've got.
And then we'll go to the bank and drop off all our items and see what this Quest
mini thing is all about. I don't know if I need any items for it, is it this?
It began with an M, so let's scroll down to M.
Let's scroll up to M.
Mystery, what do we need for that? We need, oh, we get a reward. What do we need for it?
Recommended items, none. Enemies to defeat, none. Okay, right. We'll definitely do this.
Nicely. Oh, she is right there. Okay, that makes perfect sense by that reefling. Suggested that
silly of me. If we're going to do some quests, we're going to the city, then we're going to the
city, then the door closes, won't close back. We're gonna put our items away first before we
continue with the questing. I actually have to go to, don't worry if you have to go,
thank you so much reeflings for hanging, I appreciate it. I am going to try and get level
99 in one month for cooking, so there will be plentiful opportunities to come hang.
I'm also going to do it during the week instead of on the weekend as well to give
the people who work on the weekends a chance as well to come in and join in the fun.
Okay, everyone who is fishing, if you want to cook the fish, we're going to take it to the bank,
if you want to cook it the new, and then we're going to make our way to the castle,
and then we're going to come back and, oh, my fire, my fire perished.
So get cooking, good looking. Oh wait, that's the song, hey, good looking. What you got cooking?
It's shrimp on a fire, shrimp on the barbie. Oh, we're so Aussie out here.
Can you go back to the mystery area after you finish? Oh wait, should we just do the quest?
Reeflings have done the quest, should we just do the quest now instead of going all the way back
and like here again? I finished my tea, yeah, you can't. Do they actually eat a lot of shrimp
in Aussie land? I don't know, just do the quest, okay, we'll do the quest.
I'll wait for everyone to finish up and do their thing, and then we'll start.
So let you guys cook, those who are fishing, you can un-fish and cook, and then we'll start
with this quest, and we'll pick another one. We'll do three quests I think, and I either need to do
stream split recording, yeah, for the donathons, I know you need to do back to back, so I'm actually
gonna have to get like a video put together for Azura to play when she goes to sleep.
Hopefully her PC doesn't explode midstream. Should be a way to sleep in the thing just
catch some fire in the corner of the room and she's like, okay.
We eat prawns. Are you squidding me right now? Who goes there Brian? Do you read Patreon messages?
No, so none of the talents have access to Patreon messages because it's like direct
messages, so they don't have access to that stuff? No. So no, I read Marshmallows though,
your mother won't come to send a moishie. I'm drinking water now after finishing my tea.
Okay, is everyone almost ready? I'm gonna drop three inventory space, I'll just drop
three anchovies, why not? Right, we will talk to this lady, I'll put walking on.
Let's see what happens. Help, help! Start the quest. Sure, are you guys ready to come over?
I'll get to 20 later. Yeah, we can always come back and do our thing.
Thank you for the tip though Anonymous. You really are shy, you could ask that for free,
you didn't have to give me money to ask that question. You guys are always welcome to ask and
chat, I know it can be never again, or you can ask in Marshmallow but I might be sold to respond
because I'm not reading Marshmallows right now. Thank you for the tip but save your money at the
same time, seriously. Ray, are we ready? Are you my refillings? You are. You're not quite ready,
hold on. Oh, sorry, right, I'm accepting the quest. What has happened here? We were invited to
house party on the island, not far from here, something felt wrong about the whole thing but
we went away. The house seemed pretty creepy but everything was going fine, we were having a good
time and that's when we got attacked and I tried to save her. Huey brought me enough time to find
an old boat, I went back to get him but it was too late, I'm scared he won't make it. You have to do
something, they can't get away with this. What do you want me to do? That cycle is still out there,
you have to bring them to justice. The boat we escaped on is just over there and you can use
it to get to the island. Okay, I'll see what I can do. I need to fight, I hope not. Can reflings see
this boat over here? Are you pointing the way? Let's check that you're all here. Who's got a
refling? Got a few. Okay, end of the boat, end of the boat. Benjens, how bold of you considering
she has a plan? Strania, I was wondering if you were following some kind of gay deciding to do,
nah I'm just going for it. We're literally doing quest and right now like I'm already getting distracted
from the 99 grind. Okay, I think that's all my reflings, these are
actual plots. Okay, into the boat we go, yippee! There's a chance you ask the question and
check, typically better chance, I don't know. I know but you can still do it for free, just
like keep, like if I miss it then ask it again in like a couple of minutes. Oh my god, there's so
many of us doing this quest right now, we're gonna overload this. It looks kind of familiar.
Oh, okay, we need to take a left refling, for those of you who don't have the plugin,
we're gonna pick up this bucket right here on the left. Oh no, is it instance bucket? Why are
we taking the bucket? Pick up from the bucket, is it an instance bucket? Oh no, we can all take it,
okay, that's good. Okay, drop. Okay, everyone get a bucket, pick up your bucket, subscribe by the
fountain. Oh my god, the beacons are lit, Gondor calls trade. Okay, and then we have the barrel
of rainwater, interact with it, we need to search it. Okay, there's like lots of noises going on.
Whoa, party on, bro. Oh, it's like that movie that I've not seen. Whoa, the wind totally just felt
like sun breathing on my neck. Oh, not cool, bro. I feel woozy, gurg, I see the light. It's not my
time, glurg, glurgle, gargle. Oh, that's a bit. I don't know what movie he's from, I've not seen it,
but I've seen it, you know what I mean? I've not seen the movie. Help me.
Man, you're taking a while to perish. Sid claps is on the ground in a crumpled mess,
as he falls down, you spot something shiny fall out of his shirt pocket and into the barrel of water.
Gosh, that was horrible and so drawn out. Oh, wow, he's still going.
I think he's actually gone this time. Who are you? Why are you doing this?
He didn't say anything. Scary movie. Oh, it's scream. I've got to find a way into that house and stop
this maniac. I wonder what it is that I saw fall into that barrel. Search the barrel,
reflings. The barrel's full of rainwater. I can't see what's in there. Oh, right, click on the barrel
in your inventory and use it on the barrel of rainwater. You fill the bucket from the barrel.
Okay, now what? Now we search the barrel. You find a key at the bottom of the barrel.
Are you saying strongly? Okay, now we go to the front of the house.
It's so scary. Oh, it's making a good noise.
Chop down. No, open large door. Okay, here we go. The bunny went ahead. I saw that bunny.
He closed the door behind you. Let us in the house. Right, there we go. Oh, the door all
closes. Hold on. I think the door all closed. Oh, does it all close? Wait, I can't even get in.
Is this open large door? No. I think we're all trying to get in at once, right? I'm not clicking
it. I'm just, okay, Danny. Okay, hold on. Hold on. Oh, all right, I'm getting there. We're getting
there. We're getting there. Hold on. Hold on. Why am I not going inside? It's not because someone's
doing the door thing. It's one at a time. Right, okay, that's fine. Okay, okay, I'm in. I'm in. I'm in.
Okay. Oh, that took the hot thing there. Right, let's get the other reflins in. Everyone in, everyone
in. Okay, a few more. A few more reflins, fewer stragglers. Can you come? Can you come?
One more, one more, and you come, and you come. Click that door. Right, we're in, we're in.
Everyone touch the table in the entrance way. Oh my goodness. There's a knife on the table.
Touch that table. Ooh, we're touching the table. Okay, once you've touched the table,
touch this door. Ooh, the door, the door. Oh, cut scene. Knock, knock. Who's there? Oh, no.
Gurgle. Oh, he said you're next to me.
Oh, he's using cheat see doodles. What's this? A note? I guess I should read it.
Ooh, let's go get the note. Oh, you left the note, okay. It should be a note to your left.
You take a copy of the note. Ooh, let's read it. Isn't murder just the work of art,
beautiful yet haunting like the blade of a knife as we wander through the valley of death?
Ooh, spooky. Oh, okay. Is this on the other side? Oh, okay. Everyone enter this room.
It doesn't really, really much of a room. Oh, it's a some room anyway. Oh, look at this painting.
Wait, why am I getting turned this way for the painting? Hello? Hello? Okay, examine painting.
Wait, what am I supposed to do? Oh, use the knife on the painting. I didn't
even know I had a knife on me. Use the knife in your inventory on the painting.
Beat that painting up. Show it to your mean boss. You slash open the painting revealing
a hidden storage compartment. Search painting. You find a key hidden inside the slash painting.
Oh, okay. If you found your key, come back out into the entrance way. If you've got the key
from the painting by cutting it up into the entrance way. Okay, just a few more.
Use the knife in your inventory on the painting in that room. And then once you've got the key,
come back into the hallway. We're doing it. We're questing. They have a higher pit than you.
Man, what's a pit?
Are we good?
There should be a knife in your inventory. And then you can highlight it by using right click
and then slash the shizzle of it. There you go, you key. Alrighty. And then we go through this door
right here. Oh, there's a reefing party in here, clearly. Oh, so it's spooking us behind the door.
Okay, once you enter this new room, there's a little orby thing to the left. I don't know
what it does, but it's highlighted. Examine the unlit candle on the wall. Oh, we're to tinder box
or to tinder box, the thing on the wall. Tinder box, the unlit candle.
Oh, wait, do you guys need a knife or a tinder box or is it like in this room?
Do you guys need me to trade this? There's a bunch in here. Okay, okay, that's good.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, literally all in the shelf. There's a tinder box on the shelf if you need help.
You light the candle. So light the two unlit candles. Oh, there's a third one as well.
Oh, excuse me, excuse me, Mr. Video Game. Oh, I just touched my fish. Hold on, wait.
I think she's more happy of the fact that there's only 20 people doing the same.
Literally, Jagex is like, what on earth? I'm sure they've had it before where people go
questing together. You light the candle. The room is sufficiently warm. The fuse
should now have dried out. Oh, once you tinder box all the things, do the barrel?
I don't know. And get the heck out of the room. Get out of the room as soon as you light that thing.
Hold on, let me run. Give me that room. Give me that room. Give me that room. Give me that room.
Oh, the thing about to blow. Oh, okay, okay, okay.
All right. Hey, it's the shadow one that kept closing the doors on me.
That's not a knife. This is a knife. Why are you so excited if I touch the doors and noodles?
I'm just like, it's so fun being like, oh my God, request them together. And for those
who don't have room light, I'm like, I'm the quest teller, you know? So once you've let everything
and blew it up, we can all go outside in this section. So I'll wait for the reeflings to come
over. Yeah, they're like having to get out the room because it's blowing up.
I just find it really fun getting to play games together. Momelo. So we're getting
the God Sword, right? I don't know what the God Sword is.
We are all here merely by coincidence. There's absolutely nothing in common that we all have.
Is there anyone else in sake? Are you kidding me right now?
Brian. It's 1am. I have to tap out. Sleep well. Enjoy the rest of your stream with the reeflings.
Thank you so much, Pajango. Please rest well. Maybe see you in the morning. I don't know if
this is endurance yet. Yes, there's four candles in that room to light on the walls. You take a
tinder box from the shelf, little tinder box on the shelf, and then you light all four candles in
the room. And then there'll be a powder keg that you can light here just on the outskirts of that room.
It will blow a hole in the wall, but you need to light it and then leave the room. So it blows up.
And then that's you.
Or that door. I mean, you're not wrong. I don't know if it blows up if you go out on that door,
but the other door. Or did it blow up? Boom. Okay, there you go. I blew up. I think that's
all the reeflings. I don't see anyone else hiding in that room. Can you come over? Yeah! Okay,
reeflings. Let's go next. Let's go next. We're doing it. Oh, if you click here on the foot,
on the mini map up here, it'll put running on. So if it's brown, it means you're walking. If it's
golden, it means you're running. Your stamina will regain eventually. So don't worry. Oh,
suspiciously. Let's observe this suspicious tree over here.
Please stop this. Just let me go. Oh, it's kind of messed up. We're going to play a game. Do you
like to play games? Yeah, no. Yes, whatever you say, just then it hurt me. Whether you get hurt
or not is entirely up to you. Your fate is in your own hands. What? What do you mean?
Leave her alone, you monster. Ah, Scottlefish. How kind of you to join us. Now, if you say another
word, I will end her right now. Sorry, where were we? Ah yes, of course, the game. Do you like
quests, Lissy? Uh, sure, I like quests. Do you like scary quests? Uh-huh. What's your favorite
scary quest? I don't know. You have to have a favorite. Uh, the one with a vampire in it who
lives in the big house. Good, good. And now for that game I spoke about. I am going to ask you
one question. Get it wrong and you die, but get it right and you live. How is that fair? Oh,
gothicks. Please, gothicks? Isn't that a type of armor? Oh, gothicks, please, no, please,
don't. I don't want to die. Then think hard about your answer. You like vampires, so this should
be easy for you. The question is, who is the vampire that resides in South Mish? I would be
perishing. Um, I'm to say nothing. I'm not, I'm not to say anything. He said he's gonna slash her
if I say anything. Oh yes, yes, I know it. Count Draenor. Ha, in your face, you masked freak.
Oh, Lacy, Lacy, Lacy, I did tell you to think hard about your answer. Count Draenor is in fact a
vampire and he does reside in his manor in Mithilith, but that manor is in West Mithilith. I was
talking about Count Chek. Thanks for playing. No, no, you tricked me. This isn't fair. Ask me another.
Gargle, gargle, gargle, gargle. The writing in this game is, I think it's because I have,
oh, he's leaving his notes? Okay, I'll take the note. Do you like jazz? Take the note, please.
That monster, oh, I can't do that because I actually only clicked on the note. Oopsies, take note.
You take the note, what does it say? It's like music to my ears, the glory sounds spelling out your
fate. Oh, okay, get into the, once you pick up the note, there's a piano. Where to do something with
it? Someone is throwing Easter eggs everywhere. Play piano. Okay, once you're on the piano,
delta, echo, alpha, delta. Did we do it right? Oh, there's a compartment. Can I play for real?
Oh, you can't. You can't play this one.
You can't play this one. You can't play this one. Oh, I think my inventory is full, hold on.
I think there's something I'm supposed to grab.
Play piano, search piano, search piano. Oh, once you play that, delta is just, I don't see a delta
button. Oh, very funny, very funny. Oh, it spells out dead. Do you like metal? Does baby metal
count as metal? I like OST from Doom. Doom? Yeah, Doom 2007, BFG is probably my favorite,
if that counts as metal song. Has everyone got the key? If you got the key, come up the hallway a
little bit. Oh wait, we're, oh no, we're supposed to go back. Okay, if you've got the key, come out
of the room. Let's see if there's any, who's not got the key? Got the key, got the key.
Someone's, I don't know if someone's in that cutscene with the guy.
Spelled dead on the piano from the left side. Is that Hatsune Miku? It's Hatsune Miku. Hello guys,
my name is Hatsune Miku. I'm thinking Miku, Miku. There's a refling here, but I don't know if
they're in a cutscene or not, I'm not sure. I don't know what's happening with this refling,
I think they might be AFK, but everyone, oh, I don't know. Miku, you're, Miku, you're mine.
I think so. Okay, I think so, you're hanging out with us. I don't know, oh, oh, did you get the key?
Do you need to do the piano bit? I don't know. Oh right, spell dead on the piano and then search
the piano. And left side spell dead, if that makes sense.
Damn, there's no cheer remote. There is in game. Wait, where is it? Cheer, cheer. Okay,
that's the best I got. Sorry, I was AFK, I'll catch up. Yeah, just spell, yeah, yeah, there you go,
you got it, you got the key. If you touch the piano and then on left spell side and then you
should get key. I think everyone's got the key. Yippee, everyone's got the key, right, let's go.
Come back inside the house from the side, we blew it up on the powder keg.
Oh, it's a room full of reflings. Oh no, just me in a room full of reflings.
Okay, come back into the entrance hallway. Oh, we're getting stuck on the door.
Hold on, hold on, hold on. Oh, right, hold on. You again! It's him, it's him that's doing it.
It's him that's doing it, I'm getting freaking stuck. Wait, how'd that come around?
I literally can't progress. Stop it, I can't even get through. Or is it one by one? Oh,
maybe a one by one, hold on. I might be accusing someone of closing the door and I think it's one
by one. Oh, right, oh, sorry, sorry, I just, I'm sorry, refling. Miss input, miss input!
Oh, it's a miss input, okay. Shawnee letting her imagination run wild. Honestly, honestly?
Okay, so one by one door, take your time, take your time, it's one by one door.
Right, here we come. Stop, refling! Let us come in.
Everyone's got a better ping than me! Okay, I'm in, I'm in, I'm in.
Okay, then through the other one by one door. Oh, it's a cutscene. Accusing her own
beloved loyal refling. Why am I the only one always left cleaning up after everyone?
Shuffle? Hello, anyone there? Russell? Hello, Lacey said. Scratch.
Hmm, well I guess I should go check it out. No point saying in this nice locked room when I could
go outside into the creepy darkness. Seriously? The walls and doors seem too thick for Mandy to
be able to hear you. Oh, and I don't think there is any need to take this big shiny
weapon with me in order to defend myself. Nothing bad ever happens when people go check out noises
in the dark outside the house. You have gotta be kidding. Okay, well here I go.
Bando Scotsword. Hello, anyone out here?
See, I knew nothing would happen. Must have just been a squirrel or something running about.
Oh well, back to the dishes. Phew, that was lucky.
Oh, he's behind you!
No, why me? That psycho. He was just toying with her.
Oh, we're getting left another note, I think. Is this talk to killer? Just look at what we can.
We're in a cutscene. And he's hiding away again. Another note, this guy really likes playing games,
but this is going to be the game he won't win. Okay, there should be a note on the ground for us
to read now. Here, at first, these words. Each murder you witness helplessly from start to end
as you fail to solve the final letters of this quiz. Razor sharp like a gemstone is the blade of my
knife. The last sound you hear will be your screams echo. Hita, I will have the final word
in this thriller. Okay, we need to go back into the hallway on the one-by-one door, so we need to be patient.
I'm standing and lying. I was looking in soft lock by a door. Okay, there we go, I made it through.
Wait, what was that? Oh, that makes sense. Is there a refland just out there chilling?
Are you not doing the quiz? Are you just bing-chilling out there? Bing-chilling.
Are you not sure what to do?
Okay, and then one-by-one, we painfully go through this door again.
Now we're getting waving hello, hello. Okay, we need to check out the fireplace. Okay, or also known as the heart.
Oh wait, this is chopped on tree. Examine the fireplace with a knife. Use the knife on the fireplace.
You use the knife to pry open a loose brick in the fireplace, revealing a secret panel
Search fireplace. You find a panel of switches inside the hidden compartment.
Each switch is crafted from a different gemstone.
Click sapphire. Click diamonds. Click zanyate. Click emerald. Click on it. Then click ruby.
Blue, white, orange, green, black, red.
You hear a click sound. You find a hidden key. Okay, that one's a bit more.
SD, Z, E, autumn. How are you supposed to figure that out? I love riddles in this game.
Must have been the wind. Would you be upset if it was ink you were cleaning instead?
Oh man, I can't believe this. I can't find my old character anymore.
I wanted to bring in a high-level character to help out. I don't worry. Also, there's a boss fight now.
I don't have any combat. The final letters of the note.
Oh, I have the final word in this form.
Okay, okay, that's actually wee bit smart. I'll give it a wee bit smart.
Just a wee bit. One by one door. One by one door.
One by one door. One by one. Cheeky one by one. Oh wait, is everyone done with the hearth?
God, you guys were so quick at the hearth.
Okay, Cheeky. Cheeky one by one door. That's it. Let me in.
Stop! You don't even need to come in this room. You've already done the quest.
Bruv, I don't have high enough ping. I can't get out. I actually don't have high enough ping
to get out. I'm not even being funny. My ping is so bad. I can't get out. Bruv.
I don't know what to do. My ping isn't fast enough to respond.
The background keeps reminding me of the godfather. I've never seen the godfather. Is it gay?
Fail to solve the final letters of this quiz. Fail to solve the- Ah, okay, okay. Oh, okay, it works.
Okay. Alright, in you go.
Right, once we're back in the engine's way, we one by one on the door over here.
We're spinning on the door.
Let's refling. Here we go. And then we go. Boom.
We got a cutscene. I wonder if there's a way to make the text bigger.
Show yourself, you coward.
Monkey. Monkey, is someone gonna get stuff?
So, we meet at last. I have to say, I'm impressed you worked out my riddles. Well,
maybe you aren't as smart as you think you are. Or really, all the dead bodies suggest otherwise.
And what did you do to stop them? Nothing. People think you are some big hero, but no,
you're not. All your adventures are the same. Nothing but opportunists. What are you on about?
Well, I did have this big speech planned out, but quite frankly,
I don't think you're worth the effort it would take to deliver it.
So, this is the end of the line for you. It is time for the final act.
The showdown. The finale. Let's see if you're up for the challenge.
Probably not. I'm too- Ah, if I die, do I lose all the money that's on my hand? Push mirror.
The mirror can't be pushed any further. What are you on about?
Oh no, I missed. Wait, is there like a timer?
Hello? Oh. Logic puzzle? Wait, do I need to like-
Do it all the time? Wait, hold on. Push. And then push. And then push from here.
Boom. Oh, what? He changed. I don't know which one he's coming from.
Did I just have to guess?
Oh, for goodness- Wait, I can't see when it's coming.
Is it that one? I think I'm too. Like, can you just randomize to this one where I've already
said it all? Please, that'd be great game. Wait, I'm supposed to run about that fast?
I don't think I'm that fast. I'm fricking too late.
And- Oh, right. Okay, there's like a weird shadow thing, but I don't know if I'm that fast.
Seriously. I'm not that fast! Oh.
Bruv. Did I just need to camp at one? He's too fast! Oh my god, he's like so fast!
Hold on. Oh, please be it. Oh no!
Oh, right, okay. Wait, I don't even know where it's coming from. Oh, right, okay. Shadow, shadow.
Okay, he's doing it again from that one. Okay, okay. Quick, quick, quick!
Is it- Oh, shit, I'm too- Please be this one. No!
The randomizer is so cruel. You know for a fact you can randomize elsewhere.
Okay, another one, another one. Oh, dang right out. All right, okay, okay, okay,
we can do this, we can do this. One, two, and three. Oh, just in time. Oh, we did it.
I flopped out. Oh, I think I may have underestimated you.
You lost at your own game and now it is time to see who you really are under that mask.
Wait, no, you, but why? Why on earth would you kill all your pals? Why beg me to come here and help
them? You just don't get it, do you? So big-headed, so used to it all being about you, about saving the
day. Well, I'm sick of it. What do you even mean? Adventurers, you're all the same. Everything
always has to be about you. I don't understand. Of course you wouldn't, because you can't see
past yourself. Believe it or not, I used to be like- Okay, at least to be like you, I hear about
some dance alone distress and go to help. Have my moment for me to be the hero for once. But you,
you and every other adventurer, every time I get there to help is too late.
It's already solved. The disaster is averted. Reward has already been claimed. Every time you
and those adventurers steal my moment, but not this time. This time, it's all about me. I'm the
star of the show. Me, me, me, me, me. Well, not any longer. The show's over and there will be no
curtain call. Oh, but there's always a curtain call. He he he he.
What? How? There was two?
Of course. Every good show needs a good support and actor. Now take off your mask, darling. Take
a bow. You've earned it. Of course, my love. It's Sid! No, it's not. It's Harvey. I'm sorry.
You, but how? You were almost heckin' gone. I saw your wounds.
No, what you watched was what I wanted you to watch. A masterful performance, if I say so myself.
But what's in it for you? Everyone loves the limelight and who better to share it with
them, my beloved Abigail. But your friends? They didn't deserve to perish.
Perhaps not, but neither did I deserve to be cast back into the shadows where I deserve the
spotlight. Yes, well, we deserve the spotlight. And now I have my starring role, our starring role.
Gelinor will forever remember this night and what I've done here.
No, what we have done. Quiet Huey, this is my moment. No, this is supposed to be our moment.
It isn't just all about you either. We're in this together.
Stop ruining this, Huey. I have worked so hard for this and I'm not gonna let you take it away from
me. Well, I'm not gonna be push aside either. We were both in on this as equals. We were never
equals. How could you possibly compare to me? You're egotistical, selfish. No, my love.
No, what have I done? It wasn't supposed to be like this, but you just couldn't let me have my
moment. Why, Huey, why? I loved you. This could be my chance to take advantage of the situation.
Okay, pick up the knife. I'm not going out of her empty-handed. Yeah, pick up, take the killer's knife.
Yonk and I'm not go- wait, equip the knife, pick up the knife and equip it and then stab her.
Take that, hack and slash. Well, thanks Sarah Domen. That's over. I should get out of here.
Just like that. Are they still alive? I don't think he's in a very talkative mood. Are they both?
Okay. Okay, let's get out of here. Let's get out. Let's get out.
The crying says, you'll never escape me.
You dare try and ruin- wait, what? NPC spot? Isn't she supposed to be parish? Try and ruin my moment.
Oh, wait, no. Huey is hurt because of you. It's definitely to you. Oh, wait. Now it's time for
you to join. Oh, you're not killing anyone else. Oh, again, absolutely. She's spanked by the-
No, this can't be. She just got specked. Whoa, that was close.
Mandy, how are you alive? I watched you get shanked. I did get stabbed, but I was born with a rare
condition called Dextrocardia. Dextrocardia what? Dextrocardia. It means that my heart is on the
right side of my chest, not my left. Oh, that's so specific. So when the killers thought they stabbed
you in the heart, they actually missed? Well, missed the heart, yeah. I did still get stabbed,
though. I'm actually feeling pretty woozy. Oh, yeah, right. Yeah. I will wait outside the house
after seeing to this stab wound. You should come talk to me there. Okay, okay, okay.
Hey, right, outside the house if my- Oh, no, are you guys stuck on the mirror section?
Are they stuck on the mirror section if they're still in here? Or are they just in the cutscene?
Someone throw in their snowball. I'm starting to think you aren't throwing snowballs anymore.
No witnesses, the roofling's never taught. My medieval fantasy game with medieval-
Oh, my medieval fantasy game with medical term. There's still one more roofling stuck in there.
Are you stuck on the mirror quest, beyond it? I'm on team finish faster than throwing it. I need to
read it out. I don't think these are snowballs I'm getting covered in or something. Should I have
fought Abigail? You pick up a knife. Oh, did you just leave? You might have to go back inside
and redo that mirror section sadly. Whoa, wait, it's okay.
I mean, did you shank her? All right. Oh, the roofling's out. Is that everyone?
All the candles floor, all aboard. Oh, we're talking about humors and bail there.
Okay, that's all the rooflings. Everyone into the entrance way.
Turns out you can't fight her. Nah, you don't actually hurt Abigail yourself.
Right, and then we talk. Oh, no, it's one by one door. Oh, it's our biggest enemy. It's
literally our biggest enemy right now, one by one door. The game's like sending me away.
Right, I'll wait for the rooflings to go first. I'll let the rooflings go because they've been
playing with me without having a go time. No witnesses, the rooflings will never talk.
Fair and square. The actual end boss of the game. I don't think there's snowballs either,
but they may contain some terms in common. All done. Okay, we need to talk to the
Mandy right here. Oh, hi, Scottlefish. Hi, Mandy. How are you feeling now? Much better.
Thanks and lucky to be alive. Thanks to you. No small part. Well, we saved the day in the
team, so thank you too. Here, I found this in the wardrobe. I don't want to take it,
so please take it. We did it! We got another quest for level eight crafting and we got rubies for
it. I like that. Well, I think we're ready to go back. Is everyone ready once you've collected
your mission? The question is, what quest do we do now? We'll do the free quests.
I'm level nine crafting. I went, oh yeah, you're just rubbing in my face.
Looks like everyone's spoken to Mandy, almost. A few more wheat funds.
Someone's really enjoying just talking to all the wood. Is that everyone? I'm just trying to check.
Are you coming too? No? Yeah, no, maybe. Right, all aboard the boat.
Who do I talk to to finish the quest? Mandy, she's outside that castle.
Yeah, we did it! We did it! Wait, wait, let me do a celebration of moat. Can I jump in the air?
We completed the quest!
Okay, I think we should go to the bank
and put all our items away and then we'll pick what quest to do next. What's a free quest?
That's easy. Goblin Diplomacy is pretty easy.
Erin is the chicken. I think you need to have combat. I think you need combat for Erin.
Sleep well, good night, those who have to go.
Good night, Trony. We'll see you there, Bessa. Until later, I don't know if there's anything easy.
Erin is the chicken. It's probably the easiest we've got right now.
I think we need to level up, so that's not only why we need to level up.
Just a runaway segment.
All kind. It's all the refunds here.
Yeah, I've got some stuff to do. Try not to get food.
For those who have to go, don't worry if you have to go. Understand, it's not possible.
We'll do Erin is the chicken and then we're going to go back to fishing.
Sorry, we're going to go back to leveling up cooking.
Okay, is everyone here? I think everyone's here.
I don't know if that other refling is still stuck on the island.
Possibly. That went crazy. Didn't we just see him back on this island?
Wait, there is a refling that got stuck on that quest? I think.
It's called scrawny sea.
Oh no, that was a good thing. Okay, see you later. Bye bye refling.
Thank you for joining for the ones who have to leave. Don't worry if you have to leave in game.
Right, if you want to follow me, if you hover on me, it should say follow.
And then I'll take you to the bank and then we'll do Erin is the chicken.
I don't know what is, but we'll do it anyway.
Oh, I'll walk. Sorry, I'll walk. I always forget to walk.
We've got a refling army, honestly.
See you later alligator in a wild crocodile.
Yeah, I want to, I want to go to the island.
Why would you let me go? Did you guys see that Stephen Hawking meme?
That sounds really terrible, but that's what the meme was.
So when it came out that Stephen Hawking went on the island,
someone like did a quote and it was like, I want to go to the island.
Why won't you let me go?
Oh, I just love the brave word.
I know the stream isn't over yet, but when do you think the next runescape won?
Probably in a week's time.
My endurance stream is Skyrim for next week,
but I am going to try and get 99th cooking.
Where am I trying to go?
I don't know why I need the map to go to the bank and all the bankers.
My next, I'm going to try and finish 99 cooking.
In one month, I want to finish 99 cooking.
Bobby Lee or whatever.
Yeah, yeah, that was it.
No, it's just going to be vanilla Skyrim for my endurance stream next week.
Endurance stream next week is Skyrim and Runescape.
I don't think today we're going to do the full 12 hours
because I've actually done quite a lot of 12 hours.
Go upstairs on the top of the bank.
How are you everywhere?
Am I going crazy or is this a bot?
Or is this a leafling that like is just no,
like how are you leveling up outside here?
What we didn't even get here.
I'm going crazy.
I swear that's a leafling.
Right.
Empty everything inside.
I guess you can just drop the notes from that minigame.
And then Erin is the chicken.
I'm actually going to equip my sword and shield.
I'm pretty sure I got unequipped for some reason
and I don't want to be completely defenseless.
I'm not out there.
I think we just draw destroy you, I guess.
Wait, am I not allowed to destroy the notes?
They'll just put them in the bank then.
Okay, I'm just putting the notes in the bank.
I don't know why.
No, that's me.
All right.
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
I can just what I was like,
I'm sure that's a leafling genuinely.
Anyone want my three gems since I can't bank them?
Oh, me, me, me, me, me, me.
Send them to Mommy who said that.
Me, me, me, me, me, head a...
Ah, I can't trade you.
What?
Oh, I've only traded you?
Oh, well, at least you can send it to me at least.
Yeah, I dunno why I wouldn't want me to do that.
Me, me, me, me, me.
Oh, my god, my, my, my, my, no.
We should fight the level 152 chicken at the gate, ill.
Is that true?
Is that real?
I don't mean to alarm you,
but NaNNa and Cookin make take...
Someone said it can take 30 hours if we max it.
I can't trade for another 52 minutes, that's okay.
Err, right, erm, Ern is the chicken, we're gonna do Big Ernie the checkin' buck buck
er, show on the map.
We need to go, oooh, outside this location here.
I don't know, do we level up?
I feel like we need to do a bit of combat.
Well we go kill cows for like, I'm not even kidding, we'll go, er, kill cows for like,
five minutes.
So we're gonna go across the bridge and get cows.
Reeflings, come down to the castle, I'll wait for you at the front of the castle.
Make sure you have a sword and a shield equipped, did you got it from Tutorial Island.
A hundred hours are five strong streams of frogs in the lake!
Honestly.
Yeah, we go, right, we will just go outside the castello, er, and I'll make sure everyone,
I don't see anyone coming down the stairs from there, I think there's no one.
Everyone's on, you guys are quick, I don't think there's anyone, I don't see anyone.
Okay, we're gonna cross the bridge, five streams must be short ones, honestly, er, just five
streams.
Ugh.
Give me one second, I'm getting...
I'm not gonna do this.
Nine streams, one minute is like absolutely all of this.
I'm getting...
I'm getting a freaking seal, what?
I'm getting a big difference.
Ugh.
Okay, I can breathe again.
Right, we're gonna go into the cow's pen, and we're literally gonna go nuts in destroying
all these cows up ahead.
Okay, just so some people get nine in cooking by at skill 33 with 6,000 grapes and turning
them into wine.
Is that the fastest ice pee maker?
I thought it was sharks, but sharks are expensive.
Me.
Oh, someone wants to trade, sorry, sorry, I didn't see the offer.
What do you offer me?
Poison?
Are you telling me killing them?
Oh my God, what did you do?
Poison and fish food.
Reefland!
That's so mean!
I got given poison and freaking fish food.
Tell me, tell me you don't like me, without telling me you don't like me, Reefland.
Sheesh.
Right, let's absolutely destroy these cows.
Even if you just get a few, like to level up, I guess.
Even a tiny bit of a level up is better than nothing.
Something about not being able to burn wine?
Wine making's the fastest.
Okay.
Based Reefland, someone said.
Okay, just get the cows, just attack the cows at all willy nilly.
And then we can level up our combat a bit, because our combat is so low that we're like
really vulnerable to pretty much anything.
Destroy that Reefland.
Mods, slap them silly.
Mods, remove this man's chest.
Just cult things.
Why you following this noob?
Okay, I love that answer.
Is there more cows over here?
Oh, there is!
There's like tons of cows.
Okay, and don't worry, you can attack everything in this field.
We'll just level up.
Oh, he said enjoy.
We will hunt them down.
Mods, put chewed up gum in this, in his best shoes.
Mods, make sure his pillow is always warm.
Yeah.
See, we're like literally already covered.
We're getting so strong.
We're just beating absolutely everything up.
Why did, actually, how did they know I'm a noob?
Is that the way I dress?
I'm literally wearing a thousand gold dreads, and they called me a noob.
Not to brag, but my combat level is five right now.
Like, I'm sorry, but runescape players quake when they see me.
I'm sorry, they just quake when they see me.
They can't help it.
Their timbers are shivered.
Whenever they see skullfish log in online.
Oh, I've only got four health.
I should maybe be a bit more careful, honestly.
Oh, I've only got three health.
Maybe I should be really careful.
Hmm, I'm not sure I can maybe fight the baby cows.
If I get beaten up by a cow, I'm going to be really embarrassed, okay?
Oh my god, a baby cow, destroy it.
Combat level five, literally.
We quiver before you as well, but for different reasons.
Oh my god, the way that we think rolls over as well is so sad.
I'm planting some booms.
All right.
I can only attack baby cows, because I've only got three HP.
I swear, if any reefling perishes against cows, I'm going to be embarrassed for result, okay?
Oh, sorry, someone said they wished to trade.
Sorry, sorry.
Let me beat up this baby cow, and then I'll accept the trade.
Wah, wah, wah.
Oh my god, I'm on one HP.
No way this baby cow is going to get me.
Mauds, are you...
I'm going to get killed by a baby cow.
I need to get out of the field, oh my god.
I'm one HP in a dream.
Hold on, right, let's try that again.
Okay, I literally am the one that's going to perish from the cow.
Hold on, let me accept this trade.
I'm so sorry.
Chin up, offer?
Oh no, can you not trade?
That's okay if you can't do it in time.
Uh, I guess we'll just hang about here, yeah?
We're just going to hang about...
Oh, they're cooking meat.
Cannot trade, yeah, I'm a new account.
It's because I'm not cleaning up.
Do you have meat?
Excuse me, little reefling.
Uh, can I get some of your meat?
Please, one bit of meat so I can heal.
Just one meat.
Oh, you not got any?
I saw you cooking though.
I do not have any.
Oh wait, I can make some if I pick up some off the ground.
Wait a minute, hold on a minute, I can do it my...
I'm an independent strummer.
Use the meat on the fire and then eat the meat.
It's genius.
I did it!
Okay, we can go back to slay and let's go.
We'll get a few more combat levels like this.
Chicken's going to only hit zero, so that's good for you, accounts.
No, we need a challenge for the coup.
Uh, we're now attack level four.
Oh my god, we're getting too strong.
We can't handle this.
When we enter the lobby...
I'm going to actually cook again because I want to heal up.
GGG.
I'm gaming so hard right now.
Oh no, I burnt it!
I thought we were high enough level not to burn level one me, honestly.
I don't know what combat level we are.
We're combat level five.
Surely that's enough for questing.
Surely.
Copium.
Let me know wild strong, you can survive in nature.
It's rough out in nature, it's rough.
I just need to heal and then I can start walloping everything again.
There, boom.
Uh, let me keep the attack or is it better to like swap between like the same thing, so...
Cows can burn.
It's genius!
Shit over here.
Why do the farmers randomly let you perish their cows?
Honestly, I'm not even sure.
Wait, I think it might be faster to do like strength and then I might get like a combat level faster.
I'm not sure if that's right though.
I could be completely wrong about that.
Wait, there's like more cows over here, we can use annihilate.
Yeah, there's like tons over here.
Best to train strength.
Alright, maybe defense because like I've not got much HP points.
Like I only got 10.
Oh sorry, someone wishes to trade with me.
Drop some meat over here if you want to strong any things I can't trade.
The reeflings feeding me.
Oh, they're feeding me.
Thank you reeflings.
That's a lot of meat.
Jeez, you're a packin.
Is that six whole meat for me?
It is, thank you.
Am I baiting to it?
Oh wait, I'm already full health.
Wait, I only have 9 HP?
No, I have 10 HP, that's like tiny.
Azura remainder.
Azura duly is going live.
I'm unsure what game she's playing.
Oh my god, check out the outfit.
Check out the drip.
Let's say drip out in the color scheme.
We're getting there, we're getting there.
Surely.
Oh my god, do you know what that reminds me of?
I think the reason why I laugh so much at that
is because of this.
Right, hear me out.
Hear me out.
Where is it?
Let me find it.
I think that's why that makes me laugh so much.
Because it looks so good.
Oh my god.
Let me find it.
I think that's why
that makes me laugh so much.
Because it looks so ridiculous.
That's the only reason I like the headbanging
the most.
This is absolutely ridiculous.
Wow.
I don't know.
Is level 6 combat enough to not get attacked
all the time?
Sorry, I look sussy.
Sorry, I said that wrong.
I don't mean to say it like that.
Oh, I'm level 2 strength.
Check me out.
Oh sorry, someone wants to trade with me.
I'm sorry, I missed it.
I'm too fatigued.
I'm too enthralled
with perishing these cows to get some level ups.
Very beefy.
I'm sorry.
Look, I've got things on my mind, you know.
Are the marshmallows up again recently?
Oh yeah.
Hee hee hee.
Okay.
Accept trade.
What? Show me what you got.
Oh, it's a strength potion
and cooked salmon.
Okay.
I don't know how long.
I only wanted to be here for like a wee bit
and then we'll go straight back in
to leveling up cooking.
I accidentally save questing a little too much.
What I wanted to do was get some levels.
So when we do airness to chicken,
we don't all perish.
I think we can run away
for whatever is going on.
Oh yeah, you know all right.
Hee hee hee hee.
I just didn't want us to perish
really quickly when we did airness to chicken.
I don't know what Azur is live with.
Thank you very much, Refling,
for all the food supplies as well.
Um.
Almost like up my strength.
Level up, level up.
Ooh.
Combat level six, unstoppable.
Truly unstoppable.
They cannot, they cannot.
Strength potion for stronger.
Ah.
Okay, I took a sip.
I don't know how long it lasts.
Wait, where's the effect?
I don't know how long these things,
the pots last.
Ooh.
I've cast up this much of a fate.
I fear what bulls are capable of.
She can now destroy baby cows with ease.
I truly am evil.
Truly.
I don't know how long it lasts.
Strength potion, yeah.
Top left the fist.
So the strength boosts.
60 seconds?
No, it does not last.
It lasts 60 seconds.
It's so small when you heal.
Oh, salmon heals a lot, actually.
We need to start like a salmon ring.
Is it normal to heal multiple,
strong voices simultaneously in my head?
I hope not. If I left the echo on.
One boosted start point,
dreams every 30 seconds.
That's so quick.
Ooh.
I'm no strength level four.
I'm rolling these cows.
There's no echo.
Okay.
It's just a reef flings finally losing the plot.
I now can have a live in HP.
Okay, maybe we should have done
a bit of training a wee bit earlier.
But look, we're leveling up.
That's the main thing.
We're getting there.
I don't know if we should maybe go for like
five.
Hmm.
I'm thinking he's becoming an extra strongy pill.
So it depends on how strong your potion has boosted you.
Azure is playing one shot.
Like how strong he sounds excited
every time she unlocks levels.
It's so satisfying.
It's like, you've unlocked a new level,
but yeah, I have.
I'm such a big girl.
I'm so smart.
It's MRT.
Hmm.
Hydration check.
I think the echo effect,
if I was playing a video game,
doesn't sound that good.
Like, this is, for example,
what would sound like,
oh, I'm just killing this dude right now.
It just sounds mental.
It sounds like you've lost the plot.
You've actually lost the plot.
It's not sounding good, you know?
There.
That should be it back to me.
I think I got unsubtremised
channel. It's very plausible.
I think it should be in
my description.
Right, we'll do
five defense.
We're almost level seven combat.
Let's go.
Oh my god, Serenity!
How are you doing? How was your stream?
Even though you'll probably be exhausted
and the last thing you want to do
is get a ton of heck in comments
and be like, I'm not making a stream.
I don't know.
How, hopefully it was good though
and you had fun. Hi Raiders!
I'm Strony Cuttles from Veiler
and I'm currently doing
my stream snipe game of the day,
of the week, sorry.
We're playing old-school Rinscape.
We're in World 3a, which is free to play
and we're just leveling up our accounts a little bit
because we are super weak
and I'm scared to
send us quests, because someone might fall down.
What level is your attack?
My attack is four.
Strength is five and defense is one.
I'm currently doing defense right now.
Just to try and get
overall combat level.
Speedy Bun Raid.
I never saw Rinscape before.
Oh, it's basically
an incremental game
and you just click.
Literally, this is the graphics.
I'm not even kidding, check me out.
I've got a gold plated chef's hat on.
Gold apron on.
You've not seen anything bear.
Just amazing.
It's a sweetie bun raid.
Bun bun raid.
Help, I've fallen.
I'm literally dropped out.
Why did I get a message?
I'll be logged in in 30 minutes.
But yeah, we're just leveling up
because
we want to do some questions.
That's weird.
I always saw the YouTube make up
that's not the default graphics.
Oh, at least even worse
than this.
Oh, it's been six hours
already. I didn't realize either.
Sorry for stealing all your time, guys.
Time flies when you're having fun.
Time flies.
This is peak graphics.
You do not get better than this.
The year is 2024.
Let's admire
the daisies right here.
Let's zoom in a little.
Look at these, man.
Beautiful.
You can see every poly...
What's that, a poly thing?
Every triangle.
Oh.
All the triangles are made out.
Oh, I've reached
a total level of 100.
Ooh, our accounts are getting bear.
We've
started on fresh accounts.
So, all that got censored.
It did.
Hold on, let me eat a salmon.
Well, we're at combat level 7.
Oh, we are getting potent.
Okay.
Polygon, that's what I meant.
Yeah, polygon.
But if anyone looks as funny,
I'm gonna get them.
Level 7, go and get them.
They can't handle.
They can't handle it.
Laracraft,
honestly.
Okay, think
we're getting there, we're getting there.
Maybe we do 5 on each.
Eat combat means
we can survive a little bit of a hit.
A little bit of a punch, if you will.
Triangle.
Oh, that should have been...
Is there a other name?
Yeah, we tricked everything.
Wow.
And then wherever Ernie's chicken starts,
I'm actually unsure.
Wow, level 4.
Did I put my combat?
We're at 7.6 for combat.
I like how it shows you the increment as well.
To be like, you're getting closer.
I'm pretty sure prayer counts
to your overall combat level as well.
So, I hit Fondle of Triangles.
So, I don't know if we should do some...
I've never done...
Is it the altar?
Dragon bone altar run, but they're so expensive.
And I would need personal guards
all the way over.
See, that's the fastest way
to level up prayer, I believe.
But yeah.
Watching Stronny and Emile and Spirits
playing a game on my own almost feels like
I have a friend.
Isn't there no sensory overload doing that?
I feel like
I'd be like, I couldn't handle it.
I feel like there's too much going on.
Is Emi enjoying her game so far?
I already need a P again.
I feel like whenever I have a T,
she's loving it, oh, I'm glad.
That's what I like to hear.
See, I knew a picture.
Oh, I'm level 4 health.
Sorry, 4 HP.
I think
there's everyone at least level...
So we've got level 6 refling.
Yeah, that's good.
Okay, apparently we get
level 5 in attack.
We're getting leveled up.
We've got level 10 refling over there.
I can't tell.
We've got level 6 as well.
Yeah, we're getting a bit better.
Getting a bit better.
We're definitely not to be tripled with
even though we're not level 10 combat yet.
But we're not to be missed with.
How do you pee so much yet so little?
I know that caffeine makes you want to wee-wee all the time.
So I think it might be because I'm having
so much T's from my throat.
Yay!
We're like doing little mini tasks as well.
Someone wants to trade.
You wish to trade. I accept your trade.
What do you wish to trade me?
Oh, I don't know if I can wear this, actually.
I don't know if it's too...
strong.
Like, I can't wear it yet.
I trade absolutely nothing.
Oh no, I took my apron off.
Oh my god, I have to pick between drip or function.
I think I have to pick between drip.
I'm so sorry.
Do you want your steel plate body back?
Sorry, the drip is for life.
For real, for real. The drip is for life.
I mean, check this out.
I mean, check it out.
It's so good. Okay, sure.
You want to trade with me?
I swear if it's more poison.
What is this? Crossbow?
Oh!
Whoa!
Wait, a pink skirt? Are you dressing me up?
I can't believe reeflings are dressing me up.
First cosplay stream confirmed.
Oh, look at the long drip.
I said Tee-hee.
I said Tee-hee, you're not getting Tee.
I put little crossbow ball tips on.
Whoa!
Okay, okay.
Wait, I think the skamar is better.
What is it called?
A steel skamar.
Okay.
I've got skamar.
I'm not afraid to use it.
Even in the game,
she has a dumpy, honestly.
The pencil dress.
Yeah, I mean, look at that.
Wow, look at them polygons.
Oh yeah, it's all coming together.
Great.
We will start airing as the chicken, I think.
Oh, there's an imp.
If I pick up a bead, I'm pretty sure.
Beat that imp up.
Or I'll beat it up.
Don't worry, I'll get it.
I don't want, I don't want because the cave's in the way.
Okay, now we beat the imp up.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, beat him up.
If he drops a colored bead,
we can use it for the wizard quest.
I just realized I never killed it,
so I can't tell.
We'll never know what it dropped.
Oh wait, did it drop something?
Oh, it did!
Okay, we need it for the wizard tower quest,
but completely forgotten,
you need like four different components.
What are the consequences of death in this game?
I think you keep your three highest
priced items or something like that.
Right,
the three reflings are,
I'm going to stand at the gate,
and I'll wait for everyone to come over.
So if you want to stand outside the gate of the cow pen,
we will go do Ernest the chicken next,
and then we'll actually do some
cooking again,
because we're going to need a,
if we're wanting to wrap it up in a month,
I'm definitely going to need to stop getting so distracted.
We'll do some cooking.
Oh, the refling's out the pen.
And then I'll walk again.
Right, where the heck is Ernest the chicken?
Uh,
Starting off.
Four quest points.
Oh, that's the rewards.
Able to survive a skeleton level 22 attacking you.
Surely we're leveled up enough.
Surely.
Talk to Veronica outside of Draynor Manor.
Blah, where is it?
On the map.
Draynor Manor.
Draynor Village.
Oh, it was like outside that creepy place.
Yeah, here.
Okay, okay.
So how do we progress?
We go across the bridge,
and we go up,
and then we just keep going along,
and then we can go up again past the window.
Okay.
I shall take a breath and break.
Don't get me.
Oh, no.
Wait.
Okay.
If you want to follow me,
if you want to follow me refling,
is there anyone who's left behind?
You're not.
I don't recognize you as a refling.
There's a refling getting beaten up by a cow right now.
But reflings come outside the pen,
and you can follow me with a golden heart.
I crafted the schemata and shielded myself.
Heck yeah.
Not all the reflings like watching this one refling be up a cow.
I'm trying.
Don't actually worry if I get stuck.
I'll catch up.
Who is this Shirley you keep talking about?
It's me seeing Shirley.
Okay, there.
Refling.
Is there any other refling?
I don't know.
Render distance isn't helping.
I think that's just natural.
Okay, let's...
If you want to follow me,
I have the golden heart.
I'm going to be very careful with my pathing.
Maybe you can follow me.
Choo choo all aboard.
I made it to level four.
Wish me luck.
We're getting there.
We'll definitely maybe do a bit of combat training.
But yeah.
All aboard.
I'll just kind of click one by one
to make sure we don't get any actually stuck on something.
How many reflings do we have in game?
I don't actually know how many.
We've had a few went offline
because we have hit the six hour mark.
But we do have a good amount of reflings all hanging out.
We are going to do cooking though.
I need to cook.
Jesse.
We need to cook.
Refling.
Okay, I'm following the bunny.
Honestly, I should just follow the bunny.
Right, we're just going to follow report.
Follow.
Wait, wasn't the bunny the one that gave me the poison?
Why would I follow the bunny?
Hope I can join in next time.
Absolutely.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Oh, scary.
Oh, no!
It doesn't go stuck.
Oh, no, refling's there.
I was an AFK refling.
Okay.
If you want to see where we are,
we're in world three AA
and we're outside the creepy,
creepy drain or manner.
Now, apparently we can get hurt in here.
So if anyone doesn't have food,
do you want to trade me
and I'll share my food with you?
If you send a trade offer,
I'll give you some food
because apparently we can get hurt.
But I think we can run away.
We just need to run away.
That's all.
I crashed.
Time to head back in game.
The forest is pretty scary.
Okay, we got a light.
Follow the bunny.
Last time I did that,
I found myself in Wonderland.
Okay, this refling needs some food.
Here you go.
Is there another?
Or has everyone got food?
Did you all cook meat?
I think you all must have cooked meat, yeah.
Oh, there's fires to cook meat
if you picked up meat from the coals.
Only now I notice that the strange
horse head refling
that walks strangely is no more there.
We are safe for now
from the strange walking refling.
We've got someone giving us a gluck gluck
outside the gates.
Been cooking the coos, right?
Okay, I don't know what happens here.
But I think the forest attacked...
Oh, wait, wait!
Sorry, sorry.
The quest is out here.
Talk to the lady here.
Sorry, talk to the lady.
Talk to the lady at the door.
Can you please help me?
I'm in a terrible spot of trouble.
Start, Ernest, to chicken.
Absolutely.
Ah, sounds like a quest.
I'll help.
Yes, yes.
I suppose is a quest.
My fiancee Ernest and I came to this hoose.
Seeing that we were a little lost,
Ernest decided to go in and ask for directions.
That was an hour ago.
This house looks spooky.
Can you see if you can find it for me?
I'll see what I can do.
Thank you, thank you.
I'm very grateful.
Okay, what are we?
Did we go inside now?
I'm scared.
All right, open the large door.
Oh, wait!
Requirements for the quest.
You need poison and fish food.
Oh, no!
Where do you get poison and fish food?
For the other reflins.
I thought you were being funny, other reflin.
I didn't realize.
Oh, wait, you're giving me something?
Why are you giving me?
Is that a boat plug?
A holy symbol.
What does it do?
I wear it.
It's like a star.
Anyone need poison or fish food?
Yeah, I thought that reflim was being funny,
giving me poison fish food.
Turns out it's actually for the quest.
That Samsung Galaxy Slurp.
My life can't handle another MMO
being through four in my life.
So this refling...
So this refling will just keep chat company.
We're only doing 99.
I don't know how to get poison or fish food.
There might be a refling that has enough supplies.
I didn't realize.
I never said.
I'm crazy.
Recommended items, none.
Or can you get them in the house?
There's a spawn for them, but they're very slow.
Okay, at least we can spawn the items.
In the house.
Right, I'm gonna very quickly go for a pee.
I don't know why I need to pee so much.
I think I'll make a tea as well.
Sorry, my voice is like really struggling.
I really want to stream for long.
I'm worried about how long I can last during my ASMR stream.
A little tinkle break, yeah.
A little tinkle-winkle.
The poison's in the house near the kitchen.
Okay, so at least we know the fish food
and the thing he does respawn.
I'm gonna make another tea.
I'm so sorry about all the breaks today.
It's my voice.
I'm getting, I'm getting nervous.
I'm not gonna be able to make it.
But for the ASMR and the sweet trying stream,
like, oh, sorry, I just stood on the mic.
Sorry about that.
I just absolutely obliterate your ears there.
Don't apologize.
I'll be back.
I'll literally be in a minute, okay?
To pee.
Yeah.
I don't know if it's a jumpscare when the tracking doesn't catch me coming into the room.
And I just unmute and I'm like, oh.
Oh.
You died.
Woman in the scar.
Why is it so loud in the music menu?
Thank goodness it doesn't link the details on the audio.
I think we're in skating with it.
Some people stream, what do you need?
Right.
an air nest.
Chang.
One refling went to go grab some spades for people who don't have one.
Oh sugar, I don't have a spade either.
Oh wait, what am I doing?
No, this one.
And then this one.
Uh, okay.
Are we waiting for spades?
Trade for spade!
Trade me! Trade mommy! Trade mommy!
Mommy needs a spade!
Just one, please.
I did make another spade.
I'm happy to say my pee was clear.
Um, I don't think I can do endurance.
My...
My throat is very sore right now.
It's very raw and it hurts, okay?
I'm needing your ink to help me
unironically soothe my throat.
So I think what the deal is
when Mercy goes live,
which is in T-minus
two and a half hours for snippets,
we'll raid into her.
If that's okay.
Um, there's a spade inside as well.
Just woke up. How's runes keep going?
It's going good!
Um, sadly my voice can't keep up.
This is when I get really frustrated for streaming.
I could happily stream 12 hours right now.
But it really hurts.
Okay, dropping some poison and fish food.
Okay, we'll wait until it loads up.
Honey, ink, tea, honestly.
Mercy's in two hours, yeah.
Oh good, been having tons of fun
and it's already a long stream, don't feel bad, yeah.
What do you mean? This is a baby stream for me?
Are you joking me?
Literally a two hour stream,
which is like the average for a VTuber,
is like a millisecond in my time.
Like, oh, I feel so bad.
I'm only going to stream eight hours today.
Ah!
I mean, what do you mean I got to play a multiplayer game
with quite literally, like,
how freaking blessed is it to be able to play a multiplayer game
with Reeflings live
whilst we're having a carry-on,
just meme-ing about freaking doing head-banging,
like, I've been dripped out,
I've been getting gifts and stuff,
people giving money, like,
it's not a job!
Like, this is fun!
Like, I'm having so much fun!
Ugh, I wish there was some sort of secret
to, like, fixing, like, my voice from vocal strain,
but the sad secret is it's literally just
shut up, stop talking.
Ugh, which is so annoying.
Better to end early than strain your throat.
I mean, it's already strained right now, but, uh...
What do you mean, multiplayer-to-ever talk,
yapping sessions, honestly,
is just yap, yap, yap.
We got a little spooky boy!
Spooky, spooky, bump again!
You're so misunderstood.
Oh, did you like Emmy's cover?
No.
Mo!
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah!
Oh, it's in a mo!
Oh, you're yawning just head off!
Oh, that's hilarious.
I'm waiting for the fish food to load,
so the others can grab it,
but I actually don't see it loading.
Having so much fun just hanging out at the Reeflings,
have all of the quests done already?
No, the quests are not done, please don't worry,
we're doing the free quest,
Erin is the chicken at the moment.
We've done a hand...
Oh, I've got my BS forehead in the way,
hold on, let me just close this for a second.
Here is all the quests we've done,
so free quests, we've done Cook's Assistant,
we're doing Big Erin Ease,
the chicken right now.
We did the mystery,
the restless ghost Romeo and Juliet,
Sheepshearer, X marks the spot,
we're finishing Erin is the chicken,
and then we're going back to update,
to grind on our cooking stats.
Can't expect you to do constant endurance streams day after day,
sadly I hate it,
I don't like doing short streams,
I just feel so like...
I don't know what the word is,
I have been yearning for this day,
for an entire year,
for this time, sorry, not for this day in particular,
but for this time,
and it's just like...
It's frustrating that the only reason I can't stream more
is because of my voice,
and not because I'm tired,
or I don't feel well,
or I don't want to type thing,
it's frustrating,
it's my voice.
That's it.
That's the only reason I can't stream for long,
because it hurts to talk right now.
Jesus, you haven't seen the whole song!
Try to live up to the name, you know?
Maybe.
I asked for a little bit off the top.
Hey, yo, who's the barber?
Man, we gotta go both.
Okay, the poison isn't loading on the floor for me,
but I think we'll do it,
so as long as you guys have accepted the quest,
we're gonna go inside now, reflings.
It's taking nice and slow.
I think the trees hit you on the way past,
so just be careful you don't stray from the path too much.
Assumers supposed to go...
Ah, the tree frickin' went for me.
Open large door.
Okay.
Oh, there's like haunted things.
Where are we supposed to go?
Get the gauge and tube.
Where is that?
And not here, maybe it's upstairs?
Okay, we...
I'm gonna wait until...
Oh, that's not good.
Wait, I'm just gonna check how the reflings made it in.
Go up the stairs, reflings, when you come inside.
Is that the last refling?
Who's that?
I think that's the last refling.
We all need to go upstairs.
How are you even there?
The chair's attacking him!
Oh my god, that chair being yours!
Okay, that...
Is there no refling there?
Oh, I'll go up the stairs.
Oh, he like...
Oh, someone's beating them up.
Wait, where are we supposed to go?
Up here?
Up these stairs to the left?
As soon as we come up?
Nothing's being highlighted for me.
Runlight, you're failing me!
Am I supposed to go here?
Talk to the professor?
Be careful, there's lots of things...
Brian!
It frustrates you because you can't control it
and that's the most frustrating thing.
Not being able to control something.
That's right.
Thank you, Iron Looper.
For the tip.
And yeah, just like...
Runlight is telling you to use...
Wait, hold on.
Oh no, I'm messing up.
Hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on.
That's not so easy.
Well, look at them.
Oh, maybe I should be reading that out.
What would that say?
Runlight is telling you to use your poison on your fish food.
Okay.
Okay, I have poison fish food.
Wait, never mind.
Just hypnotize yourself.
Strongly trust me, I love you and enjoy every second,
but your health is important.
Yeah, like, as long as my voice doesn't break,
then I'm good to go.
In my pain.
Where...
Where is this freaking map telling me to go?
I'm so confused.
I wanna go.
We were to go outside?
Oh, right, okay.
Oh, no, sorry.
Close the map, not close.
Right, so go downstairs.
Okay, come downstairs.
Poison the fish food and then come back out of the mansion.
Okay.
Oh, this is a rough one to do together, I think,
so if you've not got...
The door won't open.
Over here.
Okay, okay, okay.
How do I get over there?
Wait, open the door.
The chair beating you up?
Oh, no, they just run around.
I thought the chair was like,
beat you up in the game on my cheek.
Oh, there's a rubber tube.
I get it.
Get the gauge in the tube.
Oh, my God.
Open the door.
What's that?
Oh, I'm actually kind of scared of that.
Wait, I can't go in.
The door's locked.
Oh, right, okay.
Someone's dropped a speed ahead if you need it, by the way.
But we're taking the long way around.
Okay, I'm glad the chairs don't beat you up
because, honestly, death by chair is pretty embarrassing.
Right, open the door.
Or I'm gonna throw rocks through your window.
Open the door.
Okay, so one by one door, but we can add it.
I need to get the key first.
Well, she's a stubborn one,
but I guess she keeps up till the day
she can take care of herself
to some fish so hard, man.
Okay, okay, we're now outside.
This is a very hard one to follow,
quest-wise.
Especially if you had a rune-like,
rune-crafting guild.
Stop.
Are you telling someone that we're rune-crafting guilds?
Okay, I'm just following the Easter bunny.
Follow the bunny, the bunny, the bunny.
Follow the Easter bunny.
To east, to east, to east.
Search compost heap.
Heap.
I love it.
A bit of cheeky vandalism.
Okay, we did it.
Oh, what did I do?
You find a small key.
Okay.
And now...
Oh, there's a thing ahead.
Okay, there's a fountain ahead.
I don't know.
Has that already come to you?
I feel like...
I feel like someone's probably stuck in the house right now.
As long as you try and come outside, then you'll be fine.
So as long as you've all got the key,
come to the fountain next.
There's a fountain through the trees.
The trees might whip you,
but you should survive.
Like, it's literally one HP at least.
Poisoned fish food on the fountain.
Use on the fountain.
Oh, the tree just made a noise.
Use it on the fountain.
Okay.
The piranhas start eating the food,
then dine float to the surface.
And then search the fountain.
There seems to be a pressure gauge in here,
and a lot of dead fish.
Well, yeah, you just roll them,
smoke them.
Come outside.
Yes, I see, I see.
Okay, once we've all stopped
head banging into the fountain,
then we go back into the house.
Anyone got some spare poison fish?
Ah, the poison was in the house, I think.
Wait, we're outside the house.
How do we get back in?
Why is it making me go around in a circle?
I'm spinning around.
Get out of my way.
I didn't think for how much time
you prepared for this, by the way.
How is it, is it like you expected?
To me, you're having a lot of fun,
but maybe you have more to see.
On RuneScape?
I'm getting whipped by a tree.
Sorry, sorry, Ruflin's getting whipped by a tree
because of me, sorry.
I didn't mean RuneScape, it took a little second
to get ready to stream out.
I wasn't that bad.
Scale it in time, you just have to run in
and pick the tube, then run out.
Make it in turns, who wants to go first?
Ah, fuck it, I'll go first.
I need a lead by example.
Okay, grab the tube and then...
Okay, I got whacked for two,
so just make sure you get out in time.
Would you prefer to be whipped by a tree?
Is it instance,
or are we going to have to wait for that to reload?
Oh no, you've got it, you've got it.
Okay, that's fine.
Are you beating him up?
He said nah, hold on, let me do this,
Ruflin's like all this.
He's going to skillspec him, he's going to skillspec
he's going to do the little twirl thing.
Oh, streaming in general has been absolutely fantastic.
It's gone exactly the way I wanted it to.
I love streams, Nathan,
and I love long streams and yapping people's heads off
and it's just gone absolutely amazing.
Just fantastic.
For me, I don't like the mega
super professional streams, don't mind me.
Some people really like it.
Let's go, has everyone got it?
Thank you, Ruflin, for killing the skelly boy.
Has everyone got the rubber tube?
I don't think everyone's got it.
I don't know if it's been a bit funny,
but you should be able to go in and get the rubber tube
now that you've got the key.
Oh, someone's getting attacked over there.
Is there a Rufling? Oh, I thought a Ruflin just perished there.
Ruflin just perished there.
I'm happy to hear that, yeah.
There is nothing like a professional stream.
Where's the fish food?
Upstairs is the fish food reefling,
someone says.
I'll wait here until the other reeflings are caught
because it's not fair to skip ahead.
I like when funny Scott women yank to me for hours.
Simple as, nothing more.
Now, people really enjoy professional streams
from other people, which is great,
but for me, I'm just like...
It's the best I can say.
Oh, we're getting two head bang.
Yo, I'm starting to think this is getting...
Hold on, oh no, I can't wait, wait, let me zoom up a bit.
Let me take one more step
for no particular reason at all.
Okay, let me take one more step
Because it's absolutely no reason at all.
We are literal children, this is terrible.
That awful getting...
Hey, hey, hey, hey, he dancing on it,
he dancing on it, he doing the split on it.
I love your silly yapping.
Oh my God, a ghost is going for it.
Is there a refling on the outskirts?
Oh, I think I'm too far away to be able to see
if someone's at the compost heap right now.
Oh no, someone's getting beaten up.
Oh no, it's not him though.
I have salmon if you want it,
a refling that's literally protecting us all.
There's salmon juice, whoa, what is that?
Oh, is that for me?
Wait, should I do this in the middle?
I don't know what he does.
Scottlefish, are you there?
Should I do it or no?
I don't know if the old man's got a good quest or not.
Did I talk to him?
Do it, okay, someone says do it.
Oh, there you are, I hoped you would talk to me.
I get so lonely, I have a present, I must get going now.
Oh!
Oh, he just gave me an uncut emerald.
I didn't even ask anything.
Oh, don't mind if I do,
I thought he was going to like whisk me away.
But he didn't.
Oh, I see the poison.
Whoa, poison's like 700.
Well, I know where the poison is,
if I don't need to know, it's by the left.
As you come in.
Does he need help?
Wow.
You wish to trade with me, what do you wish to trade?
Oh, you're giving it,
oh, the diamonds,
how you call them.
I don't know, the rocks in the ground.
What are these called? It's not jewelry.
But they're rocks.
What are diamonds category?
What are the category of ruby and plafa and that?
Gemstones!
Oh my god, I forgot that word there.
Jeez, low waist.
I literally forgot the word gems there.
I apologize.
Watch ads showed up tipped and left.
Or, yeah, or in gems.
I got out.
Oh god, we're all headbanging.
Are you practicing later?
For when the next 10 audios come out?
Wait, where is it? Headbanging?
Headbanging.
Oh my god, we really are a call.
Clearly, look at us go.
Oh, do you need, you need help,
holy crap you need help right now.
I've got salmon.
This should heal you up.
Go, go, go.
Is there any reeflings?
Oh no, they're self healing.
Is there any reeflings on the outskirts?
I can't really tell. I don't want to go ahead in case there's someone outside doing that. Fountain, but, um...
Is everyone here? Did we make it?
If there's a roofling, oh.
Who did that? Who did that?
That was you?
Okay, we're reporting you for harassment.
Interesting, we're in sync for me, but on stream.
My ping is really high to everyone.
They've had plenty of time. Yeah, is everyone here? I think so.
Hi hi, how's stream going?
It's been going amazing. Look at me and the roofling gang, we're doing questing.
Okay, I think everyone's got the plastic tube.
They get the gauge and tube.
Get the oil can next.
So, open this door.
We'll go through.
Okay.
I think we're all ready.
Don't have the tube, but also got the gauge.
Wait, you don't have the tube?
No, I do have the tube.
Okay, we need to interact with this blue thing over here.
Wait, you've not got the tube?
Who's not got the tube?
Tube, you just run in and pick up when it spawns.
Go in the closet and get the rubber if you don't have...
I shouldn't have said that.
Oh my god, the shadow band GB's Twitter.
All of our Twitter's looks like a shadow band, it's ridiculous.
Like how sensitive it is.
Oh, what's that? It's a big thing.
Oh, it's gone.
Did they get the tube?
Did you get the tube? I think so.
All right, fun part of the quest. Let's go.
Let's go. Oh, the door...
The door's fine.
Hold on, sorry, I probably just closed that door on you.
Okay, search the bookcase.
Search the bookcase.
Oh, is that one by one?
Maybe a one by one moment. Hold on.
Hey, let's go.
Okay, go down the ladder.
Wait, go down the ladder when you're ready.
Is that everyone? Yeah, that's everyone.
Once you get through the bookshelf.
Okay, we did it.
The whole gang's here.
No replaying left behind.
Oh my god, we're beating up the rats, literally.
Oh god, what do we do?
Okay, there's a lever on the wall.
Pull lever alpha on the wall over here.
I assume this is going to be instanced to us.
So...
I don't know.
Then pull lever, bravo.
Oh, the music's all like...
Okay.
Now this gate is a jar.
And English, if it's like slightly open,
it's a jar.
Pull lever D.
Oh, I'll pull the D lever all day long.
Come over here, weak one.
What did that do?
Okay.
Oh god, it's a one by one gate.
Why is there a biggest issue right now?
One by one gate.
Oil can has a slow respawn as well.
I need an oil...
I think we all need an oil can.
So we're just going to have to go for it and be patient.
I'm sure you can wait.
I don't know if all the levers are the same for everyone.
It looks like you guys are going different ways.
So I think it might be different.
World hop when you get into the room
and then hop back.
Yeah, you guys are really going different ways for me.
So I think it's different for everyone.
Oh, the classic one by one gate.
It's over.
Lever solution is the same for everyone.
How's everyone going...
Are you guys...
Do you see this one?
That way everyone can grab it faster.
Yes.
Okay.
Okay, I love this runelight plugin
because if I had to do this
by my brain, it would be over.
This is crazy.
All levers are unique in their own way.
Exactly.
Wow.
Let's see.
Pull this lever.
We're almost done.
Okay, I was going to say that's like a lot of fricking questions.
Oh wait, sorry.
I'm going to see if my tea is at an acceptable temperature
if I'm going to scold myself on it.
That's why there's one or the other.
That was...
All these doors.
Oh, right.
Am I taking it?
And then you guys are world hopping?
And then you're coming back to this world?
Yeah, this track is...
Gen 2 based after
old school runescape tracks
question mark.
Oh wait, I should be facing you today.
Honestly,
I wouldn't mind that.
I'm kind of down for that.
I was actually thinking of
Legend of Zelda Minish Cap
but brought
to kind of modern standards
for Gen 2.
Runescape OSD?
If we had like a mischievous little brat thing,
this song
was kind of like
not Circus S.
I guess it was Circus S.
Does everyone have an oil can?
Or...
Oh, there's a respawn.
That took a whole second.
Everyone got an oil can?
Maybe I know you're taking that now.
Okay, if you have an oil can,
go back out to the center over here.
If you don't have an oil can,
wait for it to spawn in that room
or you can do what's called world hopping
where you purposely swap to a new world
and it should
be like a new instance.
But if you have an oil can, you're allowed to come out here.
Minish is 20 years old now.
Stubious brat.
I would watch Zelda.
I will uncontroll.
I just want to support whoever gets sea shanty.
No, it has to be like hidden,
but when you know what it is, you know.
Oh, there's a reefling there.
We're not ready yet.
I'll just check if anyone's back here.
Other than that reefling.
Oh, there's one there.
I was just straight up reefling.
You actually got the name reefling.
I'm surprised no one else took it.
I guess we'll just beat out...
We're gonna beat up rats out here.
Okay, we're just gonna get our combat level a bit higher.
Oh, I just leveled up.
What did I get? I got a taxix.
Oh, there's spiders as well.
Yeah, let's just level up her combat a little bit.
Why not?
Woo.
Us following her gives me
Ugandan knuckles flashbacks.
This beat only fake queen.
Would you hum shanty?
Hmm.
Yeah, I managed to get the reefling name
still five hours a day.
Yeah.
That's sea shanty.
We're just leveling up her combat.
Hmm.
There's still a reefling over there getting absolutely...
What are you getting annihilated by?
A rat? Oh, okay, that's fine.
And there's one there.
There's a third?
Yeah, we've got Hatsumiku chilling over there.
Hmm.
Reefling.
Now we have a max roll.
Hmm.
Let's get some level up.
No way that rat just dunked my shield.
I went bonk.
Yeah, Amy would have chosen...
Maybe.
She would show us maybe.
I remember that meme went like absolutely viral.
Someone said that was the start
of the brain rot meta
when it comes to memes.
Which I found rather unsafe.
Wow.
I think there's someone else
that's fighting that.
Here we go.
We've almost got all over
cans.
And then we'll level up on fishy.
I keep saying fishin'.
It's not fishin', we're doing kootin'.
My PCs fan just started
up. I get nervous when my PCs...
I'm like, what's wrong?
What's wrong?
Oh?
Last reefling that needs to can?
The question mark?
I don't see anyone else doing the levers.
Am I going crazy or are we clear?
Have we did it?
Are we ready to move on?
Oh, he's done it.
I don't want to say dancing.
Okay, if everyone's got a can,
up the ladders, please.
Little reeflings, if everyone's got a can.
Oh wait, no!
Sorry, there's one more.
I
think they're still doing the lever
stage.
I'm sorry, reefling such a badger.
You can come back down and we'll keep
killing the means.
He's
going to be absolutely beaten up by
that rat, so he'll help you out.
There you go.
Uh...
Did you get it?
I don't know.
You're moving around erratically
as a reefling...
I don't know, are you stuck
on the levers?
You're not taping.
Go on, I'll catch up.
Are you sure, reeflings?
I won't feel anyone feel left out.
VR chat was well,
and that's just
a bit weird.
I was going to have to play VR chat
to learn how the
3D models work. I have no idea how that
3D model streaming works.
But I don't know if you can use
other programs as well.
Oh, I'm leveling combat,
not to brag.
You will learn.
Can you say error again?
Error?
Error.
Error, switching tracks.
You don't need to use VR chat
for 3D models.
I honestly don't know
anything about it. The girls want 3D models,
and I'll pay for it.
That's pretty much all I know about 3D models.
I'm like, joking.
If they want 3D models, they'll get it.
VR chat isn't interesting at all.
Oh!
I've saw VR
ASMR videos. I thought that was pretty cool.
And plus, it would be cool to see
the height difference of the girls as well.
Go on, y'all.
Okay, okay.
We're being sent away by the
reflying, right? Upstairs, everyone.
We're being sent away.
Upstairs.
Okay, there's a lever here.
Pull the lever, crunk!
Oh! Okay, okay, okay.
Right, we need to go up the stairs again.
Right, let's go back here.
I'mma sip my tea.
Okay.
You literally talk like a real mummy
with the girls. They want 3D models.
Yeah, I'll just pay for it, darlin'. There you go, darlin'.
All yours. I don't know what it's about,
but you just enjoy yourself.
It's true. They'll be like, I want this.
I'm like, oh, you just, oh, you get it.
You just enjoy yourself, hen.
Right, okay. Talk to the professor at the top of the stairs.
Oh, you found anything yet?
I have everything. Give them to me here, then.
All his.
Oh, you put them.
Noises are being made?
He's a man!
Thank you, madame. I was dreadfully irritating being a chicken.
How can I ever thank you?
Well, a cash reward is always nice.
Of course, of course!
You're awarded 4 quest points of 300 coins.
Yay!
That was really quick. Other than, like,
the horrific issues.
That was like a really quick quest.
Um...
Right, we're not doing any more questing.
We're leveling up.
Next.
Money, let's go!
What is this pressure gauge?
Don't touch it. It's going to explode.
What do we do?
What pressure gauge?
It's really like any other scientific
thing.
I guess that's it, and we just leave.
But that...
It's in the fountain.
It's in the fountain. That's why you need to poison it.
How bizarre.
Oh, there's the fish food.
Ugh!
I guess that's it. We're already
freaking done this quest. Hold on.
Wah.
Oh wait, why did you not let me out that door?
Open large door.
Wait, why does it make me turn backwards?
I keep... It doesn't let me out this door?
Open large door.
It won't open.
Front door is one way.
Oh, so we have to
go all the way around again?
Oh, okay.
Another interesting take
from the dev team?
Alright, let me sip into my tea.
Okay, yeah.
I'll go another one by one door.
It's over.
The chair's chasing me.
Can you even go that way?
Oh, you can. You can come around this side?
Can you teach me?
Why to play Rensuke Tempah?
Get ready. Go right back.
Ow! The tree!
I don't want to go in a fight. Move!
What's going on? Why can't I move?
Hello?
Am I missing?
Why can't I not...
Why? That tree literally
had me in a death grip. Oh my gosh.
Mostly was a...
a guy of fun.
Don't get skill checked by a tree.
Literally, one error.
I almost died there.
I think the tree liked you, honestly.
Okay, we made it.
But I don't think that's all the reeflings.
This is dangerous, literally. Oh, there's a reefling there.
Right, we'll wait until a cool army.
I have an army of reeflings requesting,
but we're about to go level up our cooking next.
I'm trying to finish my honey tea
before it gets cold.
Wah! Okay.
Um, next thing
we're going to do is we're going to
travel north. We're going to take
a west and then north
and we're going to be outside
the village.
But we need to go get fish and rods and stuff.
I don't think there's a fish shop nearby.
So I think we're going to go to the Grand Exchange
and buy fish and rods.
Army, definitely not cold.
Yeah.
This music has given me
a fatal dose of nostalgia.
Passed so much
since the last Get Rektor is.
Hmm.
As I get stuck
I'm ruffling fans and bye.
I've never gotten a runescape.
It's like either you got into it or you didn't.
Right, I think that's everyone.
Hopefully, question mark.
As we head banger way of victory.
I don't know about the other
reefling that got stuck and sent us forward
but thank you for not holding us back.
By the same time I feel bad
because it's like the whole point of this is to
the question and stuff together.
Right, let's get in the nicer parts of the channel.
Let the evil at bay
type of thing go away.
Wait, let me finish my tea.
Either you got into it
and you're still playing this day or you didn't.
I got into Guild Wars instead.
I never played Guild Wars.
Hmm.
Trying to finish this.
Ah.
Oh, I thought it gave us feathers but it didn't.
I was just an image of a feather because we need
feathers to do fishing.
Hmm.
I was so into it and was so shy that
in taping class I'd want big letters, RuneScape rules
and wait for someone to see it and ask me if I played.
Aww, that's such a shame.
Feathers, we need feathers.
Birds of a feather.
Right, we're gonna take
a left
and go...
Oh wait, no. Do we need to go to Port Sarim?
I think we actually need to go to the fishing
shop to buy our rod and feathers.
The fishing shops
are west
and south so we'll go west and south.
Just follow me
with my golden stuff.
Oh no, I'm gonna follow the rabbit.
We follow the rabbit. You coming?
Refling?
Yes.
Uh...
Take us westward and then south
on the main road.
Feathers. Oh no, am I saying feathers?
Oh, we need some feathers.
Wait, how did you say feathers?
Feathers.
Feathers. Feathers.
Oh, it sounds like I'm kind of
saying father.
I guess. Feathers.
Your father.
In this line you also say
your father, isn't it?
And it's like, ah, that's my dad.
I don't want change.
I never played Guild Wars Organscape.
I want silly Scottish women!
Feathers.
Your wee feathers.
You'd weave it behind, Refling.
You'd put your wee running boots on.
You'd put your...
Feathers.
Oh, we're gonna do a brawl.
Uh... at the end of the stream
We're going to hop over the wall and fist fight each other and I'm going to get a rose and I'll give it to whoever wins the 50 cups.
Oh, pardon me, I'm broken.
Ok, in this shop you will need to buy a rod. Most of you already have one.
Ah, you guys so fast.
So trade with Garrett and then buy... oh no, there's only one.
That costs five coin, so buy one.
Do we need feathers or do we need the fishing bait?
Is it a fishing bait we need?
I made this tea so honey.
Oh that's sweet, that's too sweet. I can actually finish that.
All the sweetness is at the bottom. Feathers for trout and salmon.
Is that ticking up? Oh it is.
I don't have the money.
Or maybe I do.
Ok, that's all I can buy with what I've got.
I haven't got enough for anything else. I've got 73 feathers, I didn't think this far ahead.
I opened a stream and didn't see you here.
I wish this to trade with you, except trade.
Eh, I still have a key.
Oh, that's going to be a lot of feathers to spread about, not going to lie.
How do you have so much money?
Right, let me buy feathers for... what are these? Feather pack?
What's that?
I don't know. If I buy fifth... oh you can.
Oh, that's so smart! Inside the feather pack.
I'm going to keep some heels on me.
Right, I can give feather packs to reeflings.
Why does that not buy when I click it?
Wait, I'm dropping them! Oh, hold on, I'm being dumb.
I can trade the feather packs.
Ok, I've got like a thousand feathers now. Who needs feathers?
I think everyone needs feathers, honestly.
If you need feathers, trade me and I'll give you... wait, actually.
I should like give 200 feathers each?
I'll just say buy 50 and then I'll give 200 feathers.
I love spreading feathers on my...
Should we get a harpy? We should totally get a harpy.
I'm glad to take a feather pack.
Ok, trade me if you need feathers. I'll try and give you like 200.
Whose outfit is that? Is that even a reefling? Are you a reefling?
I don't know. I think that might just be someone caught in the crossfire.
Right, let's see. Accept and then offer...
200 and then we'll go fishing.
Accept.
Wait, what? Hold on.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, why did that not work?
200 and I...
Yeah. Oh, jeez. Sorry.
I don't know where that went. It just disappeared into space.
Ok, there's 200 for you and then there's two...
How dare you?
Just trying to see.
And then 200 for you.
And then sugar mummy.
You say that as if a reefling didn't just hand me all of his paycheck and runescape.
Where's Johnny at now? We're at Port Sarim.
We're on World 380.
We're currently at Port Sarim buying...
Ok, my PC just sped up trying to zoom that in.
And then we're going to go up to Barbarian Village to get salmon because there's a permanent fire there.
And we'll do 200.
No, I've done it again. Sorry. I keep teasing you with a feather.
I've done it again!
I can't stop teasing you right now.
I'm tickling you with the feathers.
I'm like, oh, do you want the feather and like tickle you and then run away with it?
Like pushing it against your face like ASMR and then like...
You need feathers too.
I'll buy a ton as well so when we head over there, we should be fine.
So if you need more, I can always get like always just trade more.
Teasing us with a feather, honestly.
Thank you, pretty lady. Played with me.
Has everyone got what they... Where the heck is the guy?
Where's the NPC to buy, awful?
I can't see. There's too many of us.
It's Miss. He's not for me.
Alright, where's the guy to buy freaking things off?
Oh, there he is.
Gonna buy like a bunch of feather packs and open them up.
Oh my god, have I already spent 10k on feathers?
Jeez, this game is not cheap. The economy's in shambles.
Right, that's like literally almost 5k. That's more than enough.
Does anyone else... You need some too.
Does that work? It did work, thank goodness.
How did you know that our weaknesses are feathers? Stop using your powers on us.
I don't think I ever thought of feathers. Did I do a tickling?
I may have got... I don't think I got... No, I think I got you tickling me artwork.
You're welcome.
Does anyone else need any feathers?
Or are we all ready to go?
We need to thank Sugar Daddy, Weflin...
The one that gave me poison that I thought was being bred.
I realised and I was like, I didn't accept the quest and had to loop with the chick.
Oh no, sorry, did you manage?
I could take some please.
Trade.
And then offer X amount.
Alright, has everyone got a rod? Not the one that's already attached to you.
One bought from the thing.
Were you giggling? Were you Sugar Daddy, Weflin and...
Giggling?
Kill... What's... What's heavier?
Kilograms.
Right, is everyone ready to do the walk? The walk.
Yes, I finished it. Oh no, you need some... Hold up.
Except trade.
We're getting there, we're getting there.
Wait, no, I don't... No, I don't need your rod.
Stop, I don't need your rod.
You keep your rod to yourself, Weflin.
It's not the time for that.
I do have a rod for vision.
Now I need some feathers, thanks.
Sugar would catch up me.
Right, is everyone ready to follow me and I'll take us to Barbarian?
You need a fly fishing rod for the fishes.
Oh, we need a specific type of rod. Of course we do.
What rod of alcohol? I've got a fishing rod.
I need a fly rod. Hold on, trade Garrett.
Fly fishing rod.
Right, does everyone have a fly fishing rod?
Before we move on to the next location.
Lesson two hour warning for Mercy Modest.
Nope.
Do you need...
Me...
To...
Oh.
I hope it restokes.
You're out.
I do have a pretty fly rod.
Pretty fly for a white guy.
You know it's kinda hard just to get along today.
He asked for...
What's that? He asked for ink.
He asked for a 13 year.
Instead they drew a fairy one.
It's a fairy one.
I don't know... They're not restocking.
They're like so slow to restock.
I don't know if I can...
Wait, we are...
We're gonna be right next to the grand exchange.
Maybe I'll buy some off the grand exchange.
I'll go with the grand exchange.
Yeah, okay.
We're gonna make it to the grand exchange.
Don't worry.
If you don't have a fly freshen rod,
we're gonna be very close to the grand exchange.
So don't worry.
You can follow me.
Follow Golden...
Golden me.
Is there any more reasons in that shop?
I actually can't tell.
The camera is like...
I'm sure there's a way to turn off first.
But...
Right, we'll follow...
Our...
Gated...
Our gate, our bunny gate.
A little hopsy.
I hope I'm right.
Yeah, okay.
This is in the...
The shop.
Everyone's here.
We're going to go to the grand exchange
to make sure everyone has a fly freshen rod
and to also deposit all of our items
because our inventory's getting like
pretty full of stuff.
And I don't want to be walking around
with like so much money.
Oh, there's the brawl.
This is where we're gonna do a bar brawl.
In a bar.
Da-da-da-da-da...
Do-a-da-da-da...
Yay, bye!
Ba-kuh-ba-kuh-ba-inter bolt...
Ah!
You can always hover over
and then just say follow.
Follow...
Follow the leader, leader.
Oh, no, someone got stopped
by a mysterious old man.
Oh, you should always talk to
the mysterious old man
he'll give you, um...
Gemstone!
An uncut gemstone.
Put James in.
Okay, we're all ready.
Follow the leader leader.
Our ink shall block the sun.
I have 10 strongies.
I got some there already.
Okay, okay, okay.
Always talk to the mysterious old man, Godot.
Isn't that in...
Sometimes he gives you a maze to run through.
Oh.
The series old man giving uncut things.
Say yo.
The old man can offer to send you to solve a maze
and that one gives amazing rewards.
Okay, okay.
I know the signage lady doesn't give you anything good.
I'm like 99% sure she gives you a bit of cabbage or something.
I like this spinning one.
I can't remember what it is.
It's like the item spins around
and you have to identify it or something.
Amazing rewards.
Love that maze quest.
Love it.
Oh, it's going to skeal him.
No, it's not getting him.
Oh, I'm not too...
Two songs.
It's terrible.
It's absolutely terrible.
Oh, no.
Our biggest enemy, a bridge.
Right, we're going to go to the Grand Exchange
to empty our inventory
so we only have feathers and a fly fishing rod.
I don't...
There's a few fishers.
I don't know if they're bots or not.
As long as they're not talking,
then I think we'll be safe.
Because I don't want to turn off public traffic.
Because I don't want to turn off public chat
because it's fun having you guys talk
both in-game and in-stream.
It's where the real fishing begins.
The seventh grade computer lab day fishing.
Is it terrible?
No one is going to argue she wasn't that one.
Right, we're back at the Grand Exchange.
Right, where's the reefling that has the rods we desire?
For those reeflings who don't have a rod, please...
Reach out to...
To me.
To Kamin 1000.
If you don't have a rod...
I don't know where Kamin is.
I can't...
Oh, there, here, here.
There.
The one in the smithing cape.
If you don't have a fly fishing rod, trade then.
I'm going to put my stuff in the bank.
Uh, but...
Uh, this is not enough.
Let's just put everything in here other than...
Like, all of these?
Keep that...
Wait, why have I not got the money?
Oh no, I have a bear shield, that's why.
And then put that away.
And then put the fishing rod away.
And then put the money away.
Oh no, I didn't mean to click that.
Okay.
Okay, we did it.
We're ready to fish and cook.
Apparently everyone has a rod.
Jeez.
It must a...
A rod?
A fishing rod.
It's the mighty of the strange.
Old women in the forest isn't for...
Oh, there's so many strange requests.
Uh, I guess we're ready to take off
if everyone's emptied their inventory
and you should have a rod and feathers
and then we are going to go fishing
and level up our cooking eggs financially.
I'm ready.
All aboard the golden apron train.
I'll just make sure in case someone's stuck
at the bank right now.
It's kind of hard to tell,
because there's, like, somebody...
Oh no, there's only...
Rods are ready, everyone.
So few female reeflings.
And...
It is what it is.
Oh, wishes to trade with you?
Okay.
What's up?
Are you giving me your...
Are you giving me your banana?
Oh, yeah.
Wait, is this a thing?
No, it's not.
Okay.
I've just been given the banana.
Did you just finish?
Be honest.
Oh, I ate it.
I'm sorry.
I just ate it right in front of you.
I just ate your banana.
Wait, is that everyone?
Can I store it somewhere
or just drop stuff off?
Oh, yeah.
So, do you see over here how it says
bank banker?
And then click on your inventory
and it'll put it in the bank.
So, this empties out your inventory.
The only thing you want right now
is a fly fishing rod and feathers.
Banana or banana?
It's a treat all over again.
I actually had a lot of fun making that to me.
I don't know what it's...
I don't know if it's gotten more popular or not.
But when I woke up, it was, like,
1,000 likes and I'm like,
ooh, that's a lot, I mean.
Okay, that should hopefully be it.
And then we'll take all the reeflings away.
Actually, we'll...
Well, I don't know if all the reeflings are ready yet.
Thank you, God.
She just ate that man's banana live on public.
On stream in public in front of everyone.
Okay, is that all reeflings?
I like my name so...
Oh, no, one more, one more.
There's one more reefling.
Look at that fit.
Look at the feet size difference.
Okay, we now follow
the reeflings I thought was making a threat
via the poison in fishfish.
That video was good.
Okay, reeflings, we're going to Barbarian Village.
Hopefully there's no bots talking.
I'm probably just gonna click ignore
if there's any bots so we don't have to world hop
because this is a pretty quiet world in general.
Yeah, it was great.
I lost that video.
Really?
I was, like, wondering should I, like, overcomplement...
overcomplicate it and, like, say,
like, certain words, phrase or whatever.
And I was, like, no.
Just be super simple about it.
So I was...
Did it.
Right.
Okay, so this is Barbarian fishing section.
It's normally bought it, but I don't know.
These may be real people.
This is the best, like, free-to-play area.
We'll do here.
We'll lure our fishing rod.
And how are you a cow?
You were a bunny a second ago.
Oh, I've already caught a fish.
Whoa, the fishing is so fast.
Oh, my God, really gonna be levelling up so quickly.
Well, once whatever you catch,
there's a pair of my fire over here that we can cook on.
Everyone did get level 20 fishing, right?
Or I've just dragged you over here for nothing.
I hope everyone's...
Oh, you're all up to 20?
Oh, no, I thought everyone was 20 fishing.
I'm so sorry.
Oh, I'm not level 20.
No.
My suggestion, if you're not level 20,
you need to get that net and go back to the thing.
I joined late.
I'll level in dreams night later.
Not me, but I'll jump over and get a quick view of it.
Oh, no, there's a banana on the floor.
Random banana.
So, only that video in your altar is one of the hottest.
Oh.
How many likes is that?
I'm allowed to know.
If you aren't level 20,
I would suggest going back to Lumbridge.
Teleport to Lumbridge.
Get your small fishing net out the bank at the top
and then go back to that spot until you're 20.
And then coming here...
Well, I'm already level 21.
Jesus, so much faster doing this.
It's crazy.
Is that 1.4?
Okay, we'll go.
How long has people enjoyed it?
That's the main thing.
What level to bait fish here?
I'm not sure.
I only brought feathers for fly fish.
No comment.
Should I do a burp at the end of one of them?
Maybe I should.
They're like a burp version.
Hmm.
But yes.
We're probably going to be here for like a hot second.
Mercy's going up in an hour 40.
So honestly, I think for the rest of the stream,
we're going to be here.
So if you want to level up to 20 cooking,
you certainly can.
Sorry, 20 fishing.
And then like come back here.
Like we'll probably most likely be here.
And hopefully I can stop burning fish
and then I can start burning through the supplies
that were gifted because like I think I got like
2000 fish gifted to me.
I'll be back.
Good luck.
Yeah.
Have a good time.
You can teleport via your magic spells.
Get on to, yeah.
Get to Lumberge again and do that small thing
and then come back here once you've got your fly fishing rod.
And I've got loads of feathers on me.
Yeah.
This is where the ground begins.
We are currently at 25 cooking.
Which is decent.
I wanted to get 40 before stream.
I think 40 is part of that cow animation.
I think 40 is 40 realistic before
Mercy goes live.
I'm not sure.
Bait fishing is 25.
Oh, that's even worse.
How do you get grapes, actually?
From the Grand Exchange?
I don't actually know where you harvest them.
Tea time.
We're actually going to get decent level in fishing.
Yeah.
Whoa.
It's 50 eggs per fish.
That's quite a lot.
All things considered.
I'm going to level up in fishing again
on this one stalk of inland water.
Yeah.
Oh, that's a lot of trout on the floor.
That's literally 10k worth of fish.
13k XP per hour.
If you don't cook the fish.
Yeah, we're going to have to stop and use this fire.
But this is a permanent fire that we can utilize for ourselves.
Which is fantastic.
Would it make sense to just buy them in bulk?
Yeah, especially if you do that route and just buy 66.
Oh, that would be daunting.
But it's definitely a possibility.
I'm wondering, maybe we could do react andy content.
I don't know if there's stuff that's safe for YouTube reaction.
Whilst we do this.
Because don't get me wrong.
I'm entertaining.
But I don't think I'm that entertaining for like a 30 hour grind.
If I was doing grapes.
Oh, just do the last one.
So maybe we put stuff on in the background.
70 eggs pee for cooking trout.
Whoa.
That's so fast.
We're literally 26 already.
That is so fast.
We need Minecraft parkour.
Subway surfers in the bottom stream.
70 is so much.
When we unlock salmon, I don't even know how much salmon is.
XP wise.
Oh, stop burning it.
Stop burning it.
Oh.
Just put some surfers in the corner.
Yeah, so this is like free grinding as well.
To pick up this fish that people drop.
Oh, we literally went on two cooking levels doing one batch of fish.
That's crazy.
I'm so fast.
Here, fishy fishy.
We need to be quiet.
Salmon or 90 cooking eggs pee.
Okay, that will be good.
I'll listen to you whenever, but I've lost my mind entirely.
See you tomorrow. Rest well.
Please rest well.
Gotta get up tomorrow with Khan.
Oh, fun time.
Oh my god, it's Rinscape in real life.
It's trying to get easily watched.
There has been nothing but yapping.
It's because of my voice.
It's so sore.
My face meant no dragon.
Harpoon specking on free world.
Oof.
Wow, wow, wow.
I haven't seen it for a while.
Honestly, we...
We thought we were going to do 40 before Mercy comes on,
but we managed to like fish to high heaven.
We might be past 40.
I don't know. I don't want to jinx it, but...
40 on the first Rinscape stream seems pretty decent work.
And we also did fun questing.
We got how many quests?
One, two...
I'm gonna go so fast.
Three, four, five...
Six and seven.
Well, maybe do...
A few more.
23!
Got overtime tomorrow, so I'm gonna have to...
So I have plenty of listening time.
For anyone that needs to go to sleep
or you need to go do some things,
please do not worry. You're not missing out on much.
This is literally the gameplay for the next hour and a half.
I'm not even kidding.
We're just fishing and then a...
We're catching the fish and then cooking them
and then leveling up cooking.
Are you squidding me right now?
Brian!
Hi Tiny Spinny!
Hope you had fun at work.
We are currently in World 3A
and we are in Barbarian Village.
We're fishing.
So the Grand Exchange,
Varrock, Telopore,
and we're at the fishing village.
We have a fly fishing rod
and we have a feather
and we're catching the fish and cooking them
on the perma...
cookie thing.
Once I'm experienced enough
not to burn fish,
I most likely will cook all the fish
that the reeflings gave me
because I don't want them to go to waste
because that was a lot of money
that the reeflings handed me.
I don't...
I'll cook all of that
and see where we are.
I think lobsters...
I've got quite a few lobsters.
Trout, salmon, all of that.
So we're going to cook all of that.
I don't think we're going to be on Wains
by the time Mercy comes on.
I think tomorrow's my eighth more stream.
So I definitely need to try and rest my voice
so that it's going to be so smooth.
I'm ready for another 2AM YAP session.
We're listening to the Scottish last.
I've got plenty of YAP
and we're like, I'm slow.
Oh, someone's got a mini...
mini quest.
A toot!
A toot free power.
Such a tent feeling free.
Oh my God, it's so intense.
Wait, I'm not even fishing anyone.
That's probably the only thing that kills me
about this game,
like when it comes to fishing and stuff.
It's when the boxes move.
But it is very tempting to,
like, pick up all the fish that are already here
and just do that and spawn that.
Lobsters require 40 cookies
so it might be a while.
I don't want to burn them.
Here we are going to 4AM.
I'm ready for...
Yes, so if you want to join in
some say hi.
World 380
and Barbarian Village Fishing Sport.
Free to play.
Well, cheeky free to play.
If I get the RuneScape...
If I do end up getting the Cookin' Cape,
we might take a break
but I wouldn't mind doing membership quests
at some point
because I've never actually done them
and I'm too scared to do them on my own
but if you guys are with me,
I'm not scared.
Yes, I think tomorrow's ASMR stream
and then day after is trying sweet.
And then after is Skyrim
and I get to rant...
No, not rant, sorry.
I get to mumble away about Skyrim for ages.
Lobsters have a 60% chance to burn at level 40.
Yeah, I'm not wasting Lobsters there.
That is rough.
That's rough.
I don't want to waste a lot of weight
because that was so much better rather than...
But we're like leveling up our fishing so easily.
Right, we are full.
Let's see, can we get two levels out of this
if we don't burn them?
It burns the first one.
Dude, waterfall fires.
It gets you to combat level 30.
What?
Really?
I know I got some quests
really give you a lot of XP
but I can't wait for those more
but I'm lucky for the time.
Maybe I'll cast a bit later.
Don't worry if you can't make it to any stream.
I think the boss will stay up
and I'm not going to be doing ear licking
because something weird is going on with YouTube.
It's going on a little weird with YouTube
and I don't know what's going on
so I'm not risking it.
As I gave you all those lobs
you can burn them if you need to.
I'd rather not waste the XP
like if it was potential full XP
like it's okay to burn these trout for example.
Oh come on, one more and I'll level up.
Okay, there we go.
20.
Aw yeah.
I want 40 before Mercy comes online.
We're under the cock roof limbs.
We're under the cock.
Empty inventory.
Let's get it.
I don't know if I should fish
or if I should honestly
just put my stuff away and pick up
but if everyone was picking up
what was put on the floor
then we wouldn't have enough trout to go around.
Where would be the first ASMR?
Hopefully YouTube will get off.
No, it's like cracking down everywhere
on anime ASMR in particular.
If you want to call it anime ASMR.
It'll be faster to loot the fish
if you just want to do a cooking.
That's what I'm thinking.
If I just do that instead.
It's nice to get the level of XP
but I'm gonna like blast the head of you reeflings
if I do that.
Would you guys be upset if I picked up trout?
Hopefully not.
It would blast me forward though.
Like, compared to everyone's level.
Go for it.
What do I need?
I just need trout.
I can't cook salmon
because I'm too low level.
Wait, examine?
No, I don't want salmon.
I can't cook it.
I want trout.
Right.
We'll see how far this gets me ahead
if I do this method where I don't fish.
Maybe you guys can drop the fish for me
and we get fish train going.
There's two more.
Right, let's cook this batch.
Let's see what happens.
I like fish.
The fish are so amazing too.
Basically, if you can't see what they're actually doing
they're assuming it's like,
Yes, I think that's what the problem is.
Why?
In real life it's fine,
but anime's getting wapped with it.
I say anime,
beach over animation.
You know what I mean.
Anyway, it starts blasting.
We're fish slaves, let's go.
Sounds a bit fishy, but okay.
Are we gonna make it?
I think we are.
I said this.
No idea when I said that.
29 already?
Oh my god, this is so fast.
I'm saying it's fast now
because it's gonna be so slow later,
but I'm happy.
I only burnt four from that batch as well.
That trout is getting cooked to perfection by me, honestly.
I see trout, I see trout.
I don't know, those are cooked trout.
Right, I'm gonna have to fish and go fish.
Oh wait, someone wants to trade with me, hold on.
You'll never guess what.
It's trout.
Oh no, you cancelled.
Oh, you don't have enough inspiratory space.
Oh no, sorry.
I don't know how many I've got left.
Like,
space for freaking...
Yeah.
Trade modified.
Blink, blink, blink.
I saw serious, literally.
I don't know if that's too much.
Oh no.
Is it?
Oh, you failed me.
Oh, my inventory.
You failed my inventory.
Thank you, beef knife.
That's terrible.
But thank you very much, we've blown.
It's running out of here playing cooking, mummy.
Literally, I'm feeding.
You don't get 100% success on trout until 49.
That's so rough.
I don't remember it being so like that.
We're already gonna level up again.
I don't know when we unlock being able to cook salmon,
but it's gonna be soon.
Gonna drop all the trout in the south spot of salmon here.
Yeah.
If you don't overlap on the salmon,
it makes it so easy to pick up.
Wow, we're already up there.
Oh my god.
Are we gonna be 50 by the time mercy?
We may, honestly.
I'm cooking by gas.
I'm cooking the best I can.
Okay, we had like way more burnt in that batch,
so it really is just randomized.
Let's empty our inventory,
and then let's grab all these trout.
I'm over there, hating.
Oh wait, sorry.
I don't know if you have to take into account
how much inventory space I have.
Okay.
Yeah.
As long as you put whatever inventory.
Oh my god.
Loves yourself six percent.
The key to power leveling is slave teamwork.
Honestly, we're doing pretty good.
We're already launching the 30s.
I think we can fly past the 40s, honestly.
Hi, Stronia.
Been away from us today.
How's it going?
We have done some quests, some free play quests.
We are currently at Barbarian Village,
and I'm currently using the reflames
to slave fish for me,
so we're getting trout,
and I'm currently leveling up like crazy right now.
Every batch of trout is making me go up another level.
I'm already 31 cooking.
We're messing around, having fun on quests.
And now I'm just doing...
I'm actually tempted to go to the Grand Exchange to...
Oh, sorry, I'm pressing the wrong button.
I'm tempted to go to the Grand Exchange
to drop the fish and rod off,
just to do full inventories as well.
I think I may.
I'm going to be right back, reflames, okay?
I'm going to drop the feathers and the fish and rod away,
that you guys can stay.
Don't worry, don't get separation anxiety.
I'll be right back.
Mummy's going to the Grand Exchange and back again.
You'll be okay.
It's fine.
Mummy will be right back.
See, I'm across the water.
Bye-bye.
I'll be right back.
Literally.
All right, I just need to drop this off
so I can have full...
No, not the book.
Not the booth.
I want the bank.
I'm trying to see if I can do it through the ceiling.
I can't.
She's never coming back.
I'm coming back.
I just need to bank the banker.
There, there, there.
See, look, empty.
Look, I'm already running back.
I'm running out of stamina.
It's okay.
I'm a wee bit tired.
I'm getting a wee bit tired.
45.
Stamina.
Wah, wah, wah.
I'm coming back.
We're orphans!
No!
You can't be, you can't be, you can't be.
See, look, look, look, I'm back.
Look, who's that?
Who's that?
That's right.
I'm on the other side of the water.
Boom.
I'm coming to pick up that trout
that's on the floor there
because there's tons.
Oh, the renaissance of the fire as well.
See, we have no home.
See, look, I'm literally right here.
Is there so dramatic?
See, of all the trout.
I'm max leveling up.
I'm going to pick up all the ones on the floor.
It's better to drop the trout.
It's faster to drop it.
Who dares the spots picking up?
It's faster to drop the trout
than it is to trade me.
Right, okay, full inventory.
We're going to be in the 50s after this.
There's no way we're not.
What were you doing with all those people
in the business room?
Dropping trout.
Trout.
Oh, pardon me.
The fish.
Trout.
You don't need to see the sea
at the end.
Dropping trout.
There's loads of words that I say like that.
I can't believe it.
Check your XP per hour on the bar.
Why is it not displaying?
This is I'm cooking.
Cooked 92, 93 per hour burn.
23% burn rate.
Why is it not displaying?
I'm cooking though.
It's not like telling me.
Literally level 20.
Hmm.
Trout.
It's short for trousers.
Oh, this one.
Oh, now we're talking.
Hold on.
Let me drop all these.
It says for not fishing.
Cooking.
Where is cooking?
Where's cooking?
Here.
Cooking's purple.
Why would it be purple honestly?
Let me grab all these trout.
There's like so much on the floor honestly.
I can't keep up.
There's so much.
It says I'm gaining 2,000 XP per hour.
Oh, there's trout here.
Trout, trout, trout.
No, the trout.
Not the fire.
Now I've got to fill inventory.
Let's see.
XP gained 16 hour, roughly 2k,
but it's probably going to go up for a bit
because I'm not being done fill trout and XP left.
Oh no, it's getting covered up by the freaking layer.
I'm coming back in.
We're at Barbarian Village
at the free play fishing spot.
But I think we're definitely higher.
Yeah, this is going up.
It says we're now 2.3 per hour.
It's because we've not done it for an hour, but...
Once we have...
It says...
Actually, I don't know if you can see that.
Of course not.
It literally says like six actions left
and then we've leveled up, so that's really good.
I like that.
It kind of puts into perspective
how much you need to do in order to get next.
Next.
You can write...
Literally level 33.
You can reset.
I'll just leave that.
That's the only burnt two.
Oh, burnt three that time.
They don't burn three that time.
I'm so MLG pro.
Oh, I shouldn't maybe drop the trout here.
I don't know when I can start cooking salmon,
but it should be sent to you.
She needs that raw fish meat.
Are you treating me fish?
Oh no, I don't have inventory for that.
Is that tuna?
I'm pretty sure that's tuna.
Sorry, I don't have any...
Oh, you're giving me three tuna?
I don't even think I'm like leveling enough to do that.
What are you?
Use tuna on the fire.
Oh, I can.
Oh, it's not tuna.
Oh, what is it?
It's tuna.
Oh, burnt it.
It's 100 XP.
Wait, that's more XP than salmon.
Okay.
Reset.
It seems to have bugged out.
Okay, I'll reset.
Sorry, reset.
Oh, I know it's not the bomb.
Oh, you can actually see it though, no?
Tuna max and right now,
Manstronia just really...
That you and my definition of fun are completely different.
I mean, I'm literally becoming a little chef.
I'm able to feed all the reeflings like this now.
Oh, she'll be getting all the thingies.
Oh, it says I have nine actions left.
That's so cool.
That says like you literally have a number.
Because soon it will be like 100 left
and then it'll be 1000 left
and I'll be like, that's fine.
Her numbers are going way up.
Literally, this is like...
If you like slow incremental games that feel satisfying,
RuneScape is definitely for you.
I've never 99 something
and I want to do it
and you guys can hold me accountable for it.
I'll literally tuna max and so whatever.
Who's got trout up for me?
No, that's cooked trout.
That's raw trout, okay.
Oh wait, is this accept trade?
Do you got more tuna?
It's the tuna man.
Of course, it's fun.
Numbers goes up.
Don't for me and we all get literally...
Wow, thank you so much for the tuna.
How is everyone today?
Someone asks.
We're...
We're tuna max...
No, not tuna.
Oh, I was talking.
I was taking...
Are you squiddin' me right now?
Brian!
We love when numbers go up,
so have some numbers.
Oh, money's different.
Thank you for the tip, don't do that.
We do love money going up
in incremental video games.
We're playing Cooking Sim
and it's amazing.
Hope...
Hope your day is going well.
Smile if you see.
Always be nice to people.
I am burning the absolute living
daylights out of this tuna.
I'm so sorry.
I've just wasted all that tuna.
So sorry.
I have been here for like four hours.
Oh, I keep messing it up.
I wonder if you could sell cooked tuna
for decent money.
I don't think it's a cheap fish.
I seem to think like...
Alright, raw trout time.
Uh, fishing levels?
Uh, um...
Anya?
What the fuck?
Runescape message saying
I'm going to be logged in
in 30 minutes, max six hours play.
Wait, is that real?
Wait, you got more tuna already?
Wait, you can't have.
How are you doing?
Are you peddling tuna to me
to level me up faster?
I feel like I'm wasting all your
tuna.
Oh, no.
Wait, are we finally doing it?
Are we...
Are we got tuna slave runners?
Yeah, it's like there was log is real.
Wait, am I going to be booted out
or because I bought membership
I'm not going to be booted out.
I have plenty of tuna.
I could literally buy a million.
Hey, Strony.
Am I in trouble for cooking
my own food tonight?
Does that mean I could just jump
into the kitchen?
You're allowed to make it.
He...
That is messed up.
I'm not a child.
Literally why is the game
doing it for like bandwidth issues?
If you're a free member,
they're like, oh, we've had enough of you.
Strony becomes a master chef
but can't fight a rat.
No, it was the cow that was going to
kill me.
It was a baby cow.
And you just log in right back after.
That's bizarre.
No, my...
What?
Well, it says we've been up for seven
hours or is it because I got logged out
when I went away for like a cup of tea
and that?
I wonder if that's why.
Hold on.
Is tuna max...
Is tuna max through there?
I've got Buddha at one point.
Yeah, you've just been DCing a lot.
Okay, every time I go for Tinkle Winkle,
I've been DCed so it doesn't count.
How much do you care about doing
the proper way?
I think I'm supposed to do wine next.
Someone says, hi, Emmy.
Is the Emmy imposter here?
Where's the Emmy imposter?
Oh, there it is.
You changed your name to Emmy Bizoon Game.
Level 113.
That's a big account, honestly.
Okay, let me grab this.
Emmy's...
Emmy's a RuneScape nerd.
No, it's not the real Emmers,
but someone likes her,
so I'm glad someone enjoys her as much to do that.
Emmy the Goal, honestly.
What's the fit on Emmy?
Oh, they changed her hair to look like
her pumpkins and everything.
And give her a skirt.
That's supposed to be her blue shorts.
Okay, okay, okay.
Let him get up, let him get up.
Where is that?
We're already level 35.
We should've came here, like, from the beginning.
We wouldn't even have had to do anything.
Yeah, and that baby cow has been caught in front of a king.
Hydration check.
I'm actually running out of water.
What's mercy, one hour?
Wah.
It gives me, like, relief drink and water
for a millisecond,
and then I feel the pain of talking again.
Let's do this raw trip.
Raw trip.
Oh, sorry.
I keep forgetting Mr. Tuna Man.
Sorry, guys.
I got, like, three space.
That tuna man going ham.
Oh my God, that's so much money.
Absolutely nothing.
And then the value on your side
is just, like, losing horrifically.
I can do one more inventory,
and then I have to do some rune crafting
for my clan skull.
Okay, thank you so much.
Excuse me, ma'am.
We had to level up to 20 fishing to start fishing here.
Yes, you have to go back to the Castello.
Good luck.
Thank you so much for the...
Thanks for all the fish.
I'm pretty sure that is the ending to a movie
that Bilbo was in that I haven't watched yet.
I can't remember.
But it goes thanks for all the fish.
Level 36.
Oh my God.
The tuna, literally a hundred of pop as well, is crazy.
He keeps in the bunny soup girl
turning into a guy.
Oh, never mind.
It's because they're dancing on each other.
Hitchhiker's guide.
Yes, I've not seen that.
Good Lord, you're still alive?
Yeah, we're tuna maxing.
We're currently level 36.
And cooking is that purple one right there.
Here.
We're level 36.
Apparently your egg steeper hour is like
freaking 56K with the tuna.
It's like going up like crazy.
So much tuna.
You know what's really nice?
Tuna, cucumber, meal.
Like uncrusted bread.
Oh, no, no, no.
It's delicious.
Can we cook raw salmon yet?
Let me check.
Use the salmon on the fire.
What's everyone's opinion on anchovy pizza?
Oh, I can cook salmon.
Okay.
I can pick up salmon now as well.
Right.
I'll pick up salmon and trout so I can just like do it all.
Level 50 is about 100K egg fee total.
What's my total egg fee?
I am one fourth of the way to level 50.
I'm not sure I can do it before Maryse goes online.
Oh, I'll be cutting it close, I think.
Oh, no, I can't.
I would have to be tuna maxing.
Unless the salmon does it, I'm not sure.
Unless the salmon does it.
And if I stop burning everything.
I'm scooping up all this trout.
I'm scooping it up.
My inventory is getting so full.
Someone's got a mini cliff.
No, but that is huge.
It's so fast with the salmon as well.
Oh, five more salmon and then level up again.
Oh, come on, you can do it.
Two more.
One more.
Yes!
30 freaking six.
37, sorry.
I know numbers sometimes.
Oh, we are tuna maxing.
We are fish maxing out the wazoo right now.
Stronny.
You can do it, Stronny.
Cook this, Galea's base starts late.
There's neither motor.
We're going to do it, we're going to do it.
Tuna is more XP than salmon.
Salmon's more XP than trout.
But unfortunately I'm still at the burning stage,
so I'm not maximising my inventory right now.
I don't think there's any other quests that give cooking XP
that I know of other than...
There's probably a ton of members' quests
that do have, like, cooking XP.
But as it stands right now,
we'll do full inventory of raw trout.
But once we start, once we stop burning,
then we can do, like, max inventory XP gains,
which is really handy down there.
Who took that little bit sound?
Who taking my trout?
You need my trout.
Salmon might honestly be better rates
when you factor in the burn rate.
Mmm.
It's possible.
Someone else here is, like, snatching up the salmon,
which is fine.
Honestly, it's not like the trout is, like,
bad or anything.
I know we'll make it to 40.
The question is how far in?
True mummy gamey here, honestly.
Click simulator.
But it's so good though!
Oh, like, RuneScape is so nostalgic.
Look, it's like, I love how the Rune plug-in,
or whatever it's called, RuneLight,
literally absolutely annihilating out here.
Salmon's success rate at 38 is 74%.
Mmm, that's not bad.
Everyone in four?
Everyone in four.
Okay, who has the XL spreadsheet?
An optimal fish cookin'.
The best member's quest for it is the family crest,
so you get gloves that would just burn it.
Oh, I've never done, I don't know what that is actually.
It sounds difficult though,
because for something to be such a good item,
I feel like they would have put it behind,
like, really difficult quests.
Oh, if I can pick up a few of these salmon,
I'll make the photos.
RuneLight is insane.
I can never play with a vanilla client again.
Get mugged.
I suppose if you want, like, super nostalgic,
just leave it as is.
Right, we'll do the trout first,
because I want, like, I don't want to
have higher rate of burning the salmon,
since it offers more.
Do you just stream forever, strong?
I just really enjoy streaming,
and I like hanging out with refunds,
especially on days where we get to play a multiplayer game,
where we get to be together.
I really like that.
I'm actually going off a bit earlier than expected.
When Mercy comes online in an hour,
I'm raiding into her.
And the only reason I'm not doing an endurance today,
hmm, is because my voice is very sore,
and I have an ASMR stream tomorrow,
so I'm gonna have to try and rest it a bit better
than usual, than the usual
when a game is this old.
Yes, if my voice wasn't sore,
I unironically just do 12 hours again.
I'm sorry.
I would. I said it.
I said what we're all thinking.
You all know what...
Oh no, I didn't cook those raw salmon.
Silly Billy.
Oh no, it's giving me the actual salmon.
Ah, oh well.
I'm not salmon maxing.
I'm not a real salmon max, so I can't believe it.
I'm sorry you had to all find out this way.
Let's do a try.
We're doing...
We're getting pretty good at try.
We're getting pretty good.
Over eight hours not endurance.
Come on now.
I don't know, I feel like...
You know when you have like a regular nine to five job?
Like, obviously I had quite a few.
And I just put it in perspective.
Like, I'm literally memeing about on a video game.
I get to like play and like have fun times with you.
And it just like...
Oh my god, wait.
Is this Trinna Man back?
Hold on, is Trinna Man back?
Trinna, I thought you had to go do some things
with your clan or something.
Oh my god, we're Trinna Maxing again.
Oh!
Half a million?
Are you sure?
I mean, I ain't gonna say no.
How are you all so rich?
Where are you...
What are you doing to make money in RuneScape?
What are the ways to buy some good fish with it?
Thank you, Reefling.
Oh my gosh, when the time comes.
Yes, when I don't burn stuff.
How...
I have three billion on an Iron Man account.
How do you make money in RuneScape?
Seriously?
Trinna Man!
How?
How do you make money on RuneScape?
I don't know how.
I'm gonna put this money in the bank so I'm not full.
The more you play, the higher stats you get raised.
Strawni get...
get hella high level so we can do raids.
Oh!
What's raiding?
Oh, you guys teach me how to raid.
International Bank of Strawni, honestly though.
Oh, I wanted to get a pet that looked like you guys as well.
That was another goal.
So 99...
Um...
99, um...
Cookin'.
And then I want to get a pet that looks like you guys.
But I don't know how the pets work.
Golly, double neck.
Okay.
I'm gonna go put this in the bank.
No, VC.
Math wants to choose.
Math, I don't have much inventory.
I'm sorry.
Oh yeah, give me them...
Sardines?
You giving me...
Oh!
Oh yeah, we got pike ladies and gentlemen.
Get that cooked.
Get that cooked on that fire thing.
Thank you.
Get that cooked.
Oh, it made me 39!
Economic Dragon Bitter.
Not to be confused with the German word bitter,
which means please, I think.
Bitter?
No.
I don't think that's what that means in German.
Hee-hee-hee.
Also high level drops peaking.
No, I couldn't do peaking.
Oh, I'm coming back.
Don't worry, Reeflings, I'm coming back.
Mummy's putting the money in the bank.
I'm coming back, okay?
Mummy needs to pay rent, so I'm putting it in the bank.
We need to rent that location out for only us.
Bitter means please, okay?
No, Reeflings, don't cry, I'm coming back.
Sorry, I forgot to say that, I needed to go.
I'm putting this in the bank, okay?
Look, bank.
And look at that.
We're max.
Look how much fish we've got.
200 raw ship.
600 salmon.
450 swordfish.
500 lobster's raw tuna.
Like, there's so much.
I don't want to burn any of this, though.
Bitter means you are welcome.
Oh, Dankeschon.
Bitter.
Okay, there we go.
There's a sentence that you could use in.
Oh, no, Dankeschon?
Or Dankeschon?
No, I think it has a kh.
Don't worry, Reeflings, I'm coming back.
Look, see, I'm coming, I'm coming.
Look, look, look, you're gonna render again.
Yay, Reeflings!
All the Reeflings are here.
You've got money to burn all that fish.
You're loaded, holy.
Literally, a Reefling gave me 10 million.
Another gave me a million.
One just gave me half a million there.
But I don't want to waste it.
I don't want to waste the money.
Oh, sorry, sorry, I accept.
Sorry, I'm fish-maxing, okay?
Where's Mommy?
Mommy's back, Mommy's back.
How much XP do you get for this?
I didn't even know you could fish it here.
Can't believe someone went...
What?
I can't believe someone went more dry
than I did on a dragonfish.
How much did we get?
Oh, we got A.A. for these?
These are the same as mine?
We cease to exist when you leave us.
No!
Reeflings!
Bitter means a bunch of things, including both.
Okay.
My German knowledge is expanding.
I know to expand
my Puerto Rican knowledge.
That's all you get.
Okay.
I don't know how many pets I got.
Can you own all the pets that won?
Oh, they're like little symbols to show what won.
There's 24 pets!
What?
How?
How's there 24?
There are 59 pets?
What?
That's a lot.
Yeah, especially now because I have a
chain made in a void worker jam.
Is that how you attract pets to you?
You wear jewelry?
They're like, ooh, shiny.
Is there a magpie pet?
What have we got?
Oh, actually, I've picked the place clean.
That's how much I'm fish-maxing.
There's nothing on the ground.
I've picked it clean.
Oh, wait.
There's a trade.
Ah!
I'm missing.
A rubbish aimbot.
Whoa, yeah.
17.
39.
All salmon.
We're all in on salmon.
Salmon cook and run.
We're almost level 40.
40's like a melody and...
Oh, sorry.
I just punched them.
I can hear that.
There's a little anime there.
Stronti only just starts streaming.
She's already a 1% earner in this game.
Wait, really?
Is level 40 a 1% thing?
Like, hardly anyone gets to 40 in something?
Shorty's like a melody and...
I can't keep growl.
Got me singing like...
Na na na na na.
Every day.
Like my eyes.
Is it like my eyeballs stuck on the plate?
Those bars were good.
She punched the refline.
I'm sorry.
There's a fishing pit,
but you have to be on a member's role to get it,
and scaling pits are especially good.
He means the money to do some...
We hit 40!
Actually so good.
I might make one last cup of tea.
We need a lock-in.
We need a lock-in, okay.
Lobster time.
Oh no, I'm not gonna waste a lobster.
That's crazy.
I'm not gonna waste the lobsters.
Oh!
I mean, unless you give me lobsters,
that's different.
If you give me lobsters to waste,
I'm not sure what my fricking rate is gonna be.
Burn them all.
Oh, I kicked my first one correctly!
Wah!
120?
Oh no!
They're getting burned.
I know you can't see them over my...
My heart.
Can I move myself over just a tiny bit more?
I don't want it.
Actually, yeah.
Yeah?
Okay, yeah, that's better.
You can, like, really see the inventory and stuff.
Learning.
We're gonna keep learning.
If all the boys get 40 fishing,
must the point will be for pure lobsters.
Wait, you wanna do lobsters?
Wait, you guys stay up all night
just so you can get 40 fishing?
So we can do lobster runs?
120 is a lot.
Look at the success rate, though.
What does it say?
Oh, the success rate is going up.
It's 20%.
What's that?
Oh, that's mine.
That's mine.
Oh, rest well, those two sleep.
I'm sorry, I streamed so long.
For those of you who do need to leave,
please don't worry.
I'm literally doing this until the end.
We're gonna read it in a mercy,
because my poor voice is feeling it, Mr. Prev.
There's no way you already have
more freaking lobsters for me or something.
Oh, okay, okay.
We go pick, go pick.
This is crazy.
Can you get in trouble by Jagex
for doing this?
I can stay until 40, fish up or lobsters.
No, that's crazy.
I'm at 31 fishing at the moment.
I got distracted watching you
forgot to go back more.
Goodnight, sleepers, rest well.
Never can see how much seafood you are wasting.
No!
I just meant for the lobsters.
That one.
Long streams are good,
because I can catch them when I wake up.
I will sleep when I'm beat
by drowning by more domination of the cheese.
Oh, my God, we're almost 41.
Oh, freaking crazy.
We just wear a 40.
Sleep is a construct.
Construct is a government I've never given.
Oh, my gosh.
Can we do it?
Can we make it 41 already?
One more?
Don't burn them.
No, don't burn them.
I should burn it.
40 freaking one.
No!
This is so good.
Oh, my God.
You're already trading with me.
I hope I can't get in trouble by jargates from this.
Stuff like this can run the game for new players,
so be careful about donations for new players long term.
I have played,
I do have a basic concept of the game,
but if you're going to ask me to do
dungeoning and stuff,
I could not tell you where the gargoyles are,
but apparently gargoyles.
Hey, Strony, how do you get a fishing rod?
I've never tried this before.
Aw, you tiny culls.
You would have to level up
with that fishing net you got from Tutorial Island,
but you can't use it here.
You would have to go back to Lumbridge.
This is Lumbridge, where you came from.
You can use the magic spell to teleport,
and you have to do net fishing here until 20.
And then you can come here for a fly fishing.
I'm so sorry, Little Reefling.
There are gates to level up on fishing.
They're probably a lot better than my method,
but that's why I've always used it with the kids.
Gargoyles are decent money for mid players,
but 75 slayers is probably the slowest of them even.
That burn rate is looking a bit rough on the lobster,
so I'm not going to lie.
Anyone got some feathers on them?
So, well, I guess that's all great.
Aw, thank you, Little Reefling.
That burn rate is looking rough.
Oh, my God, what should I do?
I feel about it.
How expensive are the lobsters?
I feel like they're probably breaking through.
We're burnt through the fish already.
No, we're not.
I tell a lie.
Let's forget.
Who are you coming so fast?
You just handed me them.
Is there a bank nearby?
I thought the bank was over there.
Am I going crazy?
Is there a bank up there?
He's just disappeared again.
Ageville has a bank.
Oh, I'll make sure you...
Call meville,
because, I don't know, there's something.
If I could trade.
I'm so sorry.
Wait, I'll trade.
I'm sorry.
I'll trade.
Okay, I'll trade.
Bro's hacking.
Can you even hack in RuneScape?
That sounds like it's nice and possible,
because of the way the server is.
Call meville, because I'm edging.
Yes!
I came up with that myself.
I did.
It's true.
You could start using a range closer
to the bank rather than the fire rate,
since you don't fish in anymore.
Probably.
That's very true.
Oh, that burn rate is rough on those lobbies.
Every lobster that we burn is a missing,
like, 120, which is, like,
so frigging thingy.
I lied.
I made it.
Wait, there's another refling.
There's the strategy.
Hold on.
Wait, you've got lobster runs as well?
Whoa!
Isn't this not, like, thousands,
like, thousands of gold?
Am I not going mental?
I feel like this is, like, thousands.
Go ahead and run.
Energy needs to recharge.
Whoa, we got a full shoot.
Five in a row.
42!
It depends on how fast you want to get this level,
but Bar Village is more...
The most...
The most cooking ranges.
You can make a million per hour?
A million XP per hour?
Strony, even if it says
and you've already been given millions?
Honestly.
If you take the exclamation mark,
praise?
What?
Stop!
Did you make me...
Did you just make me fall for something obvious?
I don't know.
Yeah, I spent 160 on 2k.
That's, like, two voxels.
You have to take that.
I'm afterward.
Oh, knee drop, knee drop.
Oh, yeah, that was a much better lobster
cooking batch than the previous one,
the other one that I absolutely cooked with them.
Ooh, fishy.
Oh, right, okay, take that.
Let's try and do this.
Exclamation mark, praise?
Let it all be set to error.
Oh!
It worked!
Oh, there are 150 a pack?
Ooh.
If I buy feathers from people we drop on?
Okay, 300k.
Oh, great.
Right, don't buy any more fish,
cos it's literally I've got
less than 50 minutes now.
I'm gonna go quickly grab a bottle of water.
Cos I'm so thirsty.
I don't need to,
I don't need to.
Ooh.
Wow!
Ooh, ooh, I hear burning noises.
I hear burning noises.
Cos we're burning deficies.
Right, I've got a new bowl of water.
I'm so hydrated, but I don't want to pee, I want to fish max.
I need to fish max, you don't understand.
I'm fish maxing, you wouldn't get it.
I have lobby maxing, you wouldn't get it.
You wouldn't understand, Mum.
Mum, I need membership.
I'll give it a try, I'll be back in a minute.
Go for it.
I've only been listening to ASMR for about a minute,
so I'm excited for starting ASMR.
I definitely am not the best.
I would say like, Mercy and Icy are like super professional.
Super idol.
43!
And we've had a lot of two-stacked...
Oh, I was about to say, we've got two-stacked
for all of the lobbies not being burnt.
Spoke too soon there.
Hydration check.
Wow.
You know, as much as the chef hat and the apron are made out of gold,
I don't think it's actually making me a better chef.
How much longer before you have to leave?
Is there a exact time?
Mercy is coming on in 45 minutes.
I'm going to redirect into her because I need to do vocal rest
before the ASMR stream tomorrow.
And it hurts to talk right now, which is a shame.
It's literally the only reason I'm going offline.
I probably didn't during the stream every single day if I killed it, honestly.
But my voice is sore and I need to be quiet for the ASMR.
Tomorrow's going to be a short...
No, you guys are so quick on it.
This is crazy.
It doesn't make sense.
They're gold, literally.
Drink some nice hot tea.
Yes, I've had too much tea today.
Because I put honey in my tea,
it gets, like, sickly if I have too much of it,
so I have to swap to water only.
What's your target that you're going for this stream?
I wanted to get 50, but I don't think it's possible because of time.
I didn't realise how fast cooking the fish was going to be
if I wasn't, like, doing those quests.
But I had fun doing quests for the reason, so actually, I don't really regret it at all.
I'll be cutting it close.
Like, if we're literally, like, a couple of minutes away, then I'll do it.
But, unfortunately, my voice is, like...
Yeah.
And most of all, I felt that one literally...
I do look stylish, though.
I mean, look at that.
Something a little cosy.
Look at the detail in my eyes and everything.
The polys are the favourites all the time.
Honey in tea is good.
Maybe I'll add less honey.
I don't know.
I feel, like, sickly if I...
I don't know, I just can't.
It's just not working.
I know you can have those throat sweets,
but I don't know if they actually do anything or just, like, make my teeth feel a little sugary.
It's, like, my biggest frickin' thing.
Wait, hold on.
Am I taking this?
I can't remember who I keep taking off of.
I'm sorry for whoever the other lobster runners, like, I can't remember between...
200k feathers under me.
Damn.
Damn, you're in a wedding dress and everything.
What the heck?
All of your black hair, this is cute.
And your little cape.
Oh, I forgot to get us green capes.
Oops.
We'll do the next thing.
Can you say throat sweets again?
Yeah, throat sweets.
They, like, help with your throat when you feel sick or whatever.
Or if you've got strain, I guess.
Are you still streaming?
Yeah, um, we've got roughly 40 minutes.
And then it's Mercy's time.
We're gonna redirect into Mercy.
Bon bon.
Oh, I'm making an absolute mockery of this one.
I don't think I'm gonna burn it, alright.
Yeah.
Oh, we're close to the 44, though.
Bicola.
Wait, Bicola?
Wait, what's Bicola?
I can hear that, Bicola.
What's that mean, chan?
Huh?
Eto?
What's that?
Bicola.
A tape of throat lozenger.
Oh, it's a cough drug.
Bicola is a brand of lozenger.
Oh, okay, okay.
Oh, sorry.
Wah.
Here you go.
Lobster runner.
I can't believe it.
Might as well do 99 room crafting while we're at it.
You guys will make it super easy.
It's the comical jingle that was very common.
Oh, it's a commercial jingle.
Sorry.
Ah, I see, I see, I see.
But not I see smokers.
But I see.
There's a new...
New room craft minigame, and it's fun.
Anyone else able to see the feathers yet?
No, you might have to pick them up in case it's too much when you defawn.
No feathers.
Yeah, hopefully they don't defawn,
because 20k feathers isn't cheap.
Did you time the six feathers?
Johnny's so cool and got excited.
This is Coca-Cola.
It's so much.
How long does it take after doffin'?
I thought it was 60 seconds.
If it's been 60 seconds, I would just scoop them back up again,
because I would hate them to...
No, not the headbinds!
What a book.
Wah.
Level 40 fricking four.
If I could stop fricking burning them lobsters,
they'll...
Wah.
They'll accept trade, accept trade.
We're getting there though.
Do you have less burn chance on a...
a grill thing?
An oven?
A grill thing.
30 seconds to appear to others,
three minutes to despawn.
We're learning.
We're learning the ways a burn stage is done.
No only in whose side it is.
Wah.
Range and fire are the same kissing chance, mostly.
Okay, there's no point.
I was like, maybe we should move this production line,
but...
I think the rooflings are just fishing away.
They're just having a good time.
We definitely need to level ourselves up,
because we're the target for a lot of NPCs
when we're trying to travel through areas.
The stream's ending in 40 minutes.
Does that mean brush teeth intend?
Yes!
We have to brush our teeth.
Okay, thank goodness I didn't make another teeth,
because I wouldn't have been able to brush my teeth.
If you're having...
If you want to brush your teeth with us
for your enameled...
Don't eat or drink fizzy juice.
You can have water for the next 30 minutes,
but you're not to brush your teeth if you've eaten
after 30 minutes,
because it hurts your enamel
rather than helping it.
I think that's my only note
if you want to brush your teeth with us.
Not so fun story.
My brother once choked on one
of those throat sweeps
and helped with the throat throat.
Ooh, that's terrifying.
45?
We're at 61 8 feet.
Oh, goodness.
We may actually make the 50.
You know that.
Ah, my throat farted when I swallowed it.
Did you hear that?
That was like an internal throat fart.
I said that!
1 in 3.
Oh, baby.
He learned so much from this educational
and professional streamer.
That takes me back to the toothbrush
somewhere.
We are so going to get 50
before Mercy comes on and makes me funny.
Oh, Mercy's actually...
I think she's decorating alternative
outfits for us.
So...
We are in...
Have our lobster reserves ran dry.
Have I perished all the lobsters
for sale in the Grand Exchange?
Oh, unless.
Unless.
You guys are sweating to get me to level 99.
You're actually so kind.
I just want to say a special thank you
for those of you who are like
unironically feeding me.
This is going to make the school
way faster doing this.
Hmm.
You'd say that Stronny's a really good drop.
What?
Do you think she'd make you one of those?
What is going on?
No stops on this lobster train.
Literally.
I know the fishing spot.
Nearly one million XP an hour.
Stop.
Is that it?
Unlucky.
I love stories.
I suppose if I didn't burn them,
that's very plausible.
Every stack is like...
What, 26 inventory?
Like...
I think five tables are shooting it.
I don't know.
With some tick manipulation.
I don't know what the tick rate manipulation
stuff means.
I hear it all the time though.
It's like, oh you just got to make sure
you do this on the tick
and you have to eat.
You have to eat the food on the tick.
Oh, can I swap out prayer?
I need a prayer flick.
Like, I'm like, what does any of this mean?
You're crazy.
Crazy.
Also, for those of you using runelight,
if you don't want an item name to show up,
can hold,
alt,
and write...
the irons here.
We're getting the real stress here.
Being an apron has always been a dream of mine.
The game runs on 0.62nd increments called ticks.
That's it.
Oh!
That basic...
Okay, that just like explains everything.
That's it.
That's all it took.
One sentence and it all makes sense.
Okay, because I was like,
prayer, I need prayer flick on this tick.
Like, over prayer flick.
I'm like, what?
I'm not, I'm even sure that's supposed to be
having the games played.
I don't know.
Did the devs intend that?
But they never patched it out.
So I guess prayer
flicking is the right way to go.
Because prayer drains so fast.
I'm getting new brain cells just from streaming.
Level 47?
No.
Oh wait, sorry, 46.
Two more.
If I don't burn these.
If I don't burn this one.
46.
Oh my gosh.
We're so MLG pro.
Look at me, bro.
MLG pro.
Let me see.
Oh my god, my tummy's rumbling.
You could hear that over the background.
Wow.
I'm literally slid.
It's not intended,
but Jagex just accepted.
I was going to say,
if they didn't,
whenever like something gets discovered,
like, so this is for the overwatch players,
but Mercy had a guardian angel leap.
And it got discovered
and it was never patched out the game,
which meant it was intended,
even though it was never described.
So that's how I take it.
If the devs don't patch it out,
it's allowed, basically.
Once you get to level 92,
you're halfway there.
Yay.
Anyway, congrats, dumb dumb.
This was the stream I was looking forward.
The less,
but ended up probably being one of the funniest,
really?
It's just me receiving,
like, tons of in-game currency for doing nothing.
But please don't worry,
if you're interested in more,
like, multiplayer games
where we can play together,
I definitely am doing,
like, a whole variety of things going on.
I would definitely, like,
other ones, like...
No, that's not what's official name.
What's the name of the game?
Fall Guys.
I wanted to give Fortnite a chance.
Apparently, Fortnite
has added, like, different game modes.
Call of Duty has apparently introduced prop one.
I don't know if we could...
Oh, there's a captain.
Do we do the captain mini-quest?
I don't know if we do the captain one.
At the Fortnite metal path.
I just shit out my hands.
It's...
Is it bad?
Is it a bad quest?
Is it the captain,
or is it a good one?
It's quick.
Okay, if it's quick, let's try it.
Problem is, these old-time...
Uh, sure, I'll help you unlock your chest.
There are three columns.
What you need to do is match up
each picture on the column.
A bar,
a ring,
and a bowl.
Oh, got a wee golden ring!
Um...
What'd I do with it?
I already have a diamond ring on
from a wreathling,
so I can't take it off.
Oh, I'm sorry, sorry.
I completely forgot
we're trying to lobster max right now.
Oops.
One less space,
one less space,
because I'll drop the golden ring.
Oh, I could have gave you
the golden ring, actually,
because lobsters trading there.
The ring's your problem now.
Captain is the worst random?
No.
The sign which lady is,
she never gives you anything good.
Hail divers,
mollo player.
Is that easy to say at all?
Well, sign which lady
and quiz master already.
Quiz master's rubbish,
I don't like that one.
Uh, for...
Stroudy, please don't play Fortnite.
Oh no, what's wrong?
It's bad game.
Get that steal,
but yeah,
I think it's kind of drop in,
drop out.
Um,
I would like to play among us
so I can start screaming at you,
and I'll be like,
it's red, it's red,
wreathlings,
you don't believe me,
it's red.
But we'll have to,
we'll have to try it
and see what happens.
Okay, I'm done.
I'm so, I'm so emoji.
Look at me like,
I'm literally hovering
ready for the trade offer.
Like, yeah, yeah,
give me the trade offer.
Oh, look, your problem now.
There you go.
Oh, your problem now.
Oh, yours golden rings yours.
Thank you for all the lobsters.
Among us.
You've never played among us?
Deep Rock Galactica.
We can play Deep Rock together.
Can I force you guys
to play that Mains of Moria game with me?
I'm too scared to ask the girls to play
in case they absolutely despise it.
So,
although I may be able to convince Sheebie.
There's a Mains of Moria game.
It's like,
it's literally Deep Rock Galactica,
but Lord of the Rings,
Quidditch.
You want to try Warframe.
It's freeing up to four man squads.
Ooh.
I think you can force us
to do anything you want to try.
I haven't ever heard of it.
I've never got advertised well.
The only reason I've popped up for me
is because I'm on Lord of the Rings
side of TikTok.
So, if there's anything Lord of the Rings,
Lord of the Rings related.
Oh my God, we're going to level up.
40 freakin' seven.
Oh my gosh.
This is getting
insane.
Oh crap.
Thank you.
Thank you, Reflings.
I appreciate it.
Literally everyone feeding me.
We're all like,
fishing away, leveling up and stuff.
I think we'll play
RuneScape during,
on the third week of streams,
I think we might do a double RuneScape
to make sure we really get there,
XP-wise.
I'll break it up in between the week
just so it's not like a full day of RuneScape
and then one right after it.
Because I know RuneScape isn't for everyone.
I know it might be a bit
of a snooze fest,
but for me it's so satisfying.
Like, bigger number?
Bigger number?
Big number.
Like, it's like really good for me.
But I guess maybe watching it
it might be better,
like if it was a compilation
or like a highlight, you know.
Still do Warframe.
It's the worst game to be a new player
and 100% confusing
and there's a neat tutorial.
Deep Rock Season 5 is a bit
of a horror show right now.
What is it?
Number go up.
RuneScape is definitely a talking stream,
like a datzu, like back and forth.
I like meme-ing with one of each other.
I'm like learning about the game and stuff.
I don't know enough about RuneScape.
Literally, I was in kindergarten when I said
the best I did as a kid was do cooking
and then probably do 40
and then that's the best.
I actually don't know how the game works.
So much lobster.
Rock lobster.
Nuh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh.
Uh, b52 is anyone?
The Reflane is,
could you trouble you to play
Voices of the Void?
I don't know what that is.
Is it an MMO?
Or like single?
Or what?
What kind of game?
game. This review thing is a deep one. Final Fantasy 14. I was gonna give it a shot but
yeah. I never ended up playing it. I don't know if they say they roleplay a lot in it.
Honestly, I don't mind. It'll be fun to roleplay.
A roleplay is what though. I don't know what a roleplay is. I've had a choice to roleplay something.
I don't know. Save Heroes is free to play. Super hero animal. Oh, I think I said I wanted
to play Marvel Rivals. We might play that but I don't know if it's in beta or if that's
it fully out. I don't know. Oh, my tummy's wobbling. I don't know what to do.
Strony and her 100 husbands. Isn't this the life though? You know, you have to wait to
get your one-on-one attention but then that makes it so much more worth it. Why do I keep
fricking snail blinking? I'm gonna have to change that. Please stop blinking one at a time.
I'm gonna have to make the sensitivity different. Any trenches in trying Lord of the Rings online?
Like Shadow of the Rings online? You mean Elden Scrolls online? Or is there like a Lord
of the Rings online I have no idea about? I'm actually playing Final Fantasy while watching
the stream. Speaking of fact, cannot decide. I work in accounting and I'm the only guy
with nine girls in the office. Hey, what a ladies man. Check it out. You get a nice view
all day long. There's a Lord of the Rings. Maybe I've seen it and I'm just being a dum-dum.
I can't recall it off the toilet in the head. Should I move? I feel like I'm like in the
way here. Oh, I can't even access the fire. Oh, I can't even access the fire though. Dum-dum.
Oops, sorry. I'm already accepted. It's pretty old. Does Lord of the Rings online still even
have server? Yeah, I don't even think I've seen any gameplay of it. Unless I have in
my brains just not putting them two together. 171 successful cooks to go. Not sure how many
could in burnings, so probably ten more traps. Wow. We're at 81,000 XP on cooking. We need
20k more when it's mercy. 20 minutes on mercy. I don't know. If we could stop burning. There's
no way you're still headbanging over there. Are you not tired of clicking the button?
Brightly Lord of the Rings is microtransaction to heck. Okay, that's probably why I haven't
heard about it because everyone just saw how much of a grab it was. I lost my little face. Yeah,
maybe I am. Maybe I'm just headbanging. I mean, barbed village is a thing. Yeah, we might maybe
do a watch along of stuff for the later levels. Oh, 48, man. That's so good. Literally, I was aiming
for 40, and I'm so happy with what we've got. Obviously, special shout out to the reflins who
are supplying a ridiculous amount of money and fish and everything to me because it is insane.
And literally, the reflins down here that are just chilling and fishing away, they're just having
a good time leveling up fishing. What are your fishing levels? Hold on, let me type. Fishing
level check. Fishing level check. I'm still struggling early game fishing and cooking
so the lumberjoo shrimp, it takes forever to net some shrimp and then you burn them to heck.
If you guys want to catch up to her, I'll give you what I have left after stream.
Out of curiosity, are you avoiding profanity for any reason? A little bit. The AI can tell,
like the AI can read what my voice is, so I kind of try and swap out words over time
because I am quite outrageous at certain sections, so I try and tone it down as long
as you get a good 80-20 mix, then overall you're fine, which is why I swap out words sometimes.
I have enough eggs to be for night night twice, unfortunately.
A little refling's cute surprise of the stream. Oh, we keep burning them.
Oh lobbies, you're not as easy to cook as I thought. My little, my caviar.
But yes, I maybe need to think of, like, maybe we watch movies whilst we runescape
in the background or something. I mean, I can do a set of watch one movie,
obviously I can't show it, but I can show the timer so as we jump in at any point.
Maybe Harry Potter, do you guys like Harry Potter?
I've watched it through for the first time, a couple years back, I've not seen the full thing.
Not particularly, okay, maybe not, sorry, sorry, maybe not, maybe it's a girl's movie. Apologies.
Is there a C- John Wick series? We'll watch the John Wick series movies, that would be a good one.
I think everyone who's ready for RuneScape and Chill, honestly, John Wick RuneScape and Chill,
I'll put down the sound of the game like really low and we'll just watch the movie.
And it's just me going, in the movie, and then every time I level up I also go,
the first three movies of Harry Potter is pretty comfortable. Yeah, I guess really
dark at the end, which I don't. You could do a pool on which movies, yeah.
Just because of how long, like the grains are, I would kind of want to do series movies and
John Wick has three installments, I'm pretty sure, which is why I quite like that.
What about Shrek? Oh, I don't like the later Shrek. Is it Shrek happily ever after?
John Wick has four?
Have I seen the fourth one? I might know you haven't seen the fourth one. I don't know,
there's a fourth installment. Huh. I have a silly idea. What's your idea? Hmm, you have me curious.
Speak your truth. Stroney, how do you feel about Spider-Man movies? You want to watch the original
Spider-Man? Like the Tobey Maguire Spider-Man? So we can all have a gig a lot of the dancing.
Hmm. Tobey Maguire is a must, I don't know. I remember like a freaking babbling and watching the
movies practically. Yeah, the fourth, the final chapter is the fourth. Okay, okay, okay.
Stroney, did you know that Lord of the Rings trilogy lasts less than one of your endurance
streams? I'm saving myself. I'm saving myself for the Lord of the Rings on Christmas Day.
I am abstaining from such beautiful literature, such beautiful media that was created for human
consumption. So we're not going to watch them for this. The Sam Remy trilogy. Yes, Spider-Man 3.
I don't think I saw that one. I didn't see any of the Spider-Man's that have Emma Stone in it.
But I watched Spider-Man. We're all three of them were in the same movie.
And Tobey was like, yeah, it just comes out of my wrist. And the other two were like, huh?
Because I couldn't believe it. Because I think the new, oh, I'm really bad with people's names.
The new Spider-Man has to use nanotechnology from Iron Man to get his gunk out.
I don't know what Garth feels. Honestly, any of the Spider-Man movies, the movies are great. Okay.
49. Oh my gosh, 49 just popped. Feels good, man. Tom Holland. Ah, his name's Tom Holland.
I sing the praises of the apocrity diary for anyone who wants them. Is it a movie?
I'm not heard of it. Is it a game or a movie?
Oh, my tummy's so hungry. But I can't make food. I must grind. I must fish max. We are fish maxing.
We hitting 50 before Mercy. Before, I think so. We are like blasting through these levels. It's crazy.
0.7% of the weight of 99. Let's go. Oh, I read apocrity novel. Aren't there like seven Highlander
movies? It's Mad Max, a one-off movie. I think so. That new Mad Max, I think is good. The one that
was like, witness me, and he put spray can on his teeth. That one was pretty good. Those one-off
movies are... Oh, sorry. I just clicked. I misclicked. Oh, sorry, sorry. The grind. The grind, please.
The lobster maxing. I can't do it if I'm not misclicking. It was a misinput, misinput.
Fury Road was one. XP waste. No, don't bully me over my XP wasting.
It says I need 54 cooks, and I've got level 50. If I can stop burning them, maybe two more
inventories of lobbies. Oh, maybe two. We can do it in two.
Where are... If only I knew how many hours I spent bank standing. I'm so sorry. I'm so sorry.
I think your ping may be blessed, possibly. Get that fire on. Get that fire on. Get that lobby on the
fire. Not the misinput. Blade Runner? Ooh, that's a good suggestion.
I thought about because of the Ryan Gosling. Ryan Gosling. I don't know why that was so hard to
say Ryan. Because of the Ryan Gosling movies, I thought it would be funny if we did like a six
girl watch along of it, like all six of us watching it. And then whenever Ryan comes on screen,
all of us can be like, oh, that's literally my refling. That's literally my like,
bleeding heart. That's literally my snippet. That's literally my pinpal.
I'm on world 380 at Barbarian Village. Unfortunately, I'm literally about to go off in 13 minutes.
Because Mercy's coming online. And literally, oh my god, that's my refling. Oh my god, my refling's
so strong. I'm gonna just be like complimenting you the entire stream.
Okay, it says 34 more lobsters. Okay, this time, two more inventories. I'll do it.
Can't stop burning these lobbies.
Wow.
That Gosling, literally. I wouldn't mind rewatching The Blade Runner because I didn't like fully
comprehend it at first. So it'd be nice to like see it again, kind of mildly knowing what happens.
Have you watched Seven Cycle Path? Movie before? No, I haven't. I'm not sure what that is. That
Gosling, literally. Can't wait to see us all together again. Can't wait as well.
We've got our first group collab, and then we've got our one-on-one collab coming out soon again.
So I'm gonna see. Can I please stop burning these lobbies, please?
I think I can do it. But yes. I think I said a little bit before, we're a little bit limited
on multiplayer games that we can all play together, so I think I will encourage like some
trio collabs or quad man collabs at some point, but it'll be fun to see everyone's like dynamic
with each other. I hope no one's scared of me.
Strawny smells, how dare you? How do your accusations? I smell like burnt lobster, burnt
shrimp, burnt trout, burnt salmon, burnt pike. I smell like burnt everything because I can't stop
freaking messing up. I need to kick 13 lobsters in the snatch and I level up, and I burn three in a
row, of course, when I say that. Four in a row! That's more like it. Trying to upset me video game,
it's working. I saw the fish she's handling, so sniff the stuff.
Looking forward to main crash shenanigans. Yeah, that's in July. July shenanigans.
I'm not beating the front end. Eating Strawny's burnt food sign me up. Oh, no, those are carcinogenic.
You're not supposed to eat burnt any kind of food. Wait, why did she smell like fish? We're the ones
who are questioning. We did it! We're 50! We actually did it, no way. Mercy's up in 10.
No, we've got 50. That's insane. Thank you so much, we've got 50.
And that was like messing about questing as well and all that.
I look forward to less burning. M-A-B-Zoo, congrats. Honestly, I hope I'll stop burning.
Oh my god, I'm so MLG pro at cutting fish. Ah! I'll send the crunch.
It says the value is 2.3k for that batch of lobsters?
I thought lobsters were a money maker.
Okay, well, I hope to see you play old school again. Yeah, we'll play it once next week on week two
and then we'll play it twice on week three during the week, but I'll split it up just in case
because I don't know. RuneScape isn't the most interesting. Not anymore with all the bots.
Maybe the bots aren't so bad after all. Controversion. You can't say that. You can't say that.
They wear a really long time ago. I'm wondering if that's what I remember.
Bots keep the lobsters cheap. I'm wondering how the economy in RuneScape would look
if bots were like completely forbidden, like if they managed to like completely eradicate them.
I'm wondering if it would be an uproar because everything would get so expensive, you know?
Curious, curious.
We're learning, we're learning.
Stony, Iron Man win. Oh, good luck with that. Are you joking?
It's hardcore Iron Man. You can't use bank. Iron Man is what? You lose everything when you perish?
Sorry, I'm probably standing on everyone right now.
I feel like it would probably like been working on a mech and AC6 for whatever you get on it.
Ultimate Iron Man, no bank, hardcore, lose stats when that. Yeah.
Are you serious? Do you know how much money I've made today? That's 20 million. No way I've been
given 20 million. Hello? Don't people like spend like actual real-world currency to get this kind
of going? Gold and coin together is going just like you should know. I'm putting this in the bank.
Wait, you said there was a bank up here. Hold on. Hold on, mommy's going to the bank. She'll be back
in a second. There's a bank up here? Is that one of these buildings? That looks like a ruined building.
Oh, I'm getting scared. I hope I don't get attacked. You have what level are you people?
Identify yourselves. Okay, no, I must be off of it. Oh, wait, wait, I see banker booth. We found it.
We're finally in Edgeville. This is where I was born.
Right, let's get this money nice and safe and tidy in here because oh my gosh.
Hey, leather gloves. Can I put that on? Is that going to like add to my defense?
Oh my gosh, leather gloves. That's what I needed. Oh, I'll check it out. Oh my god, I'm starting.
Whoa, that's right. Whoa, the bend of my arm is amazing.
We did it. We did it. All right, let me come back briefly. No, don't cry. Don't cry. Look over and
you're crying. No, don't cry. I'm right here. I'm just stunning on the bank because I'm really scared.
I didn't even know there was a freaking thing up there. Well, now I know there's a bank up there.
I am expanding my runescape knowledge. Wow, okay, okay, we're here. I think I might need to...
Can I get level 51? Whoa, wait a minute. Can I even cook these?
Can I cook swordfish?
Oh, I can. What did they get? Oh, burnt it. 140.
It says I have to cook 56 swordfish to already level up again.
Wait, it's taking down two? It's just 50. It's literally going down by two. 48.
47. Wait, what? I'm going crazy. Is that a chef hat? It is. It's a golden chef hat and a golden apron.
A refling literally gave me it.
Oh, I just started doing something.
You should be able to buy enough materials for 99 cooking with five million coins alone.
I've got, well, I've got 20. We might as well go fletching while we're at it. Will we do crafting?
Jeez. Not me becoming a runescape player overnight.
Like a runescape skillar, sorry. Oh my goodness, that swordfish is insane.
We're at 31. Yeah, it's like recalculating, as you guys see. It's trying to do the math, but oof.
That's insane.
How much is it on the ground? For swordfish, it's 4k for that lot.
It just seems like a shame that I'm kind of wasting that vote.
Oh, even more. Goodbye, those who have to go.
Yes, please don't worry if you have to go now. I'm about to read in some mercy to give myself a
vocal rest before I do ASMR, I believe, tomorrow. And then it's the sweet stream.
Yes. So please don't worry if you have to go. I'm literally just cooking away
an experience in swordfish XT. I sent for Scottish anime women.
Thanks for something for me. I sent for replays.
Unfathomable progress, honestly. Oh yeah, buy out those stats. Yeah, we're going to get it.
Rest well, rest well. I also shrimped for her. Oh yeah, you shrimped for me because I'm a
mesipish. I'm a sea animal, so you shrimped for me. And we're head banging away.
I'll wait the ride. I'll ask Mercy to put bad jokes written all over your new clothes design.
I'm so curious what she comes up with, like so, so curious.
Oh my god, we're 110 KXP for cooking. That's just amazing.
Oh my gosh. Oh my gosh. And there's more where it came from.
Not going to lie, I'd be part of that army if I played RuneScape at all.
Someone was like, oh yeah, start up a guild. And I'm like, I've never done it. I don't even know how to do it.
Well, we'll just play as free agents, if you will. We're free agents. Free refling.
We sent for each other a circling of scents, if you will.
Shrimping hard. The amount of progress is only possible with an army of shrimps.
My little shrimpers. Oh fine, I guess you are my little shrimpers.
Don't guild members get XP boosts, do they? What for, like, raids?
Like streams to help Algo. Watch Mercy and RuneScape schedule. Yeah!
51 on day one, 51. That is an insane progress.
Insane. Day one, level 51.
Bruh. Bruh. Bruh.
And that's with doing, like, free quests and stuff together.
I'm wondering if we, like, just, just, just, just, just sent it.
But we just sent it.
Wait, you're both doing swordfish as well?
You guys said, nah, lobbies isn't enough. We've had enough of lobsters.
You're gonna, you're gonna just sell them on? You're gonna sell them back into the,
the grand exchange economy?
We don't need sleep when we have, oh, I hope you guys are sleeping well. We got you, literally.
I hope you guys are sleeping well. I've had a few days without sleeping.
Okay, it's rough. I guess it's dangerous.
Hydration check.
It's 1pm. Uh, is Mercy on?
Wait, hold on. I'm gonna need to make sure I'm redirecting.
Hold on, Strony. Oh, no, no, no.
No, Mercy. No, this future channel, I need the link.
Nope, that was her yesterday stream. Don't be silly, Billy.
What? Oh, she's not live yet. It's like, upcoming. Oh, don't wait, 100 and 0.
Oh wait, I'll wait in.
She's, I'll wait until she's live to confirm the redirect.
I'll wait until she's live to put the oh she's literally just went live no way
That was so that's such good timing hold on let me let's do it. What if we just kept cooking
I don't know
My voice is scoffed like it's scoffed the unbelief I can't
I kind of want to rest for days more
Is there going to be any scripts? Are you doing freestyle? I might do some scripted stuff
like at the start or like
freezes or certainly paragraphs
and
This woman needs to rest her voice don't encourage her bad habits Lamal
Right, let me make sure I'm redirecting into the stream
No, I'm going to make the big boy decision and rest my voice as much as it pains me
Because I do want it lobster. It's sorry. I want a swordfish max
Okay
Okay, she's still loading so I have stalling time okay
She's still loading in the loading screen so I can still
They'll never know
They'll never know we're gonna just want more just one more inventory of fish. Okay, just one more one more, please
Just one more just one more. Okay. I'll be good. I'll be a good girl
Just one more, please
Please come on my knees
Just one more inventory though
We'll see how much xp we can get I'll be beautiful. I mean won't be so close to 52
Are you gonna do the M&M goodbye, what's the M&M goodbye?
Well even Scottish M&M again M&M again
I
Starting to nod off to that fishing myself. He's a few more minutes of swordfish maximum
Just one more just one more inventory, please. I'm not addicted. I promise just one more inventory full of fishes
Let's do it
What's the M&M thing? A lot of burnt one. Look, I'm trying my best. Okay. It's hard to cook over the fire
There's so the wind keeps blowing in different directions and people keep moving around the fire
So the air flow isn't really doing it. Don't supply her addiction
Get rest or anyone that beautiful acts in the top form. Yes, I will warn and say that ASMR streams are a
lot shorter
But I'll definitely be looking at marshmallows
I'll definitely be looking at some scripted stuff and you can always submit what you want to say as well
I think you can do like a chat command thing
Just send me the trade request just one more one more one more come on send me the trade request come on
Come on, you know, you want it, please? Please for me send me the trade request
Come on, you know, you have swordfish
I
Know we don't buckle come on give it
It's me as you're not enabling me. It's just one more
There's no harm in one more batch of swordfish
No way you're not giving me it
No way you're don't give me me it pick up the salmon
No way I'm getting picked. I'm picking up frickin salmon
You may have to pull it the hip no eyes. Honestly. I'm not addicted. I promise but let's just grab the salmon
We're like so close to 52. Let's make it 52. All right, and we'll redirect into mersey make it 52
Go on 52
Let's cook
Reeflings are cutting you off. I can't believe I'm having to pick up fish off the floor
Stop giving
Stinger grime. Let's go a bit
She almost became golem I was cool and gone wait
But I can't do it because my voice was so hard
We're almost at level 52. I'm still burning salmon
Voice box must heal stop being nice to me recently
Stop looking out for me. I can't are you done snowball at me? You doodoo head. That's all that you doodoo head
You know your ball headed as you know, you're Santa
That's all that
I can go offline whenever I want. Okay
Will you expect brief will you accept briefings instead of fish?
Depends what my lead to do with you. Huh?
Do you offer me some experience?
Right we're so close to 52 we're so close we're too close
Oh
How much XP is a reason why it depends that I get your boy cherry or not
How much yeah, try cooking one. Oh, they're not dropping any
There's no fish on the floor to cook
I have a pump in the ground who got to pump it up. You've got to know there's no fish on the ground
I can't even round up to 52 if you're close you can start next dream on a good note of leveling up
I'm not addicted we sling. Just give me the sword fish. Look. Come on. Let's go to the bank together
Look, we're going to the bank. I just need one more batch of sword fish
Give me the sword fish. Look. We're literally bank maxing right now
Come to the bank in Edgeville. I'll take you to Edgeville. Look. Here's the bank. It's so pretty
Just one more batch of sword fish
Or lobsters or anything or even some oh, I
I'll do it myself
Where's the bank or I'll do it myself cuz cuz some other
Reflings were king enough to give me all the salmon's. I'm taking this salmon
I'm taking it away stinky reeflings. No give him no feeding my fish addiction
I'm starting you have a problem. I don't I don't
I'm it's called fish maxing. You've never heard of it. Oh, I just accidentally opened up a thing. Oh
Why did that open up in another browser? Where the heck is the fish? Have I gone past it? Oh, no, it's here. Sorry
Yeah, we're gonna level up. Oh, hold on hold on in bot in bot need in bot work
Okay, there we go. We'll be level 52 and then we'll redirect into America
Gonna have to send you up to the 12-step program in a minute
Thank you. How do you I'll have you know I'll be the least once a week. Oh, I just show her this morning
Oh, I washed away. Oh my good
Stranny need therapy. Who is that other personality so similar?
Oh
I'll finish my inventory and then I will call it there
Hmm
You can literally do this any other day. You have to control your screens
Okay, I'm going I'm going I'll go rest. I just need to finish the inventory. Okay
You're lucky there's no fish down here
Put the fire out don't there's a pair of my fire
No, wait, what you're gonna give me more. I don't know. I think I need to go and I
Wait, you made me walk all the way to get that salmon when you have freakin in your inventory give me it
Give me give me
No way, no way
Okay
As I was saying I'm not addicted. I just need one more
I had lots of fun too. It was amazing
The story how many errors have you been listening to the song on this? I don't know. It's good. It's like a snake. I like it
Mercy's gonna end up raiding in the strong a
Okay, I won't do anymore. We will raid into mercy because that's not fair and we can all watch mercy designers
I don't know what she's gonna do guys. Just one more level. I swear
We will play runescape again next week
Um
And then on week three we'll play it during the week to give people a chance to work on weekends a chance to join in through the day
Sure get a prayer level here are five bones
She's gonna draw you in a swordfish costume at this rate
I haven't played it in a long time, but it's kind of fun doing the quest with everyone out there today
Oh, I'm so glad you managed to join in on the quest. We'll definitely do quest next time as well
Um, I don't know what the next quest is. That's easy to do
So Johnny's gonna turn off stream and keep no I want to achieve everything on stream literally not even a bit of fish xp
Right as you I'm gonna close the game. Okay
As you guys watch me log out, you're really gonna hear it log out
But how do I log out without I mean
I think the game saved that last batch, but I'm logging out
I upside bye bye and chat and then I'll close the game. It's just the music's gonna stop
Okay, hold on I need to go
Okay, let's close right I've logged out so you guys can see it
Hold
Wait a minute. This is literally a preview to my stream tomorrow
Oh, excuse me
You want to swordfish max with me you want to cook max with me
You want to run bank run max with me
There that's your hint. Oh
Oopsies I'd put
eyes
That's your hint for the ASMR stream tomorrow
It's your it's your runescape ad jump here by
But yeah, this is your hint to what's happening at the stream tomorrow
I'm gonna be all up in your face
And
I'm cooking again. Oh, I'm cooked again. Sorry. I got cooking on my main. I wonder why wonder why
Which is I'll see you guys tomorrow for some. Oh wait, where's the audio?
Oh, no, you can't hear the audio they don't all of them
Oh, you can't hear the audio. Oh, well, um
But yes, I'll see you tomorrow
For some ASMR. This is your hint for what the ASMR is going to look like
I'm going to try and raise my voice as much as I can
I'll see you tomorrow about everything won't I?
Yes
And we're gonna have a good time
Enjoying just in time for like please enjoy mercy
As best you can
And I'll see you tomorrow and thank you for everyone who managed your stream stay
We already achieved one of my goals, which was stream stay then
And then I'll have missed you already. I ain't even clicked golf lane. Yeah, I didn't even click the end broadcast
But I'll see you tomorrow
and
ASMR short stream but fun
Real fun with what I've got planned
Okay, see you tomorrow we things
Be there or be square. Hopefully they I don't think that ASMR is going to take them so time living in the future
Okay, bye. Bye. Thank you for hanging. Bye. I go rest my voice. Okay
By replaying
By replaying bye
Bye-bye-bye-bye-bye