What is that noise? It sounds like the fire.
Oh, there we go.
Oh, he's like, this world is free.
Oh, this is too early.
Three, he believes it.
Right.
Obviously, I've jumped into the game.
Oh, wait a minute.
Oh, wait, can I hear myself?
Oh, wait, I can't hear myself.
Jeez.
Get the door.
Mama.
Mummy's here.
Uh, I'm going to open.
Um...
Hi, good morning. Good evening.
Good afternoon.
Uh, how is that all fit to scale?
Oh, wait, that doesn't fit to scale at all, Runelight.
Is that like that last stream?
It doesn't... wait, why is this on top of the freaking thing?
No, don't do that. That's even worse.
Go below.
Why is there two Runelights?
Do I have the game captures myself?
Okay, no, that looks correct.
I just need to do that.
Okay, Rinscape is just a funny-shaped game, okay?
It's going to be scoff.
It's just a funny-shaped game.
I'm too dumb for to figure out.
Is that a refling?
Refling, you already in?
Other player has accepted?
I'm like, damn, Reflings, you're quick.
We are in world high...
Oh, it's replays.
Hi, uh, red e-fling.
That's how I spell it.
Damn, Reflings are shown off.
I'm not even freaking said like,
oh, this is my update for today.
No way, they have freaking Gangnam style
and freaking Rinscape 07.
Old school.
I don't know why I said 07 though.
Oh, my Gangnam style.
Uh-oh.
Sexy refling.
Up, up, up, up, up, up.
Open them Gangnam style.
Howdy-ow.
Good morning, good evening,
and good after noon.
I hope you guys are ready
for a cheeky endurance stream.
Hi, Reflings. Hi, Strone, I guess.
Uh, yeah, I hope you're ready
for a cheeky endurance today.
Um, I...
had a bit of business
going on behind the scenes
business, business, business.
So, uh, I hope to have
quite a fun update soon.
I've just told the girls what the business was,
and, uh,
someone's very excited.
I just read their message,
but it made me giggle,
but I can't say or else spoilers.
Let me open up my inventory
so you guys can see what's up.
Yes, we are business, business, business.
We're doing, like, straight-up business, business, business.
Um, like, I'm...
The only thing I'm used to is
sponsorship people reaching out to me
and being like, hey, for a 60-second segment,
I will pay you this much.
This is what is going on.
Um, and then I'm just like...
Oh, yeah.
But this time,
um,
I got...
I will talk about it a bit more.
I'm gonna ask permission if I can talk about it,
because, um, the person is associated
with an agency that helped out to...
and if they're comfortable with it,
I'm happy to talk about, obviously, nothing.
Azur got monetized?
Are you telling me Azur got monetized?
I went to bed and Azur wasn't monetized.
Shibi was, which made me think
within 24 hours Azur is getting reviewed next.
I just hope her massive fucking
honkers don't, uh...
Uh...
I know
DEMPA isn't
in here right now.
DEMPA's just messaged me.
She's...
strong angry. You have a lot on your plate.
Do you think Ace of the Masters?
What do you need, DEMPA?
I won't charge.
DEMPA, I won't charge, darling.
Oh, DEMPA,
you're so adorable.
Never charge friends.
Always do it for free because
when you have friends like these,
life is good.
I have not even known DEMPA
for more than two weeks
and she's been nothing but a sweetheart to me.
Right, I am going to go to the bank
and clear out all my fishes in the background
whilst I ramble to you.
I have absolutely terrible news.
Just...
upshot news.
I tried to take a Joby,
but the Joby wouldn't have come.
So...
I'm probably going to have to take a big steamer
in the middle of the stream
which I'm raging
because I hate...
I'll always go for a shower
after I do a big
Joby
because I can't... wait, should I just make a...
I think it would actually be faster.
Hold on, Reflens. I think it's going to be faster
if I take wood out and
I...
Do I even have wood?
Do I even have an axe?
It must... I do have an axe.
Okay, then I need a
tinderbox.
Okay.
I don't actually have a bit of wood.
Right, that's fine though. We're going to go get it.
Right, we'll chop here
and then I'm going to make a fire outside the bank for now
just to eliminate
all of my inventory.
Oh, juice.
Oh, tiny cuttles
wants to trade with you.
What's your name?
Well, baby cuttles.
Um...
Hi. Oh, you already given me one.
Thank you.
Yes, I will be needing these. Thank you very much.
Little easy.
The best way to ruin friendship is get money
involved.
I went until I learned
about the development team drama.
Oh my god!
I've got a really funny fucking comment.
So, you know how I'm always telling you about
like, oh, we...
All I have on hand for wood right now
your wood is
more than enough.
Little roofling, I assure you.
A winky face, because we all know
what we're talking about.
Um...
I'm a mor... Oh, damn, bullshit!
I was talking about you!
Um...
I'm so scared.
I never streamed on YouTube.
Oh, you don't actually have to mod anything.
It's like customary to make you
mod
so that
you stand out more in chat.
DEMPA, I'm so sorry.
I was just exposing you. I just said
that you wanted an ASMR script
and I'm offering it for free, because I would never charge you for that.
You're...
Oh, freaking sick. I'm just not...
Wait, let me pick up... I'm doing two things.
Right, let me finish up the...
Why did that only take out one?
Oh, it's not looking good.
Now you all know that I'm a RuneScape noob.
Oh, yeah, YouTube custom.
Yes, you're learning, right?
Use Tinder Box on the logs.
Oh my god, you got a little cabbage head going on.
Okay, right.
Oh, I don't want to brag, but I'm level 2
if I'm making... Right, we are going to just get rid of...
Not rid of, but...
But yeah, you don't...
Yeah, so, as I was saying,
we got a little hate comment today on YouTube.
But do you want to know why it's so funny?
It's because
most of the comments were like,
vealers aren't going to last a month.
And then it went to two months
and it went to six months.
Do you want to know what today's hate comment
and quotation marks was that I had to delete
vealers aren't going to last
two years.
Motherfucker, if vealers last
two years, all three generations
are successfully out.
I don't... What?
Are you dumb?
I like how it went from not even going to last
a week, not even going to last a month.
Two years? Two years, all three genes are out.
Two years and I have succeeded
in what I wanted to do.
Duh.
I literally just like multiplied the time
dramatically.
And literally, it's a supportive message.
I'm like, nice try, but
bruv, wait, sorry. I think a re-film is trying
to trade me. Sorry.
Sorry.
I'm sorry, bruv, yet it didn't mean to not trade you.
What?
10,000
swordfish? Isn't that not like
99 right there? Am I going crazy?
Are you sure?
Oh my god.
Wait, wait, wait.
Another reflin?
Uh...
Oh no.
Oh my god, reflin.
Alright, I'm getting drunk.
I'm getting drunk as a skunk.
Actually, I think we're doing
drunk stream near the end.
Helps make the job a...
I literally
got like freaking 10 kabillion.
Right, thank you. Let's go for a job.
Let me drink that. Let me eat.
Oh, I love the little bubble
sound effect. If I ever make a song,
like an actual song, like custom made song,
oh my god, 10,000 swordfish.
Oh my gosh.
Right, in order
to make this super simple,
I'm so sorry for anyone
who like is really good at organizing their
shit.
I'm not. I'm literally just going to shove
all the fish items to the top.
Please don't judge me.
Right, I'm pretty sure that's all the shit.
Raw trout, you as well.
Raw herring, you as well.
And that's cooked salmon.
God, what a bank.
Gee willikers, I sure hope no one cracks
into a skullfish.
If you move to members later, it'll get
faster. One morban, literally.
Right, shrimp. We're going to
call the shrimp right now. Unless the fire
is out, I think the fire is out.
Wait, no, someone's lighting the beacon.
Gondor calls for aid.
We're just going to clean up our inventory.
I say that as if we didn't just get 10,000
freaking fish. Thank you very much.
Does me, I'm glad I could help.
Thank you. Bank tabs and shambles.
I'm so sorry. I know people are
really good at organizing their tabs.
I just couldn't, I'm just like, in and out.
Let's go. She's a hoarder.
But she's our hoarder.
Visucky
is done for. They can't compete with
velour, literally.
I bet you velour won't last until
velour stuff exists in.
Isn't it interesting?
Look at me right now.
Valia might only last
two years, but that's still a year.
22 months, 30
days, 23 hours,
59 minutes and 59
seconds longer than he probably lasts
when he touches a woman.
Bro, literally, oh wait,
whoa, whoa, whoa, wait, did you just
did you just roast him?
Thank you for the tip, Toria.
I was like, oh yeah, yeah, yeah, until
I heard the very last sentence.
I was like, a Brian?
Brian?
Oh my gosh.
That was,
I didn't expect that at all.
Right, I can put this away because there's a kind of rifle
in making fires. Right.
We'll do anchovies.
We'll do
the...
No, don't eat. Oh wait, they're cooked.
Okay.
My apologies, such a fake gamer for
I cannot, oh my god,
really starting a freaking fire outside the bank.
Wait a minute.
I'm not the Rockwell uprising.
Like, I was naughty.
I'm not there all the time.
I'll be honest, I'll put my hand up
and I'll say I'm not there all the time.
I had a little peek yesterday
about what you've all been
anonymously chatting about
and someone said,
yes, Trony, I understand
Blackwell
headquarters.
And I was like,
that's so fucking funny.
So yeah, your comment got me excited.
I was seeing someone,
someone's like, a ritual
posting about Shibi and it's like, I am nothing but trash.
I'm just Shibi's foot and I'm like, yes, yes, yes.
Then the OG
Sons, those Czech and the OG Sons
they were spoiling I see.
Absolutely spoiling it.
He's throwing it off topic question.
What's your tip for Germany,
Scotland today?
Is there a football match on?
Use logs on fire to make bonfire.
We'll not go out.
Isn't that all RuneScape 3?
I don't think that's a thing here.
What about having many fires?
Hmm.
Any thoughts on doing
Iron Man so chat can't just give you everything?
VBop
You have far too much faith in me.
I'm not even going to pretend otherwise.
I know I'm not supposed to
name chatters
but my guy
you have far too much faith in me to think that I could do
the only way I could do this on my own
is by picking up
dropped fish and barbarian village.
That is the only way I know how to do it
because I don't have the funds.
I don't know how to make money in this game
and we'd be at this for hours.
Since strong debut,
something about her reminded me of a Pokemon.
It has been on the tip of my tongue
for an entire week
and I finally figured it looks like a
Cray Dilly if it was an anime girl.
A Cray Dilly?
Hold on, you're actually getting me to look up something.
Cray Dilly Pokemon.
Oh,
I know them.
They're in Ruby.
Kill things to make money.
Bro, goblins don't drop money.
The most expensive item
goblins drop is goblin mail
which is 500 a piece purely because it's a quest item.
Thank you Thierry for the other tip as well.
Honestly, I could see that.
Yeah, the fossil type.
Goblins are the best.
You're trolling me.
I'm getting trolled.
There's no way you guys actually think that.
I got my first bond via marbles on stream.
I wish you could do marbles on stream
on
thingy.
On YouTube.
But things are very slowly getting
integrated to YouTube.
But I
definitely feel YouTube
is becoming stronger and stronger
for streamers.
And like,
I think what we're saying
is that discoverability, who
dare add it.
DEMPA!
I don't know if you're still lurking.
DEMPA goes, I didn't think that far ahead.
What do you think would be cute?
I think she likes the kind of creature it is.
I'll write some creepy stuff for you.
You were strong and we were rooting for Scotland
today in the years. Oh, we're gonna do shit.
It's fine, it's fine.
The life of a Scottish
national...
Wait, no, hold on.
Nationality of a Scottish person.
Because we understand we're just terrible.
Although we're decent at rugby.
I'll be honest, we're actually no rough at rugby.
But the fit ball.
The fit ball, if you didn't know
football in Scotland,
you say fit, like F-I-T.
But no pronunciation on the T.
And then ball, fit ball.
Okay.
I feel like
YouTube could make discoverability so much better.
See, I think it does
enough. It's Twitch that has poor
discoverability. However,
people disagree with me when I say that.
And I'm like, oh, okay.
I actually thought
Shawnee literally never leaves
her arms until she makes
her display.
Born blue, thank you
for becoming a member.
Enjoy the emotes back.
The girls emotes have been ordered.
I do have a bit of bad news
about it though. The person
that I get them done by, they're like
it'll take me a month. And I'm like
excuse me?
A month? And they're like, yeah, a month.
Is that okay? And I'm like, hehe
I guess.
And then they're like, oh
but we've also put the base price up.
And I'm like, oh, okay then.
Okay, that's fine then.
And I'm like, okay.
That's just kind of the worst of all worlds.
But yeah.
Everyone else
is going to get emotes before me.
I'm submitting everyone else's emotes before me because
I don't think it's fair.
My reeflings, you know how
unbelievably
well behaved you are for me and how patient.
And it's nicer for the girls
to have something to celebrate.
Because you already know I'm going to be here
every day.
And
Oh, I was saying that my first drunk stream
I'm not sure how much people
are going to like this. And I can already see
some of you typing and rolling your
eyes. Keep your eyes to the
front of your head. I don't want one
eye rolling to the back of the skull.
Um
What am I saying?
My first drunk
stream was going to be
uh
drunk apex but I don't go off
line until we win.
But okay.
How did you time that?
There's a stream delay. How did you even
time that?
Fucking reefling in game said
eye roll. How did you time that?
ever stream. I well thought that
but then I was like would you guys rather
jellybean game? Some sort of drunk
multiplayer game.
So the stream is just never going to end pretty much.
Apex. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Everyone's like dunking on apex.
Well, there's other multiplayer games
we can play if you'd rather drunk
that. But I feel like drunk jellybean
is just going to be me like
please, please,
please let me, let me
get to the past and first level
please
I don't want to spectate.
Like and I'll be drunk and all that.
Why is so much fire? You had drunk
runes. How is drunk runescape fun?
I
put the shrimp on the
fire
it cooks the shrimp
and my level
gets higher
drunk fire cave
Oh
got drunk. I accidentally achieved 99
fletching
runescape is never fun.
You drink every time you make an alcoholic
drink.
We won't let you get past level one
this time around.
That's what I'm worried about
the true endurance stream for real
for real. We'll bank the bank
runescape is a job
Honestly, that's funny.
Oh wait, no, that's kitchener
but you're
un-cook-trure herring.
Castle wars is
for you play. Right, hydration. I need
to finish my tea.
which
yes
I
I've also planned
out the membership
streams for next week. Again
if you are unable to member, please don't
worry
dear little reeflings, I stream
every single day free access
What movie did I pick?
I think I might have picked
Austin Powers
for the movie
question mark. How are you keeping this
up?
I don't know. I thought you could only have one
or she'll start leaking secret.
No, I shut off about all the insider stuff
now. I'm starting to
leak it. Well, I've not said anything
that I regret saying. I don't
regret being like, yeah
we don't need talent managers
because it turns out if you give
actually I will like to expand
upon that point. Now that you've got me
on that subject, hold on a minute little reefling
the reason
why talent managers aren't necessarily
needed is because these girls
have streamed and they have plenty of
experience. Who goes there
and
to
go from
independent where you pick your streams
and you pick everything and then
you're on a one week basis where you need
approval every week to stream what you want
it just doesn't make sense or it doesn't make
sense to me. Okay, so
yeah
sad I'm going to miss the first membership stream
I mean you can always go back and watch the vods
at any point you become
a member you can access the
vods on the membership
strums. I just need to
once I make
the lobbies for them
I just need to make sure I do it for the correct
membership here
and holy crap we're creeping on the next level
I actually don't know what level we are
we're level 52 we're about to be
53 we're like slowly creeping up
wait are they flirting what's going on here
agility, construction
and slayer
oh we're all debating on what I thought
runecrafting was unanimously voted the worst
it's been stressful
with a manager I just
feel very strongly that
I mean
obviously in my instance
the girls in that are happy for me to say
all of them streamed way longer than me
why would they need to come
to me for permission to stream
it just seems rather odd
you know
just doesn't make any sense
runecrafting has a minigame now
all to make it faster
I'm thinking of
how many watch hours I need to stack up
when I get home though honestly though
I've
planned out
the
Elden Ring streams
but
I just realised I might have to delay it by a day
because of time zones I don't know
if the DLC has a time zone release
but from being
an upside down land
whenever there's an ad for a game
and it's like this game comes out on this day
I'm like well that's a lie
it's not like time synced
because I'm in the future
right now I'm in the future it's 4am on the 15th
like I'm in the future you know
so I might have accidentally planned
my Elden Ring stream a day too early
before the DLC comes out
but then again
we could play it
early
actually no it's not going to be a problem
because we're not even going to be able to be at the DLC
because we're starting fresh
how's the future
I mean
it's alright
I ain't got much of a quarrel with it
that's a lot of marks of grace
yes
that's going to be a major endurance stream
back to back
I've planned 4 days
around it
it might leak into a 5th day
so sorry to anyone watching that
the Elden Ring isn't your thing
you know
arise you tarnish
do you have a save file already
no I was going to start fresh
I was going to start from the beginning
yeah because I like when you guys
get to hold my hand
so the stream
and someone sent a marshmallow
and I was like can we invade
and I'm like that's actually what we do
so 2 reeflings come in
as an invader or enemy
and it means we can safely walk around
the areas and stuff
I didn't know if I should bring out the shock collar
so every time I perish
you guys get to shock me
I don't know if that's a bit too weird though
for what we're...
I feel like it's more going to be like nostalgia run
of like all of us being like I remember this
I remember that I remember when we did this
remember when we did that
and then I've just got a shock collar going
me every time
every time I mess up
ummm
we know what I hurt you
I will probably be on here runescape
and during that oh I need to finish my teeth
they're cold
I've been making my
teeth with far too much honey
it's rubbish
alcohol poisoning no I cannot
I cannot drink and play runescape
Elden rings there's no chance of that
the shock collar is
with sin I actually need to mess with her
because unfortunately
I need to delay that stream due to
obligations
because essentially week 3
is Elden Ring and then it would be week 4
Elden Ring with sin and
I think that would
alienate
too many
supporters being like oh god
get off that game already
you can do it
don't let you get in the way
don't let yourself get in the way
honestly
I do have a fun update for those of you
who enjoy seeing my hands
I have successfully ordered
the Uwu Market
keychains
and merchandise
like I bought my own merchandise
type thing but I got a discount code
and all that I've got the keychains
of all the girls coming
so I'm going to do
like a little hand ASMR soon
for anyone
now don't worry this content
will be made public that I'm about to discuss
for anyone who is currently
on Patreon
they got early access to
a YouTube video
which was absolutely outrageous
but I'm just wanting to
know if anyone in chat
did listen to that outrageous
audio and what were your thoughts about it
um
I'm also using my Patreon
as a
big archive of anything that I produce
sadly
4 audios are unable to be
uploaded to it because I was
very dumb
I've made a 4 part
series
that has hypnosis
in it but Patreon actually doesn't allow
that
so I'm going to upload it on my
Twitter for free not a problem
I just need to edit it and get out of the way
but it means
I'm now missing 4 audios
um
raw tuna
that's cooked that's cooked that's cooked
that's cooked so
Lobster's tuna and then we tackle
the 10k freaking
swordfish
this is going to be interesting
I keep running out of love
um
the hoodies
no nothing is limited by Ubu Market
um
actually I need to talk to them again
because
Azura is coming up
um
y'all
why does he not like hypnosis
Mastercard
our unloved overlords
have deemed that
hypnosis isn't
consensual for some reason
even though it fully is like you will never
do something that you don't want to do
um
and unfortunately
Patreon always have to bend the knee
a lot of people have issues with Patreon
but the reality of the situation is
our overlords that we despise
the ones who are on Epstein Island
all the time
but deem hypnosis as non consensual
so it cannot be
uploaded to Patreon however
um
I'm going to say something and this is a bit controversial
but guess what
Elon Musk announced that Twitter is absolutely
fine with that kind of content
so I'm sorry but one up on Elon
Musk because he couldn't give less of a rat's
arse and to be honest
that's kind of what I'm looking for when it comes to
just making content
we're all adults here we're all doing our thing
like there's no need for
all these things going on
uh
but yeah
yes um so unfortunately
it means I have four missing loot
oh I shouldn't say those words
sorry four inkable
audios so I need to go
like record so
I'm not actually sure what my
fourth upload this month is going to be on Patreon
because
um
originally it was supposed to be
a part one of this series
but it's not possible
um
yes
um but yeah did you like the audio
for those of you who are on Patreon
because it was absolutely outrageous
you can probably monetize twitter eventually
oh you need
five million impressions I'm not sure we're there
unless like well she
stares
and Mercy
managed to get caught in the algorithm
when
this new meta came up
so they actually probably do
have that
um
but uh
yeah like if twitter is like
oh I burnt all of them
I have five
lobbies out of that that's terrible
ooh
that was a really rough run right lobbies
we've got 500
let's see how much we just absolutely
waste honestly
I'll do the camera and go like that
eh
it was very unhinged that ASMR
yeah
I thought it was hilarious I was like
freaking jumping around the mic
I was doing like backflips trying to like
come over and like get it louder and stuff
do you know how many I put so many
like noise dampening filters
on the audio as well
but the clap was so loud
it was outrageous
um
I don't know if it'll survive on youtube
but I'll still upload it as a yolo anyway
cause it's hilarious and I don't care
and to be honest
I never really did anything that outrageous
cause it's just sound like to me it's like
just the sound of someone clapping their hands
okay it's just what's actually
happening that's a bit outrageous
but because there's no audio it's fain
eh so because
there's no visual unhinged
isn't a negative thing
the audio is the reason
eh
I'll have to go stuff to see the
7th grade
yeah basically I did clapping ASMR
but I didn't use my
hands
I wonder
well I'm gonna see if I can get some fish
I don't need any more fish if it's for me
I'm sure you've got 10k swordfish
um but yeah
that's the audio I made
oh my god we've almost leveled up again
that's fantastic
what a genius entrepreneur truly
I fell asleep to the begging one
really?
that was so popular
I definitely hit the algorithm
because
well someone said on one of my
ASMR stream
wait what happened there
someone said on my ASMR stream
that
I was on tiktok
feature page
but um
vealer doesn't upload to tiktok
we've reserved everyone's name on tiktok
just in case
but it's more important to do youtube
shorts vs tiktok
like over that kind of thing
um
what liquid you put on your
not hands I heard you spray something
at the beginning
oh it's coconut oil
it's oil
in the audio
you can hear me take off my prel
I left that in on purpose
because I breathed
heavily through it and I was like
I'll edit this out but then I was like
oh maybe someone would enjoy it
so I just left it in
so you can literally hear me take off my weapon drew
an armor
nudge nudge
tiktok clippers
no like um so on tiktok
it's called
a video format it's called tiktok
whereas youtube it's called a short
and twitch it's a clip
but it's all the same thing
oh I leveled up I got
54 oh my gosh
maybe 78 is gonna be
like way before like at the rate
we're doing these lobbies
um coconut
my beloved
ah thank you
um oh my god that voice crack
70 is fast yeah I feel like maybe
I might have
underestimated how much we're gonna get
the little extra sounds add a lot
oh right so I can actually tell you
the behind the scenes of recording the coconut clapping
let's call it the coconut clapping
that'll be our code word for it
um so
the reason why you hear me go
oh and then
I do it is because I had to hold on
to my
my gooblies because they were
bumping
and jumping because of like
in order to make
um your buns of steel
clap you have to like go up and down
quite not violently
but you have to make it quite fast that's something
sometimes I do it slowly and then sometimes
it's like one after
what I'd clap that coconut
I mean what the cool thing
is that you can fully unleash the Scottish accent
does that mean it tastes like coconut
I mean right now probably
oh I should do that smell trend
I keep forgetting coconut clapping
like want to bite them
if you cook at a range next to where you're burning
ah I can't be bothered moving though
I want to stay with my reeflings at the fire
I was gone for five just strong
he died no I'm level
54 we've
just came to realize I've probably
severely underestimated that we're
achieved 70 this stream
we are most likely going to have
a lot more than that
um
aggressively clapping coconut
well at one minute I was like I feel like
um saw
I think I said saw but what I meant was
jaws that shark like that din din
cause I was away I went
walked further away from the microphone
and then came closer and it was like
din din din din clap clap
din din din clap clap clap clap
this is one of the most ridiculous
audios I've ever made but
I got halfway
through editing my
first
1k thank you
oh wait I've got salmon sugar
I didn't notice that salmon there
wait I'll finish off the salmon
um
I got halfway through
finishing my first like 1000
special ASMR
and it's just me rambling
in dune tingles it honestly
probably feels like a live stream like
when I just start rambling whilst I'm doing tingles
but like I was having so much fun
like
being like guess what this is
oh my god this is actually a sponge I don't know
if you could guess that type thing like I was
just getting so excited so it doesn't
sound like ASMR again
from the aster
tuber
I like 92 is halfway to
99 XP wise
hey oh dear lord
this is going to take a little cheeky while
um
hi hello thank you for joining
don't worry 70 isn't even halfway at 99
hmm
well I wanted to try and finish it
in this month because I had on week
4 I had 2 back to back
runescape and I picked
the movies I'm like 99%
sure we're doing John Wick
all of
John Wick series
um
as if I burnt a singular
salmon
eh we'll do all of John Wick
are you squidding me out of here
month long cooking stream honestly
anonymous
thank you anonymous
thank you Brian
honestly
it was freaking hilarious
like you could hear me
do it
oh thank you for the super chat
your boy Stephen Adams
holo n fan
what do you mean
b-boys and your favourite holo n
the way she was going to call her
fan page bebble pales was
hilarious I can't remember it wasn't bebble pales was it
oh no it was pebble pales or something
it was absolutely hilarious
um I remember
being like
she said what out loud when she said
that I was absolutely he ho in
um
but then she couldn't keep the fan name
and I'm like it is probably for the better
people but you're absolutely hilarious
please do not change
um
is this the cost grab the worst
the tuber is
for their manager the bear are literally
oh
will I tell you
I won't tell you
um
but yeah literally
it was hilarious
isn't that what everyone jokes about
pippa they're like oh pippa such a headache
for her manager
how is self management treating you
delicious I don't have to do anything
literally the girl
as far as I'm aware the girls are happy
they can pick what they want do what they want
um unfortunately
because
Azura and
Emmy are on a warning
um
by juicy youtube thanks to their
hidden ASMR update gameplays
um
I am, did I say thank you for the tip
and on this
thank you for your tip
um
oh
unfortunately I've not
well I've kind of discouraged them
for doing ASMR until the warning is up
because it's very dangerous
if they get a strike
I'm like brav
YouTube please
I'm back
I got distracted oh don't worry
I'm literally here for 12 hours
don't worry we're doing an endurance today
I have had so many short streams
this week it felt so weird
like
I do have a lot of time to like finally start editing
I have a heck of a lot
of VTuber ASMR collabs
coming through I wrote an ASMR
collab for two of the girls
and they all were together
um
and
the girls
one of them reacted and thought the plot
was adorable
it's just super basic short plot
I never want to overwhelm the girls
with anything that I assign them
so please don't think it's like some super mega
do do do do do
I know
that there is a collab with Mercy
that's both audio and
we get to play Goose Game tomorrow
not tomorrow
not tomorrow next week
next week
I am going to play RuneScape
before it because
I am going to stream on
Mercy's time zone
like when she normally streams
so basically we're going to play
RuneScape for a solid
chunk and then I'm going to go offline
and rest my voice for like an hour
or two
hours because I'll be in voice call
with Mercy one hour before
the collab if you didn't know
it is common courtesy for VTubers
to show up one hour before
a collab which is where you
do all of your
um technical
failures as I had with
flipping
again special shout out to
Shibi for keeping my head on my shoulders
I was panicking when
we could not do it up
and
she's grinding so fast
baby won't you
grind on me
relax your mind
church your time
will move
that's all I know of that song
I got one cake carambua
of the pussy
wow
when you start cooking members food
I have like
10,000 swordfish to go through
I have no idea what even potential
XP that might is
that might is okay
well one you're done what English was that
um is that a threat or a promise
um oh I was gonna
do marshmallows
actually I've got such nice
marshmallows you guys need to stop being so nice to me
because if I get emotional
and start reading them I start getting
teary-eyed and I'm like I can't handle these
right now because it's gonna like make me cry
like happy tears
um so you guys need to stop being so nice to me
there's currently a riflin
um
who's keeping me updated about their addiction
right now and they're like
I don't even feel the need to go back to my addiction
I'm like oh my god you're kicking your addiction
I'm like how
how are you what how
like that's amazing like I could get into
the nitty-gritty of like how insane addiction
is and look
your brain once it creates
a neural pathway it likes it wants to keep repeating
that it's nice and easy it's why nostalgia
is so powerful because you don't have to like
learn the new lore of something
it sounds silly but
um
like it's very easy
to fall into addiction
and especially
your makeup your genetic
makeup can make you predispositioned
for it as well it's quite it's quite fascinating
because it's like it's kind of like
gamba like I spoke previously
I had a
advertisement offer
of four thousand US dollars
to insert a 60 second
gamba ad
and I said no because
it's gamba
but it's very interesting
how
severely gamba seems to
affect individuals
now this is just an observation
but whenever I've seen
gamba ads that are like stop when the fund
stops a ten thousand
swordfish should get you to level 78
let's go oh my god
78 by the end of the stream
um
whenever you see a gamba ad that's like don't
is like stop stop when the fund stops
they always show a guy
and I'm wondering
um
not the pre
the socialization
because obviously if we're being
very stereotypical of society
we live in a society
guys are normally more interested in
sports and
is the environment around it that it's
normal to gamble
and kind of like put a cheeky
a tenner here on this
bet a 20
quid here on this bet type thing
before it snowballs out of control
it's quite
fascinating I actually had someone
in real life I knew
that
they weren't a family member
but they were like an acquaintance and I learned
of their story
and basically
the guy gambled away their mortgage
and
it's just
it's such a shame what kind of
grip it has
on certain people because
for me right now
I
I'm like confident that I don't
have that kind of addiction
I
I don't it doesn't appeal to me
I would I would walk away
like angry that I wasted
my money type thing like my brain
doesn't go oh
if I gamble again I'll make back
what I lost like no my brain's like
what a waste of time that was I'd rather play
like a video game or something else like that
you know
I wish I could join you but not on
RuneScape wait what's wrong with RuneScape
it's old school
look these are all reeflings we're all just hanging
out outside the we're all hanging
out in Edgeville for no particular
reason
um
yeah sorry I don't know if
I need to turn down the
that sound effect yeah
I'll turn down the sound effect just because
it's very repetitive
and hopefully you can still
kind of hear a bit
sorry
we're in Edgeville together you can do better
90% of gamblers quit
before they've been big now I have seen
those memes I have to admit they're a wee bit funny
but it is
just a very curious
predicament that people seem to get
themselves into I mean that's kind of what
kick the website kick.com
if you heard about it
the only
reason they are able to be
fueled so high is because
of Gambo
there's no other
reason and it's perfectly
fine to say that
but it just kind of goes to show
you how big the house always
wins if they can offer this
business model on the side like I
remember I don't know if you guys remember
when Twitch like officially announced
it's like banning Gambo
it's just very curious
because
there's a lot of
discussion you can get into and you can say
well the person that's Gambo
and it's their money
it's their life
it's their choice
but if like
the oh I'm trying to
think and do two things at once and it's not coming out in a
sense so
is it the
right hold on hold on let me put my sense together
when is it not a choice
when is it not a choice is the
question why is it it's
addiction and not a choice when it comes
to Gambo but it
might be a choice when it comes to other bad
actions you might do in your life
why is Gambo marked out for one
why is alcoholism marked out for one
obviously when it comes to alcoholism
your body does change the tolerance
but you could argue the same for Gambo
because your brain literally
lights up like fireworks
when you win
and
it's just very interesting because where's
the line drawn from someone is consenting
to do this activity and someone
isn't able to consent to do this activity
because it's causing harm because
you could argue sitting on runescape
for 12 hours well that's causing harm
oh well
we'll need to take her offline
because she's not well because she's doing this
for 12 hours because that's bad
for her health sitting for 12 hours
type thing you know
like do you know what I'm trying to like say out loud
I struggle to say the words
RATMA thank you for coming
I'll member to your destructive behaviors
that have historically
been deemed as vices that's where it is
yeah like we're being
called out literally all runescapers
getting called out from across the line
wow we're about to level up again
oh my god just hit just let me
do one ramble and we're gonna be
99 overnight like just
give me one subject to ramble
about and we're done there is a log out
timer after six hours and I will
most likely log me out when I go for the big job
I don't need one right now
um
but yeah
me and college maxing on runescape
citizen homework real
the lanes do get but well that's
it's the interesting thing it's like when
where do laws come into place to
protect gamba
gamblers sorry
um because when you lose
your money you're told tough
tough bananas
yeah 56
yatta
when you lose all your money you're told
tough bananas
when you lose your money to a scam
the bank says see tough bananas
yeah there's laws in place to
protect you in quotation marks and to
get um the scammers
put in jail to get well you can't
really put um
casinos in jail so that doesn't work
uh that's a terrible
uh comparison
um
hmm
hmm well
I've kind of shot myself in that line of
line of thought I've uh completely undone
my that line of thought there I do apologize
um
yes yes yes yes
there's really no good answer no there
isn't that's the thing
that's the thing that's the thing I want
to highlight there is
no answer and
yet we still have some laws
such as you know obviously twitch
isn't law but twitch is a reflection
of the community views
or the community the views of the masses
now do you remember
when uh
wikimane was like yeah gamba bad
and then all of a sudden twitter
blew up and then twitter was like
gamba bad and then twitch
was like okay now we'll remove
gamba like
that is a perfect
example of
the most basic movement now don't
get me wrong movement isn't world changing
but it is the basic example
of someone who definitely
has a larger platform even denying it
going hey this thing
bad and then everyone going
wait a minute yes
this thing is bad
and then boom
twitch
got rid of the category
and outlawed it and said no bad
now that is
and just
a bloody perfect example
of how
the community
the community in
specific areas and pockets
do have a voice
and do have a say
as much as you might not think on an individual
level you don't have a voice
it might be true but have you ever
seen planet of the apes
monkey on own
weak
monkey together strong
it is true
you can't even deny it there's so many
examples of this
like think of revolutions
such as the french revolution
one individual would get their head
guillotined okay
I'm not being funny I'm being so
true this is my rabbit hole
but like literally the french
revolution one person stands up
and gets their head chopped off right
no revolution no movement
community is not you know
community is not going to rise up
but hold on a minute the people are revolting
the people are
revolting the masses are outraged
how can society continue
if everyone bands together
and
historically every 400 years
society
shifts and what do I mean by
society shifts something new
comes up for society to be
a part of okay
so before capitalism
which is when global
economics became a thing
the industrial revolution
global economics there was
region locked capitalism
okay and it's called feudalism
or something like that it's like
it's not feudalism it's like feudalism
okay
which was when
lords owned
the plots of land and permitted
peasants to generate food
on those lands okay
that was region locked capitalism
before we know capitalism today
okay but that got outdated
when the revolution came in
because you know
people learn fast to
grow certain crops
and if you breed crops I can't remember
who did the crop breeding
what's his name
I've forgotten
feudalism is with lords yes
yes the chickens are revolting
finally we agree on something
bro it's not 400 years it's like a decade
stuff changes all the time
but like another massive example
of a shift in society
some of yous are not going to like this
you're in for a rambling stream
you've got me for 12 hours
as if I'm not going to get on my high horse and teach you history
okay
if you did not know
in Christianity
there's the Old Testament
and there's the New Testament
the New Testament
was created
I believe
in roughly the 15th century
the church got together
and went look the Old Testament
isn't doing it for the masses
people are starting to question that
because people are becoming aware
that you know
some things aren't working out
in this story
and basically
the New Testament is just
friggin made up
years later after
Jebus the source
supposedly passed away
you're so right strongy let's eat the rich
fondly thank you for this too
like some people can't conceptualise
the difference between a million and a billion
dollars
now take that million
and add one and then add one and then add one
then add one and keep going and keep going and keep going
and keep going and keep going
but anyway
casually red fill in the masses
bruv I'm not kidding I will keep mentioning
the game
needy streamer overload
I don't believe they put that in the game
that kind of thing
but anyway
anyway that's just me
I don't know what you guys are thinking
but that's just me
but I could really get on my high horse
I should actually I want to do an education stream
about feudalism
because
and kind of how history and how society used to work
because bargaining used to be how
it was done
bargaining used to be like hey
two weeks
would you trade me one potato for two
weeks that's how it used to be done
that's how there was value in things
that's how humans
did it and
there are
there are some examples today
of it kind of thriving
and
so runescape is historically
accurate yes
you guys trading me right now
you are calling upon your ancestors
to give me the resources that you don't need
in the moment
you are looking after me and in return
I will scratch your back later
it's literally why I'm such a big believer
and you scratch my back I scratch yours
because that's how it used to be
return to monkey
replays return to monkey
we were so nice
we had some communities
we had said it's a belonging
it's so
nice
the old test schools
I'm curious
I've not touched old schools runescape
what's with the cooking not cooking window
on the top left so I am using
a plugin called runelight
you can see it up here this plugin
can track your things
there are good bad examples of this
one stick is weak
many together are strong
like the 1940
not good monkey
thank you Iron Ripper for the tip
get a name
thank you for the super chat
um
but just
I'm
literally you guys are
what?
oh no
I'm me
a bit of Netherlands in the chat
stupid work meet
and now I can watch the story
oh my god there's Netherlands
mentioned
give a bond
so no members
will you
now or later
reading Dutch is so funny
questions from you
exams
later is good
oh
Dutch chat
on my chat
more likely than you think
voila
Anders
Ike Mein Dar
nemer op kunnen focusen
ha ha ha
later that's fucked
Scotland being Germany
I have no idea
I probably not I think
wait are these reeflings I don't think
what did you say about my mother
I don't think these are reeflings are they
are you reeflings
uh
I like the uh I'm not in the message
very charming hey strongy just dreamed
just dreamed just joined
how's stream going stream is going amazing
I have rambled my
bruh I have rambled my way
through four levels so far
and ran it so yes we're still 3a
hmm
I'm not sure
we could all be Dutch I can't
believe it the Netherlands
profit
but
how are you doing
I am
hungry I am hungry
I love you
that
that I want
you to play
runescape
with me if you please
reefling
yo
mmm
there you go there's your dutch
for the day I ain't got any more dutch
in me so that's the best I got
she's casting black magic
strongy opens her
analytics it's suddenly 99 dutch
ah
Netherlands
what the fuck good pronunciation
I'll try my best
uh
right
57 we're getting there so quick
also
in Flemish it's Flemish
oh
the Flemish
is like
Dutch German
French mangled and mashed together
can you
yodel
bruh I was watching a zero
on the telly
stream she was
karaoke on her way to herself
I was like yeah damn you got some lungs on
your lady
um she was
fantastic honestly
you wait what no
I didn't mean to do that I don't need the collection
box my apologies right
we have finished the salmon we will
be back to lobbies
uh
fuck me
how many languages you know only
English and technically
scott's is a recognized language
but I am
a scottish
oh that was another funny image
aww but I couldn't save it
when I was playing assassins creed brotherhood
someone did a
text post and it was like
be me pic related 1500
um
some mumbling assassin comes my way
leaves me in my balls keeps rambling walks away
or something
but I couldn't save it
I want to save it because it's a funny meme
I like saving like the memes that you guys make
because it makes me so happy like looking
why do I keep clicking that one
oh my cat's outside
Gimli you're no coming in the day
that was ridiculous yesterday
I freaking shouldn't have let her in
because now she thinks she can come in
all the time and I'm like Gimli no
we can't come in so she's just gonna have to
go outside my door until she gets the message
I'm sorry Gimli
the last time she played stardew
she went karaoke for 5 hours
she has endurance over her mummy
literally she was on for like 8 hours
the last time I checked I don't know when she went off
um
do you have plans to get membership
oh I already have membership
um I'm just playing on free to play so I can hang
up all the reflins like check us out
look all these reflins
we're all just hanging
we're all cooking
wait you guys aren't cooking
oh you're putting more logs on the fire
but I'm cooking
oh thank you
thank you fireman
cabbage patch head is doing something
I don't know
oh we've got just a neck
oh we're linking
the fire
oh I understand
but yeah all the reflins
I didn't want to alienate anyone
if they can't do members at the moment
and we're not cooking
wait a minute
we're not cooking
um
any membership items yet
so we don't need to go into membership world
a lot of reflings gifted me
a ton of fish
so I'm just powering through that now
um and
and another reflin
gave me 10,000 frickets sword fish
I don't know how long it's going to take to get through that
I don't know if that may actually take us
to the end of the
stream
10,000 fish
since a lot
you betrayed Gimli I know
you don't know french
I've been lied to
oh sorry Mizzio
I can't
I can't do it
I can humorously do
what is that today
um
what are you doing
I don't know
I can do french
scottish just to like mess with you
type of french but
the actual french
speaking
like
I'm trying to think of a sense
to say
monchichons
machichons
I think is french for my
yiddies
oh my brain
my brain can't parley the french right now
it's too hard
my roommate that showed me
your content just DM'd me that
cause of that super chat
they're like I know
what you are
oh Gimli
I can't have you in the room hey
she's just gonna
go back to sleep I was playing with her
I play
with my cats before a live stream
to tire them out
but I couldn't play with her too long
so she's currently going nuts right now
but she'll go down for a sleep cause she wasn't sleeping
when I was sleeping so she'll
don't worry don't worry about my pooders
and whenever I go make a tea in that
I go give her some attention
baby boy is really independent
though he's like not he couldn't care
I don't know if it's cause he's half
munchkin that he's
more tired than the usual cat
like you can get depending on the breed of
your cat it can be really tired
in general and need like more sleep
like I'm pretty sure there's
a type of dog that's known for sleeping
oh wait it's greyhounds
greyhounds are like the laziest
dog ever but they can do like
one burst sprint type thing
um
yeah 21 million
um literally I got sugar daddy
out the wazoo cause of reeflings
they were throwing them
coins to me I was like I'm not gonna
say no this is gonna fund the
I don't know if we're doing wine
I don't know wine is the
fastest level up
once I've like cooked everything
if I push it I can
finish my first save file in November
oh I haven't even finished a save file
I was considering doing some eating runs
just to show you guys
what
the binding of Isaac is all about
um
who needs a bot farm when you have a cult
giving you everything you need
literally though
when I had a st. Bernard
it felt like it slept for 20 hours a day
yeah like depending on the breed
um but she's just
moody I fed her and I played
with her mouse
but the problem is because
I let her in yesterday
she now thinks she can come in whenever she wants
um
you're a bit of a diva
Gimli you're a bit of a diva
I have to admit
but I love her
I love her
you're always cooking
oh I ain't just cooking in Rinske
um
I can't
tomorrow's crash bandicoot
um
yes
I think
July streams
I'm gonna focus on Xbox games
to get my gamer score up
um
I've done decent progress
on my goal of collabing with 100 vtubers
with
a 3d old thing
like 3 ASMR collabs
I have absolutely no issue with actually collabing on stream
yeah good luck with that
I'm too shy
I've made great progress
I think I'm just shy of
6 ASMR collabs
um
and then I need to
reach out
and do
hmm
I want to make all of my goals
happen before the one year mark
which means I have to work hard now
um
so
and we've got membership coming up as well
cause we've got a lot of lost time
to make up for but I hope
like you can see with my efforts
and all my hard work there like
I'm making up for lost time
you know it's going good
like I want content out the wazoo
um
I want it to be like good funny times
like literally uploaded that meme ASMR
like please let me hold it
any plans for halo yes
I would love if I could actually
do
a vtuber collab on halo
but
I don't know anyone who's played halo
I will ask the violour girls
first before I ask around
and see if anyone's played halo
um
not that you need to be
um good at halo
to play it like you need to know about it
but I'd rather
I think if you're playing a nostalgic
game I'd rather like two people who are
familiar with it play and that sounds
really rude I hope it doesn't come across as rude
but I mean
I'm sure there's another halo vtuber that's
freaking played random question
are you playing any drg streams
what drg
what's drg
sorry you're gonna have to spell it out for me
my brain is very slow
um I
will like to
check
oh deep rock like to cut yes
um I think I can play with you guys
just
as a word
a word of warning it's not a word of warning
AC snowpaws
is live with space
channel 5 part 2
and imibizu
is live with
the coffin of andy and leily
and she's doing an endurance stream
I'm so proud
as my cat is currently kicking down the door
oh my god
she's getting really frustrated
um
but yes
uh
I think I can play deep rock galactica
with you guys and it's not an issue
at all
she's trying to do the good ending
sorry there's only one ending and andy
and leily and I will not be taking any
comments I don't even
um
there's only one true ending
and I won't have it
any other way
me trying to hold in her
oh god the peeler
we literally can't outrun them
that gartic phone stream was so
fun though the girls are so funny
um
but yeah
the
already levelled up again
literally I am rambling through these levels
like nothing on earth
like I wake up on the other side of the ramble
and we're literally 58
that's fantastic
oh my goodness
all these lobbies
I'm burning them a wee bit but it's fine
okay you and emmy agree hard
on that ending yeah
literally I'm sorry but why on earth would you make
why would you
why would you play the game and be like
uh I'm not gonna do that ending
no the whole point is to like
be fine with human curiosity
like as long as you don't produce any offspring
no one gives a rest
no one gives a
honestly
um
hmm
halo would be a fun way to do community games
uh like the halo molly
player I never actually played much of it
I heard
the bat
was it a halo battle pass came out
and it was just an absolute shambles
like it was just a terrible
multiplayer launch
and it and then they did battle
pass and then it just became
like this terrible
thing I don't know
what ending the one
true ending
oh actually
I was lurking quite a lot someone was like
wait I don't get it are we emmy's brother
the reason why you can
see emmy at all times when she streams
is because you're her dead brother
watching over her
I will spell it out for you
you are her
dead brother watching over her
which is why you can see her stream
which is why you can see her thoughts
on twitter okay
I'll spell it out for you
the pin pals that don't get it
out hold on hydration guys
hydration please hydrate
hmm
very important
very very important
oh actually
tomorrow's crash bandicoot
but I'm 99% sure
buckshot roulette is after
and it's like a super small game
em if it's a small game
don't worry I'm going to
whenever I do like a two hour stream
just know I'm cooking in the background
like trying to edit collabs
or get a collab together
or do something for the girls
em if you didn't hear
the good news she be caught in bum
is monetized and oh
the poor darlin
she tweeted out how it was like
a childhood dream
and she was like crying happy tears
and stuff and I'm like oh my darlin
like I'm so happy for
I'm so proud of her like I'm so glad
that she can see the results
of her hard effort already pay off
em she be
has said this before
so before anyone's like oh you're not supposed to
she be has said she has
an in real life job
and I am very much hoping
she can turn around and be like stuff that
job up your arse after one month
so please don't be afraid to sign up to
she be caught in bum's patreon
that helps her immensely
any merch sales
ubu market got back to me
and they were like
wow this
aces fans and mercies
fans are absolutely
like supporting her out the wazoo
and I'm like I am so glad so please
don't be afraid to support
the girls via ubu market
they get 100% of
the income generated
veiler do not take a cut
and the girls can attest to that
em we don't have
anything to do with it
and it completely and wholeheartedly supports them
if you wanted to
collect all the key chains of the girls
that could be something very sweet and cute
that's what I'm doing and I'm gonna make an ASMR
of me tapping it with my little fake
mermaid nails that I showed on my handcam stream
em
but yeah
she be love
she be all
she's basically a lean
I'm so glad
that the girls can see their hard effort
pay off right away
they've been nothing but fantastic
they really have
is the merch limited
no it's not
it's gonna stay up
until we expire
ubu market has been
absolutely fantastic to work with
em they are
super good I am aware
that they got a bit of flat
cause of some production issues
but they actually moved
em they moved
locations quite a few times
cause their business expanded so fast
that they basically had growing pains
but I have never personally
had an issue with them now I know that's
kinda being like well you never had an issue
with others that's just dismissing the others
relax I understand how it works
but em to work with
ubu market they've been
they were so understanding from the get go
cause I messaged them and I'm like
hey violers the thing
I'd love it if the girls can keep 100%
of the earnings
we as the company don't want to take a cut
and they're like yeah we can set that up
no problem and I was like here
here's all the references to the artwork
yeah we can do that no problem
and just they've handled everything
and it has been really nice
to not have to deal with anything
it makes things nice
and juicy and easy
em
one of the things, few things about
violers the lack of corporation greed
yeah I just
I I mean
Shawnee can your patterns
go in reverse
no they can't they can not
they only go in reverse if I do that
it'll like should yeah see
how it goes in reverse it's because
it has to reset to the top
of my head in order to do that
reverse thing oh we can
test that again yeah see how it
reverses to the top of my head that's
to make sure it works thank you for the 10
barrel you know you could ask that for free
you guys don't have to
ask questions via
em
money it's not necessary
it's really not
necessary you don't have to ask questions via
money you're more than welcome to ask
in chat or on Marshmallow if you want to do it
anonymously please don't worry
em
but yes em I am a very strong
believer in
em the girls earn the money
they get to keep the lines share
em
because I don't
I don't think it's very nice
if the girls were only earning
like the standard 50-50 rate
like what's your motivation to work
if every time you make 100 bucks
a management take 50
for doing a full
other than like handing you the model because
at this point in time it's kind of like
again
egan
excuse me I have a question bruh you didn't
even put anything in it
thank you for the the super chat
you didn't even put anything in it
can you have a rave party with your
hair, Neil
I can't do anything else with my hair other than
Toggle
I just like hearing my name spoken with a Scottish accent
you should teach others how to speak like that
I think it could be a thing
well she'd be starting to develop a
not a pretty decent Scottish accent
em
I don't know how much she used to watch me
wink wink
em but she certainly gives
an impression she's listened to me for a decent
amount but when we were playing
Gartik phone and
and I was like oh when the jobby hits your
stay on the way out
and everyone was like what's
a jobby I'm like oh my god
I really need to put a game together to teach these girls
just letting you know I'm
tiny cuttles in game
tiny spain e
I hope my money buys raw fish on the
GE I'll be back and hopefully be
ready to get cooking experience
see you tonight
yes enjoy work I'll be
online when you get back thank you so much for the tip
as well tiny spain
e
that's how you told me to say it so I'll say it that way
I was in Mercy's chat
and the snippets were baffled by what a
jobby was
bruv literally I'm like oh my god Danny I do the
Scottish slang stream
I wouldn't mind doing a Scottish
history stream that would be quite fun
but I've got the Scottish game
show on St Andrews Day
and I'm like oh yeah
that's right I can't do the Scottish stream
until after fill lobby
no burn fill lobby no burn
let's go
full inventory no burn I don't know if I've
achieved that before but
all let's go and we've just finished the last of
the lobsters we're going to be on swordfish duty
boys
are you squidding me right now
Jack that isn't even a question
purple burglar
see I can say it if I'm not doing heavy
flying purple burglar alarm
but if I like to say it together
purple burglar alarm
oh I bet you want to turn on my purple
burglar alarm
yeah that's right get ready
let's
go on our
clear
right we are officially
tackling the
10,000
raw swordfish
we'll see where we are in an hour
right let me
what's the past 22 minutes
past okay give us
an hour and see how many swordfish we are
because I don't know how fast I can
like get through these
thank you for the
super chat Jack
yes I draw me
oh is that the thing Scottish cannot
say yeah it gets
caught on my tongue gets caught
on the roof of my mouth to try and
annunciate burglar
burglar
the box at the top left tells you how fast
a thousand
a thousand per hour
so we will finish the swordfish
I think we might be able to finish
the swordfish if I don't get distracted
and don't need to like
go make too many teas
I think at the three hour mark
we'll take a toilet break
and I'll get some food
because I don't have any food in the morning
like I just I wake up and I come on
streaming I'm like alright what's going on
that's what we're doing
um
with a steady pace you can do
one an hour one K an hour
that's that's pretty good
that's really good
um
right let's whittle this down to nothing then
by the end of the stream we'll finish
the stack of swordfish and see what leaves
is that can you say
Hamburglar
Hamburglar yay
who the hell are you
I brought a new
what's that
what's that I caught from
wow wow we're about to level up
it's strange that in these days
what Brian
Brian do you talk
do you talk
Brian
I didn't
wow 59
I didn't hear Brian talk
I wonder if Brian doesn't talk during super chats
Brian
Brian start talking during super chat
Virginia thank you for the five
mommy not getting distracted good luck
literally though
Brian is the name of
TTS for anyone wondering
who the heck Brian is
the name of the text to
speech voice you hear when
someone very kindly gives me the tip
his
like the actual name is Brian
of the function I don't know what the name
of the other versions are
but his is Brian
which is why I always go Brian
when someone does
a very kind
yeah
wow a guy wearing a skirt so femme boys
so kawaii
and extremely distressed Scottish lad
bro
killets are always the first thing folk hone in on
but
you only wear killets during special events
like weddings are probably the biggest
kill thing
is gimme inside my door then am I going crazy
um
but yeah
I wish they had a kill in
Elden Ring so
so then you guys can show
up in a kill and we can all get married in Elden
Ring together
um that would be cute
you know you're not supposed to wear boxers
under a kill either
um easy access
easy access
yeah gimme I'm pretty sure gimme
he's going nuts outside my room right now
I'm so sorry if you can hear him yelling
she gets attention I promise
I promise baby boy and baby girl
get attention
um
ooh we're getting
we're already at the
10.3 we started at
10.5
ehh
strongy shows up in Elden Ring like a blue
power ranger am Scottish
like that dress from
DS1
it's for the ventilation
literally you cannot get swamp ass
via a kill congrats
um
but your
fatty bojangles will be bojangling
I think
I don't know how elastic
yeah okay gimme is yelling out my door
I can hear her go nuts
she might start hammering on the door
because she opens them by going up on her back legs
and like pushing with her front paws
so if you start hearing like
that's her currently
like opening the
well attempting to open the door
um
you need to listen to this song
donal where are your truzers it's a joke song about kills
I'd play it but I'd probably get copyright
ridiculous
oh my burn rate is
9%
well hopefully that can get lowered because
missing out on 10% xp
on full inventories is rough
is rough
but we're getting there
sorry how do I use it on the
thing
ta da
let the boys be free as nature
intended true
yes I love wearing a kill always
makes me feel confident I remember
that one scene from the carry on films where the
scott shows their to scare
to scare people
I'm sure it probably
like get it up here
look up the skirt
18,000 to climb
a level we're starting
to get there
where it's taking a wee
minute but that's okay
we've got lots of time
we got all the time
in the world
um but yes
I'm going to let the
girlfriend begs you to hold it
ASMR video cook for another day
or two because it got
boy
the PLU allegations are getting worse
no
Emmy
Emmy thank you for keeping me up to
date with what
what is Emmy doing?
is she still endurance in it or did she go for a
tinkle?
thank you for the
tip as well boy
she loves holding her
pee
I mean
I know I am aware
that it is an interest
in certain individuals
so whoever
those individuals are
I'm glad you are
enjoying your little sister
tormenting your little sister
okay
she peeped and then
went back for more peep holding
dang
I
never tell you that time someone paid me
well no sorry
let me rephrase that
someone wanted to pay me
$200 to stream
but I drink
bottles of water every hour
but I don't go to the toilet
it was their thing
they wanted me to be like
oh it's so full
I'm so full
basically and I was like honestly good money
good money
unfortunately I regret to inform
I did not carry out with such a request
however
it was rather interesting learning about that
because that was the first time I had ever been exposed to it
thanks everyone
if you don't wear underwear
people call you a true sportsman
the big brothers were two we can let her go one
bruh as soon as emmy starts begging
sorry I could never say no to like any of my daughters
I cannae do it
I cannae handle it as soon as they ask for something
I'm like anything for you love
like per emmy I completely forgot
I was waiting on me making a script for her
and like I was in the middle of like
doing like 10 billion different things at once
like doing business business business
and she's like oh what about this
and I'm like oh yes my daughter
I completely forgot please forgive me
I'll update you very shortly
and like I gave her the script she needed
and all that
em I literally cannae say no to them
I don't think I've ever said like oh oh
so you're saying there's a chance
oh it's not you
was it you
calling yourself out in chat
gonna do some slaver
we'll leave the main here oh slaver
sorry I'm not slaver
slaver is what's coming out my move
cause I cannae stop salivating right now
even though I'm like super dehydrated
but
there's a tactic to
me being dehydrated
it means I don't have to pee as much
as I can be here and max out
the swordfish run
yeah cuddles you're too subby
you're not a good bat corrector
oh no they they get their way
I'm sorry they all get their way I couldn't
as long as they're happy I'm happy
I get
I genuinely get a dorphins knowing that
they're happy or they have what they need
em that's all I'm
all I'm thinking about
I am excited for
emmy's toll stream
I know that sounds really odd
as a sentence but I want to see
her little toes cause her hands were
fricking adorable on her
cooking stream
em
mercy might be doing a hands
cam at a later date
so I'm excited to see that I'm like
oh but does everyone's hands look like
I feel like my hands are so like
login skully all
em but everyone has like
such beautiful soft looking hands
like oh
friggin I know icy hand cam stream is gonna
go nuts I'm like
you know in another life I'm probably
you know
I want to be an og stand up with it
oh I keep doing that I want to be an og
stand like up with the og sands
em but I'm pretty sure
icy has like totey hands
totey means like miniscule
tiny
wee like she has
I'm pretty sure she's got totey hands as well
oh speaking of icy hello
hi icy how did your stream
go on your
your space channel 5
I'm gonna be honest I've never heard a space
channel 5 lamal
em
but that's the pressure
hi snowberries hi icy
please do rest icy if you need
go to sleep please feel free to sleep
she's got doll hands probably
yeah I was just saying
to them icy that when
if and when you want to do a hand cam stream
I already know your hands
are like so friggin precious
and tiny and adorable
em I was saying that
a emmy
is sorry twins em
emmy is doing her foot cam
stream this week which is hilarious and I can't
wait to see her little
toes to nibble on
em that's absolutely terrible
I'm so sorry emmy I probably
say the worst stuff about emmy
but it's because
em I'm
I'm biased towards emmy's
design the most because it's like
if I had a lighter voice
it's everything I want to be
Gimli
Gimli you need to give up
it's been like an hour now
of me howling
icy ended up doing a full set so
awww did she answer all the
OG Sans question
the worst part
is that you're not even sorry
I'm not hi snowberries
em emmy
is currently live if there's any mods
that can do a link to
emmy stream emmy is currently live
playing the coffin of andy and
laly I believe she is about to finish up
the last chapter and get the correct
ending there is only one
true ending to that game
please do feel free to check out
emmy the now she's probably doing something
much more interesting because
I am currently ranting
and raving my head off whilst we are
cooking and burning the absolute
everyday lights out of these swordfish
em
we currently have a stack of 10,000
swordfish thanks to an
incredibly kind refling
literally spawned in gave me it
and then disappeared
he's gone he's not even hanging
about he's like nah I just have fun with the swordfish
stick emm
so yes snowberries please
do not be afraid to check out emmy
she's doing something a bit more engaging
a bit more fun emm
so please do not be worried at all
about yeah I'm gone
alright alright sorry sorry sorry there you go
Morgan Morgan
yes we are
just doing 99 cooking
we are currently
emm and
sorry it must have been a refling mention in the money they gave
me in chat I'm sure I read someone saying
I gave you that and then what
emm we are
59 cooking we have a stack of
10,000 swordfish which was
which was not cheap at all
not cheap at all
we are currently cooking through that and I am
ranting and raving
my head off
emm just about anything and everything
emm
but yes I was currently gushing about
the girls doing hand cam streams
now that sheby's monetised
I actually don't know when she's doing her monetisation stream
emm
hold on let me just
let me just ask her when
are you doing
monetisation stream because I might need to put her monetisation
live
emm eeps
eeps because I've not put her monetisation live
emm and before you're like wait
you control monetisation
no in order for the girls to be less
stressed I do the
kind of boring stuff which is opening up
memberships and setting it
the price and adding her emotes to her
badges for example
emm hey fart head
hey shit
emm yes
so if sheby plans on
doing it the day
I will have to quickly run away for 5 minutes
and quickly set that up because I don't have
access to her account
on the cp your cash is
20 times the cost of that swordfish though
I know but I didn't do anything for the cash
or the swordfish
I just came I just got here
emm
wow level 60
wow
that's amazing
frickin 60 how many
are we burnt or burned
percentage is going up
cause I know swordfish is a bit harder than what was
cooked
we are still doing 1000 an hour
it is possible
I will beat the swordfish
stack before
emm
eh
just saying the chat that gave you the
JP is 20 times killer than me
emm yeah basic management
tell me said
emmy said she is doing it tomorrow
yes emmy and I say I am putting their stuff
live probably after
the stream
because I need it to go up 24 hours
cause so youtube says they need to
approve the membership tiers
but they don't approve nothing
they literally
can go for it
level 99 by the end of the stream trust
just doing endurance stream right after closing the
endurance stream honestly
eh
I could never do this I'm just giving it a
shot it's always been a childhood dream
of kinda like reaching 99
in any level as you can
see we haven't even touched any of the
member skills but
or my combat is so low
but
literally having it up here is really nice
emm and I picked
cooking because
I have incredibly
baby memories
of me being outside the back of
Lumberge castle
and I had my
pickaxe I had my tinder box
I had my little basic
bronze sword
and I used to
kill the big rats outside the
back of the castle cook them
and I think the highest cooking
level I ever got was 40 as a child
emm
which is just freaking adorable
which is why I want
cooking 99 first cause I've just
enjoyed it literally these gender
norms have hands of course the wham
and picks cooking oh we're about to get
to 9000 the stack
is getting weir it's getting
smaller getting a wee wee
stack burnt swordfish
is probably worth more than cooked
on the open market these burnt food
collectors are pretty oh I'm aware
about the burnt food collectors
emm and they just give you
a price for it which is pretty crazy
emm
fire making is probably the next
fast this is winter tot
yes that was a ghost
fires in winter tot or am I making
that up
I might be making that up I'm gonna be
going crazy
emm
my current level is 60
on the dot
I did title the stream 70 question
mark but someone did
napkin math and said if I finish
cooking all these swordfish
I might be 78
which is just fantastic
truly
emm
but I thought the cooking thing was a
meta meme like mommy knows how to cook
there is the proof I mean honestly we could
do it that way as well but I kind of did it
is like oh these gender norms have hands
I just really enjoy cooking like I know
there's this in real life
runescape chick and she has
massive knockers I'm talking
a zero level knockers and I used
to just sit and watch her cook
lobsters and like so many
people would come in the chat and say such
horrendous things when would be the best
food for winter tot so we
keep all gimli
give it a rest darling I can't
have you in the room
she's up she's losing it
she's losing it
I don't know if it's coming up in the microphone
or not but she's losing it
this is I shouldn't have let her in
because now it's going to take a couple of days
for her to unlearn that she's allowed in
this room gimli
I can't hear her okay she's currently behind
the door going
basically
um
she should have given up by now
it's been
it's been quite a while she should have gone
to sleep I wouldn't be honest
I should have
played with her more but I ran out of time
because I was making a cup of tea but I did feed her
and I threw the mouse
a few times to give her a few laps around to
her dog she's not a dog
she's a cat
hmm heaven
forbid some tatas
admit it we're all gimli
I was kind of I was like
talking to um
Viggo
and how he gets really
excited when I finish a stream
um and I was just talking
to him and I'm like oh baby boy
and I was petting him and he was purring
and I was like I need to
I need to I've got two baby
boys I've got refling
and I've got baby boy Viggo
um and I need to split
my time between
um between his
um so it's really adorable
he's such a good boy honestly
he's like um
D refling are you there muggers
wait talk to that man
whoever D refling is because he'll give you jewelry
um
cute female kangaroo called
Kimberly she's a refling
to never give up
but she's got the she got that dog
in her
cat girl is someone from Gimli
I was actually gonna do
an in real life video
where I put um
a licky lick on the 3D
ears and then both my cats will lick it
but I don't know if
YouTube will be weird about it because
I don't know what's going on
what you're looking in YouTube right now
it's absolutely terrifying
um
I don't
keep messing that up sorry oh my god
I'm not I'm not time maxing
okay she's now knocking on the door
Gimli
don't do that
ah mum he's no impressed Gimli
didn't he do that I shouldn't have let her in yesterday
it's opened a can of worms
oh
um but yeah
can we see them the next hand cam
you saw Gimli's back
in the foot
in the celebration stream near the end of it
you saw Gimli come in the room
but I had to take her out because she was gonna knock over the webcam
um
I do have a picture of them
um they killed a rat
um
so I thought Gimli was the hunter
but no
Vigo was the hunter
he caught a rat in the garden
I don't even know
it was there and he
destroyed it so quickly
um
I'm pretty sure he like
so if he didn't know the way that cats hunt
is they apply pressure
on the throat of the
prey
so basically it gets
either suffocated or you know
damaged out which is a shame to say
Vigo
I let him out in the garden
and within 10 seconds
he had perished
the rat
I didn't, I have a picture of it
I'll maybe post it but I know people don't
like seeing dead animals so maybe it's not too nice
maybe I'll put like
a little black bar over the rat's eyes
just to protect its identity
you know
and eat and respect its wee family
um
damn though, put it in my base
cat almost knocks you
honestly
um
wait, cat almost knocks me
are you that fucking fanny
honestly, if you are, go and just leave me alone
um
but yeah we
uh
wee family, wee Vigo
mmm
is there somewhere we can
send cat pics? I mean you can just
at me
it's fine on twitter
uh
honestly
honestly honestly
my cat is being a menace
to the local bird population
it's illegal to let your
cats outside in Australia
or I don't know if it's just
in Victoria
but it's illegal to let them out
so I have a
caged off
which is such a shame
but I'd rather they get outside time
than no outside time at all because I actually don't think
it's natural for cats to be inside
um
but yeah, they made it illegal
Australia does have a wild cat problem
oh my god, it's so sad
I wish I didn't learn about it
but they basically call wild cats
instead of just doing capture and release
because it's like so out of control
type thing
and I'm like
although it's kind of like learning about cat island
in Japan, there's
a tourist state island called cat island
but the problem is
none of the cats are fled or looked after
or new urge so the population is completely
out of control
oh my god, Gimli
she's doing my head and
oh my god
Gimli
I know
you guys might not be able to hear her
she's going absolutely berserk right now
she should have given up like a long time ago
and gone back to sleep
what have I done? I've created a monster
because nobody wants to see Marshal no more
he's chop level
I don't know the rest of the words
oh my god
I can't think when she's me on
wait hold on
right
I don't need to do her monetization
of the
video
okay I don't need to worry
about sheepsters but
I will be putting M.A. and A.C.'s
thing live
praying that a speller member names right
but I'm pretty sure it's
Snow Bear
Ease
and
Pin Pals
to be further driving the berserk thing
I just think it's very
dramatic
you've been telling me I've been breaking the law
for the past 23 years and didn't know
apparently it's going to slow
and England just made it
that your cat has to get microchipped
now
and I'm like interesting
but what's the real reason behind
that because is it just
another tax on pet owners
oh if you're a pet
owner and you need to use litter
by the way like a litter box
you know how it's really expensive for litter box
like pellets
and all that
play sand
cats love to take big massive dookies in play sand
which is the cheapest thing ever
it lasts so long
especially if you can have an outside litter
tray for them if they have access to outside
you will save
literally hundreds upon thousands
of dollars over the years
it costs
eight dollars for a bag of sand
and it costs 20
for a decent cat grit
just give them sand they love it
you can scoop it it's super good
and it saves your pockets
so much money
because there's such a tax
on pet owners
the only thing I haven't figured out yet
is how to get good quality food
because
I was actually thinking of making like
homemade cat
the fire is gone
no
rifling what happened
wait let me pick up the ashes hold on
oh wait I can't I've got too much swordfish
wait hold on hold on
I'll pick up the ashes and take them out of the way
I need to put them out of the way okay
now the ashes are out of the way
no the embers have went out
I've just picked up burnt fish as well by accident
slim cuttles
or strongy shady
excellent cuttle stones bearer
em always
thought it would be cute to have a big chalky cat
oh well thanks for the tip
I can't even remember what the tip was
thank you for putting the fire back on again replaying
it's over
they didn't kindle the fire now it's the age of darkness
crazy concept
go fish
the riflings with happily taste test
your homemade cat food
yeah I've wanted to make homemade
thank you for getting me back on the subject
cause I completely forgot what I was rambling about
em
I wanted to make homemade cat food
because they were struggling
to eat like that pre-made stuff
and the thing
this sounds really bad
but on the
boxes of cat food it says not fit
for human consumption
okay
now the reason why that alarms me
is because I would never want to give my cat
something that I couldn't eat
and cats eat meat cats are
wow
thank you
thank you riflings for funding my cooking habit
em
eh yeah
I just find it a bit
hmm and sus
that
it's not fit for human consumption
when the content is just
supposed to be meat that's possible
for cats to eat
which I don't like
VV buys a rotisserie chicken
my cats didn't like
Willy's chicken I fed them it
actually you know
who liked Willy's chicken more than
my freaking cats
the magpies which I've yet to name
em it's
a husband magpie
a wife magpie
and a daughter magpie
that visits me
oh no
rifling
oh no it's the rifling afk
that normally does like the big log pile
wait I'll clear away the ashes hold on
there you go it's out of the way
wah
I keep clicking collect
bank banker take that out
then take it out raw
ooh we're at 9.8
fire fire fire
we're so on fire
praise the fire
praise the sun
em
pet food in general is a rarity
let alone
affordability hmm
it's like ridiculous pricing as well
like I'm not happy with the price as well
em but I thought it would be really cute
to make like
homemade cat food for them
it wouldn't be the best but like I've seen
this youtube channel
I think it's called Joon's Kitchen
and it's literally dedicated to feeding
the cat's gourmet
homemade food and it's the most adorable
thing ever and I'm like that's what I want to do
for Viko and Gimli
em cats are hyper carnivores
yes carnivores I almost said
omnivores but omnivores is both
what's
vegetarian
oh wait what oh sorry I did that
I was pre-firing I got excited there
ok we're now 9.7
let's go 9.7
oh hydration check
my voice is starting to waver a little bit
herbivores that's right
that's right herbivores for
dinosaurs is
vegetable
hmm
oh dear my voice is breaking
and we're partly even got started with
the injured stream you
just friendly reminder
in the link in the description
M.E.B.Zoo is live with
the coffin of Andy
and Laylee a very fun and
unique experience video games
storyline and plot very unique absolutely
no one is denying that
I'm lucky I work as a cook
I just bring home
food for leftovers
and it's free most of the time
yes oh my god when I used to work as a waitress
the best part
was like getting sent home with all these
treats and food and aww
it was so good
oh man she's almost at 6k
so am I? wait what happened
I was 5
I was 5,000 yesterday
hold on
hold on let me do a new batch
where did we celebrate in 5k
wait how popular did that freaking
ASMR video get
am I missing something
am I trying
hold on
where
that ASMR video got 18,000 views
I only have 5,000
subscribers
what
what happened
what did they get
is there a tag it got picked up on
hold on wait I can
ah I can't see
if there's a certain tag it got picked up on
what
how bizarre
um wait
let's see what the analytics say
ok that traffic
source browse feature
other youtube features
channel page suggested videos
and external what's browse feature
is browse feature like
in the feed in general
eh
hold on let me do a new stack sorry
I know you can't see the stats that I'm looking at
is browse feature just like
in the side window
probably hit the algorithm
oh good
oh
I'm at 6k I've not even done the first thank you
celebration
wait hold on let me
screenshot this so you guys can see what I see
you can see
I'm not a
I'm not a secret kind of creator
I'll show you what I see this is what I see
on the video it hasn't updated
the
where is it
it hasn't
ah that would be too easy
wouldn't that image
make source
this is just youtube
stats video I guess
ok
and then pick this one on my desktop please
is that it this video
wow
wow on air
you see that
holy
on air
that got pushed so much
look at browse feature
76%
browse feature my goodness
but look
it says I got 300 subscribers for it
the money hasn't updated because
it takes like 48 hours for the money to show
wow I didn't
not expect that
the fact the watch time
is 1.8k hours
if you didn't know to get monetized you need
3k watch hours
holy crap
maybe gen 2
should come out with an ASMR video before
debut but kind of ruins the voice
although saying that you hear the voice in the trailer
in the shorts anyways that's not much of a deal
because it might help with the culling if the girls
came out with an ASMR video for gen 2
um
nice when quality is rewarded
but look at that
browse feature source
that's pretty nice
sorry my tongue is rumbling
if you heard that
um literally
I've not even got my first thank you for
1k out yet
oh
oh my god yeah
wow I'm 5800
I literally tweeted
thanks for 5k yesterday holy crap
that's insane
your trailer
hooked me pretty hard
well I wasn't lying
during debut and I was like you'll be eating good
if you're an ASMR enthusiast
it's unlikely I'll get that first
video out today
because I'm doing
AC and Emmys membership when I get
offline and then probably collapsing
unless
although I will say it's really fun editing
my thank you
videos because
I'm not making it
super professional and like editing out
all the bumps I'm just lowering the bumps
in that so it's still like on the same level
the culling was so
silly it was
absolutely insane on AC
I mentioned this yesterday
so don't worry if you didn't hear it
but AC got called
1500 subscribers
and on the same day
I got called 700 subscribers
even though she had more
shorts out like I was pushing shorts
on AC
at the time
that's just crazy
do you love a cheeky bit of ASMR
it was so rough
on AC but she's been doing fantastic
honestly
I am
still interested
in a clipper program for the girls
I'm just waiting for the first month
of income to come in and then I can
kind of open up pie charts and be like
right is this going to be
possible for Vehler to do
a clipping program like Idol N has done
because I really like it I think it's a really
good way to get clippers involved
and help promote the girls
and all that jazz
I think it's fantastic so
we are still looking into that
and hopefully it will give the girls a cheeky boost
I've had to resub three times
I had to
subscribe back onto the girls at one point as well
I was like bruh we were
literally all each other's first subscribers
and I got booted off and I'm like great
you've stolen it from me
absolutely stolen it
I hope those missing
1500 OG suns
find their way to her
honestly though
I'm sure they will I'm sure they'll be like hey
wasn't there a cute polar bear around here at one point
if
you interact with the content
like leave a like on stream or leave a comment
then the algorithm
will show the girl more to you
so if you are
an OG sun you're like
her streams are never showing up please do consider
like just going on her
short feed for example
wait don't like this stuff
right away like genuinely sit and watch it
because if you don't sit and watch it
then the algorithm knows that you
are just sitting there
it's really annoying but the algorithm
is now too advanced
because
before way back and much older
YouTube days if you left the like
you left the like
but now the algorithm is like
this person left the like at the 2 minute mark
maybe something interesting
happened 2 minutes in
okay because of that statistic we're gonna now
promote this video
to people who
have interacted with this
VTuber because they're related or something
like the algorithm just gets so
silly
I'm dying for the Hypno Viz
the Hypno Viz can actually
go on YouTube. YouTube allows Hypnosis
Patreon doesn't
make it make sense
but we love YouTube out here for that reason
it's very strange
very very strange
probably the first hit
sorry here take this burnt
burnt swordfish
the first ASMR
I'm gonna do is forget your name
and replace it with Reefling
um
I will not
make it a permanent effect
I will make it
a session I think maybe a 30 minute
session if you will
um
and I'll give maybe give it
like 2 hour effect I really
do not want to do mess around with permanent
effects too much it kind of scares me
permanent effect stuff I have to be honest
I'm a bit of a scaredy cat
ooh our burn percentage is up to
I think it's holding steady at 15 though
and hopefully
lower as we get more
leveled up
um wait no Hypnosis
no Hypnosis is
ban it is a
bannable um
offense suspendable
if you will um
there was a ASMR
artist actually that got their entire
Patreon taken down not even
a chance to
um appeal
or uh get suspended
and then delete the content sometimes
Patreon will suspend your account
until you
your content applies to their
TOS so if it's not too offensive
whatever you've done or made
um but there wasn't ASMR
recently who got their entire thing just
taken down which was pretty
crazy just making me
permanently less procrastinate
yeah honestly only
a bit of mind break I feel
you yeah
chubby uh weight gain
that got taken away
um which was
crazy absolutely crazy
I'm not sure
I mean I
I can
see why
because sometimes the stuff is like tie down
to a chair and funnel fed or whatever but
it just gets
ridiculous because whoever's participating
or creating especially for when it comes
to audio side of stuff like no visuals
no nothing like
it gets pretty ridiculous like
that you can't do it like
but anyway uh all healer
mastercard overlords
yes yes yes yes yes you win
yeah again you win you win again
hey ho you win again
um
who's thinking up all these rules and
restrictions are overlords
don't you not know about them
see there's this company called black rock
and then there's a second company called
I've forgotten the name of the second company
and they own everything um
and uh
oh wait until you learn about politics
oh my goodness can't wait to get started
about the political
side of thing and no I'm not getting into politics
but I'll get into destroying the
economy and we should restart
society or run away to
a farm together I'm more
opting for the farm side of things
um
because yeah I think the farm
would be a heck of a lot better option
um
CNC is not okay
with Patreon which happens yes
we are 62
thank you 62 it's
nice to see you 62
um
but yes um
so people from an outside
perspective think
hypnosis um
you don't do anything you
don't want to do when it comes to hypnosis
I am a full believer in that
I absolutely do not think
but because of the way it seemed
comedically in the public eye like
for example when a magician
does hypnosis oh look
they made this person drink a bottle
of vinegar type thing
um because it's seen that way
publicly when the reality is
when you participate in
an alternative context
you do not do anything you don't want to do
this is a fact it's just
how it works you
like people seem to think
like you completely just like oh
you're inhibitions you can't control
anything you're so and it's like no
mother that's not
how it is
all reeflings
all together and put a money in
oh should we buy a castle
should we
where should we what country
though I want to see a castle
in Scotland but um it's very hard
to although saying that if we
had a green a glass house
a greenhouse then we
could have tons of um
produce maybe
we should get a castle in Scotland
and then we can have
a big garden and we have like we feast
on the meals every night and we
can try and make me for the first
time
uh black rock van
garden
those are the names
quick tooth and
squiddle kingdom anyway if I can't get
banned because I've started talking about black rock
it's been a good run been a good run yeah make sure
you support the girls uh
all hail our overlords um
yes
um we can try and
learn to make meat but I feel like
I'd poison everyone if I did it
oh
someone just leveled up congrats
15.8
did that go off I thought it was
15.3 I was hoping it was going to go down
it
it was fun it was fun well it
lasted it was let's go castle
with a farm yeah could you imagine
um like we all have our like little
bedroom and stuff and then when we need
gen two to be made we just turn the
lights off and see what happens
I just want to say some things but I refuse
to say it that might get you banned
shove it in my marshmallow then
show me what I want to see
I want to cultivate tea
oh my gosh and I can make
honey tea for everyone
and then you guys get to know
what honey tea tastes like when I'm always like
oh I want honey and you guys can make me
my special honey tea see there's honey
tea in general and then there's special
rifling honey tea I need special
rifling honey tea because my throat is
perishing and I'm sure it'll help because
it's full of vitamins
um oh vitamins
yeah um
so we need that as well
because apparently it's full of
vitamin what vitamin
is it filled is it vitamin E
you need to give me your vitamin E
rifling come on come on get it
out wipe it out right on the table
just like that
mummy needs her
mummy needs her special
honey tea although I
should actually write an audio like
that holy crap why have I not done
that yet I'll do it this month
because there's a myth in there oh I just
really started really hard I said myth
if you hate that oh my god
there's a missing audio this month I'll
make that plot the audio this month
please can I make that the plot for
Patreon this month where I need
my special honey tea
oh my god yes
um in
February I know February
so far away but I actually have a meta
audio roleplay month
as well but yeah I'll
make it my missing thing
uh
I do want to care for
a little garden yes
so um there's a lot of hardy
plants so hardy plants are
considered plants that can tolerate
close to frost or very
low temperatures
um these hardy plants
are things such as potatoes
leaks these root vegetable
type things um
what's another root vegetable turnip
very big um neeps and
varieties um
is turnips and potatoes
these are very successful
hardy plants in Scotland
so these are probably what we'll focus on
and make up the main majority
um berries, strawberries
um and
blackberries for example
these berries are actually quite
successful in Scotland
against all odds
um because
they're quite resistant um
is really quite fascinating
um there's a lot of strawberry
production and manufacturers in
Scotland if you didn't know that
a little fun factoid
um
potatoes, boil and mash them
stick them in a stew and we make
a big dinner and we have nice
yummy dinners every night
um a carrots
yes carrots a fantastic example
a ground vegetable yes yes yes
um
wow
9.4
we're about to hit 9.3
we're about to hit 8 we're getting so close
we're getting so close
uh gollum would be fuming right now
so the leaks are a winter crop yes
um
and we can also have like garlic
and I can teach you about the drying
process of garlic as well
um but we would need a shed for that
surely one of us
we flings are like DIY
and can make a shed although
oh my god we're like getting two steps away
from being Amish at this rate
I've not even been funny because
like the Amish are known for like building
stuff really fast um
but like I'm sure
if all of us rooflings came together
on the castle farm we could build
a shed and then I can teach you all
about garlic uh
curing you need to dry out the
garlic because if it's wet it
will rot but if you dry it out
successfully the garlic will last
an entire year from
harvest season to the next
it will last an entire year it's absolutely
fantastic and we need to get massive
freezers to freeze all our produce
so we can do massive meal preparation
as well how big of a shed are we talking
it would need to be decent
um
I'm too scared to learn about canning
food because I've heard about
it literally perishes people if you mess up
the canning process however
there's one process I really
like and it's
dehydrating
food so you're left
with the dry
husk of the food basically
but I trust that and
apparently that stuff lasts
20 freaking years if you
put it away right
dehydrating food lasts 20 years and I'm like
oh my god
um
I'm like absolutely right this is
just me being a weirdo I absolutely
love the idea of like a zombie
apocalypse now don't get me wrong
I will perish within the first few days
I will be bitten I'm sorry I'll just
admit it there's no way I'm not that good
I'm not that guy trust me I'm not
that guy um
but I really like the idea of like
having food reserves and like
um I think they're called
a bug out bag yes
a bug out bag
um I
freaking love the idea of a bug out bag
and like all this like food that's like
good to go is it MRE kits
I wouldn't mind trying an
MRE kit taste testing stream
that would be funny like a hand cam
MRE thing um
that would be curious
and then we can judge it from different places
because apparently South Korea
has the yummiest MRE kits
uh America has neutral
I think UK is neutral
maybe France might have something better
MRE
clogs your intestines
oh no does it
I don't know
oh like space food just add water yeah
like space food we can try space food
as well when we try the MRE kits
rating MRE kits live cam
I just rate it and then like
say like a bunch of like stereotypical stuff
about the nation that I'm rating
um
my life wouldn't change if a zombie apocalypse
happens just close
in the house to it for seven
yeah I really like the idea of
dehydration food because
it lasts years which is
just a mind boggling thing
to me like I absolutely love the concept
of it um
I just
find it so fascinating that we could
preserve foods like if you think
of our ancestors who had to live
on a yearly crop basis
and like if your crops were
messed up you were in trouble you had
to find a trade quick like if
you were a lumberjack and you cut wood
or you sold
I don't know you sold yourself
but that trade really didn't
uh still doing it today baby
keeping
my ancestors proud
um if they're lumber
um probably fire could chop
in probably root harvesting
like harvesting mushrooms from a forest
like if you knew what ones didn't hurt you
um it's like
4800 calories shoved into
a box I wouldn't be surprised
wait really maybe I should eat our MREs
cause
I don't eat properly recently
I've been really strong I don't
no ehh ehh ehh ehh ehh ehh
reflin reflin reflin
do not tape
doom
do not tape doom
I will talk to you openly
and honestly I've been struggling
to eat a little bit until
things settle down
I'm very happy to
say my A-bomb has calmed down
it has calmed down
it was preventing me
from eating properly
basically
I could start eating but then I got
adrenaline burst which stops
me from eating cause I'm not hungry when I get
an adrenaline burst
but I'm very thankful to say it's subsiding
I've managed to eat a bit better
recently
but no doom
no doom
ok
9.2
oh we are doing it we're doing it
the stack is going to be gone by the end of the stream
mark my words
you keep activating our worry mode which is why
like I
what level are you now I'm level
62 which is fantastic
no doom here we're only winning
glad to hear you're eating but yes
so I because now the girls
are getting monetized I feel
a lot of relief
a lot of like
all of it off my shoulders cause
I was worried that the designs
that I had given Shibi and Azura
are going to prevent them from earning
money for a month but it's not
happening I'm so happy to say
it's not happening cause Shibi got monetized
which is absolutely fan
fantadelastic truly
fantastic
I am very happy about that
please take care of yourself
yes I am doing thanks
still feels like doom stop it
reflying stop it no doom
it was because
I was so worried about monetization
because
the girls
I've kind of said it
a lot of them are wanting to
move out
and I think it's actually very
possible
for the first month but we needed
youtube monetization just to really
elevate it
and the thing with youtube monetization
as well is that the vods can be
the vods
the streams like if someone
watches back the stream
well the girls get like some of the money
from the ads as well so it's like generated
free income you do not have to actually
physically you know
hand over money to the girls
because you generate money
for free watching their asmr's
their asmr's are going to go up shortly
and I forgot to do mercedes
I'll need to give mercedes hers that's what I'm doing
I'll put emmy and ac's membership live
and I'll put mercedes meme video
unlisted so she can upload it whenever she
desires
and I'm gonna doom no no no
no don't doom
I have about a tiny speck of doom
why would you doom everything is going so well
the girls are getting monetized
emmy and ac are about to do their celebration
mercedes celebration was
fantastic
someone was gifting her 50 bombs
which was insane
no dooming on main literally
no dooming on main
everything is just gone
so fantastic
I tweeted out like thank you for 5k
and I was saying like all that self-doubt
and everything is just melting away
which is true it has
generate money for free
yes oh my god
please don't ever feel bad if you
can't genuinely give money
you don't understand
you interacting with posts
you're promoting them more in the algorithm
you're watching their asmr
if you watch an ad
the girl gets money
for that
it is just
please don't ever worry if you can't handle
money
I always say like oh I'm always streaming
for free you don't have to be a member
the membership streams start up next week
but you don't have to be a member
to consume at all
type thingy
scrawny I care about you and the girls too much
I'm always gonna worry
no you're sounding like me
I was worrying over them
I was like full mummy mode
thankfully I got an 8 hour sleep
last night
oh my god
why I probably sound
a bit tired
I woke up at the last possible minute
for stream not because I don't
love you because you guys always go
mummy's late she doesn't love us anymore
no I
took medicine to put my ass to sleep
and I got a full
8 hours and I'm so freaking glad
I got a full 8 hours I'm like
oh I feel so good
it feels so good to get a full 8 hours
to sleep
but yeah
mummy loves us
is the mercy meme video
be a problem did youtube unlist it
no it's not out yet
I need to upload it to her channel because
I subtitled all the meme videos
edgeville bank
that was to the theme of 64 zoo lane
which is a british TV show
or was I don't know if they make new
episodes but yeah
so if we
like commenting streams
that helps yeah it helps like
immensely like so
to give you an example
ic does an
ASMR stream
you like that stream
and then emmy does an ASMR stream
youtube algorithm goes
hmm there's a connection between
these two girls they've both done
ASMR and this viewer both enjoyed
them to leave a like
and then the algorithm goes
hmm this
other youtube user
both enjoyed these two girls
I'm going to start recommending this
user these girls
em and then it's kind
of a knock on effect so
em
youtube will recommend
someone who's never consumed
ic's ASMR before
because they liked emmy's
ASMR and then
that also goes further ahead to
other vtuber ASMRist for example
the algorithm is like
an insane tangled
spider web of a mess
em
and anything you do will
affect it so for
example
if you go on twitter right now
and you type in emmy bezu
and it'll pop up her twitter
you've just affected your algorithm on youtube
because unfortunately
em websites completely
cross platform everything whatever
you type in even if you go to
rule 34 and type in
the girls name you are
you will affect the results
of your youtube browsing experience
because of what you've typed
in on other websites as well
em
it goes
very deep but unfortunately
your websites are all interconnected
whether or not you want to
whether or not you say like no to
cookies no to this they are connected
it's undeniable em
does youtube listen
in the chat too so youtube
will see
you interacting with me on chat and it'll
say this user like
strony well em funny
enough this other vtuber
is like strony i will recommend
this person strony
another version of strony type
thing em sorry i'm not very good
with my words at the moment em
we'll probably
we'll do a tinkle and a refuel
at the 3 hour mark em
i'm definitely going to make another tea
and i'm going to get some yummy yummy snacks
em
i bought
a nature valley bar and i'm like
is that the worst snack to eat on stream
there's just going to be dust everywhere
are you stop looking at me misspelling
your name how can you not
strony kettles
strony
kettles
strony kettles
how can you spell it wrong
but yeah like literally
if you go on twitter
and you search
vealour
again you're manipulating the algorithm
when you go on youtube
you'll probably have a few more vealour streams
recommended to you on your page
or down the sidebar
because the algorithm knows
that you have an interest in vealour
it goes so deep
unfortunately cookies are just
websites are such liars being like
we don't track you via cookies
only the essential ones you
liar you liar it's just
the way the internet is these days
we're just such shame but
em
for the last week
i've been getting ads regarding the scotland
honestly
come visit scotland
this scotland tourism industry
come to edum
actually i think edum
is the most expensive than glasgo
although it's probably
it's such a small amount
of difference
so if we're watching like scottish youtubers
we should get more scottish youtubers
em
i actually don't know about getting
really super rare
imma just say this on behalf of all
scottish vtubers right now
a lot has to go wrong in your life
in order to become a scottish
vtuber
now to become a vtuber in general
that's perfectly normal if you're any other nationality
if you're scottish
and a vtuber
bruh whatever happened in your life
i feel for you hen so if you're a scottish vtuber
listening in i feel for you hen
don't worry i went through it too
ha ha
you know
i am only
aware of two other scottish
vtubers unfortunately
they are not for me
content wise
definitely not for me but that's just
my yeah that's just me being me
em
definitely not on the same page
when it comes to
thought process
or like how we were raised
and all that
you can kinda tell when you hear someone talk
you can kinda tell
the way they've been raised in scotland
which sounds terrible
sounds almost classic but i'm not trying to be like that
i'm just trying to be like
i don't know
you can
tell when someone doesn't gear
and then you can tell when someone geyser
and i'm much better with
people who don't need geyser
you know
if i infect other people's algorithm
em
i suppose the only way
you can do it
oh we're almost at 8k
is
by posting
youtube shorts in particular
in locations where it's appropriate
so just say you're in a general vtuber fan discord
if someone were to
watch that short fully
you have successfully infected them
algorithm wise
em
because they consumed
that content it's fascinating
honestly i actually am quite
interested in the infection
side of it but yes
you can successfully infect someone
the vealor virus
em
em so i just
wrote that comment
yes you can affect someone by doing that
if they have never consumed vealor content
em
but you maybe make clips
of the girls and they click it for the first time
because they got recommended or you post
in a discord that's appropriate to post
the vtuber stuff or maybe
a vtuber reddit
actually there i think there's
so
vealor do have the vealor reddit
but it's not being publicly posted yet
but i sh
i don't know i mean literally i was just gonna
do everyone's oh sorry
this is why i can't talk and think at the same time
em
there is a possibility of just posting it for memes
but we were gonna have to put it on approved
posts only
because it can get nasty pretty quickly
em
and i do not want any of the girls to be
subjected to anything
nasty
let's go infect some replaying
i have no idea what you're saying
but i'll take your word for it thank you
is edinburgh a bad place no it's not
it's just more
rich
and sometimes rich people
are not very empathetic
em but that was such
a mean and nasty generalization
when i say rich people i'm talking like
multi-billionaires
multi-billionaires type stuff rich
em the average do everyone's
empathetic to one another each other
but if you're not very empathetic please don't worry
i'm actually gonna do an educational stream
on human nature and empathy
empathy is a practice behaviour
you need to practice empathy to get it
you need to
flip the switch and be able to
have abstract thoughts about empathy
as a whole
and i'm actually going to challenge you guys
and i'm going to make up scenarios
where you need to be empathetic
and you need to give me a reason why you feel empathetic
but i'm going to make the scenario
super hard so at a glance
you're like that's disgusting behaviour
that's
but
but we have to learn
to be empathetic and we have to think
about why the person
may have behaved that way
it'll be an interesting
concept either the stream will go terrible
and everyone can laugh at it which is fine
i don't mind you guys are allowed to laugh at my
stream ideas because i have a pretty bizarre
concept sometimes
oh man we have a place like that too
in Milan never got Milan
so it's like London but smaller and prettier
yeah it's pretty old
there's a lot of older architecture
Edinburgh is turning people
into an English city in regards to the most posh people
i definitely
feel more comfortable in Glasgow
and good old Glasgow
mutual comfy
disgusting and
i'm going to pull the lever
and make everything worse
what does that mean
the Scottish accents kind of come from
yeah so
the more slang you speak
statistically the more povo you are
and it's completely normal
to be in poverty in Scotland
the statistics
are 1 in 5 children
are growing up in poverty
however i actually think the statistics
is probably going to be 1 in 3 now
so it's
completely normal to be
impoverished when you grow up
it's absolutely nothing out of the ordinary
anyone's rich type ideal
i like that
i like human psychology
that sounds pretty interesting
are you trying to get us to empathize with some scoundrels
no nothing bad
but i want to
oh no
oh no the fire
wait let me pick up the ashes
i will clear
oh no you've already cleared the campsite for me
thank you refling
wow we're at 8.9
we are getting through it
oh look i burn
you dancing
who's dancing back there
no i burnt 98 lobsters
because i had 500
hold on
thank you fire maker
you're so on fire feeling hot
hot hot
you're so on fire
anyway look at the drip
what about my drip my goodness
look at the eyes
that is hilarious that they're just blobs
honestly i love this game
that's so good
i heard a lot of good stuff about glassy
yes firepog
flames yes
um
is currently british english only a thing
wait sorry isn't current british english
only a thing because they didn't want to be associated
with the nobility of the plague
yes there is a very
viral clip that
a guy is being interviewed
um
and
oh god what was the word
i can see the interview in my head
it's an english interview
and the guy
speaks what we call
posh english
and then the guy replies
tomorrow that's it
the guy goes like tomorrow
and then the guy replies tomorrow
it's like not trying to correct him
but he's trying to be like wow
look at the difference in this regional accent
but the problem
with it
it's not that problematic relax before you're like
well steady on you've got blue hair haven't you
nah relax i ain't got blue hair
calm it fenny's in on the opposite of me
um
the kind of thing was it
is because posh english accents
are associated with wealth
are associated with grammar schools
for example a grammar school is
a rich person school
high education school
public education is kind of
associated with not necessarily
pro but if you can't afford public education
you can't afford it
um
so the guy was like oh
look at this accent
this man clearly
you know wasn't educated
in a grammar school type thing and that's
when it becomes a wee bit of an issue
uh received pronunciation
uh
it's them also calling it the queens english
yeah just finding out
it's not glass
wait glass go
it's a shame
it's fine if you accidentally name a city wrong
like edinburgh
and edinburgh is normally pronounced
edinburgh
by folk who don't come from here
that's perfectly normal
i'm sure i say all these
applications in different countries wrong as well
like arkansas
is arkansas and like
mississippi and
what's another state in america
um road islands
um colorado
i'm sure i say it funny so please
don't ever be embarrassed if you say it funny
um glass go is said glass go
but in the
regional dialect it can also be
glazga um
don't ask why it's glazga it just
texas yeah i'm sure i'll say
uh i don't know
if there's some locations
in the states that i can name
uh anaheim
is a place in
california because they
hold conventions
i'm pretty sure there was some
anaheim convention at one point
if i ever visit the uk i'll go to
glazga honestly it's
like such a nice although edinburgh
is pretty good for tourist stuff like
the edinburgh castle and
the edinburgh museum are pretty close together
um
did you say wheels is
associated with posh no wheels
in wheels wheels
is associated with kind of like the mining
towns and all of that and the
the welsh accent
i can't do
what is the welsh accent
i can't think of a welsh uh sentence
specifically to start the accent
have you had a coke and rum please
oh no the only example
of welsh accent i have
is this little
britain skit where the guy's like
i'm the only gay in the village
because he was like was so proudful but
i was like no don't be silly that
guys or that girl
or that lass like type thing and he's like
i'm the only gay in the village that's the only
exposure to the welsh accent
to be honest which is absolutely terrible
um all of a sudden
we're drifting up to the northern island
uh heavenly father
who art in heaven hello to be thy name
today we're gathered with the reeflings
at hedgeville uh we're currently
cooking up a storm with swordfish
but we still have a high burn rate
my burn rate is 17 percent now are you
joking why is my burn rate
getting higher i'm leveling up
wheels is associated with sheep
i will tell you the reason why wheels are
associated with sheep it was
elite well it's illegal to
steal a farmer's sheep it
wasn't at the time many a year
ago to um to
have um
actions with a sheep
which is why
people would pretend
that they had had action
with a sheep instead
of stealing it because you can't
get arrested for actions but you could
get arrested for stealing at the time
okay that is why
poor welsh people have to deal with
that stereotype and it's such a shame
um because it's not true you just
need to know a little bit of history to understand
a little bit more
abridonians profusely
sweating aye what is it abridine
abridine can he kick her jelly
absolutely short in behaviour
stealing was the death penalty
yes okay that would be it
it was even more severe than i originally
had anticipated
i shan't be in scottish i'm getting
the football off i
said oh my god sin
i have bad news i might have to delay our collab
into july
because of work reasons
because of each of our agency
reasons you'll have to forgive me but
i do have my shock collar for it
but you're gonna have to give me some time
i shan't be in scottish
wow
we're level 64 and we're
got a total level of 150
level 2000 here we come
i'm kidding we are not
doing 2000 there's no way
i'm not even talking to you ever again
sin i'm sorry
i don't even have you on my fricken account
oh no i've just went in the
discord someone's getting banned
from someone everyone's chat
for being annoying oh no
reflans
i hope it's not one of you
someone's getting banned
shawnee had to reveal
to me alive in front of millions that she
hates no what the heck
you're such a reflans sin for saying that
reflans are oh mommy hates me
i need to delay it until july
okay give me till july
give me july sin
and then we can shock each other with
collars do you have a heart rate monitor
by the way i was gonna wear my heart rate monitor
so you can literally see my heart spike
every time you go
she hates me
what if i die before you
better not sin
i'll be raging are you joking you've just got
that 3d model on every hand
i honestly i love
your 3d model streams i don't know how
you're not exhausted by the end of it honestly
i'd be shattered after like 30 seconds of
moving around i'd be like right that's all i've got time for
it's been nice reflans but i gotta go
and rest i need to lie down
band check no
i wore a shock collar for 10
oh no i'm
i'm not i don't even
i don't even know how big we're
gonna get it done
sin will always be
a reflans
did you kicked my
toenail off the wall a few times
um
what a
what's your community name again because i remember
when i when i saw you getting started
it had been
named something
but i don't know if you're still named
that and i don't want to say the name
okay it's imps now okay
it was something else
um it was something else
way at the start and i didn't want to
say it obviously
can suspicion i know he's getting banned
just do a couple of them clapping
with no hands audio sounds like
you got a good workout and brah
i was so out of breath recording
that like horrifically
out of breath
like you can literally here we go
like
clap clap clap clap clap clap
basically i was
so bad
i was so bad
man
what level did i just get 64
wait why can i not kick this
yes oh my god it was
it was suggested
sin cells that was it i didn't
yeah i'm pretty sure it's an incel
and um
what's that other word simp
like a ban phrase on twitch now
do they still do that do they still
moderate that
i remember it got banned and i was like
isn't that
like i don't like the word simp
because i feel like it's used anytime
where a guy just genuinely enjoys content
from a girl which is so like it's quite
frustrating because it's just like
i don't like the terminology
but to like outright ban it
is like what did i miss a few
yeah twitch doesn't allow those words
but i've never really tested it out
you can get banned for it that's pretty
um
yeah like i'm pretty tired of the
word simp because i think it's used whenever
someone just genuinely enjoys content
that just happens to be from a chick like it's
really
but anyway i think outright ban in it is like
a bit severe i just hope
that the definition
slowly changes over time did someone just
talk there no
maybe later oh wait was that for me
oh my god i wasn't paying attention
ebes was that for me
uh
the moderation
is inconsistent say the least
yeah it's why i don't really enjoy
twitch a lot of people right why not
twitch why not twitch but i have seen countless
examples of what
how they don't apply the rules
fairly at least with youtube
it does seem like
a overall blanket
which is very easy
to be like oh okay right because
like um now i'm aware
that you're looking isn't allowed now
i don't know why
older videos that are made eons back
are fine but recently not
no like azura was eating
a cookie azura
was eating a cookie and she got
a warning for um enjoying
a cookie just because her voice is so
silky smooth um
it's definitely being generalized to any sort of kindness
towards a person but especially women
yeah like it's why
i'm i'm pretty tired of hearing about it
to be honest like i think it's overstate
it's welcome to because it just
gets used to oh you enjoy
any type of content from women
and it's like bro
i'm just here to enjoy the runescape streams
like my god i'm here to enjoy the rambles
and how we're going to take down
the big banks um
i prefer youtube twitch
reason sub prices oh my gosh
yes at least with youtube you
can decide on membership price i
see that as if i didn't begrudgingly
raise my price by a dollar of
pure rage but i will make it up
i will do as much streaming
as i can to to earn that money
um
but yeah twitch
just seems to be taking
a sin moving to youtube
if you type in
twitch that you're
an age you get by
100% yeah
it was a very
mmm mmm cookie indeed
can't eat a cookie on stream
youtube is really crumbling apart
thank you thank you i came up with
that myself thank you hi reeflings
oh it's the person that i actually got
the name reefling after like five hours
hi reefling reefling
no no i came up with that joke
myself i promise it totally
totally wasn't uh
how is she looking how is she looking
sideways is she supposed to be looking
sideways
i just really she's never looking
why are you looking
to the side i know maybe she got
like a sore neck or something that's okay
yeah i didn't miss the
yeah
it turns out all i had to do was open
the application in order for it to make
noise i accidentally
closed it the other time i tried it
and couldn't figure out why
she's so shy she can't look us in the eyes
honestly like look into my eyes
not around my eyes
yeah
it's like when you see a guy call someone
a simple watching girl and then you look
and they watch some big muscle male streamer
for nine hours a day but that doesn't
count
allegedly glorkin hard
on it but
he's a whammin bad but male
good
bruv we're tired
bruv let's just enjoy let's just enjoy the
conspiracy through okay let's just enjoy him
if it makes you
a simp for listening to me
coconut my cheeks
and make them clap for 15 minutes
and hey ho
then hey ho
snakes and stones may may break
my bones but you'll never get
more quality content
from another streamer
when it comes to ASMR no that's a lie
that's a lie
oh 8.6
8.6
bronze
my issue with twitch at the moment is
something about the vtuber
yes that was a recent tos update
if you did not hear the news
vtubers now
must
conform
to the attire
rules of in real life streamers
but the problem with that is a lot
of vtuber models you know
they have a bit of appeal to them
a bit of personality on show if you will
and because of twitch
is incant who goes there
inconsistencies
it's very hard to ascertain
if
oops sorry whoa
how do I do that
hold on I'm just gonna check
if any of the girls
are streaming
please
be advised
that shibi
cajun boom
is live with vampire
masquerade 2 mods
I give you permission momentarily
to
post the cheeky link
or if emi bezu
playing coffin of andy leily
endurance stream
and also holding in her
urea
there are 2 other
vealer members live right now
please do not be worried
if you cannot watch us all
once I heavily recommend watching
the other girls first
because I am locking in
an endurance stream today
thank you very much vealer mods
please do not speak ever again
actually you know what mod appreciation
and ironically
I do appreciate all your hard efforts mods
thank you as much as I am a little meme lord
please do not
I've locked in for a 12 hour stream
you will not see me offline
until 11 hours and 55 minutes
cause that is exactly when the vod breaks
em
so please do not be afraid to watch
my gen mates and enjoy them
and then you are welcome to
come back to me at any time
whoa this person got gardening
gardening isn't got
a freaking cabbage on your back
aww you got green cakes
aww I forgot to buy his green cakes
we should probably buy green cakes
aren't the twitch attire standards
based on what you are? doesn't that mean vtuber
need to... yeah so
on twitch
you can stream in a bikini
if you are in a pool
or a hot tub
so that is like saying I could pop
up on my bikini toggle right now
and put like a hot tub asset
and then I am good to go question mark
like that seems pretty redundant
em I will close that cause it is kind of
covering up
em
don't forget that twitch has the hot tub category
which is only worth watching
when some insane guy in a lab coat
show oh no the fire
we got so distracted
we got so distracted talking about the
um
let me take the ashes
so they don't get in the way
I thought ashes got in the way of cooking
am I going crazy did I make that up
fire
thank you much
more depreciation
I completely forgot what I was saying
in real life youtube is
barely having a time I feel like they get away with
anything
youtube is definitely more
wait am I dumb
youtube is definitely
so much nicer than me
em
it's just the facts bro
I'm sorry you can argue
to a wall cause my burn rate
keeps going up
stop
stop burning
you shouldn't be burning
em
I'm here for the long haul
oh yeah you got endurance for 12 hours
abusing mods
streamer abusing mods
but they like it though
don't you mods
but you can't speak
this is a one sided conversation
em
I think all the girls got extra mods
by the way so do check your discord
or whatever you applied with
I have no idea I didn't handle the mods
so if you got picked as a mod congrats
wasn't it me
em
but do check cause I think
3 people didn't respond
even though they were super keen
em
twitch
admins have their favourite
mods and shambles
tell me about the dude with the lab coat
in the bikini
wait is that real
gotta get your hair blow up
there are potions to help you last
longer
oh my god that's terrible
mods aren't real they're like birds
post what you want
alright I do have mods
we need to keep things above board
ok
another mod flexing on you
by deleting your message
lmao
and slap
I don't know what the lab coat thing is though
twitch feels better
as a dedicated streaming site
but the actual infrastructure management is awful
yeah I would say discoverability
on youtube
is so much better
in my opinion especially
with the shorts algorithm
I would say on twitch the only
way I could
you know foresee
someone
em
fore fore see
foresee someone being
em
discovered
is the raid option
which is called redirect on youtube
if you get
a streamer that is kind enough
and is massive and raids into you
it can literally
make or break you as a streamer
it's pretty insane it really is
em
I have told the girls please
to always raid into each other
to keep a train going
if no other talent
is online then you're more than welcome
to raid into another agency
no problem at all
like I
yesterday called in a favour
with a friend
mimosa
was it yesterday?
no it must have been the other day
she was so polite
and I said look I'll raid into you
but do me a favour when you finish up your stream
raid back into a violour girl
and she said that is more than happy
with those terms and I was like yeah
I'm more than happy calling a favour for a friend
yes I
absolutely don't mind it at all
the v and u girls have been absolutely
fantastic some of them have been
raiding into me I actually need to start
messaging some of them and being like hey you have
3d o microphone question mark question mark
em
I still find the violour mentality
of mods please do this thing thank you
now please be quiet affectionately
yes em
it's very
I don't want to say jarring
em but for someone
who may be new to stream
and
the streamer
is having a repertoire
but a back and forth with mods
that are named it's a bit not
isolated but it's like
it feels like you've missed out on lore
and it just gets harder to enjoy the streamer
like someone could be lurking watching
me for the first time right now
em and just being like
was she all about type thing and if I'm like
oh mod x mod this mod y
mod b mod c and like
cracking like you jokes all the time
em like it's not
very
enabling to come in for the first
time
em whereas I quite
like the mods don't speak
but we are incredibly appreciative
for you you know mopping
mopping the floors
and making sure everything is good to go in
stream yaw
em
do shorts still work for discovery
emory said they
attached dead people to the channel
no
emy isn't entirely wrong
but she isn't entirely right
shorts
definitely have a subscription
subscriber count
effect
em and they also have discoverability
not all shorts people
who will subscribe to you will show up in a
live stream that's just facts
some people purely enjoy shorts
mind rot and they will just
watch shorts and nothing else that's
perfectly fine so emy is both
right and both a wee bit wrong
it's very good em I do
have
brah I have three
shorts editors and all three
of them are busy for a couple of weeks
and I could absolutely smash their faces
because I need help I don't have
editing skills
em I think I'm going to have to reach
out to an editor that I like
to style of
because I'm drowning
I need help with shorts and I do not
have the skills for it nor do I
have the time for it but I'm
now that the girls are monetized I'm wanting
to
close through em I'm wanting
to start pushing out shorts for the
baby girls now em to help
with overall sub count
we are going to put some advertisements
into the shorts as well so
some might have more views and others
and we'll take it from there
look it's just a kind of
em my current goal once
everyone has done their celebration monetization
stream is my current goals I'm going to
get everyone to 5k subscribers
em
which
shouldn't really be
too hard
em I do have a collab
ASMR that's going to go on AC's
channel em which should help
boost her a little bit em
because the culling was just so
wait we're going to approach the naughty
number soon
any naughty number approaches me
em
new viewers feel like they are walking
into a friend group yes
it definitely
em
especially whenever I
kind of
talk I like to say
oh I spoke about this yesterday but
don't worry if you weren't there
because it's also quite
nice and kind language to use
for people who may genuinely
who couldn't have been there
em
types of how do I keep
doing that I don't know how I keep doing that
I'm being such a silly bully with that
em whoa
8.4 okay at 8000
I will call a break
and I'm going to pee get a cup of tea
get some snacks em
and hopefully Gimli doesn't
come flying into the room the moment I open
the door but I think she may
em
if the streamer is only talking to their moz
that's fault the rest of the chat
your sub count will be inflated
but it's still a net positive it's a positive
overall I
I'm happy to see this publicly I
really want to get play buttons for the girls
I think
I would absolutely love that
em
it'll take time
it will take hard work it'll take dedication
but em
I will show the girls what
is working for me what has worked what is
working em and
you know
if they do shorts with me if they do
ASMR collabs with other girls
em if they do
zoom collabs with the girls
em I think it is very
possible I actually
do not see it as an impossibility
if the girls let me cook and
equally they also cook
em I think it would be
absolutely lovely to get the girls play buttons
and before anyone
asks is Veeler holding the play buttons
eh no
why I'll say it again
I
would never
ever hold
a beautiful symbol
of their hard work their dedication
their love for their craft
their love for their community
from the girl
absolutely not pointing fingers
but
I think it is very clear
there is
corporate greedy agencies
that care about accolades
to prevent them
from to prevent their talents
from holding such a beautiful symbol
and then there are
agencies like Veeler that says do whatever you want
here's the money
basically here do
you want have fun here's your money
here's your play button
em yes
you don't want the play button on your
giant mega yacht no
I absolutely do not
care for that
right I have to ask I actually don't know
if it's real I only hear it from the memes
is the yacht real is there actually
a yacht or is it or is it just a meme
hello do you plan on playing
Titanfall 2 absolutely
it's a fantastic game
I would love to give it a
a shot
for the first time as Stronu Cuddles
meh meh meh
and we can see BT
together and this time
I will get uppies from the correct BT
and not an enemy that
freaked me out because I could have sworn
it was
nah it's a meme
okay it's a meme okay I thought it was real
I thought it was actually
real and someone was like oh my god
this person owns an actual yacht on the
back of these VTubers hard
work and
I don't know who it is
you know who you are
whoever keeps telling me
to save the blue one
I can't
my guy for one
and two LaMalle
you're starting to
I'm starting to think you're just daily
asking that in my Marshmallow
so I keep bringing it up
I cannot save anyone
I cannot save them all
but those who seek
the violor route
I will do anything and everything
in my power to help you
achieve your dreams
and I hope my girls are
ready to test to that
I am happy to
discuss that I always root
for the underdog
and I think
you should too always root for the underdog
sheebie
sheebie has
finished her masquerade
part two yet did you finish the game
in like under an hour
hello sheebie and harem
hello
shriebsters
we were talking sheebie
about you getting monetization
and how proud I am of all your hard work
work
but sheebie went to go
oh is she okay
oh she got migraine
oh no
oh poor woman
she cried herself
so much happy tears harem
that she gave herself a migraine
the following day
oh poor sheebsters
I hope she feels better
hold on let me send her a message
I'll just put
harem have told me
you're not well
please lie
down in a dark room
hydrate
and possibly caffeine
might
help I don't know I heard
chugging
one gallon
no I heard chugging one litre of chocolate
milk also
destroys a migraine
but I don't
suffer from them so please
forgive me sheebie
I'm dumb
but I hope
you're okay and I'll
take care of the harem
well
you feel while you rest
up there we go
that's literally my thought process in typing
hello harem
thank you for joining me yet again
mabzoo
link in the description
it's currently live with coffin of andy
and lele
the snowberries that joined us
a bit earlier
and
if you are I'm doing
a 12 hour endurance stream so if
you do not feel so inclined to watch
me cook sardines
to cook 10,000 swordfish
do not worry I'm not in solid harem
please do check out
mabzoo her link is in
my description as long as my description
is comfortably correct
or if you really want to help the
youtube algorithm type
mabzoo in the search bar
and it will do wonders for the
algorithm and pushing violaer to you
yes I am not kidding
that is very true if you type in
the search bar on youtube
mabzoo that's I
M M Y
space B I S O U
she is live with the coffin of
andy and lele she's doing the correct thing
and she's also holding in her urea
for her chats
satisfaction I'm not going to judge it
look I'm not here to judge
I'm just here to deliver
Brian
wait
no message but Brian
Brian
okay thank you for the tip
Brian but there is no
message so Brian didn't talk
really interesting and good to know
yes Amy is doing the correct ending
to Andy and Lele so if you are
looking for a bit more of engaging
engaging gameplay
then rip for Brian
I'm just here to burn swordfish
to be honest yeah honestly I'm here to burn them too
18.1% the burn rate is going up
I'm not
beating the burn rate allegations
they're not doing too well at all
but thank you for the tip Brian
less robotic please
that is how I type
it's the only way I can get words out
and stuff it's terrible
I have like really
poor
I have really
poor I don't mind
talking about it I always talk about it
I have problems reading and writing
which I don't you guys
are more than welcome to poke fun at my grammar
my English my spelling it does
not bother me at all because
I get to be like a smug little
about it and be like oh yeah
I've got problems reading and writing and yet my
entire job surrounds reading and writing isn't
that hilarious and I get to be smug about
it because it's like oh well
it worked out so far even though I can't
do it properly
but I
please don't ever be like oh I'm scared to
poke a little fun at me or whatever
you're more than welcome to it doesn't
it doesn't
what if I search Azura
what if I search Azura doesn't appear
her channel though no you have to type
her full name we've only been out
for a week the algorithm isn't going to know you're
asking for Azura delay the VTuber
you have to type Azura as a
ure a space de ure
de a e te there you go Azura delay
I know it has a T
in it unfortunately it is French so
you drop the T wow wait wait wait
whoa whoa whoa whoa
French and Scottish people drop in the T
in their pronunciations what's going on here
no
I simply type the surname with the double
L that's the problem
Katoos you gotta
give them the government name oh
silly how silly how could you forget
scrolling
Pinterest
and it's just AI generated pics
of koalas with big
what wait what
did you type in one of our
VTuber names and then came up with that
by the way strongy since I never
played Rinscape could you sell me on it
number go up
yippee
it is a slow incremental
game although it well depends
on how you want to play it I
am literally just cooking
I'm cooking away look see this little
progress bar cooking
I'm currently level 65
and cooking and
I
I'm watching
the bar slowly go up
and it's beautiful
and I get dopamine
every time I says I level up in the game
it's gorgeous I just can't help it
I'mma be real I'm not even here for the
gameplay I'm here for rambling while I play Isaac
I thought about doing Eden Isaac
runs shortly
for like a shorter stream idea
if you didn't know the most
Isaac runs last one hour
so I thought maybe for a shorter stream
I would purposely do a four hour
stream so I can redirect into Emmy
because I never redirect
into Emmy I finally got to redirect
into Azura yesterday
and but I never do it
for Emmy and I can never do it
for Icy unless I pulled an all
nighter I might pull an all nighter
so I can say I redirected into
Icy just to be a smug little about it
but I wanted to do
a four hour stream so I can redirect into Emmy
at one point because poor Emmy never gets
redirected in my reeflings
are never exposed to Emmy
and what sentence
I didn't even mean that sometimes I mean it
when I say sentences and sometimes the
sentences just have happened
I thought dropping T was an American tip
not the harbor
don't remind me of all
that beautiful tea
this is a preparation but she cooking
for real for me
everybody feeding the fire to keep up
yes special thank you to the reeflings
that are just helping stock a fire
this is making this go
so fast like so so fast
so thank you for all your help
I do appreciate it greatly
ummm
but yes
okay say no more I'm sold
and yeah Isaac all day every day
in November I'm warning you all now
November stream sniping week
I'm not even kidding I want to play Isaac
back to back to back to back to back to
12 hour endurance
I've not done that
oh no I would have to do all my
membership streams in one go
unless I make a deal
with membership people
hello scrawny
first time chatting just came here from
shebeestream hi harem
she wasn't holding up
no she has a migraine
I honestly I don't know
what reason she has a migraine for
because I'm pretty sure migraines have no
rhyme or reason but I'm like 99%
sure she was crying
happy tears might have affected it and she
maybe is pretty dehydrated right now
ummm
an hour for a run mine last like
5 minutes I suck at the game oh don't worry
wow
micah's big fan thank you for the
10 gifted membership congrats to those
who caught it with your face
if you are lurking
you might have a thing that needs to enable chat
but congrats
thank you so much for the gifted
membership enjoy the emotes
there's 10 emotes right now
I will be last to update
my emotes because
the emotes artist is taking their
emotes and unfortunately they need a month
so it goes I say
I mean mersey shebeezourame
for updates
on emotes but the girls get
to pick their emotes now I'm not going to ruin
any of them because it's not my business anymore
to ruin or spoil the behind the scenes
ummm
the hypno cult rose
did I catch it you didn't catch it
with your face rip
rip and piss
but yes if you are
lurking and you are a member you might have to
enable it from chat
whoa I only burnt 3 that batch
that was a really good batch hold on
we are cooking
by gas reeflings we are
oh my legs fall asleep ow ow ow
my legs got those like tingles that really hurt
ow
and before it's a blood clot
oh my god if the blood clot goes to my lungs
and I die I just want to say I love you reeflings
I've had an amazing time
the girls get to hold the rates to their IPs
and let them just have
100% of the money I don't care I'm dead
at that point so ow that
freaking hurts I don't know what I did to my leg
also
give sin sister
all my youtube accounts she can run it from there
it's fine
give her the veal
account while you're at it as well why not
don't say such a thing
bruv I don't know why my leg is sore all of a sudden
I doubt I pulled a muscle sitting
on my leg the way I usually do
I don't normally do any of that
I love you too
no I'm not allowed to die yet
you know if death ever comes
for me I have to say hey death look
now's not the time the reeflings need me
and then he'll go aww you're right
you're right and then death has to
back off okay
maybe clapping with no hands
contributed to it
no I actually did that about
a week ago
I think
about a week ago
sorry thanks which leg
your massive third leg oh yeah you want me to have a big
third leg for you
come here reefling
mommy wants to play
some things I say things that I'm like
that's creepy not the other way around
put it on the table right now
pooch
scrawny I can't die I'm too busy
literally I am too busy
to die I'm not even being funny
have you ever heard those stories where
people are like in a coma and they're like
close to passing away but then they go
like I'm sorry I can't die right now
like my family member is going to be
pfft or like oh
I'm too busy to die right now and then
they wake up from the coma
have you ever heard those stories they're pretty
crazy you can't do
that I was caught by surprise away
I worked
we will kill
death to keep you safe scrawny thank you
I appreciate it
no I am far too busy I'm
I'm not going to say too much
because I want to respect my
my girls my gen ones I've obviously
doing a lot cooking actually that remains
many to go ask for a collaboration from another
VTuber and I have no idea if they're going to accept
they might accept they might not
hey ho we'll try
currently gen 2 is cooking
and yeah no I'm not naming
them you'll be happy to know
I'm not naming them
but it's very
busy trying to maintain everything
all at once
but I did say I'm a workaholic
and I really
enjoy working I
enjoy giving value for money as well
especially in this day and age
where everything's getting
greedier and greedier I'm like no
we're going to do a business tactic
called undercut in the market
yay
undercut undercut
that kind of thing
damn the hey ho gets moved
hey ho let me finish
my point now
I really like pushing myself
to offer value for money
it's why even with membership
streams like on days where we do a membership stream
I'm still going to do a cheeky 2 over stream
for it
and then we can enjoy our
more cuddly membership streams
I have absolutely no issue with that
it doesn't bother me none
and life is good
we are bingchining
bingchining
undercut in the market
love
as I said a bit earlier
but for the harem
that might not have been here when I was rambling about it
I was saying that even if you
cannot physically give any money
to the creator you're watching
just liking the stream
or subscribing to them
or just hanging out and lurking
all of this contributes
to the algorithm and leads for the girls
to more success
especially vaude watchers
special shout out to vaude watchers
especially if the girl streams
in a not good time zone for you
if you go into
mersey's comment section
there's like one dedicated vaude watcher
and I'm like you are helping her out so much
I understand
watching live stream vaudes
is not the funnest thing
because the person isn't live
but a lot of you are saying
you kind of listen to me ramble in the background
that is perfect
because you engage
with the content for long periods of time
again boosting the algorithm
for the girl
having cross promotion
with the vealer girls
it's just fantastic
it really is
12 hours of content for free that is value
yes like I don't mind it
now it's absolutely
it's not I'm very serious when I say this
this is absolutely not a reflection
on any other
VTuber streamer whoever whatever
I
do not find
this to be a job
okay this is
fun I'm enjoying myself
I am breaking my voice
rambling to you talking about
all these plans I've got cooking
talking about how things are
like this doesn't feel a job
feel like a job and I feel
sorry for streamers
where it does feel like a job
and they can't publicly come out
and be like that
wow 66
maybe that should be my
donation
like a tip sound instead of
are you squiddin me right now although actually
I quite like are you squiddin me right now
no thanks
to the time stampers
oh yes special thank you to time stampers as well
VOD watchers
for any of the girls this applies
to any of the girls seriously
you
do not go unnoticed especially
on ASMR stream
time stamping on
ASMR streams is very good for
me
because I do have plans to
clip the girls ASMR
I'm currently
in talks with someone to do it for me
but the problem
is you know the profits
aren't the profits won't be there
for the clipping ASMR thing but
you know what we'll get there
all of the
violour girls are perfect for background
noise you all have very beautiful voices
oh thank you
I'm sure all of us appreciate such a kind
comment like I love her mixer voices
accents all of that
to go wait what's
1700 to go the fish
oh no
wait what's 1700 to go
clipping ASMR
ASMR is a good idea yes ASMR
is a very popular category
so
did Emmy get the right route
pin pals and Emmy
did you get the right route
did you get the right route I said
route instead of route
hi Emmy hi pin pals
don't worry you don't have to talk too much because I think you're
bursting out the seams so please feel free
to go to the toilet at any time
the pin pals mouths are open
we got the right route that's why
that's what I raised you for
that's what I birthed you from my loins for Emmy
that's my Emmy
hi pin pals
yeah a pin pal came into my
stream and tattletailed on
Emmy saying that
the pin pals
are not giving her permission to tinkle
pin pals
what do you see to such
accusations pin pals
per Emmy's
bladders about to
break
no no you've been
tattletailed on
oh she went snitch a
oh no scared that's right I'm on it you pin pals
you don't think I'm watching you you as much
as you watch over my little sister
I need to watch over you too
no one was supposed to tattle
we were
discussing it we were like
yeah it's quite an interesting
interest snitches get stitches
well pin pals already have
stitches haven't you seen your adorable design
you know little stitches
over here I plead the fifth yeah
you better plead the fifth pin pals
you're in trouble
just to keep you up
to date with what is going on
on this lovely occasion
AC has finished her
stream
sheebie
has also finished her stream
unfortunately sheebie isn't feeling so well today
so don't be afraid to send your love to sheebie
and she has gone away
oh if I'm biscuit
okay
I'll trust you or that you looked after
your little sister
why only do
want Emmy's love
bruh has Emmy mind corrupted
you so much that's not even English but we
only do what Emmy loves oh right
sorry I'm just going in a canry
oh that was me that was me
that was on me I'll apologise
apologise pin pals that was on me
I'm getting
mine corrupted just thinking about Emmy
let me do a
hydration check so thank you for
coming in I am just doing
cooking on runescape not very fun
I know boring
boo
Azure
oh my god is that all the streams
wait is there no mercy stream
no
tell me you're lying
is there no mercy stream
shoulda picked mercy
she's playing
no there is a mercy stream
you should play in a prank on me
she's playing harvester part 2
I'll bean machine thank you for
becoming a member
she's playing harvester part 2
so don't worry
in
T minus snippets
any snippets in the chat
T minus
1, 2, 3, 4, 5 ish hours
mercy is coming online
I am
just playing runescape
please do not feel forced to watch it
I understand it's not the most exciting thing
if you are not into runescape
we are currently in world
380 at edgeville bank
edgeville
that's right edge
edge for me right now
bank and hydration
did I forget to put that burnt
swordfish away
we are currently
azura is playing straight
why does it not display
youtube is really
sorry
youtube is really struggling to show
me when the girls are going live
oh her thumbnail is adorable
oh look at what azura's thumbnail is
oh it's adorable
she's got a little
her hair on the cat
ok azura is up in 3 hours
just reach 69
how are you a higher level than me
did we not start at the same time
we can't be
we flinger at a higher level than me
yes
t-minus
for the bleeding hearts
t-minus 3 hours for stray
a lovely little meow meow game
and then
snippets
warning in 5 hours for harvester
who is putting
are we getting drunk hold on
hold on hold on hold on
let me drop this
let me get drunk right now
oh that actually made
i love that noise
we flings you're allowed
to go take a drink if you like
right let's use it on the fire
did you
select the funny all bell
on the sub button exactly
i don't see azura's stream
i didn't display for me either
i only displayed mercies there
i
i am under the impression
that we are going to
be added to holodex
soon which is a website
which will
list all of our streams
and automatically do it to your time
zone
so
that will be coming soon
if i'm not mistaken
i don't know how it works
but it means that it will auto show you
everyone's stream
violor we did consider running our own
website but
it was like another expense
that you know what holodex does it
for free and i'd rather
put any expenses like back into the girls
back into shorts back into promotion
there is for those
pin pals that are listening in
and any snowberries
there may or may not be an asmr
coming
for snowberries and pin pals
i hope you enjoy it
when it does come out
but there's a little hint for you
yes
holodex takes an average of
20k on all channels
as prerequisite
ok well we're coming for it
for any
yappening
that you may have missed out on because you are watching
the good ending
on emmy
stream
long story
short
azura
is the last one that we
are waiting for monetization on
and all of the girls have been
successfully
monetized i really started
through that one
and the monetization streams will be
happening soon tm
you can become a member as a reefling
you can become a member as a snippet
and tomorrow
snowberries and pin pals
you can also
become a member
because the girls are doing their membership
celebration
so please do not worry though
the girls will always be streaming for free
as well they will not be
exclusively doing membership streams
that's not how it works around these parts
but please do look out for it
because once my
endurance stream ends
for 12 hours i'm doing a cheeky endurance stream
once my stream ends
i am going to be the one pulling the strings
behind the scenes and opening up membership
so if you really wanted to get it
before the stream you can
but it's better to do it on stream
because the girls will say your name
do you want to hear the girls say your name
don't be silly
let the girls say your name
my wallet isn't paying waiting for membership
you can become a vill
oh okay
this isn't emmy in game before anyone
thinks it's actually emmy
that's hilarious though
we've got a pin pal
and they're waiting on emmy
singing
say mommy would you like us
to send you emmy's latest deleted audio
in maro what did she do
what did she do
what did my daughter do
what did i miss
peeler
did she just
did she just end stream
and then give you the audio
of the
bra
snitch it she didn't do anything
shut up shut up shut up
shut up shut up
hey guys
i knew it i knew she was doing it
she may or may not have been forced to
i'm like
i need to join in too but i feel like
my peeler
isn't going to be very fun because i
hardly have any liquids
i swear it from my hands and feet so much
oh i need to clip that
actually i need to clip that
fucking part of stream where the pop rocks
popped to prove how sweaty my feet are
i'm probably going to have to make that clip
myself actually now that i think about it
join them mommy
the allegations are unfounded
no who hasn't
tinkled yet
i have not tinkled
has azur i don't think azur is tinkled
can we return to burpler
and not be pissy
honestly
as long as the girls are happy
and uh
you guys are happy and everyone's happy
couldn't give less of a
couldn't give less of a rent
not no mercy
and no azur
okay
i found a new video very funny
oh did you enjoy it
i'm glad you liked it
um
for anyone
who is on my patreon
don't worry i'm talking about early access content
you will get access to this content
i'm about to talk about for anyone
who is a
patreon
membership link in the description below wink wink
i uploaded
a
interesting audio
where
i did clapping asmr
but without my hands
uh
yeah so you can listen to that now
if you so desire it's about 15 minutes long
i believe or 18 minutes long
yeah i heard the let me hold it
ASMR did you love it it got so popular
wait hold on hold on i have a graphic
to show you guys
boom no wrong one try again
where is it
boom
i have no idea how
popular that video got
i celebrated
5k yesterday
and that one video
has almost put me to 6000 subscribers
which is insane
to like absolutely
insane so you know
super thank you to everyone who subscribes
um i am a very big believer
in the
rising tide lifts up all ships
um
wasn't it 18 the last time you showed it
no this is this is like what i've got
like right now
um
i'm a big believer in a rising tide
rises all ships or whatever the saying is
um so i am very thankful
i will always promote my girls
i am very happy to say
merci's meme asmr is around the corner
so is emis and
aces
once the girls have done their monetization celebration stream
their meme asmr can go up
my meme asmr was please let me hold it
where i absolutely lose
my mind
begging you and pleading with you
to please let me hold
your fireman's hose while you take
up
um and it did
so well i genuinely
like i it has 18 000 views
but i don't have
18 000 subscribers
so it's like
doing so well i couldn't
have asked like a better kind of
result if you will for like uploading
so thank you so so much
strone you're at 5.88
right now jeez
slow way
i'm half of the viewers yeah you enjoy it
um
is that 19k views
now that's fantastic my goodness
i couldn't have asked for better
um we need to pump those numbers up
yeah no no that's more than enough
i am very happy so um
it means i get to promote my girls more as well
i get to be like like check out these girls
strone
there is an actual chance
that this being an endurance
stream will get you to 6k
i don't know if the video has got much
steam right now you should all hit the like
and subscribe button right now
exactly this refling knows what's up
um
wait i could let me show you
what the stat says now on the video
i'm happy i i
i don't mind i'm happy to share so
hold on let's screenshot this
yes
so this is what i see as the leecher
on the other side of the map
blah
um and then file say that
blah blah blah
right so this was
hold on
i'm freaking accidentally screen recording
i keep accidentally screen recording i don't know why it does that
oh hold on the refunds are talking
also hit the little bell icon
see you guys are better
at pushing that stuff than me
i like i forget to say
like oh like and subscribe
in this stream oh like i always
forget to say it even though i'm live for
12 hours i have 12
hours to remember to say one
sentence and i fail the
challenge every single time you guys are
just gonna have to do it in the chat for me
it's kinda ridiculous um
right so this is currently
uh
oh i guess it didn't update so you
can see like all the stats wait i'll update
it to the new one hold on
um it didn't update too much
cause i'm live
boom
so if you've never seen the behind the scenes before
this is what it looks like when you
upload a youtube video
these are the statistics
you get you get your viewers you get
your watch time you get the subscribers that
were directly earned
from that video so people
discovered that video for the first time and they click
subscribe because they really enjoyed me
pleading with you to let me hold
it as much
um the reason why
estimated revenue is not
visible is because it takes 48
hours for that statistic to update
if you guys really want to see it
i'm more than happy to share it doesn't bother me
none and
i and then you guys can
kind of see the fun behind the scenes but
yep um that's
what it looks like it says the video has got
18.7
51 views
like subscribe smash the
smash the bell member
share the video yes um
but yeah that
that is fantastic
you can see the little trend if you see that
right right side trend
and you can see when the video was
released it had the highest view point
and then now it's still actually going
pretty strong it's not
doing bad at all it really
doesn't um
but yeah i'm more than happy to show that
kind of cool behind the scenes stuff
you have went from 555
to 5.8 the stream
mmm
like that video is like propelling me forward
i'm hoping the same happens for the other girls
meme asmr
because i am not putting
any advertisement money into
myself i had to
at debut because we kept getting
called below the 1k and we needed the
1k for
redirecting into each other
um
crowd sourced
self promotion
question mark oh my tummy is rumbling
i forgot to get some
that's okay i can ramble
for a bit more um
but yeah
i'm gonna
miss the chat you're gonna miss the fact
the chat is slow oh no no no no no no
no no no no
you see i know how to gatekeep myself
and do you want you guys want to hear
i'll repeat this story as many times as you
like if i start throwing
out asmr videos people
are gonna subscribe for asmr videos
and then they're gonna say oh strongy cutles lives
i'm gonna go listen in
hold on a minute
this this
vtuber is ranting
about how we need to take down black rock
this is an asmr
i'm not watching this shit live
and then they'll only just watch the asmr videos
and just like that
i have gatekeep myself successfully
because i know how to do it
so you're welcome
you're welcome
that's right i've been sitting on this plan for a year
and i will scoop it from the rooftop
but that's the best part
yes because people will be like i want
i want asmr
but you're not doing asmr live stream
and it's like no no i'm not
what you're gonna do about it you're gonna leave
oh no my
how do you call it a tight knit community
oh no my tight knit community
terrible we're in shambles
even though i'm finding major success
truly in shambles i'm on my knees
but yeah you're welcome
don't think that will work for long
well you'll be surprised
i've spoken to other asmr creators
especially twitch asmr creators
i had a friend
who used to stream asmr
and
she got
700 viewers
concurrent on asmr
and then she went and played a video game
and she got 40 viewers
and the entire chat
was spamming
someone would come in and spam when's your next asmr stream
and then leave again
it tried and true
i'm aware this
and it's gonna happen
it's just
facts
that logic is flawed
how dare you
how dare you say i'm dumb
even though i'm clearly dumb
but i've seen it happen on twitch
yeah
yeah it's not that uncommon for asmr streamers to branch out
yes no
it's a tactic
because i'm always gonna be a gamer
i'm always gonna be gaming every day
actually we're playing lego lord of the rings
i can't keep quiet about it
it's too back to back
streams again
i'm so excited
because on the first day
we play through all the missions
and
get like 100%
and then we get to play in middle earth and it's so fun
and i'm so excited to play
so yeah we get to play lego lord of the rings soon
and it's like one of my top games
because it's just so fun and perfect
although it always glitches out at this one ice lolly place
i will show you what i am always glitches out
and it annoys me to high heaven
because i've played the game all the time
lego lord of the rings
is super good lego game
will you still play hobbit afterwards
yes
i'll play hobo
4x67
i'll play lego hobbit
at a later date
it's not my favourite because
if you didn't know
well now you're gonna know
and insert my knowledge into your mind
um
lego hobbit is only 2 games long
and it just
abruptly ends
there's no public
explanation
that has been released
there are only theories
as to why only the 2
lego hobbit
2 hobbit first movies
were made
into the lego and not the third
but warner brother
being shitheads
it's just a mystery
why the game abruptly ends
at the 2 movie mark
but it just
is what it is
so unfortunately
i do not fully enjoy hobbit to the same way
i enjoy lord of the rings
i apologize
they lost the source code
no
i'm pretty sure warner brothers
is it warner brothers
as one of them
were being
they were being very
there was a lot of production issues
with the movie hobbit and then to base
something off of the movie to get the rights
to do something it probably
was just getting even worse
the production issues on the hobbit
were insane
i've kinda spoken about it but peter jackson
he's the director
he became so violently
ill
tending the fire for mummy
he became so violently
ill
he lost a bunch of weight he developed stomach ulcers
honestly i felt like peter jackson
when we were developing gen 1
i was getting ill
i honestly convinced myself at a few points
i was like this is it this stomach pain i feel right now
i've done it i've done it peter jackson
and then got myself a freaking
ulcer in my stomach
do you like the hobbit
yes i love the hobbit movies
i love lord of the rings and hobbit movies
and we're going to watch if
on
christmas day we're watching lord of the rings
extended and then on boxing
day we're watching the hobbit
extended so i can sing all the songs
cause
boffer has an amazing song
when they're with the elves
if i can remember the first
sentence of this freaking song
oh and
also had a tipsy cat
who played the five string fiddle
he squeaked and he scored
and he quickened his tune oh wait i'm skipping
the lyrics someone needs to play the lyrics
of boffer's song
oh well
there's
an inn there's an inn
there's a merry old inn
beneath the old grey hill
and there they brew a
beer so brown the man on the min himself
came down one night to drink his
wine
oh the osloor
had a tipsy cat
who played the five string fiddle
he squeaked and he scored and he quickened his tune
and the landlord
shook the man on the min
it's after three he said i can't remember the lyrics
you'll need to put the lyrics so i can sing it but
i freaking love that and i also hate
em and that's
what bill bull beggins hates
was it
blunt the nice
into forks
and burn the corks
that's what bill bull beggins hates
oh i love it so much
and then obviously misty
mountain far over
misty
mountains go
i just forgot i'm supposed to be a dwarf
when i sing i'm not supposed to be all the way up here
but i'm so excited i'm all the way up here
back down here
scuff the floors
honestly isn't the extended
like 12 hours original for the trilogy
then i might have to make a second
watch room but that's okay
em that's fine
i say again the siren can't
sing i just refuse oh yeah you think i can sing
yeah you like that
wait until we do drunk karaoke
you've been lying
you've been him
cold
i can't remember the rest
yes we'll do
drunk unlisted karaoke i think
at some point
and i don't care if i'm not hitting
any of the notes i don't care if i'm tone death
we are gonna have an amazing time
i will try and do it on a weekend
when we do drunk karaoke so you guys
can get smashed with me
i was gonna say shit face but you know
you can get smashed with me
and i will take
song requests
but we need to do it in advance so i can learn the song
because if you guys start asking for me
like rap m&m
the best i got is green day
okay i got none more than for you
other than green day
thank you so much turbo the dog
for becoming a member i vote for misty mountain
oh i wanted it to be like hype drunk
we get like hype drunk on the weekend
like it's been a long
it's been a long week for you guys
i'm about to head off to bed please rest well
yes rest well however i appreciate the gaps
see you when you wake up in the morning
the misty mountain cold in the trailer made me so excited
for the movies and there wasn't enough singing
if you listen to the extended editions
there's a few songs here and there
and gandalf sings the song from the
books as well
it's like oh the
the road is long
that talking
thanks for becoming a member i appreciate it
turbo the dog i already said that
what your donkey kong picture
no listen to a
rap god
smash and mome
unleash the stress
so you're not gonna sing rap god and godzilla
and scott absolutely no there's no way
i can only do like old school m&m
and i still need the lyrics up on screen
because i won't be able to do it
like efficiently what's her burn rate
oh it's going down
18.2
i'm pretty sure her burn rate was 18.7
2k
donkey kong
dk
donkey kong is here
he's finally back
to kick some too
oh dk
you want the scottish version of donkey kong rap
i can't remember
yep
drink on and start singing them bars
literally
i can't wait to myself
believe
that's planet air
turns
slowly
it's hard to stay
say i'd rather stay awake
when i'm asleep
actually i'm gonna do a meme song cover
you guys inspired me during
my james cameron's avatar stream
i am going to make
a meme song cover
of drumroll
secret tunnel but scottish
the artwork for it
someone drew a meme artwork
of me which i need to reach out and ask for permission
to use for it
but someone drew me
and then in the next frame
i'm blasting a scottish meme
and i want to use that artwork
in the music video
so
i'm going to see if i can do it
so basically
two lovers
i'm gonna get someone to mix it so at least i'm not
monotone deaf on it
forbidden be one another
and i'm actually gonna have to
write the lyrics out for the music video maker
because they're gonna be like
what is fey
from fey
secret tunnel
through the mountain
secret secret
secret tunnel
basically it's gonna be like less than 50 seconds
but i think it's funny
little question for mome
are we eventually going back to needy streamer
overload for other endings
mmm
maybe a membership stream
i don't want to play games
i've already done before
but a short game like that
is very good for membership streams
in my opinion and again if you're not
membered and you're listening please don't worry
i stream for free every single day you get free content
you get content out of the wazoo with me
okay just let me cook give me time
i just need a bit time
just need a bit of time yes
give me some time
yeah
a bit of time
wait
when are you planning to do the first membership stream
next
week once the schedule goes up
you will see the membership streams
i will have it listed on
the schedule there are three
membership streams next week
they are all at different days
as well to try and enable
members to try and
get a little cheeky
a little cheeky
shot
on
coming to join
i will vary the days as well and i'll vary the plots
but it is a watch along
a member ASMR
and a
tier list rating for the first
membership stream week
we're going to spend an awful long time
on that tier list rating so i do apologize
it's going to be a bit of an epic
bit of an epic
mmm
thank you
oh how's the toe
i
i might be
losing my toenail
so
i went to the doctor
managed to go to the doctor all good
and
they've given me
an option
they've given me an option
i can either remove a side of my toenail
or i can get the whole
thing taken off
and they told
me that
if i get
the side of it taken off
because of the shape
of my nails i have what's known as
C shape nails i have no idea
if anyone listening knows what that means
i have C shape nails
which means i
am more prone to this
issue
so they basically said
ingrown toenail that's what they said
i thought she cut into my skin
but she cut into my skin
and down the side of my nail
which is why it was so messed up
so
i have an option
to either get it cut on the side
a little bit or get the whole thing taken
off
and i've opted to get the whole thing taken
off because i can't be arsed
hahaha
i would just still love me
if i didn't have 10 toenails
they said
it doesn't grow back
for some reason your fingernails grow back
but your toes don't
so yeah
they said the risk
because of my nail shape
the risk of me having this problem
occurring is pretty high
but i thought i had normal toes
but apparently i have unique C shaped
toes wherever that means
yeah you still love me
yeah for some reason
if you lose your fingernail
it will grow back
your toenails do not have this ability
today i have learned
so i have opted
just to get it yanked off
it's coming up in a few days
i think
after my buckshot roulette
i am perfectly fine to stream
i asked i was like
my toes built different
i said is this going to put me
at a disadvantage
will i be able to
i need to be in bed rest
and they said as long as
it feels fine
i feel well
i am okay to set up
i am completely okay
to set up and stream
because i still want to stream smile
hahaha
because
if i needed bed rest
but i don't need bed rest for it
which is good for me
just means we can paint your toenails faster
honestly
should i show what it looks like
once it's healed up
they told me the healing takes a long time
so i am going to be taking
vitamins
i also have been advised
i need to go sit out in the sun for 5 minutes
to get my vitamin D up
if you didn't know your vitamin D
your scars heal faster
if winds heal fast
not a scar sorry if a wind doesn't heal fast
it becomes a scar
but i looked up some pictures
of what toes look like
that don't have a toenail
it doesn't look that gross to me
it just looks unique
and
oh no the feet lovers
are in shambles with me
i am so sorry if you are a foot lover
i recommend imibizo she is doing a foot cam stream this week
i am afraid i can no longer
take over
yeah
so
it's probably never going to get a pedicure again
i am sure that surprises no one
the funny thing was
i had looked up
stories about going and getting
pedicures done
and i was like that sounds so silly
that's never going to happen to me
the one time i go
and get my freaking toes done
but i am not mad honestly i find it
quite funny like some
people might be like oh my god how are you laughing at this
i don't know it's just funny
like i feel like your body
tells stories
and like my story
is like oh i got a pedicure done
for my reef lens and now i have
night and toenail
like i think that's a funny story
like i think that's serious like your body
is telling all these stories
of all the fun you had in your life
and i have a scar
on my boob
because
i handled a feral kitten
don't recommend ever picking up
a feral kitten but unfortunately it's an emergency situation
so i have a big scar
a little
well it's not big sorry it's a light white scar that goes
along my chest
and i just think these kind of things
are like little funny things
being like oh i remember when that happened
i burnt myself on my mum's
lamp
she had like a nightstand lamp shade thing
and i burnt myself on it and i've got a burn
on the back of my elbow
i think these are like funny kind of things
some people might be embarrassed about scars
or things going on with their body
but i'm like that's me
that's what makes me me
yeah i've got like a scar
on my knuckle
because i rode my bike
into an event
at my grand's house
it's just how i'm made up
it's just part of me
as a little child
sorry i just kicked the mic sorry i'm lifting
my feet up hold on
you put my feet up yeah
i don't think anyone should be embarrassed
um
about scars or your body
it's you it's what makes you a silly goober
you know
so my father was a gamer
hmm
gotta kick it well you can
kick me again mummy
well if i get a plushie
i hope you're ready for the amount of ASMR
you guys are gonna see my hands so much
if i get a plushie i'm not even kidding
i'm gonna make so much hand cam ASMR
um
you got a scar on my right pinky
no clear right front
we're like tindly saying brian
ah
honestly though i think that's like a pretty cool story
oh wait i did that way
to prematurely pardon me
thank you so much for the
the tip reluctant to say yes
i have it right now
i did tell you guys i am on painkillers
unfortunately it is
it's throbbing and not the good kind of
throbbing
i got it assessed
and booked me in
but like the doctor was super lovely
he was so nice
i have not had him as a doctor
because i normally have a chick doctor
and she's really nice
but like all the doctors in australia
shout out to the health care in australia
you guys are like actually nice
what the heck
you guys actually want to help people with their problems
so yeah ripped to my ill fable
but i'll keep you guys updated
it's after the buckshot roulette stream
so after buckshot roulette
originally i was gonna do a foot cam
i'm gonna be honest i think i'm probably gonna be on an ice pack
by the time we're on buckshot roulette
i think we'll do heart cam
no we will not do heart cam
that's just my chest
we will do heart beat
i think azura has a heart beat monitor on
i was watching her play stardew
and i'm like what's 86
what's 82 what's 76
what's 81
oh my god it's her heart beat
she has a heart rate monitor on
i was like what
heart surgery cam honestly
the toe not growing back
could be different per person
woah your toe came back
aww they told me what they need to do
is like they completely
i'm not looking forward to it though
cause they said they have to do like 2 injections
and then yank your freaking nail out
which is kinda gross but hey ho
recovery
i think they said roughly 2 weeks so
if you guys really want to see it
i'll show you but
kinda gross
are you squiddling me right now
anonymous
maybe a new pedicure will fix the old one
is that not how it works
no anonymous sadly
the reason why
i had a plaster over my toe
is because
when they give you a pedicure
they cut around the skin and they cut your nail super short
because they're gonna apply
gel to it
and the girl
accidentally cut into the
side of my skin
and then cut into the nail
itself
which is why it's causing all these
problems and basically acting
infected
cause it's now growing into
my skin which sounds really gross
said it like that
but unfortunately
not happening
my poor elf able
did they say
anything about putting a chemical on it
to prevent
i think so i can't remember the full
conversation basically
the conversation was like
you've got this
what do you want to do this is what happens
if you cut the side of it it's a possibility
of coming back and cause of your nail shape
it's much more likely to happen again
or if you just get it off it's one and done
you don't have to come back
everything should be fine
i don't need antibiotics
it's not like that
it's just bad
so i
i'm just like get it over and done with
i want to be in and out i want to be back streaming
i don't want to have to like go back in
and all that
nah just take the whole thing off take off
we gotta go bald take it off we gotta go bald
thankfully because
i get to sit while i stream
as opposed to someone who's forced
to stand while they stream
question mark anyway
the healing
process isn't an issue
cause i explained i was like
i'm stronger
i don't have to be bed ridden for this
and he was like nah you're fine
if you're sitting for the full day then just sit
i need to change the bandages
though which i'm a bit
i don't know if it's gonna be gross
but i'll try my best to behave
uh
don't worry even if it doesn't grow back i don't care
yeah he's still like my
nine toenails
bandage changing
oh you're feeling brave
i think it's going to be
very
not pleasant
you'll have to wrap the top when you take a shower
i could probably take a bath easier
than a shower cause i can just like dive into the water
with my leg out of the bath
mummy streaming from the hospital bed
i probably would
i'm not even joking
i'd probably
if i was ever in a hospital for a long time
cause of whatever reason
i'd probably just buy a gaming laptop
import my model on it and be like right
that's it let's go
and then like the nurses come in
and they're like what are you doing
and i'm like oh don't worry about it
need me to chat
hospitals that's who would go hard
why
well we're almost at 7000
fishies
god we are getting through it
the question is are we going to finish the fishies
by the endurance
well you keep streaming from the shows how you
raise the nurses for real for real
why is it nurses are
so caked up for like no reason
i have a
i said i'm becoming a nurse only to
get an even larger rump
okay i'm gonna become a nurse
so i can get a larger rump
my friend
had his removed forever ago it doesn't look that different
just an indent where the nail was
okay so true nurses
have that cake
you can play old school rinscape on your phone
but i kinda stream it though
oh it's the bunny reefling
that i thought was telling me to hurt
myself because they gave me
fish food and poison
the 1002 smelly
socks in your bank
that's reeflings giving me a big
beauty
let's just say
there was no ink left
in the intent
strong it's your body your decision but
are you feeling you might regret it i couldn't
give less about
my toes i'm gonna be honest
i
don't
they don't do anything for me
i don't paint them
i'm not very feminine in terms
of getting my nails and toes done
it doesn't
affect me they told me it doesn't
affect my balance in any way
my feet will adjust very quickly
to applying pressure
while walking
i'm not trying to dismiss your thing
but the fun part is
if you put the meshy stick thing on the bed
if it comes off
yeah
that hurts to take that off
it doesn't bother me i've never been
into doing my nails or anything
like i literally have fake press on nails
to do ASMR with when i do show my hands
you've been playing for a while
consider taking a break from streep
jagax
do not insult me
do not insult
me
i'm being insulted by jagax
i did do the
salt water yes
1000 boobies
honestly
what's your best feature then
my butt
my outrageously
redonkulous
round
juicy
twerkin
butt
that's all i got going for me
small chest big butt thank you very much
10 toenails
spay thee
there's no way
i still have 10 toenails
give him
get a little cook
i'm not going to yank off yet wait for buckshot
roulette then you can make fun of
then we can hold a funeral at the end of buckshot roulette for him
how about that
that is hilarious though
thank you for the tip oh my god
oh also anon thank you for the tip about the pedicure question
yes sorry
i forgot to thank you but yes
unfortunately pedicure does not cure it
for what i hate
that smith
built like a pear
yes
68 68 68
zoolene
that doesn't work
68 oh my god
oh hydration
i'm pretty sure i said i was going to go get a tea
in hydration like two hours ago or something
but one more
let me get to 69
we'll go for a break how about that
deal
please do hydrate me flings
please do not do as i do
do as i say not as i do
because i do terrible for me health
but i just hate taking breaks
i like being in it
i like being bosnip
i started late but it seems like i'm catching up to mummy
stop no you're making me scared
are you guys going to be ahead of me
all of you guys getting 99
without me
hypnosis when you sway back and forth
and make us obey when soon
my first hypnosis
is forget your name
and your new name is reefling
you will respond to reefling you will get praises reefling etc
it will not have
permanent effects it will be
roughly 30 minutes long
but it will fade away
after two hours i'm going to do a two hour
fade effect
i am very cautious about doing any permanent
effects stuff it makes me
slightly nervous
very nervous
strony what if
our name is already reefling
you already respond if i have loved you into reefling
reefling
who's been a naughty reefling
hmm
have you not been looking after yourself
reefling
how are we supposed to look after each other
if you don't
look after yourself
hmm
that's right i'm going to guilt trip you into looking
after yourself and there's nothing you can do
about it
it's over for you reefling
it's over before it even started
okay this is too real
but i've already been permanently affected
by you momae
i stood at attention
i turned up
reefling
time to line up it's time for your daily
inking
what hole are you going to get it's a surprise
that's terrible
why do i say these things out loud
also me when
my content gets limited
i had some curious i wonder why
hmm
thanks on you
my name's already been reefling for a week
oh wait it has
literally because you're cold reefling
i like surprises
sounds like a bit
the game is right from the start
it's inking time not yet
not yet
because we like it
the algorithm must be haunted
hmm
actually i need to
tell the girls to be careful
and say more substitute words
so if you didn't know
youtube auto caption streams
doesn't even matter for the full 12 hours
youtube auto caption it
and the problem with that is
that's why you need to do
substitute words because it will identify
the rate of things being said
and it'll be so you can swear sometimes
but if you swear too much
you're in trouble you know what i mean
so
i'll need to tell the girls to maybe do
some
i just hear a really weird noise there
is that in game
hmm
are you squidding me right now
anonymous
no
no way
anonymous
no way you freaking assimilated
the slang
are you being saying like
are you being saying like oh i
instead of like yes
you're like mmm i can do that
oh my god we're doing it
oh and on can you
can you do this excel sheet
i can and they're all looking at you
like what
you didn't tell us you were Scottish
you're like oh oh oh
just pull the old
brian assimilation any percent
that's amazing
oh emi's
vaude is totally not going to be kept up
even after editing out
she's already on a warning
so i'm very worried about as you're in emi
at this stage
i don't want to tell the girls like hey you need to like knock
it off because that's not fun for anyone
sorry my microphone is
just playing a prank on me
they're pranking me john the Scottish accent
it's funny until it's too late
to be honest i've started typing
i a lot more
hmmm
how do warnings work
so none of the girls have a strike
on their youtube channel
but they have a warning
that lasts 90 days
3 months
so if they were to do something
against tos they get a full strike
which limits them
for a week
they can't do anything for a week
they can't upload
they can't update, they can't do this, they can't do that
and i am a bit
nervous
but as soon as the warning expires
at the 90 day mark
i think
all is good at that but what the heck
is that
what the hell
oh my
there's no way
way
hold on big ass he's right
it's not
messed up because
it gives a warning
and not a strike
but the length
being 90 days is pretty rough
i have to admit considering
youtube haven't announced their new
updated tos or their stealth
tos wherever you want to call it at this rate
um
it's a bit messed up because
they've updated it but because they gave
a warning
if they gave a strike then yes i would agree
and say that's really not fair
because you've not
you've yet to say that ASMR ear licking
is against the rules yet even though
you're applying it
um
type thing
but yeah so i have to confess
i've reached 90 cooking 3 times
before this stream you cannot have
i only started like a week ago
you can't you mean
before though like before
you can't have done 99
because that's like
they say it tastes like 81
hours to do 99 or something
oh azura got a warning
for eating a cookie unfortunately yes
like azura
i don't know what's going on with azura
she wanted to do
an exercise ASMR stream
and unfortunately
management was like
bruv you're gonna get a strike for that
you literally got in trouble
for eating a cookie
what makes you think you can do heavy breathing ASMR
working out
and it's such a shame because i never want to say
no to the girls
but
i don't want to risk her money like her income
i know she's not monetized yet but she's about to be
i do not want to risk her monetization
and
like if she wanted to
record it and upload it
like on twitter that's fine
i have no issues with that
the cookie embargo honestly
yeah the sounds youtube sucks
and
yeah she wanted to do work out ASMR
but that would result in like heavy breathing
in the mic and
i don't know what is going on at youtube
headquarters but it is
absolutely
going to the dogs
i wish they would just come out and see what is and what isn't
instead of playing this weird
guessing game of like oh
but that's fine oh but that's not
fine
oh my god
but yeah the
very curious very curious
well i got a thousand
likes on that ASMR video hold on
in the money
you may not
have a cookie youtube literally
i think
because azura's voice is so
silky perfection and sex
who is why she got walloped
with it which is a shame because it's not fair
that's not fair at all
and because that is just her voice
i i'll tell
you something in the interview
with her i thought she was
putting it on and she was going to like
reveal her voice to me in the interview
no that's just her voice she's just
straight up a goddess
no questions asked
hmm
purple burglar
you're the second one
you're the second one i see you
see you taking it
um literally
punished her for her default voice
i thought literally there was a lot of
actually there was a really interesting thing about the
introduce yourself videos
a lot of people did their
character voice that they currently
like do as a vtuber and then they were like
hi viewer
in their actual voice
and it was quite interesting
it was nice seeing the swap
and i was convinced i was like oh azura is like
yeah putting on a voice and i did the
interview and i was like oh
i didn't even know people had goddess voices
like this um
do you know how much money i would make with your voice
yes thank you give it to me now
i literally i was like if i could grab
all the girls voices
you guys seen
that movie with a mermaid in it
where her voice gets stolen
oh it's called the little mermaid yeah
her voice gets stolen she's like
me she did 40 push ups
yesterday and the noise is
your voice is
okay you like that right
lads time for a group session
get your tentacle out
and then get your lotion
and have a wee go at your tentacle
and then once you're ready you'll ink
everywhere thank you lads
that's literally how i thought
my demo recording went
it was absolutely awful
who's stunting on us with these lava
capes
vivi pronouncing it below
still sends me
it's adorable
i literally if i could steal the girls
voices it would be over for everyone
unanimously at once
i could do lollipop i could do
milk i could do me
i could do yandere
you know but i can't
but that's okay
because sometimes i can go
but the only way i can do this
is by closing my mouth basically
would you still watch me if i was a lollipop
beecher burn sounded like that
don't you want to watch me
yeah
i had so much fun with you
drop
more like your mom
dropped her on your head as a baby
your family this dude
can't get rid of me
yeah
today on our risk game
we're gonna
get the swordfish
that we're burning
i don't even want to
with the burn rate of eating
it's not working
i think i'm down here comfortably
and i'll stay down here
only if you had the same personality
i cannot lighten my scottish accent
to do
lollipop scots
it's impossible
oh here we go
no the accent gets
i can't do lollipop scots with a head
are we going your bike
it doesn't work
i can't seem to lighten my voice
and keep the accent
no i just said
that's impossible
it's not possible
i can't put this together
don't worry
impression
oh wait that's mario when he falls off the map
he goes
wah
oh we're getting there
god we're at 6k actually
well wg
wait who did you ask for wg
did you ask for someone else
stroney and stroney
and there will be no other
i'm here for you as you
i love you as you are
i love you too
she sounds like she's talking with wg
speaking of wg
nah
i feel like
between scottish and slavic
i can mimic ac a wee bit
oh wait
hold on i've lost it
i've lost it
wg
wah
i feel like i'm insulting ac right now
i'm not trying to insult you
wah
hold on let me pull up ac's stream
hold on ac's small pause
get us on it
having a stroke is not a good game
classic me
get her voice in my ears right now
if i don't have my med
won't have my med
it's best for myself and everyone else
this is
otherwise my
ah yeah so
okay hold on
i'm overthinking it as always
i overthink stuff a lot
it's not working
i'm not mimicking
that was a terrible attempt
at least i tried
i sounded a lot better during the asmr
i think that went a lot better
agent smith
no
you should totally go take
a break and let us get
let us get
i mean i'm getting another tea
mmmm
refractory period already up
i need my tea
if you could mimic the wheezing laugh
that would be impressive
does following someone stop me
from being kicked from afk
i have no idea
i'm sorry
she really is all six girls
i think i did mersey's laugh
pretty all right during the asmr stream
right when am i taking a break
when we get 69
yeah look we're almost there
literally what a couple more inventories
i need to wash some dishes for a bit
oh you're such a good wheezing
you're looking after the home for me
thanks for
washing the dishes
do not attempt to mimic
mersey's laugh
if someone can send me a sample of it
like a time stamp
i might be able to
we're almost level 69
and then i will call we'll do a pee break
i'm gonna get loads of food and all of that
i'm gonna make another tea
sorry my bottle is crinkling away there
mmmm
please not this
the voice thief
not voice pyre safe
you steal the person's voice
they are mute forever
so who voice will be
my voice?
if you're on ruin light
you can look for the logout timer
like it's funny but i'm afraid
for her every time it starts
you're gonna record the
nooo
i don't know the peeler allegations probably aren't going away
i'm gonna go away
my burn rate went up again
it really is just
identity theft
isn't our joke starting
oop
strongy you're at 5.9
am i actually on ironically runescape duration
to 6k
i mean
i don't know
i don't know how often that ASMR videos
getting recommended to people now
it dies off like after the first
24 hours the recommendation
dies off
i'm
i don't know
what does it say on that end
wow it says 5900
heaven subscribers
go a leg
that was a terrible burp
you shouldn't even write that one
i mean
you wouldn't download a voice
lol the soundtrack with the anti-piracy
advert was a pirated thing
itself oh did they not use their assets
properly
stopping at 6k would be ending
way too early a yellow
yes i do
i have my 1k
first 1k celebration on the way
i am gonna break up the ASMR uploads
like maybe every 3 days
i don't want them to be one after another
after another type thing cause there's no way people
can enjoy my 12 hour streaming experience
and
my ASMR on top and with the patreon
uploads you just can't handle it can you
i'm just giving you too much
you can admit it when it's too much refund
i like when you say it's too much
it's cute
you can't handle
what mummy dishes are
that reminds me
is strani the only one
who hasn't been peeler? no
em
you're sending us to edgevillay that
azuro and mersey have not
been sent to peeler
em
and neither have i
the other 3 girls
pretty sure they have been sent to the peeler allegations
as a celebration
for 6k subscribers
here's me joining peeler
to edgevillay
oh wait azura did do it
i can handle
anything mummy throws at me
oh yeah
wait until i do the no refractionary
script
that'll be fun
em
i'm able to put a lot of love into the
scripts that i make but i don't know if people
like em but i like em
and if i like em then good
why
kfp spidey thank you for the 20 gifted
that's a lot thank you
congrats to those who caught it with your face
check out chat to enable it
if you haven't already
it'll do like a prompt
but thank you congrats
to those who have emote access now
feel free to spam any emote
thank you
20 big number
you're squiddin a bit too much
let me turn that down a little bit
you're squiddin a bit too much brian
squiddin
got the kfp song
honestly
we share in the hair color
kind of well i'm more of a war
watamelan i love that meme
watamelan
squid on me mummy
i'll squid all over you
i have to go do adult stuff
be a wage slave on a saturday
i used to absolutely
love working on
weekends
i know that sounds silly
but sorry enjoy your wage slaving
i too used to be a wage slave so i'm allowed to say that
anyways
streamers don't know how hard you are
go and be real
do you honestly think i'm someone who's never had a
fricking job that's rough
fricking safe
i really enjoyed working
on weekends because it was so busy
and the day goes by so fast
and it
meant i could do stuff during the week
like on weekdays
monday and tuesday was usually my day off
when i was a wee waitress
i miss my waitress job
guys can we open up a cafe
at the castle with the farm
so i can be a waitress again
i really enjoyed being a waitress it was really fun
i used to work in a tourist cafe
and
you get loads of tourists
and i'ma just say this now
for the americans in the back
we love when americans come in
because you guys tip
you guys tip out the wazoo
actually i'll tell you one story
so
in
so anyway
americans come in absolutely fantastic experience
and i'm like
okay just for
to pay your bill please come up to the front
because
you need to pay at the tail type thing
this guy hands me his card
and i'm like what
and he like straight up
hands me his card and i'm like
to like walk away with
to walk away with his actual bank
card and like put the transaction
through and i'm like
no i cannot do that
you need to be there to witness it
you need to be there to agree to the amount
of charging you like you cannot just give me
like your car
your credit card that has no freaking pin on it
and
i was like no you need to come up with me
i'm so sorry please do like come
with me to the tail type thing
i was so shocked to learn
that in america
you part with your card super easily
there's no pin on it
the limits are like 5000 us dollars
i'm like
what there's no pin
put in a code
that's just a default
please if you're listening right now
make sure any card you own in your
worldly possessions has a pin on it
because that is
insanity i was like so
flabbergasted and ironically
the word is flabbergasted
um that were pinless
honestly um i was like
so i was like why are you handing me your card
um
actually i had
one american family that came
in and he must have been from
texas or something
i could not understand
him we couldn't understand each
other actually that's how humorous it was
he wanted water
um but
he was saying it really funny like i
couldn't understand it
and he was like oh can we get some
can we get some water but he like
really said it fast and i was like
i'm so sorry i do not understand you
can you say it a bit slower for me
and he was and then the daughter
of the family was like
water like she said it the way i could understand it
and i was like oh water
of course i can do water that's not a problem
um
and then um
basically he was like
oh it's just because you've got a funny
accent and i was like
oh actually mate
you're the one with a funny accent around here but
in a nice way we weren't being mean or anything
but like we're he was like oh
you're at us because of your accent i'm like
mate you're the foreigner in this country i can
assure you that much
but we were like joking
about it it was good vibes and he tipped
me um
we love tips we love
tips shadow wizard money gang
we love giving waitresses tips
um
uh the pin
is only if you go to an ATM debit cards
only use pen credit yeah
don't have credit cards down with credit
cards
wait until i get on a rant
about how uh credit scores
just made up uh numbers
for you to what what
credit are you trying to take advantage of
ah
uh excuse me level
69 you just interrupted me in my corporate
greed rant uh we will we will continue
but we made it we're at
oh nice nice thank you
please please can i get nice in the chat
hey i'm i'm gonna type a nice in the chat
nice
and then i'm gonna type a nice in this chat
there we go nice oh it's dancing
i've forgotten how to do that is it like
slash wave or something
uh nice
nice yeah thank you thank you i'll be here
um
credit scores were invented to stop
women buying homes hey yo
i've not gone down that rabbit hole
i've gone down the
rabbit hole where
um you're told oh
being in debt is bad but the
anonymous oh
oh you gave me money for that oh
thank you anonymous oh
thank you for the six dollars
and ninety cents anonymous
i see you nice
pen and i get a pen
and two for the six point nine
thank you you
didn't have to take me you know you can
take for free you know you can take the stuff for free
hey
hi i'm gonna
cry oh hi
um
i am full tin foil
not yet soon maybe
i am a of
the tin foil hat where the system is
rigged against you to
go into zarian
the tip as well
thank you for the same thing
you guys can take this for free you know you don't
have to give me money to take
nice i said type it not
type it in the the tip
and
where was i
the system is set up for you to fail
so you've been told
your entire life ooh being
in debt bad debt bad
and yet the most
american infrastructure you have to
put a down payment to get a car type thing
and debt you can buy
things online in four installments
that's a debt
and then the worst
offender of all
mortgages
mortgages are just
normalized debt
for normalized
debt enslavement
there is no way you can guarantee
you're gonna have a perfect income
for 30 years
and then ah
ah i could absolutely
explode off the planet
they also close your account
if you don't use your card anyway
sorry what are mortgages
so a mortgage is when you go to a bank
and you say hello bank i would like to purchase
this house the bank will then
own your house
that you pay a monthly mortgage
into with astronomical
fees over the years
with the charged interest
by the time you have finished
off paying your lovely jubbly 25
year
mortgage with interest
you have paid an astronomical
amount that isn't even houses
aren't even valued the materials
of houses
aren't even at that value the
construction isn't even at that value
the entire system
is wrecked
it is rigaton needs
to high heavens do not
ever feel embarrassed
about still living at home
with your parents do not
ever feel embarrassed
if you're in real life friends
from high school or whatever
have moved out
are able to rent do not
ever feel embarrassed
about any of these aspects
you the system
is rigged against you
do not feel a shred
of it multi-generational
living was incredibly
common for
centuries
way before capitalism came
into the picture do not be
embarrassed about living with your
more living with your grand
that is your sense of community
is beautiful to even have that
and I would absolutely love
to see the uprising
of multi-generational households
I would absolutely love to
see the uprising of
people going back to farming
another thing in
World War I and World War II
people on mass
were instructed
on how to grow vegetables
at home with the rise
of supermarkets capitalism
who here
knows someone who grows
produce themselves
I know no one
that grows produce themselves
because of how
how much lack of time
people have maybe
your grand may do it
because she has time because she is retired
did you know how common it was
to have a farm
to have farm animals
such as chickens how common it was
to grow even the most
basic of vegetable such as
potatoes such as tomatoes
such as peas
okay
you?
I want to see this
become a thing
another thing
notice how tiny gardens
are getting for houses
hmm
I wonder put your tin foil
someone give me a tin foil PNG right now
hold on tin foil
PNG I'm not even kidding hold on
let me cook
tin foil hat PNG get me on this right now
get me on this right now
I'm not even kidding we're doing this live
why are all PNG's
fake PNG's
why are they all fake
PNG's
can I get one real PNG
jeez louise one real PNG
you look like a real PNG
oh
hold on a minute
no club penguin tin foil
hat PNG there's no way
hold on hold on
hold on
oh pause pause
where's it
let's go
okay let's clip it to my head
hold on you feel like
right and while I'm at it
sorry I just jumped up there in excitement
and while I'm at it
hmm
isn't it curious that garden
spaces for the average house
have been lessening and lessening
every year I wonder
do they want the people
not to have the ability to grow
produce in the means of their
own production for survival
hmmm
isn't that curious
isn't that curious that flats
massive sky scraping building blocks
have no garden space
so people cannot produce their own
produce their own vegetables
their own fruits their own herbs
so people are forced to
rely on supermarkets
yet again
capitalism strikes
isn't that curious
I find that so curious
at this day and age
with all these
advancements on building so many houses
the garden spaces are getting so tiny
you cannot even have a produce
producing tree and isn't it curious
that even when there are
fruit producing trees
that
they purposely don't have
fruit producing trees when they have to put trees down
instead they use pollen trees
which are good
I don't get me wrong they're good for the bugs
but they never give free
produce producing trees
I fucking saw a story where someone
got given lemons from
the garden and she didn't know that you could
just straight up cut the lemon open
and add it to the juice they thought it had to be
produce isn't it interesting
that in school you hardly
learn about the cycle of the farmers
and how you never are encouraged
to go to farmers markets
instead of the big fricking Tescos
or big as their big this or big that
talk your shit
damn straight I'll talk my shit
isn't that interesting
that you hardly even learn about seeds
seeds I will tell you
about seeds right now
to remember the three threat factors
of growing seeds it's what
W-O-T
water, oxygen, temperature
that is how you grow seeds
the other part of the fun is when
Monsanto tries to sue people for using their seeds
and another thing
there's states where you can't even collect
rainwater it is illegal to collect
rainwater what would you use
for rainwater hmm
you would water your own crops
with rainwater
bruv this
system is
fuck
it's beyond bull
don't look too deep into it
or you're not going to enjoy what you see
you have to look around
and say we live in a society
that's all we can do
Reeflings
we live in a society
amen
okay I'm going to get off my soap box
for a minute there
let me remove this asset
let me remove my tin foil hat
but don't think I won't put that hat back on
hold on actually
I have this hat
okay
we can put this hat on we're back to meman
okay it's a bit wonky but
it's really wonky
right above calm down we live
in a society
ooh
thank you for letting me rant about that
but it makes you think
it's illegal to collect rainwater
yes
but is that because
it might drinking water might be contaminated
why do you think that's contaminated
is it because these mega
corporations bribe
their way
into being allowed to pollute the waters
did you know in the UK
there is no
swimmable rivers
that are not toxic
for they are all actively
being polluted in
hmm did you know that
all in the name of what
reeflings
capitalism
shocking behavior
sorry I took my tin foil hat off
zero
yes zero
by the way I also have a friend who has like
20 different crops growing in his basement
so a garden is technically not needed
and that
should that gentleman be having those crops
right
I'll get, ooh pardon me
I'll get off my high horse
I think I may need to eat for I haven't eaten anything at all to do
in fact I've only had a cup of tea
and a half bottle of water
it's not looking good for me
so yes
I will do
another batch
so when strongies farm
airing on BBC
oh they'd never let me air it I'd be going nuts
yeah actually
we'll go back for it a little bit it's not too tin foil hat
during world war one and world war two
where food scarcity was a thing
in the modern day age food scarcity
is not a thing please do not be under the impression
scarcity is a lie
food
scarcity was a thing
so people were encouraged to grow
farms to do very unique
plots to do
legumes to do potatoes to do
the most staple foods you can imagine
and with the uprising
of supermarkets people stopped doing it
and who benefits
who benefits
when we
the individuals the small
communities no longer grow
our own crops no longer
have thingy
we are fully reliant
on the system
which is not good
you never want to fully rely on the system
but guess what if you don't want to
rely on the system what do you need
oh well you need a plot of land to grow
okay and you need time
but wait a minute even if I
fully outright buy my
plot of land wait a minute
I still have to play some
to pay some sort of yearly
land tax
towards
the place that I'm living in
because there is no place that is truly free
you can you buy
a house in UK and every year
you pay council tax
even if you don't participate in the services
that they provide
you do it in Australia they have a thing
called land tax in America
they have a thing called something tax
even when you
want to fully
no longer be a part of the system
they already got you
hook, line and sinker
and it doesn't matter what you do
you can't escape it anyway that's me
property ownership tax yet
farmers are struggling
yep so
em
every time
there is a shortage
in Australia recently
this happened a couple of months back now though
there was a shortages of eggs
and the prices went up
because there was a shortage of course that makes sense
so more people are wanting eggs
but there's less eggs ah hold on a minute
what's going on here we're in the information age
a major
em
major egg producer
in Australia came out and said
em actually
there's nothing wrong with production at all
if you want to know the truth
they're actually not giving us
as much money as they used to
yet the prices are going up
and we don't get to see any of that benefit
are you telling me
these mega corporations
are artificially
hold on
are you telling me
these mega corporations
wait how is there two
how did I do that hold on a minute
I need to put my tinfoil hat back on
no
it can't be
that all these mega corporations
are actually hand in hand with one another
no
wait
the cost of living crisis
is actually artificial
because if one shop
raises their prices
the other shop can justify that
but then the major
no that can't be right because
capitalism obviously
what the frick is that
that's very grand sitting on that table
but then oh no that can't be right
no
the good businesses aren't
wait a minute
Coca Cola owns
all of the market
wait
but I thought capitalism
bred competition
no no everything I've been told
that's not right
wait a minute
something's not adding up
Coca Cola seems to own
literally everything
wait a minute who is the sole business owner
because everything seems
to be getting acquired
wait
wait a minute it's a conglomerate
everything is a
fucking conglomerate
and they can put up the prices as much as they please
because there's no true
competition
even if there were cheaper
brands that wanted to get on the shelves
brands have to pay
to be on the shelves in your common
supermarkets
holy moly
my head
spinning just thinking about
how deep this rabbit hole goes
maybe
we should focus on the one rabbit hole
that's important to us
and that's Sheeby's hole
we love you Sheeby we hope you feel better
after your migraine
what a way to end that
okay okay I'll take the hat off
I'll take the hat off
I'm sorry I get very
passionate okay
I get very passionate
right I'll calm down I'll calm down
I am going to take
a lovely joe ble break
and by that I mean I'm going to
tinkle make a tea and I'm going to make some food
so I'll be roughly 4 minutes
if I come back to one message
that says mommy hates me
and not I understand strongy
was it blackwell rockwell
rockwell
then yeah
much better the tinfoil hat was blocking your hypnotic
raise
you heard
the insane thing
take
your bio break
my bio break honestly
more time to catch up to mommy
mommy loves me yes mommy loves
me
no not doom break
no doom break
I will grab that
burn them all
right I will be back in 4 minutes please reeflings do stretch
do get up and stretch your legs
we don't want any booty hole problems
but don't worry if you have a booty hole problem I'll apply
the cream myself
do get some water
do get some liquids do tinkle
and do get some food as well
I'll be back in roughly 4 minutes
the toilets right there and then you boil the kettle
and all that jazz okay
bye I'll be right back
you
are you squinting me right now
do you hear it
reeflings black rock is coming
for strongy she knows
too much and they are coming
for you too skull
you
oh my radical
I mean reeflings
sorry
did you tinkle
did you tinkle let me see you never let me hold it
you never let me hold it
I got a whole 3 minutes I was away
day 100 still in the mummy
insight
oh boy
do you hear it reeflings
black rock is coming for strongy she knows
too much and they are coming for you too
no
thank you for the tip boy
um
no I will
I think I have got my mesh
is back
I will um
I will refrain from any more tin foil
and unless you guys get me started again
then I just can't help myself
I have a can of cola
I have a honey tea which I need some help
the reeflings with
I have a neutral green bar
a nature valley crunch bar
and a blueberry muffin
I can't really make it make a noise I can smack the bottom
of the casing
I don't know if you can hear that
um
but that is pretty much
what's going on
I really remember
moving to my head to express
she came back she loves this
of course I do
remember that time I thought I wasn't going to come back
that was rough
that was rough and then I come back
come back even stronger
yes I
for endurance streams
it's not possible
for me to prepare food
unless I did it in advance but I am a lazy fud
um so
I have bought like a load of
drive food or food that
is zero prep time
I don't have any boiled eggs
I ate all my boiled eggs
and my meat sticks have kind of
overstayed their welcome
no no no no no no
I am going to take a bite of my muffin though
I did not realise
I had been streaming for five hours
I literally had nothing but a cup of tea
and a half bottle of water that's outrageous
that's how distracted you guys get me
that's how much I freaking love it
um
oh my goodness but yes
I am going to take a bite of my muffin
I do apologise if I am not
talking for a few moments
but I eat my muffin
itadakimasu
oh my goodness
it's nice and jelly
oh yeah we distract you
yeah
I can't believe it
I can't believe
we really enjoy each other's company
it's crazy it's a crazy concept
honestly couldn't imagine being a VTuber
that hates our audience like bro
why are you even streaming
cause I am pretty sure I have heard a few
sent stories like that
where they are like oh I hate what I do
I am like what if you hate what you do
like
go clock out and do something else
what the fuck
how can you not enjoy your time
actually
well I am on my high horse about VTubers now
how can you not enjoy your time
you dictated everything you get to do
you don't have to do a single thing
if you want to play game play game
if you don't want to play game don't play game
you want to zazoo zazoo
you don't want to zazoo don't zazoo
wait a minute what's going on
nah I refuse to believe there is any VTubers that stream
that actually don't like streaming
they don't like everything
it doesn't make sense
the Elden Ring
DLC comes out
and I get to do nothing
but play with you guys
for again what half a week
maybe more actually maybe 5 sessions
I have no idea how big the DLC is
I don't even know
if they have given an indication on how big
the DLC is
I just want money for existing proof
and another thing about capital
I'll stop
no more hi-hat
no more tinfoil for now
I will burn you out on my conspiracy theories
T-
1 hour I believe
for our lovely
the goddess
of fertility
or mummy
she is your mummy canonically
she is quite literally your mum
nah
it was enough to be nearly a full game
ok might need to change up my plan
for the 4th week
do you want to hold it strongy
the DLC
I want to stack donuts on it
ok if it's like
wait are we going to do a full week of Elden Ring then
if we do a full week of Elden Ring
on the 4th week
I will make up for any membership
content like I will literally do
back to back to back to back to back
member streams like you know
I'll do it
I'll do it to make up
sure
thank you for becoming a member
what do we think
does that sound to me fine
stack donuts
villager minecraft note
Elden Ring DLC I sleep
let's see
hmm
oh I tell you what
I was doing my research on a game that I might play
it's called
Boutro
it is a poker
type game
and unfortunately
I'm not very familiar with the old
straight flush flush royal flush
or whatever the only flush I do
is after I drop a big job in the toilet
and
I was
it looks pretty easy to play
in terms of me actually being good
that's a different story however
it looked like a can
to our game experience
so I was doing my research
I was watching people play it and I'm like
hmm yes I understand none of this
so I'm going to look at a few more tutorials
but we might give Boutro a little try
I'll be one of my shorter streams
hmm
not the new tinkle
the guys whenever you
poop do you always pee as well
I think it's the same for guys
I do know a secret though
if you move your fireman's
hose
your butthole clenches
I've never been the same
since I learned that fact on the internet
the internet has scarred me for that fact
it's there
see you're all twitching
your buttholes right now I can tell
reeflings
can't believe you're doing it in unison
okay
I have finished
my mini muffin
I'm going to open up my cola
to wash it down
hmm
honestly I was worried about eating on stream
but it's really easy to eat and play runeski
at the same time
a twitch butthole for a moment
reeflings together
strong
we can also manually twitch your fireman's hose
but can you do it without
twitching the butthole
no you can't apparently it's guys
biology that you can't
wah
bit cola
man by the pope
wait wait wait hold on a minute who's calling me hypocritical
cause I just talked about corporations
and then I'm currently eating and drinking cola
me
as if I can source this stuff myself in the wild
who else is going to give me my sugary nectar
I'm currently open my nature valley
I have a bowl to eat it in
because I just know it's going to go
everywhere
and
we're almost at a million eggs
wah
look
7,000
tea
did you just snipe that
I think he just sniped that little thing there
I'd like to check out mommy's nature valley
I thought a certain type of
exercise could give you that kind of
control over the muscles
do you guys want to do kegels together
and hold
2, 3 and release
2, 3 and hold 2, 3
that's terrible
don't encourage me
don't get me started
not only will we have
oh my god I'm trying to take the nature valley out
without it crumbling everywhere
I have a Canadian
maple syrup flavor
at nature valley
I got a box that has like 3 different flavors inside
and I just grabbed one
because I had to tinkle and it just
whoa wait how fast is that spawn
mmm
oh god
I'm sorry if we got my eating time
I'm off to buy groceries
enjoy the shop
try your best to
shop local
smile
whoa that like
respawn so fast that's 30k
every second
wah
mmm am I going crazy
why is that spawning so fast
is it like an event or something
mommy stir it
she doesn't need a lips of 22 million
and I'm like oh my god is that 30k
that's amazing
mmm
yes I'm enjoying
is Gimli still fine
no she's asleep
I have to sneak around her
mmm
what was that oh no it wasn't me that leveled up
I take another big bite
wah
mmm
bye bye
don't worry if you have to go
this is an endurance stream
I did not expect anyone to sit for 12 hours
with me on RuneScape alone
someone's dropping them
why would they do that
how rather odd
is he just giving them away
but what if we wanted to
am we not supposed to
how bizarre
I think it may be bad for your health
to watch me for 12 hours
I'm going to be gone now
oh my god we hit 70
we're only
just over the 5 hour mark
can we do 80
is that too much of a reach
to do 80
this shit fucking
is anything man
nature valley counting your days
that's outrageously
crumbly
chat summary shocked you
what does chat summary say
what's your favorite snack
I don't even know
it's too many to choose from
from 70 to 76
good 6am
morning never woke up this early
wait you're up early to watch the stream
don't do that get rest you need rest
wait where did the time go
last I looked it was
97 minutes in
can you guys see what the chat summary says
can you post it
I was not going to let you post it
because I'm strumming
I'm strumming my badge
I haven't played whole night
is it good
wait what that's what the chat
that's what the chat says
that's what the chat
summary is on my freaking stream
wait
wait another conspiracy theory
but I did not mention that we want to take them
rock well
hold on a minute
I went to play old school marine save
what's a good reason to give it a try
number go up serotonin
game number go up yippee
that's your summary
what's your favorite pokemon
there's too many
there's too many pokemon
to decide from and you know that
there's literally isn't there not like over a thousand
I'm pretty sure
autism game to be honest
no is it actually
oh you know who
I like
you know who I like what pokemon I like
but it sounds like a freaking racist name
sorry that was so off topic
yeah so there's this pokemon
called Qing Ling
and it sounds so racist
and I'm like bruv
it's ridiculous
but it's a cute pokemon I like the way it looks
it's really adorable
yeah the cute little bell one
yeah I just
the name just like
I'm not sure how I feel about that
17.9 burn rate
oh it has gone down
only tism havers here
we only have tism around these parts
we don't have them function in brains
hmm
Qing Ling is the sound it makes
what are you saying
sounds like a
a weird name
my favorite pokemon is mega
I quite like
what's his name
is it Aaron
Aaron
the wee iron guy
he's so cute and tiny
and he eats iron
he's so cute
you thinking of penicillin
what
penicillin
penciling
absol
Aaron is cutie
I'm getting distracted
I'm not mega
I'm missing all my swordy fishies
I definitely am going to finish
all the swordfishes though
which is amazing
I'll need to go buy something
at the grand exchange
sorry if you heard my stomach rumble there
illichid an internal far
those plate bodies are getting suspiciously close
to us now
what an error they're getting so close
exp wastage
mine is nidoran
oh really
I remember when pokemon go came out
I was really digging it
look at the bunnies dancing
oh they're doing like a perfect
you know
I can't remember what it's called but that's like english culture
when you stand around a pole and all dance around it
that sounded like another type of
dance but no
it's like actually english culture
like back in the old days
like that
why are we on the same wavelength again
god damn it streamer
I'm just trying to
you can't keep doing this you can't keep saying everything
that I'm thinking
mmm
gardevoir hypno art
I do I've always enjoyed
gardevoir thoroughly
enjoyed gardevoir
very
cool unique and different design
color scheme as well very
unique god damn it how many plate
bodies does this person got
oh my god wait everyone's
like walking towards the
as well
what how much was that
3 million
is this a refling doing this
am I going crazy
what is plate body 4
for defense they are free
but why is
why give it away for free then you're not
making money for this
what
what about me
thank you boy for the tip
wait we can't both be holding
at the same
well my hands are
relatively small
thank you for the tip
you
probes like her art too
yeah
what in the
sorry only more my hands
two hands is fine
he keeps answering you strongly but yeah it's a refling
okay
I think he's trying to
give you a nice valuable thing
it wasn't me oh wait am I supposed to chase after
I'm so sorry refling if I'm supposed
to chase after it oh my god
streamer distracted
I'm so dumb a streamer
I'm just a streamer
I stream my life
away
I'm just a
refling
I stream
my life away
away
16 points oh the burn rate went up
I got a little too excited hold on a minute
oh I think it's because it's reset the burn rate will
kind of go up until
maybe so you're under arrest
that guy said the NPC says
I'm focused on the
grind you don't want me to grind
come on mate come on mate
why would Emmy be under arrest
it should be pin pals under arrest
I'm not really enjoying
this bar anymore
rather flavorless
isn't it bro?
I'm tempted to order
take away I'm gonna be honest
I'm like
I'm doing an endurance stream
I deserve a cheeky take away
I'm such a good girl
pizza nah
not pizza
Australian pizza I'm sorry
Australia and any Australian
listening
Australian pizza is no thank you
I've not had one pizza I've enjoyed here
I just fill a grease
and like the grease is like
dripping off the thing
they could have like blotted it
or patted it or whatever but they don't
a cheeky little treat perhaps
I'm bringing you all with me
as I buy a pizza before a storm hits
oh you're actually getting a pizza in real life
okay okay
didn't Emmy burn down buildings
look Emmy needs
XP in order to summon her brother
back it's look whatever she does
as long as we can look the other way
the fact she's not actually now that I mentioned
the fact she's not even in jail
how would she be evading jail
when she just used her magic on people
who'd try and stop her
or maybe she has like influential magic
I wouldn't I wouldn't be surprised
if she had like turned the other eye type
of spells and
where it was like oh must have been the wind
and I wouldn't be surprised
if she had access to that
and her wee totems
high charisma, yeah
she has to rescue Nissan from the devil
herself
like Maggie Thatcher
I think people were so confused
they were like why the devil herself
and then Maggie Thatcher and as a surprise
there was a Scottish person
on the development team and we thought the gag
was hilarious so
there you go
wow
I drank a wee bit of cola and then we're gonna get on
my honey tea
any honey tears
I'm honey tea
and we can just be a
peeler on them and
okay they can't do anything
I cried too
wait what was my joke
wait what joke did I just say
hold on
wait what did I say that was funny
go again
go again tell me, remain me
I've already forgotten
oh the Maggie Thatcher
alright sorry I thought it was a pun
I'm not gonna lie I had my fingers ready to do that
my apologies I thought I made a pun
and I was like what did I make that was funny
I forgot
crying fish and chips for my
so do you want to hear the
saddest story in all the land
I really like Mexican food
you know what I don't like
cilantro
and that stuff tastes awful
do you want to know what
cilantro
is primarily used in
that's right
Mexican cooking
man I
hated here
it tastes awful to me
absolutely awful
I tried a
rice wrap I think it was
Vietnamese inspired rice wrap
no rice cake
with chicken in it
and it sounded so good and I took a bite
and I was like
in Australia
there's a lot more
access to Asian foods
that are authentic or really good type thing
which is why I'm currently
addicted to local Chinese
I've been adventurous
I'll try this I'll try that
and I couldn't figure out why I hated it
until I finally figured out
it's cilantro I can't handle
cilantro it tastes nasty
I'm so sorry
I apologize to those
who have
who do enjoy cilantro
yes I have the soap gene
I cannot even describe to you how nasty
and completely
ruins in any trace of it
in the food completely ruins the food as well
it is a
unlucky and unfun gene
to have
isn't it genetic
I don't know if it's genetic
my dad
I think eats it fine
because one time
he made like is it
Pico de Mayo or something
I'm so sorry I think I butchered that
he made it and I tasted it
and I was like this is nasty
but I never said that to him I just said
oh I don't think my taste buds agree with that
I never said anything but it's because of the cilantro
in it
Pico de Gallo
okay sorry
yes I think my dad tried to make some of it at home
and
yeah I was like
nope
a bit of Boko no Pico
no Boko no Pico in it
yeah
I'm a fair share of it
absolutely horrific things I've consumed
where's the yellow thing
oh that reminds me of it
we need to do a watch along
of Kevin Bridges
um
Kevin Bridges
is a Scottish comedian you might know
someone called Frankie Boyle
or what's the other Scottish
comedian's name and I've forgotten his name
and he's got Parkinson's right now
but he's still alive I'm pretty sure
and he's got a beard and kind of
big
not curly hair but wavy hair
and he's older
oh my god what's his name
Billy Conley oh
Billy Conley
it took me so long to get there
holy crap Billy Conley
hold on I need to drink my tea before I get sick
mhm
so I put far too much
honey in my first team and I put far too much
little I can never find the balance
Billy Conley
is like real Scots I'm gonna do
watch alongs of like
Scottish comedy so
you guys can laugh and I can be like
why are the reeflings running in an X pattern
so they are
assigned each other to follow each other
which is causing this four way
oh my god what are you doing over there
so they're not actually clicking anymore
their characters are following
each other which is causing an infinite loop
which is pretty cool
wait you don't pronounce the second
Billy Conley
oh Billy Conley sorry
Billy Conley I'm not good with names
so don't expect any
don't expect a miracle with me ok
it's a scrawny summoning ritual
down with black rock
I love Kevin Bridges
my brother served him at a local club
he lives close to me oh that's amazing
I really enjoy Kevin Bridges humour
because it's quite
deadpan like British
humour is quite deadpan so
we'll probably do a watch
hey you're getting sturdy with it
hold on hold on hold on let me just
get the fish out of the bank first
hey reefling getting sturdy with it
I love all these emotes in the game
I haven't unlocked any more but
other than the default ones
this stomped on raught route
really sells me on the cult vibes
oh she be playing cult of the lamb
did she finish it yet
I think she was so close to finishing it
at last on you but maybe she did it
hydration
gears are quid
you're getting stabbed is a great one
it is oh my god
oh fat boy
I know this makes no
I'm gonna tell Kevin Bridges
his joke ok
so Kevin Bridges is
a man and he's quite large in size
I think he's lost a weight since or whatever
but he said he was like 25 stone
or something which is big
and he was telling the story
where he's out late at night
waiting on the bus
and some net comes up and goes
oh fat boy
gears are quid or you're getting stabbed
and then he's like
so I start calculating my BMI
with the other people around me
type thing
and this retains that it's him
that's been picked on by this person
and he's like in order
to avoid this heinous act
against me
for the mere price of a quid
I think that's a pretty good bargain
so he did not get stabbed that night
that's the best I can do for telling the joke
but it's a really good joke
I'll get us to do a watch along
Kevin Bridges
he's a local co-op
I know I'm going to play with sheebie
and we'll force her to play with me
he used to weigh about 350 pounds
woo
oh isn't there
there's an American place that lets you eat for free
um
if you're over like
heart attack grill oh my god I'm so sorry
I look at videos of heart attack grill
I think it's so fascinating
um
there's like a weight outside the restaurant
if you are over that weight
you get to eat for free
I'm like wow
25 stone equals 160 kg
mmm
what are you going to do
stab him
he says as he gets shanked
I was a bit premature there
wow we are like
burning through these
well I don't know what level
I can cook those
octopusies
but
I think we'll go to the grand exchange
and buy some I have a terrible feeling
they are
a membership only
item
so we might have to swap to a membership world
which is a shame for anyone who's not a member
the heart attack grill
mmm
isn't heart attack grill
just a place because the owner hates fat people
and wants them to die
is that the lore
or
wines is probably better
at that point
wait carabaan
wines better than carabaan
caramwa
I'm sorry
I'm not saying that right
I'm not even going to pretend I'm saying it right
what level cooking
I am 70 on the dot
I'm revealing someone
I'm going to get some octopusies
honestly mate
right I've had a nature valley bar
I've had a muffin and I don't actually feel like eating
that's what I'm saying when a stream
I don't feel like eating properly
tick manipulation
oh I'm not that good at the game
I'm not that good at the game
tick manipulation
fat chance of me
eh
wa wa wa
oh boy
really going to get me a bye memory
wait until we've decided on what's going on
are you squidding me right now
kill more
combine
what are you saying
redheads are from Ireland
and I said redheads came from Scotland
Ireland has a higher redhead
percentage
I believe
but you must
acknowledge with that
that due to the Irish
potato famine
which was actually just a British government
starving the people
a lot of Irish migrants
went into Scotland
because it's a
very close company
company
thank you for the 5
but I want to say
I think your girlfriend's right where the redheads
are from Ireland
give them to Mumme
wait what
he wants my winemaking supplies
wait is wine faster
hold on
I'm banking
what does wine look like
how do I get wine
Shawnee if you right click game at the bottom of the screen
and click
game
Shawnee if you right click game at the bottom of the screen
and click filler
it will hate all the cooking messages
oh
thank you
Gael Gantres
for becoming a member
I appreciate it
government starving people
bet that hasn't even happened to tons of other countries as well. Redheads are from the Northern
Kingdom Catholics. I actually have the redhead gene so if any refling has it too and you want to
rendezvous with me we might make more Emmys. What? That's a lot! Wait how do I do that?
oh wait wait wait hold on hold on hold on thank you so much refling oh my god wait what do i do though
hold on hold on give the thing give the thing
take out 14 i think i take take out 14 and then shove them together like this is this faster?
oh i don't know if it is this faster
oh thanks for the two
let's make more Gert gingers together right and then do it like this okay that worked
make sure you do it every 14 seconds so you get a huge xv drop put 14 in the bank and then combine
the chat it gives about 2200 average
huh so this is more or less than cooking the swordies
i gotta go for i've got 14 second random timer
they take a bit to ferment okay i'll ferment you i'll ferment you in a minute in between these
sorry breeding more gingers into the world of strong
you can also right click the x button oh i fucked up
oh no they're gonna ferment before i'm ready don't ferment don't ferment i'm getting scared
can't throw it me real good then the only ferment when you aren't crafting wine how bizarre okay
okay i guess can you get bad wine or is wine always successful you can use the x button on
the bottom of your bank tab so you can bank all isn't it no faster if i like pull out wine
put wine away pull out water pull out grape you can make bad wine did i burnt fish people
buy bad wine then click twice as fast
is it painful watching someone trying to maximize their like xp gain and they're doing it all wrong
you're just like oh god i can't watch this anymore that's what two clicks
now it's fun to watch you can't get bad wine because you're such high level
so you pull it 14 each and can bank all after
ah was that right did i do it right
the second 14 yeah i think i did it right okay we did it we got there in the end
only non-alcoholic wine is bad oh well apparently like all the reports are now coming out about
how bad alcohol is for you wait hold on what am i supposed to do click it
and what goes out and go again i'm learning big gains let's go i'm learning i'm so fast
watch johnny burn the wine honestly i wouldn't put it past me
this is so goofy look at us all hanging out at the bank together i did that wrong sorry i did it the old way
you can click the bag button all right go go thanks for the stream you're more than welcome
thanks for hanging out please anyone uh don't feel bad about um not being able to hang out the
full stream that is not possible uh azura is going live right bank and then click click okay that's
how they're wanting me to do it see refunds are so good man they don't even gatekeep information
about the game mm baby i'm gonna take a shower scrub it up there there's a more a metronome
plug in to help you understand time picking ah
you know i honestly thought you were just referring to metronome the freaking
there's an item in isaac called metronome and i forgot like wait a minute it's an actual thing
that helps musical why gate keep info if you want to see people play the game you can also click
spacebar instead of make all in chat click spacebar instead of make all hold on
hold on right put it in do that do that together spacebar
oh we're getting even more efficient refunds we're getting night night tonight isaac brain
rot honestly it hit long ago the creator of isaac i follow him on twitter he's been utilising
twitter a lot to talk about new genics uh wait what was that other also can click on the bank
booth so you don't have to oh my god we're getting the stress um isaac players when they realize
mothers are real um yes i've been following um ed edmund i believe is the creator oh my god
i'm going to take a minute to learn these strats hold on um and he basically came out was like
oh the bounding of isaac was based on my uh trauma my religious trauma smile i was like oh my god are
you okay um because like binding of isaac's prey like if you understand i mean not that you need
to oh sorry i fucked that one up sorry sorry refunds i'm sorry forgive me um that's like oh my god are
you okay you can make it so that press and escape closes the bank oh my god there's too many too many
new strats hold on let me let me nail this first strap first because i'm messing it up right empty sack
grab grab combine space bar okay i just need to do that a few times and then my brain will
comprehend the new strike because i'm not used to doing that though that's a whole lot of trauma
yeah like um so edmund was like uh too bad seven seven fifty trout is worth like a hundred key
what empty sack click click combine space bar here we go we're getting there we're getting there
we're getting after repentance i feel like well there's been a bit of whispers about the binding
of isaac because someone did a cheeky datamine when they shouldn't have um and there was something
called the repentance plus it is possible empty sack click click combine yes i might need to do that
escape thing honestly um you can set buttons to escape in space honestly um yeah so it's possible
there might be an item update i am not parent sorry and hold on hold on i can't talk into that
at the same time it's possible that they're gonna have a slight change to some items and all that
jazz the dlc does come out in november which means we can all play multiplayer together and i'm going
to go crazy i'm gonna go crazy sorry um you literally you're gonna be sick of it but i think
it would be really empty sack it would be really good to get dead god together i think that would
be crazy because it would make it so much easier of all through like the max lobby size is four
so three reeflings at a time can do a run with me and and i'll just do it the way we did with
elton ring where i write down your name and who got in and you know take it from their type thing
oh my god right empty sack click click combine thingy okay we're getting there right what was
that skate key thing i need to do now dead god feels so close literally i could do it with
it i could definitely do it with co-op help but do you follow matters or grab items oh no i just
do whatever i want i have never actually it took me so long to like realize i don't have to
pick up escape leaves a bank interface for you wait if i just hit escape naturally
i have my finger ready to hit escape um i play on xbox no crossplay is not going to be plausible
in xbox uh empty sack take them out hit escape and then combine space oh my god we're getting there
we're getting there we're getting so close um i need to far i'm like i'm gonna lie to excuse me
could you imagine if i just he'd like that have a big sniff okay empty click click
escape combine oh i'm getting so good if you made all of those wines i'd get a million xp wait oh
i'm i'm getting nervous hold on a minute i'm starting to understand how that
streamer with the big boogers got so much out of those lobbyers making those lobsters empty sack
click on both escape combine okay we're slowly getting it into my head sorry it takes me like
so long to figure things out and
that was loud sorry what did i do she's got the rhythm click empty grab grab escape space bar
wow man trout going up even hider i made one four two key why is trout going up
did we rig the market reeflings did we become the enemy we swore to destroy
empty grab grab escape this is just gonna be like this for the next five minutes until i can do two
things at once oh when you said brap sorry sorry i'm breaking your ears we're breaking
you ain't even you're not even the fact i'd be going hard i'm breaking their hearts like damn
she's thick but i'm thicker i don't know the rest of the words actually
you caused the spake in the market honestly that's funny if true and real i'm just gonna
i'm going to pretend that's the truth
oh my god this is i will say the cooking was a lot easier to read stream the only thing i
I don't like about Wines as it's over so quickly.
It's over so quickly, it's so quick.
I can't reach out and think.
Either die here, a hero, or live long enough to be on the market.
Honestly.
Oh god, my brain can't keep up with this.
Escape.
God, we're even, we're at like almost 5k grade.
Wait, oh sorry, I was supposed to do space one up.
Do you plan on making an old school runescape pop?
No, I don't know what planning is.
I've never done it or been in one before.
I just used to be the scammer at the exchange post that was like double in money.
That's me.
That's what I did.
I can't believe it.
Wait, combine?
Oh, I never hit escape that time.
Wait, what?
Did Stony cause a spike?
Apparently the price of trout is going really weird right now.
Stony took all my money.
I'm sorry, I took your 1000 gold.
I assure you I did absolutely nothing with it because I abandoned the account probably and never bothered again.
Price trout.
Trout is 41.
Raw trout.
190 for raw trout.
Quick selling for like 189.
Did we actually?
One goes.
Oh wait, sorry, sorry.
I'm messing up the struts.
Stony drawing a big tentacle in the price chart.
Well, I'm happy that we at least reached 70.
That is good.
Sorry, I'm messing up the strut.
Please don't look.
Please don't look, I'm embarrassed.
Um, I don't know what we're going to end on.
If we do, I think someone said it was like five endurance streams.
If I just like non-stop did this, then I would reach it.
I was hoping.
Wait, oh no, I messed that up.
Oh no, it's going to ferment.
Don't ferment, don't ferment, don't ferment, don't ferment, don't ferment.
I was like, honestly, it's less about being efficient and more about saving our hands.
So you guys don't have to stoke the fire for me all the time.
Wah.
Bing, bang, boom, bat pal.
Ah, I completely did not strut that up, but whatever.
Eh, Stronner really wants that giant XP bomb.
Well, I'm wondering, could we just keep doing it until they're all gone?
I don't know how long it takes to do 6,000 wines though.
I could only do 14 per inventory slot, which is a bit of a problem.
So I need like just, what, 14?
How many 14s does it take to get to 100?
I don't know.
But I'm gonna be here for a while, I think.
Or is it 6?
No, 14.
My right wrist is death messed up.
Oh my god, are you okay, Riefling?
From this game?
Because you've been playing this game?
So many grapes.
Wait, people just XP bomb for fun?
Mostly yes.
It's not cool.
Keep going to click on that guy, but I'm not to click on him.
Right, empty the sack.
Click on the ingredients.
Escape, combine, space bar.
See, I didn't write that time.
I have to like mentally bring it to my head.
How much?
Seven.
So I need seven inventories to do 100.
That's quite a lot.
I've messed up, but that's okay.
I'm trying my best.
You need roughly 62k wines to get from 68 to 99.
Bruv!
Who picked this?
Is there not?
Right, let's do fletching.
We can do fletching in four hours.
We're getting how many wines?
There's no way I can do that.
I'm starting, oh no, I'm starting to have doubt.
Reflings, have I messed up?
Have I messed up picking this game?
It's 200 XP per wine.
Oh, that's more than the fish.
Fletching is death going to mess up your route.
Have I made a mistake picking King?
I'm getting nervous.
I'm getting chicken.
Now, I did say the next time we do RuneScape,
I'm going, we're going to do a movie watch along as well,
just so I can rest my voice.
How's the cooking going?
We're starting to feel a bit daunted now,
and it's starting to settle in like, oh no, this is a lot.
The next time we do a RuneScape stream,
we are going to be watching a movie series,
so I don't have to talk and I can rest my voice a little bit,
because I do have quite a few ASMR collabs coming up,
and I need to keep my voice steady.
I need my voice to be steady and ready.
Wines are like 480k if you're consistent.
Per hour, I mean, it's all right.
You need 87k swordfish, so wines are still faster in the end.
Oh my gosh.
Oh.
Reeflings.
I think I might have messed up picking cooking,
but I really want 99.
I've never had my first 99 before.
Oh, I'm getting nervous.
I'm getting shaky.
Just drain back.
What's with the ritual dance at the top of the screen?
Those are reeflings.
They're just dancing with each other.
We're all hanging out at the fire.
Remember, level 92 is halfway.
Stop.
Is it actually?
No.
I will not give myself doubt.
I'll see what happens after the movie marathon.
XP wise, it's halfway.
I know what happened to the legendary stamina.
I'm getting nervous.
I don't know if I have an end in stamina now.
I'm getting shaky.
Wait.
Right.
Empty.
Cooking is the fastest without completely ruined.
Like cooking fish.
Isn't it good that we'll be there with it?
Yeah.
Next runescape stream though.
I'm going to be watching a movie,
so I'm not talking too much because my voice is getting shredded.
But I love it.
Can't help.
Can't stop talking.
Okay.
Making winds is faster.
But the reeflings here in 99 shouldn't be a problem.
Okay.
Wow.
Although it'd be really cool to look back and see how much time I spent.
I wouldn't mind doing some questing after we get 99 cooking.
I don't know if I'm going to be able to do 99 cooking in one month though.
Because of the streams that I've got planned out.
It doesn't really work that well.
Because of Elden Ring.
I would have been able to put more time into Rinscape.
But because of Elden Ring.
99 cooking.
That's all because of a mediocre joke.
That you're a whammin.
Hell yeah.
You got this Johnny.
We'll make you our ma-
We'll get you a master chef.
But it would be kind of cool to look back at like the stream thumbnails and see how much time it took.
Obviously we did some questing.
The first I had so much fun like doing all those quests and like waiting for everyone
and be like okay we'll do this next we'll do this next.
Um so if I do achieve 99 cooking and I'm not burnt out of Rinscape.
Then pardon me I'm burping away here.
Uh I actually wouldn't mind um I wouldn't mind what.
I wouldn't mind doing some more questing again together because that's quite fun.
And it's more interactive than literally you do need to do a quest to cook a coambas.
I can never say I don't know what on earth I'm supposed to pronounce them as.
Um are they better XP than wine?
This is the question.
Do I need combat for that quest by any chance?
50 subs away from 60 stop.
Is that video still getting traction?
Yat. Oh my yat.
Sticking at my yat for the river.
Oh would a Scottish cover of that go viral?
Only by tick manipulating.
Right no if wait so I'm just doing wines for the rest of this entire gig.
Oh no it's only faster if you're paying attention.
I'm just doing wines for the rest.
Oh this is terrible stream content.
You guys just seem to go back and forth to make more wines.
Wait so then why was that chick doing lobsters?
We're the one with the big jibblies out.
Why does she do lobsters for chicken?
Is lobsters cheaper?
Cheaper.
Can I always switch it up?
Yeah I'll maybe finish my swordfish.
Once this batch for a minute I'll swap back to the swordfish.
Just so like everything the reeflings gave me and being used up.
That seems like the wisest thing.
It's cum.
Oh yeah you like when I yap at you?
I'll yap all over you.
All over your face.
Your stomach.
Your thighs.
Fish would be way slower but way less attention.
Yeah um the wane attention batch is getting pretty rough.
I know I can I'm sorry I'm touching my boob right now.
I'm like I'm not even pretending otherwise.
Um I've only got one hand.
Available right now.
We do love the gap.
You can literally just talk to us for the content.
That's why I'm here.
Oh no right.
I think we can finish off the swordfish and the wane.
Also it was actually really funny that you just straight up handed me like your
wane collection.
No questions.
You're not like no this is mine.
You're just like I hear habits Johnny.
That's quite funny actually now that I think about it.
You're like oh there's no point in arguing.
She can have it.
Um wow.
Wow you did it.
Rank.
Wow.
Oh that's so big.
Thanks so much.
Oh you can get it.
Oh sorry I'm getting distracted.
Wane don't ferment.
I got distracted.
I was reading.
Don't ferment.
Your yapping is so strong.
You forgot that you were also playing RuneScape.
The game is more a background to you.
Honestly.
Reef was trying to get a moment of rope.
With all this wine.
Exactly.
Forfeit all mortal possessions to the cult of vice.
No look after yourself.
Get yourself out of debt.
Buy yourself treaties at the corner shop.
And then and only then.
The fermentation is top left.
Oh.
Wow.
That's so cool.
Man Rune.
Rune light plug-in is so good.
We're learning.
Plap plap plap.
Don't ferment.
I was actually there is like this
feature of her that posted a thing.
Where this song's like.
Dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun.
And she goes get pregnant get pregnant get pregnant get pregnant get pregnant.
And I was gonna remake it and be like.
Get pregnant get main break get main break get main break.
But I can't say it that fast.
But I was gonna add like plap sound effects and all that and the music.
And like plap plap and then do my hypnosis thing.
Also that timer stuff can be moved by holding O and dragging it.
I'll leave it in the top corner where it belongs for now.
Mm mm mm mm.
Was that the one by someone underscore?
It was um it got like 6,000 likes.
And I was like oh my god I want to make a rifling version of that.
So I was like get main break get main break get main break get main break.
Yeah.
Oh I keep going to click on the banker but she's not gone.
I don't need to do that.
God there's so much going on over there.
You can perish it.
I think I remember seeing that.
Yeah I like went pretty viral and I saw it and I was like oh my god I want a rifling version.
So I'm gonna put my hypno eyes on and stuff.
I'd be all hey pregnant go pregnant go.
Well I'm not pregnant in your case.
Get your boy pregnant.
Not really for me.
Astrony you can't imagine what's happening by the way.
Wait why what do you mean?
What does that mean?
Why does that sound like a veiled?
Truth.
I mean we're almost at 4k water.
We've just done about 500 there.
I'm wondering if I can do it in one sitting and just let the XP pop and then I'll be satisfied with that.
Oh maybe.
Maybe baby if I don't mess it up.
What?
Hello I want to grab that.
Oh my god.
Riflings are such sugar daddies.
That was 7 million just hanging out on a table.
I literally actually did a gilded.
Someone got into dropping a gilded freaking plate armor.
People are storming the channel.
Are y'all winning, Astrony?
Get in pregnant.
Yeah I've never really been.
I mean I'll cater to everyone but it's not wrong for me.
I'm pretty sure the viral version was either they get pregnant by it or get me pregnant.
No Shiori no it wasn't that one.
I didn't see the Shiori.
I know what the Shiori one is but I definitely must have seen it from the other chick.
I want to grab that.
Astrony reading my words.
Let me shake your hand.
I'm already here lord of storms.
I'm just going to check when Azur comes.
What was that noise?
Why is that a look away for a millisecond and there's lots of weird noises going on?
Hold on.
Let me check when Azur comes on.
Subscriptions.
Azur.
Why does it not say Azur is coming up next?
That's so annoying.
Oh no!
Oh my freaking...
Wait I'm going to do it.
I'm going to do it.
How could I forget the Wayne fermentation?
How could I have been so silly?
I just wanted to make sure when Azur was coming on.
Level 72.
Right I'll take it.
That's actually not that bad though.
I'm quite happy with that.
198k?
Seriously?
Whoops.
That was good though.
That was really good.
Okay maybe Wayne's is the way to go because
big if true.
And I'm not even finished fermenting all the wine that I've got.
Hold on.
I'm going to put the heating on because I'm absolutely frozen in my room.
Oh.
God.
It's 15 degrees.
How am I supposed to survive in these conditions?
Yeah apparently um Australian I rent um but oh where my key?
Hold on.
Cable?
Okay I've got it.
I've got it.
I just I just popped the last into this 73.
I would have jumped three levels if I managed to do one more batch.
All right hold on.
Let's see what's going on with my Azura Deleu.
I thought she is coming up.
Oh my god.
At the Ura.
Please spell correctly.
There she is.
Oh literally in T minus two minutes.
Um Azura is playing a absolutely precious game called Shrey.
I have not yet had the pleasure to play it but it looks bloody good yeah.
Yeah if you've made the 1000 wins it would have been a too much game.
Listen to Strony Yat while at work and produce product to me.
I feel like I'm like um uh I feel like I would distract being like at work and stuff.
Honestly honestly if I had an office I feel like I'd be like one of them
bosses that couldn't just give her rats arms.
I'm like as long as you do the work go home early doesn't bother me none.
Seems like whenever someone gets a manager type job they think they call the shots and it was like
no you're at the mercy of your workers.
Let's let's not get it twisted.
Let's not get it twisted.
Are you doing Marshmallow later?
Yeah of course I'll do Marshmallow more than happy to.
I would I'll do it when we do when we go back to the fish because unfortunately the
wanes require a lot more um like fast clicking.
Every time I move to the left I need to too and I'm I'm getting nervous.
Now not to be a minger but when I tried to go to toilet but nothing came out and I'm worried
I'm gonna have to go toilet in the middle of the stream but I don't want to go toilet.
I normally take a shower after I I don't I don't.
Felt oh my most what time's come in here.
Oops but yes I will do Marshmallow it's not problem.
Use your gamer bucket please do not ever type again.
Gamer bucket.
Now pee bottles I can tolerate.
Gamer bucket like Eric Cartman style.
Ma'am ma'am I need to use the bathroom.
You gotta go for a job eh.
The birthing girl.
My team leader in quality assurance didn't solve their their premiums since months because
the workers are motivated and didn't get trained properly.
Literally just because you in the manager position does not make you a leader.
Magi playing RuneScape into N.E.24 without uh
refunds you know
the gamer bucket.
On a scale of 1 to 10 how jealous are you of men's ability to use gamer ball?
I don't think it applies to me because I have acidic like main stinks.
Actually I probably should have mentioned that to the doctor.
Eep forgot to mention it what was that?
Also if you try to do a fast knight named Fletch and your wrist would die after a few
minutes unless you learned mouse pee.
I don't have that kind of mouse I have up and down on the mouse that's it.
Good dinner ruined sorry.
Sorry okay I think we're gonna have to swap back to the swordfish just for a little bit
because this is like one after the other.
Your face your face melts off kind of acid yeah mouse keys are button presses.
However we just bought the levels and I'll just commentate over oh my god you leveled up congrats.
I'm kidding by the way we're not bought.
I don't know how bad the bots are in runescape I heard they're really bad in world of warcraft
but bots apparently keep prices low in cheeky runescape so I'm not really sure.
Gamer girl uses pee bollies more a lot.
Oh I'm already in trouble by youtube actually I should check that.
Wait no I'll check it when we're doing the fish.
Not while fest is banning the ways.
I will check it after I've done this batch of wines.
Oh yeah it's really bad and wow all versions.
I just know some people say like oh the reason why the bots are actually good is because they
keep everything low price because they're like trying to fight over the same resources type thing.
And I was like honestly that is actually valid feedback.
Right we'll go down to 5000 water and then I'm gonna swap to fish just to like use up all the
fish because it's just in there and I'll read some marshmallow q&a's if you want to say something.
Sorry I know I'm not doing that in a good way but there are bots that kill some of the
hardest bosses in the game in the tens of thousands.
Yeah bots keep runescape economy from high for inflating.
I can't believe it. Capitalism wins again even in my video games and I can't escape.
Didn't they just catch some bots and wow by placing a single row?
Oh wait I seem to remember something like that.
I think you're right.
Also just gold farmers who aren't bots they just sell the money later on.
Oh yeah you can like buy like in-game currency with like actual money so like you get given the
money or something. Because of the there's like a Venezuelan meme so the Venezuelan
Venezuelan economy went to shambles and basically it became profitable for
those individuals to play runescape and sell the in-game currency or something.
Yeah my brain's like kind of remembering that. They sell it on a third party site for
anyone who's like hmm which is against T.O.S. oh okay okay okay I don't know okay I guess it's
against T.O.S. on World of Warcraft as well then with that watch it. That could be wrong I don't know.
Azura has gone live okay if there's any bleeding hearts or any
reeflings who are needing a break from the winemaking. Azura Dooley has gone live.
She is playing a game called Stray and she's a cat and I'm not a goat so if you want to see
Neko Azura you know where to go. Mods I give you permission and thank you for linking my gen mates
when they go live because we love my gen mates. I think Azura might actually hit 4k you know
that I think she's about to teeter over 4k. She's teetering whilst I am on her
tittering this thank you I'll be here all week that's absolutely awful I'm not I was going to
repeat it in order to do that brimps but no that was absolutely awful and I should be ashamed of myself
truly.
Yeah she's at 4k oh that's fantastic. Soon Ace will be 4k as well and
I'll get her to make some more adorable little shorts and I'll put some money in it and then
she can celebrate her 4k as well. Gen mate love. Gen mate love.
Oh no this has put me to sleep this is a terrible idea my room's getting nice and warm and
runescape's so soothing and the reeflings in the back are so hypnotic hold on a minute
you guys put me to sleep hold on a minute I've just had a tea which has caffeine and
cola has caffeine in it as well oh but it'd be so nice to sleep we're doing nap in stream you
guys come nap with me actually I wanted to Bob is it not gonna say it Brian you're ruining these
tts it's Bob thank you for the five love strone is my mommy waifu and she has she has boing boing
and boing boing you mean boing boing
oh so please think of the fermented wine oh messed that up again
you don't know
you didn't know I could do that my mom so I have a basic toggle it's for it's for when I do hot tub
ASMR okay it's hot tub ASMR relax cheeky hot tub I am back spitting on the beat
but yes I am suddenly feeling very tired I think I told you guys my sleep's been a bit
hair wire but I finally got an eight hour sleep last night but I woke up 30 minutes before stream
and I tried to did a a brick cutting fart and then nothing sorry and then nothing happened
I'm like oh no did it pop I wasn't paying attention sugar it popped oh no I'm sorry where were we
oh we're like getting pretty close though oh this is so much faster though
hot tub stream should just be me and be me and a fish tank honestly that's actually pretty
great I might steal that
okay we'll get to the next level with wine and then I'm gonna have to go swordfish
and marshmallows because I'm I'm I don't know why I'm getting hit with a wave of
sleepiness but I'm getting hit with a wave of sleepiness I'm sure she's the other I put the
heating on I have made a greatest error ever I'm not gonna make it I'm funny oh yeah that's
what I was saying I would absolutely love to do like one of those sleeping ASMR streams the problem
is I fart in my sleep so it's not gonna go down well all the amaranth mute I think amaranth muted
in her sleep streams but I don't know how these vtubers and that be doing like live sleep ASMR
I'd be I'd be farting up a storm I'm I'm being I'm being so real like you're brapping your sleep
so how are these girls doing like sleep with me ASMR streams and stuff I'm like how
do it anyway no because what happens if it just sounds really bad what happens if they don't like
my toots we all have our special sleep condition I love biological weapons during my sleep my
weapons of masters but I don't think anyone would complain brah I ain't no woman here
yeah I don't I don't know and like I talk in my sleep as well my mom used to get really freaked
out with it I actually freaked out my gran one time I had a sleepover at her house and apparently
like I sat up really quickly and and my eyes were like wide open she said but I didn't remember
any of it and and when I woke up I was like I don't know why I'm so tired because I felt like
I slept really well because when I have sleepover my gran we just shared the bed and she was like
strongy you were sleep like you sat up and you're it's not sleep it's a sleepwalking if you don't
move anywhere I was sleep sat up basic clown would be extra tingles added on
um but yeah like I did it to my mom as well and she doesn't like it um but that didn't I don't know
maybe you got you maybe you talking you'll sleep too and you don't know if it's sleepwalking if
you're awake but you're asleep okay the walking is just more obvious version okay we're learning
well then they'll judge you while you sleep and when you wake up it'll be rooflings only yeah
get filtered get filtered get filtered get wrapped get wrapped get wrapped um
um
I just think I sleep badly no talking or walking yeah I never remember my dreams but because
I have an alarm set to make sure I'm awake for streams I seem to violently like wake up in the
middle of a dream um which is a rather cutie it's honest that it's rather cutie
over 20k xp drop created in wane already can you oh there's no like statistic for it though I don't
know why
I don't know why Runely isn't tracking my wanes but tracks everything else
stinky
2 xp per wane over 100 wane already oh okay okay I'm starting to get it now I'm starting to get it now
did you ever have sleep paralysis I have never suffered from sleep paralysis once
I've had people explain it to me I've never had it in my entire life they say it's when
your body is still asleep but you wake up in your mind but because you're in a certain phase of
sleep things become really scary um and like you realize that you're paralyzed and stuff
um so it's rough oh I shouldn't have put the heating on I'm going in again
put on me flings you're making me so comfy I'm gonna fall asleep
am I allowed to fall asleep we'll play in my scope
scrawny dutch ovens are written brav ain't no one gonna click on that I mean they might
I had a donut song reward which is me doing an outtake lost recording in audio
oh I was too late on the fermentation but wow 74 okay we're gonna swap to swordfish
and I'm literally I'm snoozing I'm missing the fermentation time sorry but 74
we've already blasted my 70 prediction out of the water which is so good
uh right we'll pop this away for now and then we're gonna finish off the swordfish batch
I do under wait this is E hold on a minute uh up here oh my god there's 5000
oh no I know I don't no you don't need to tell me
let me open up the marshmallow because I actually have time to read chat properly now
there's marshmallows there that's a lot of marshmallows
hmm
being aquatic creatures do we reef flings when you need to be moisturized asking for
a really important time to pick a question I don't know I feel like we just kind of like
hydrate instantly when we enter the water again like we're fine to be out of the water but it's
just where we are the incoming
the incoming pregnancy is more in lore about how you gave us the girls really gets the
enjoyer in me going but are we going to get a dedicated audio for it I like how vealour felt
like our breath of fresh air both in industry and in my roster of each of us love me oh yeah
no I can probably do an audio base around that um it's not a problem at all I'd just be like
give me five babies no more no less that's all I asked I wrote a little thing on my alternative
twitter only 59k winds to go brah brah
I'm I'm touching my tentacles and right now I do it out of principle but if I ain't even
saying anything that's like good
uh hold on I need to read this one um hi strongy a few things I wanted to say and ask most of the
questions are for later than the line so feel free to disregard them if you need to be
uh first I wanted to say you and other girls really helped keep me sane last week it was tough
but you made it through oh that's fantastic congrats I don't know if you're a riefling so I won't call
you riefling um would you ever consider opening a PO box I am so sorry however um I've discouraged
all girls uh from a PO box opening due to the fact that um air trackers are I think no I'm not
accusing you of putting an air tracker in it or anything like that uh the safety reasons just
completely outweigh the fund that could be in a PO box I do apologize what is a box a PO box is
like a setup location where you can send packages and and I would go retrieve them but for safety
reasons I can't have any of that so I am so sorry but thank you for being interested in sending us
stuff um have you ever considered making a music playlist of your fave songs so rieflings can listen
to offline um if you thought something you guys won yeah my current song that I'm addicted to
is by Eust who's Dutch and the song goes
that's what I'm addicted to right now I like smashed out like five ASMR collabs to that song
I just had it on repeat I'm so sorry if it's not your kind of thing
uh but yeah me completely forgetting all the things I have learned oh no I think my my loaf
of bread is moving in my insides which means I might have to go for a break very shortly hold on
need a hydrate really quick if it's going to come up
oh I just taste that blueberry muffin
um question three not sure if you said you're interested in gathering ah I want to get into it
once uh a good place to play without having to pay a bunch of money on their official app
it's an app you can download on the computer called cockatrice it's every card and you can play in
lobbies okay okay okay thanks for answering the questions also love the ASMR can't wait for
girlfriend begging to slip a finger up your arse some more ah honestly I wish I could get away
with that because that's so funny and we could definitely see myself doing something oh please
please please you've got prostate for a reason no no the back door it's mine
wow
oh my god didn't you put my tinfoil hat on for this question I think I do on the topic of black rock
like you wanted earlier they're also deeply into propaganda in the media oh yeah even in gaming and
all their head honchos funny enough for members oh me and riflin on the same wavelength okay I can't
read this out because yeah but hmm okay tinfoil hat gang gang gang gang gang hi stroney after the
comments you made and stream about your butt today I need you to sound me and leave an imprint on my
face I don't think you'd be able to breathe the darlin I think you'd I think you'd need to tap out
so I can you know stand up and not suffocate you all right we'll do it in the ASMR but how about that
convention premium pass going wild okay you get 20 seconds and if you're still somehow conscious
after it you like get a special prize or something sacrifices mama
hey stroney you said gen 2 is cooking does that mean we don't have a chance and there won't be
additions oh no sorry uh no when I say gen 2 is cooking it took a year for concept art model
assets emotes all of that it takes a year to do that kind of stuff we're at the stage of going
all the way back to the start all the way back to one paragraph about this girl all the way back to
right what are the names all the way back like we're all the way back there so please don't there's
no one um I said in the exposing veiler stream no one got a call back um there is no call back
there is no mean um take off your clothes gen 2 is ban here no it is um we're all the way back
thankfully I am not on the heavier side of um development when it comes to names or whatever
but it's like we're now going all the way back um especially like the lower art I need to think
of the story and uh but that's what I mean when I say we're all the way back to gen 2 um
uh or did you just mean characters then and models and niches and such yes that's what I meant sorry
just uh scare you no I will it'll be the exact same pro there's no date there's no date um which
I'm so freaking glad there's no date because making a deadline is horrible and I don't ever want to
have a deadline like that again um the announcements for that kind of stuff only will come out when
things are ready and uh as I said the generation one will be up for a year before gen 2 even like
yeah it'll be at least a year like after do you know I mean I don't know if that means something
good night I'ma turn in please rest well sorry I'm a star too busy rambling sleep well those of you
who need to sleep um but yes uh it's it took a year for development it is not quick it's not easy
it's not fast um and especially when you've got artists that love to go over deadlines um
it makes everything an absolute nightmare um I kind of said a wee bit of it on the
Assassin's Creed Brotherhood stream I had planned everything to occur within certain months
and then everything went to because artists all unanimously went over deadlines so if you're
an artist that works with us look I'm not mad at you everyone did it so you know you know it's fine
but uh everyone went over and it made everything happen in May when May was supposed to be
where I fully focused on getting stuff done for the girls and like we're still kind of picking up
the pieces like I'm doing stuff I shouldn't really have shouldn't be doing at the stage
like it was supposed to be handed off or there's supposed to be something else in place um but it
just uh nightmare nightmare how many marshmallows do you have 850 on the dot actually 850 um
yes I don't even know how I got on that rant hey I still have two ideas for a gen two
what would you want to tell us which one two things that I think would be popular a lollipop dragon
there's no lollipop dragon vtuber's curious to get to do it after the pandora on anything
also I think an insect girl in the style of a traditional japanese geisha who uses her own
self to make her clothes be popular that's unique I've not heard that not a bad idea
uh I think I need a jobby
I think I need a mute and go hold on it makes me still mix going
hold on a minute refund uh i've a hydrate and then I'm gonna go for a few minutes
I think there's a loaf of bread in the oven if you know what I'm saying hold on any open up
my other bottle of water to hydrate you need hydrate to make it come out like easy
I'd mute so we can hear you screaming from the bathroom you scream when you take a job
I'm so sorry I can like feel my my my bills shifting about it and I'm like I don't
okay let's do one more bank run and I'll start cooking and then I'll mute because uh the toilet
is like right there um and obviously I don't want any
I don't I don't want that out there okay man you know I've got big heavy dents you know it's
like a big plop I don't want I don't want my plop.mp3 out there you know what I'm saying
so I'm gonna go make a loaf of bread uh I'll be a minute or so I don't I don't really know how
long it's gonna take um but please enjoy I apologize for this interruption to your usual broadcast
so
Are you squiddling me right now?
There was no loaf of bread to be had, but I took it again.
I'm also ovulating like crazy, just thought you should know.
Bro, the amount of ink that just came out of me, holy shit.
So I don't mind talking about this because I've got hands on chicks.
When whammin' ovulate, you get a clear ink that comes out of you, produced naturally.
And I just had that and I was like, what?
So I'm like, well, now's the best time to send any bibbutes.
I had no idea, but that makes sense why I'm tired because I just want, you know, my body wants one thing.
I have over 2,000 burnt pork, bitch, that was so cool.
Good to know.
That made my neurons burn.
Bro, I wish I could have shown you that, honestly.
I was like, what, an error?
Yes, I don't know what's happening with my butt though.
I need to go number two, but nothing's happening.
You like receiving bibbutes?
Go, go.
I am down atrocious, I volunteer.
Hey guys, do you want to make Gen 2 right now?
I'm ovulating.
Oh my god, we can just say that every time I ovulate, I'll be like, Gen 2.
Come on.
Oh, good to know.
Humans are just monkeys with fanfare shoes though.
Oh, thoughts.
Not quite, close enough.
But a few more evolutionary factors in there.
Multiply, refling, produce, feature, activity.
Sorry, I'm stuttering.
Well, we have over 200 volunteers.
Hi, volunteers.
We did it, we're in the, we're in a million XP.
God, wines are so fast.
We were, I don't even think we were like, I don't even know what we were at the start of the stream.
But we're already a million XP, that's fantastic.
Seriously, we're making, I think the wines really is the vehicle.
Aw, someone said, thank you for existing.
You're so awesome, refling.
Thank you for existing.
Uh...
Oh, I don't know, I kind of...
Someone is currently anonymously editing for the girls, but they don't want any credit.
But we are gonna upload the videos.
You don't need to apologize for not subtitling it.
Subtitling, don't take long on.
The videos are like, three minutes long.
So, are the Gen 1 models quintuplets?
I like to joke that I had the girls in my stomach for like, how long?
12 months?
Yeah, I guess 12 months on the dot.
Nearly there, 5.98.
Oh my god, I owe you guys so much.
There's some more videos, I'm not even uploaded the first one.
Um, I think I'm gonna be too tired after stream though, to edit and upload the first one.
Oh my god, problems of being an overachiever for the male.
Have you ever played Metal Gear Solid?
I don't think I've played it, but I've definitely heard of it.
Game suggestions, Mad Rat Dead.
It's a rhythm platform game on Nintendo.
How odd.
Creeps, it's a puzzle game with a rare art style.
The storyline is decent and you can use it to interact with chat if you get stuck.
I do it like when chat holds my hand through game.
Uh, how'd you mention SteelSeries during the collab?
Hopefully it works well for you.
No, whenever Azura talks to me, I don't know if the other girls can hear Azura.
Whenever Azura talks to me via Discord, her make always cuts out and can't handle her.
And I'm like, Azura, get that noise gate off.
And she's like, I've not got anything on.
And I'm like, what is, like, what's, what's she's in?
Cause I can never hear her, I think the other girls can hear her.
But I can never hear her when we like have a collab on Discord or anything.
And when she gets excited, it cuts into her even more.
But I don't know if she has, like, Discord filters on maybe.
Which is why I'm like, ah, Azura, are you in that SteelSeries?
Cause I've said to her a few times now, but I'm not annoyed or anything.
It's more like a meme where I'm like, ah, SteelSeries.
And someone has sent me a cat box, should it open up?
Fuck it, I'm feeling risky.
What is it? It's a picture.
Whoa! Okay!
Yep, that's the picture, alright.
Okay, I'm not, I'm not gonna open up any cat books.
Uh, links.
On, while I'm here.
Okay!
Okay, Swordfish.
Swordfish, yes.
Um...
Blumow.
Share it with a class male.
I, uh, cuddle.
Are you okay with me using soul smagment?
Smagment, oh my god.
I've got cocks on my mind, what the fuck.
Soul, small segment of the clapping audio for a meme.
Yeah, sure, if so, would you rather wait?
Now, um, now you can post it, it's fine, honestly.
It's cause it's, cause it's gonna be publicly posted.
It's not, it's not really an issue to make any of the content a meme.
I'm so sorry, ah, ah, frickin.
That was, that would poke your eye out, that's all I'm saying.
That's all I'm gonna leave out, that would poke your eye out.
Um...
Oh, she's so damn bad, just like us, real, real.
Keep being that lovable goofy gibber you are.
Oh, thank you, Reefling.
Strony!
Reefling!
I listened to the girlfriend begs the whole day tomorrow.
I remembered you apologizing about no editing as much.
I think, at least in this case, less editing of mistakes added to the quality.
I'm so frickin glad you agree, Reefling.
I have been enjoying, like, not doing scripted stuff and tryharding.
Um...
Like, I have been enjoying recording ASMR.
That isn't scripted, and I'm doing it off the top of my head.
Wait, wait, what do you say?
There was one part where you seemed to accidentally say,
let me hold your fireman, then wait, let me hold your hose, Mr. Fireman.
It felt so natural, cause of how frantic you were becoming.
Yeah, because I did it all off the top of my head.
Um...
I don't know if it was scripted, but you also yawned at one point.
If it was intentional or ad-lib, it was so natural.
No, I've been enjoying doing, like, non-hyper-edited, super production of the wazoo.
I've been enjoying doing, like, such casual...
Um, it's been so lovely.
I've been enjoying it thoroughly.
I really hope you enjoy the first, like, thank you for 1000 subs,
cause it's just me, me-man.
Um...
From work! Ayyy!
Okay, but how many strongy-hands big was it?
I mean...
There wasn't a ruler in the picture, but...
From the glance I got before I closed it, it was pretty...
3D knee...
I laughed so much in that part, aww.
I don't know if it was scripted or not, but you...
Or I'll say that...
If any of it was scripted, that kind of reinforces my point.
points so much of the audio scripted are not felt natural even the mistakes seemed no no that
that was just me that's just me being unable to read uh unable to read unable to formulate my
my thoughts into our proper sentence structure uh i know it was just the meme but it was really fun
and good i think it would be neat to do the natural style more i i freaking agree i 100%
i'm doing natural style open natural style as i said we're gonna finish cooking all the swordfish
and then we'll go back to wine just because wine is so demanding um if you want to help hold the
hose during a number one does that mean i get to hold you up when you go number one brah i would
go everywhere if you did that um straw night i felt it's imperative to let you know there's a
fortnite skin called tropical punch zoe that looks shockingly like you i swear to god if i look like
a fortnite character if i look like a fortnite uh i can i can cane to see i know what you mean
with the bows on our head i get it yeah i get it no that's not bad thankfully i don't look too much
like but i get it would only need to ask once to hold by the way the subtitles were actually fun
but why didn't you make someone else do them well when i do all that stuff there's like
no subtitling takes so much time like it's it's just such a waste of money as well because not
everyone reads the files um until like outsource that work even further is just like oh i'd rather
just save the money and like spend it on the girls type thing because i could have sent that to an
editor and i could have sent that to a video like renderer type thing it's just like i'll just do it
myself you know
oh i've got 14 more questions don't make me or is it even a question
and let me know what you think of that in people i'm not doing live reviews right now are you
joking me you guys are gonna like start hearing yourself in the desktop audio
on the topic conspiracy series one game would be a suit to watch you play disco asylum it's
basically a spruced up visual novel where you play as a deeply schizophrenic police officer have
it small solve a murder we'll constantly argue with the voices all that's interesting hold on that
looks like nice and nice she might give that cheeky go oh god i was preemptive again we're at
4.8 on our um but nothing happens at all right i'll see what we're losing
okay i can't i can't open that on stream but you know what you've said uh i love your long streams
i can do my thing even go to sleep when i'm back and you're still there thank you for your work
oh you're more than welcome i'm glad i can help you like get ready for working stuff and listen
to me in the background and then i'm bing ching when you get back the cooking sound in old school
runes sake is printed oh do you want it off
do you want it off or do you want it a little
i can't even hear it at two percent you know that four percent
there i'm gonna like blast your ears
the voices in my head stop thank you thank you wait why do oh i like them yeah please
wait why do you guys not tell me so much earlier i'm sorry i didn't mean to subject you to such um
fallacies fallacies i don't think that's the correct word brain but i'm glad you're trying to use
words outside your comfort zone
hey stroney just wondering when you plan on sitting on my face right now
lie down
since ai is blowing up right now any ideas of implementing it in your content
no and do you even want to
um
the only i wouldn't put um ai content like monetize it i don't think that's right i don't
mind like ai memes of myself or something like that like that's funny um but like actually ai
content like i wouldn't use ai content on a thumbnail and then earn money from it like i don't think
i don't think that's very nice because as a content creator like someone can literally you
know yank your voice and then make money off of it and it was like well why would i do the same
to someone else like that's not nice you know can you hold it do you think you can handle
um have you considered trading a chat box from your stream absolutely not are you kidding me that
all that thing we'll see is use the other hole refling other hole other hole other hole
that all that chat box is gonna say
i don't really use marshmallow marshmallow very often if someone wanted to send you a
bit but how it says oh you do what's called a cat box link and then you send me the link
and then i look at the link and the rest is history
asmr booth hypnoscript i've already recorded the asmr booth
plot which was funny as anything i haven't done too much hypno because of patreon's restrictions
but i do have a four part series that will go up on the alternative twitter for free because
it's not welcome and the replacement audio is gonna be my honey cup of tea
oops sorry i'm losing it i don't know i don't know why i'm like so sleepy after eating i thought
you're supposed to get energy from food you lied to me will you permanently scramble my
brain pretty pretty please oh i can't do that you're supposed to be having a good time
just pinching but hypnosis is a concept make great hypnotic focal point as you sway back
and forth and bounce off and down have you seen the the derriere vtuber models that you can get
i wouldn't mind that honestly i think that would be good
congrats on the second week of debut i'm one of the newer meflin hi hi meflin
i must say your constant chatting has become a daily routine in my life and completely infactuated
with you mostly with you and your girls so thanks oh no thank you thank you for being open to a new
like line of content you made me really happy in this vacation and i'm excited for the lord of
the rings marathon i'm christmas oh and uh if there's a question when can we expect your
membership streams membership streams start next week you will see it on the schedule that i post
publicly um that will go live after buckshot roulette is when it will go up there are three
member streams in the first week and we'll take it from there and see how we're doing how we're
doing how we're vibing actually no idea what this is i need um i think it's called like catbox
litterbox or something like that is four long enough asking for a friend replaying did me mentioning
ovulation get you all riled up i was gonna show on fanslame uh some stuff later on
we're hired wired that way
more than enough wait i need to cut the booth
oh i keep doing that early i'm not max well a burnt one
um right i burnt a swordfish who am i who do i think i am just wasting litterbox is temporary
catbox is the three days ah why is this website japanese i can't speak japanese can you speak
japanese no why did you pick a japanese website then i thought you were the gamer of six not a
weeb i still love you you dork the other websites that offer this kind of q&a thing are very broken
catbox it curious cat is very broken um so however this japanese website called marshmallow
isn't broken it's actually very highly functional other than the filters you have to be a smart level
refling and bypass the filters have you thought of more games you can play in stream snipes with
the whole chat in the future after you get night night cooking absolutely every week i plan on doing
some version of a stream snipe game um you burn swordfish until 80 on a range and 86 on a fire
um yes no there's plenty so elden ring is our next stream snipe game that will be doing tons of
november i know it's quite far away november uh definitely lots of isek and
i was going to do drunk apex but everyone rolled their eyes at me at the same time so maybe not
drunk apex i don't know some sort of drunk multiplayer game i think valerant also gets
a shout on as well and i'm like but i can have four other reeflings in the lobby
but you
why do i get so sleepy after i eat that food i don't understand i had eight hours of sleep
uh
you didn't answer the question how bb is four enough yeah
he'll be silly of course it is
are you going to have a password set up on elden ring so you can only summon reeflings yeah of
course uh maybe call it shell um or eyes because i hypnotize you with my eyes
um but yes there'll be two good reeflings and one bad reefling like an invader so we can
we don't get bonsai bonsai i thought you needed 10 hours maybe that's why
a big it wasn't even a big meal i literally had a muffin and a nature valley bar a cup of tea a
cold out which i'm not even finished in some water and my brain's like okay let's go down again
i'm like bro we're not even halfway through this endurance stream um so i heard mommy was ovulating
ambient reefling cesaris of cesaris reefling did you type this correctly or did you type it
so fast you didn't you didn't check your spell and now i can't read it because i'm too dumb
women are epee gals i can't believe it someone said plop plop plop plop get pregnant good pregnant
good pregnant yeah you want gen two shawnee i can't wait to be permanently under your influence
oh wait already i'm under your influence i don't want to get over this trance love you momay love
you reefling someone says i want you good thing i'm ovulating i want you to reefling
oh no my fire it's gone i distracted the reefling so much we forgot to keep up the fire
thank you for the fire gg even the runescapers are one-handed right now
why do you stream at 4am and why is this the time you wake up to stream is it just a spidey in
particular no also thoughts on ozzy afl very violent very violent um i've seen some slow mo
knocks in uh ozzy afl it's pretty scary i want to go see a match like in person just to be like
i'm i'm a real Australian citizen wink wink um uh why do you stream at 4am i stream at 4am
because i'm normally an endurance strummer wait i'm not kicking anymore um and
if i need to go to a doctor's appointment or if i need no doom no doom reefling um or i need to
you know go shopping or i need to go um see my chinese grandma at the shop
squiddin me right now
oh brian doesn't read it out don't worry i'll read it out kfp spidey says thank you for the
stream so far it's been great listening while i pack for my move i'm all i was also the red guy
dancing at the start of the room thank you brian and thank you kfp spidey for the five i appreciate it
i'm sorry i can't do brian's voice i'm so sorry i tried my best
my sister please in the afl she's messed up with a bomb shooting it is so dangerous like the head
trauma you can get are like cauliflower ears if you get blunt force trauma to your ears by the way
you get a condition called cauliflower ears where they like spike up spike up did he spike up is
right um but yeah thank you so much but uh please do not feel forced to hang about if you're
getting a bit tired azura duly is currently playing meow meow a bit of stray a bit of meow
oh wait no not on the ashes on the fire don't be silly scott fish
what is arsonist reflunding the wane certainly helped with the burn rate down to 13.7 actually yeah
you're right i thought you were meme in there you said though but no i do not stream at 4 a.m to
spite any ozzy's um i do it because um i'm actually a knightable um by default so it's
actually quite helpful that i stream at this time if i were to stream at 10 a.m because that was the
other slot imagine being an ozzy at like oh no shock of behaviour imagine getting granted citizenship
wouldn't that be crazy um wouldn't that be crazy i say that is if i'm not going back to scotland
you know i'll fucking spend how much money on it i'll say this again if you ever want to run a
business and you're either you can do it in the uk or you can do it in oz do it in oz you will make
you will get to keep a lot more of your money the attack like because of tax purposes if you set it
up in the uk you're just getting absolutely blasted um brine should now work on those super chats if
you want to replay wait hold on can i replay thanks for the stream so far it's been great
listening while i've had for my move i was also the red guy dancing at the start of stream yay
brine works now okay i do apologize to any superchatters who didn't wait hold on wait i can
replay the super chats are you squiddling me are you squiddling me are you squiddling me right now
i love strony as my mommy wife and she has boing boing and she's boing boing she has boing boing
thank you brine for your uh what whoa whoa whoa these oh no is camp log reefling gone
pair my camp log i can't believe it i can't believe my poor reefling has things to do
do you have a vr headset i don't not yet it may be plausible i'll be getting one because i think
oh 75 oh my god we can members can now cook rockades fish and
bats are you squiddling me right now wow guess who's back strongy it's me how are things going
we're um level 30 ed 75 sorry i have numbered dyslexia um
i was going so well i'm at 75 jack thank you for the two i appreciate it wait we're the heck
and tiny spain e tiny spain e thank you for the sorry i'm a bit i'm not flustered that's the wrong
what i'm just eating food at the bank sorry i'm not flustered i don't know why my brain is telling
me to shut down right now i'm literally in the middle i'm like i'm can you know i'll tell you what
i'll order food i'll order food and then i will automatically stay up for that food because i'm
like by the way this is oh my god a mallet i'm going to say this in stream the script master
has just messaged me this if i write something about brocon but they do not specifically say
big bro or sis but wait what our big bro but make reference to the same mother is that against
the rules yes you can't say that yes you can't say that try rephrasing please
don't worry the script master has your back that's all i'm saying he he knows the interest of the
pinpril in and we're gonna try our best to be able to um but he's joining what if you
want to get comfy in bed and then get oh my god you seen that meme that's like when your sush was
that when your sushi roll is sad and just take your sushi roll and put her down and base script
Albre of the script quality is gonna like go up dramatically after the three month mark
You're gonna know when the script master came into play because you can tell it's like not me writing that shiz anymore
You're like oh god finally strong. He's not doing it anymore. I
Say that as if I'm not writing all my own stuff
But I want to write my own stuff because I'm passionate about it not to say that script master isn't passionate
But I quite like writing my stuff because it feels it feels more intimate when I can like do it between
Me and we fling, you know, we do it together and I have you in mind. You are my muse we fling. You are my muse and
Feed the fire for mummet. Thank you
Oh
That's it when you're when your girlfriend is that Lira in a blanket layer a ruler and then yeah, yeah
Yeah, that's the one that's me
Sometimes it's nice being a little bro. Well little bros are for a zero big bros and me
I
Yours are exceptionally good. Oh, that's very kind. I I like
Um, I did have the option to hand over my scripts to someone else
But I I like doing it between us really need this fire making XP for real for real
I
Imagine you and the other girls write their own stuff. There was a hand full of girls who wanted to give their hand at it
I absolutely did not expect it because um, it's just more time and I don't want the girls like stressing out over that kind of thing
But yeah, I
Just don't want to stress the girls out if they want to do it of their own violation
We all listen and then that's perfect. Did I just hear?
She's not happy a feather
and
Day 10 of eating celery daily is so bad. Oh, no, don't put yourself through celery for that
Celery is nasty. I've never enjoyed it. I'm sorry. Doesn't matter how much like humus you put on it view a listen by a listen
Did I just say it funny bullish in bullish in there's no I okay. We're getting there
Stopped flusterers exactly
He he oh my goodness
Violation oh no, now you're getting me confused
Yeah, I love your scripts on patreon strony. Thank you. I did them off the top of my head myself
I
Will be very curious to see what the doughnut song results in I have I
Imagine the week after the doughnut song concludes
I will be having very short streams so I can focus on the rewards one at a time
And I know some agencies had a bit problems trying to handle streaming and getting rewards out
obviously because I'm such an
unbelievably
Bad workaholic or good however you want it good for people who like content content content bad for the actual
Workaholic themselves because they just non-stop keep going, but I think I definitely am in a position where I can get stuff out
relatively quick
Whether that be an audio a collab audio
Yeah
Maybe those are good if you want your money from birds. I have a huge backlog of willow logs from doing
Short streams like 10 hours instead of 12. Mm-hmm
For me a short stream is two hours, which I think someone said that's literally what the regular stream time is for the average
Vtuber and I'm like
Two hours is me like doing stuff in the background
I'm not being funny like if I have it if you have
If you look and you see I've done a two-hour stream and nothing else that day
That means I am doing like so much work in the background
type thing
Is that these scrawny cuddles? There's only one of them in this world, baby
Time to cook through my 3k swordfish literally that's what I'm doing just getting through it
It takes her two hours just to start playing the game Lamal
Management got me there hydration chick
Wow
Hi scrawny in the most loving way possible
I want to bury my face in your butt until you pass out while you hmm yourself. You're too hot. Oh
Just your gentle talk is enough to get me going sometimes when you talk about other hot things
I need a moment to calm down. Oh my god, we've got me blushing shit
Stop
I'm glad I have that control of you
That power
Makes me very happy
Um a bit too happy. I think I take a little bit too much
Um pleasure from such a thing. Is that terrible?
Sure do have powers to arrest the boot up. What is this a Windows 95? No because I won't stop yapping
I
Love to eat sushi. I could do it for hours. Oh, yeah
Is that because I'm a cutlery?
Oh, I keep wanting to freaking make that what does your oh she smell like meme
because
the reason is
Uh, what's the reason oh because I use a lemon scented soap
I wanted to post it and be like this call fish comes pre-seasoned
Um, and then I think there's only one other girl that needs to do it
And then everyone knows what the whole velour smells like
Six thousand subscribers reached
What we celebrated 5k
Oh my gosh
Ah
What I'm really excited
Why is it getting so cold
I'm so confused. It shouldn't have been
Let's statistically yeah, it should have only been pushed to 5k people. It's bizarre. I didn't expect that at all
You have all the power over us. Take more
Thank you for the tip
rilke kadmus
Any rilke kadmus
Thank you for saying it. I'm so confused. I'm like daddy you make a tweet and be like I can't believe it but in under 24 hours
The one thing I think I've mentioned this in another stream
The one thing I do not like about being a vtuber in this context
Is you have to play the numbered games and you have to play the
Oh, thank you for this
Um in terms of like milestones
Ah
And it's a hard one to navigate because if you don't say thank you thank you
You look almost ungrateful
But if you do
Say thank you. Thank you. It looks like you're counting and waiting for the next milestone just so you can spam. Thank you. Thank you, you know
and
You don't have to say thank you
Well, the problem is I'm trying to get like
Gratisom 6k moment. Thank you little wifling. Um
The thing is like it would be really good to get on vtuber news or any kind of source like that because it brings more attention to the girls in general
which is why
it's like
I don't want people thinking i'm counting
But what i'm thinking about is the probable
Like the possibility that it could gain new eyes to the girls because I want nothing for them to succeed
I've got everything I want right here. I've got my wiflings. We're freaking meman. We've got member streams. We've got multiplayer games
Uh, we've got a smart the wazoo coming out
I've got collabs of other vtubers that are willing to interact with me like I've got everything I need
I'm so freaking happy
I want the girls to achieve their dreams and the truth of
Of them achieving their dreams is one to have enough money to be a content creator
Some of them are looking to move out. Some of them are looking for upgrade equipments on their own. Um
You know, um, emmy was fantastic. She's already designed her 2.0 model because it feels more like her
um
That kind of thing I want the girls to have it some of them wanted 3d models. I wanted them to get it and
The truth of the matter is in order to get these things
That there needs to be eyes on the girls
Um, so I can help them achieve their 3d goals and stuff
Although someone said that someone was like, what do you mean by the three year mark?
When I whenever I mentioned the three year mark
Congrats to whoever leveled up there whenever I mentioned the three year mark
The reason I say three years is because statistically three years
And you're done. You're you're persona. You're whatever you want to call it. It may be
Oh my god, you really look like emmy as well in games. Uh
The
Reason why three years is this mysterious number placed on someone's head is because that statistically if you do find success
By the third year the success goes unless you make you change your content up dramatically
and the reason I say three years is because
Remember before you like wait, so strong. He's only got three years relax. Stop doing relax. No
No, that's not it's very possible that strongy and uh, like once we're all satisfied like I won't stop until you guys
Are ready for me to stop like please don't no don't do
But please don't think I'm like just gonna abruptly stop overnight. Like that's not the reality of the situation at all
It's very likely I will want to focus on
Hypnosis audio is like way down the line
Um, it's over. No, so never no if you if you don't want me to go I'll be streaming in my little
retirement home doing my thing
um
I've got an end in stamina like seriously this is
Just it took so long to get here and everything worked out in the end and it just feels so nice to be
I don't I just
Like to be accepted to be um just having fun folk want to hang out. It's just casual. It's none of this like
you know
artsy fartsy like
Oh, this vtuber is giggling their head off every two seconds. Um, this vtuber is like putting on this like
horrifically fake personality
Uh, pinna. Thank you for becoming a member. Um
The first year is an introduction. The second is establishing and third is plateau. That is quite literally what it is. Um, that is what most um
People experience. Um, if you've ever been like wait, why did that one in the vtuber, uh, go on a new account?
um
that's basically remaking a persona because
You plateau and it's perfectly natural to plateau. There's no there's no issue
Um only 155 more. We are mesh
Oh
Thank you. Peter ever in ham for becoming a member. I appreciate it. Can I be honest with you all for a sec?
Right, let's see. What's up
question mark
What's up?
Or does this reefling share with us?
We will
Strawny until we die at 99 because it's part of our little heart. Oh
I far okay. You're done reefling. You're done
Hmm deeply departed. He came and he farted
Damn you and people can't just do the same thing successfully without ever needing any variation in their content
I haven't seen examples of that before. Yes
Um, I really like the behind the scenes psychology about about at all. Um
Monster girls, please
Thank you for coming to member. Is that you asking for gen two designs to be monster girls? Oh boy. You're in for a treat
um
Yeah
There's been two designs that have been accepted
Lollilolliloll
Mods take some of his pennies and scatter them across his home wait, that's so specific
Oh, I don't know
I feel like you feel happy streaming. I can see that
Here junior. Can't imagine momy
without this
There was obviously right actually I can tell you something behind the scenes
And you're not gonna like it, but it's no longer the case because I got a script manager in
If and when gen two came around
There was no way I could keep up with the daily streaming and trying to organize all the script stuff
Um, but thank you to script master for coming into play
because without them
Being there I with with gen two starting. I probably couldn't daily stream. So
That that's the honest truth
I was going to stream my ass off for an entire year like non-stop back-to-back double streams on some days doing like endurance this endurance that
Um, but thankfully that's no longer the case. Um
Obviously
when if and when gen three were to occur
That's a lot of girls to manage and I'm not sure how realistic the daily streams will be at that point
There's my only concern and the thing is none of us have a crystal ball to look into the future
So I can't tell by zero by zero by zero every day is a blessing. No, don't cry. Don't do him. Don't do him
We're not even there. We've not even we've not even got the first model of gen two
Literally we have fucking two approved concepts. That's it. Don't burn out in spite. See that's the thing
Spite can get you very far. Maybe I will spite everyone and just say I'll stream daily and you guys weren't ready for it
It's so jovert. No
Less than six kxp for 80 million hp and I'm just telling you
That I'm from shume brap triber allegations. I've not been been
No
Stranny you're talking about the future and the game background is making me feel emotional. Okay. No. No. No. No happy happy thoughts happy thoughts
um
If you can do this and not even two weeks. I can't imagine what you're gonna do in a year
I mean, it's not really gonna change like oh, sorry
and
There's not really much like this is
Me having happy times. We do have some monthly events planned
and
type things uh
Going on got ASMR collabs planned. I think ASMR is like a bread and butter. Please
Please consider ASMR as a bread and butter of y'all or and some people kind of get annoyed when like ASMR at ASMR
um
VTubers dabble and ASMR and don't always like commit to it fully, but no, let's bread and butter
I think everyone's gonna be participating in it just silly
um
Can you spit on us? Yeah, you want me to spit all over your face?
Open it open your mouth
I'll let me spit on your face
um
Yeah, don't don't worry like
Ah freaking, you know how open and honest I'm I'll tell you what it looks like and what things are like and you know
People who do watch you can get a little tip bits of information or maybe early access information
VTubers ASMR
Finally someone combined two of my favorite things
Well, I actually got a lot of feedback where people were like, I am so tired of like VTubers
blue bowling
And they'll participate in something and then withdraw
and
Because they never really had a thing for it and I was like, oh my goodness aren't we hitting the
The hammer on the head with a nail wait
The nail on the head with a hammer wait other way around. Yeah. Yeah, then finally hitting the nail on the head with a hammer
a
because
That's quite literally like all of us are completely fine
I mean, uh, sadly, thank you for coming on a a member
Congrats on the six k-saps. What also strongly never leave us. We can't function with
When you leave for just a second, we all start no reef fling. Thank you gaming kitsune for the tip
No, I'm not freaking leaving like I'll tell you the plan
And I'll always tell you the plan what the deal is like when have I freaking
I mean, I'm only hitting like what NDA content
Even then fucking what NDA content have I got left behind at this point?
Oh a hydration hydration. I'm gonna have to drink some water
Water from my bottle of water
The farm is the real plan trust trust in the farm
So I was says where should I eat?
Um, I'm getting Mexican
I've ordered it hold on let me check let me check where my Mexican food is
And before it's sitting outside. Oh wait, hold on
Uh
Hold on
Wait scriptmasters asking
Why do you even
So the sentence mum says I'm in charge as we over the lane
Yeah
Yes, because that implies
Sorry, you guys are getting corrections. Yeah
Okay, there we go. Sorry scriptmasters trying to really help out the pin pills here
I'm I'm trying to tell them like you need to skirt the patreon to you
Boring boring inside yourself, okay
Um, we will have a castle and I'm a little little cafe
Okay
That sounds like a scary. Oh a spicy script
Very much so
Azura's four part series got finished main
My four part series is now going to be on twitter for free because it's not allowed
So I'll need to think of another four part series. Maybe
He's feeling a cheeky chinese takeout honestly chinese and australia is amazing
It's so good
How exciting bye. Bye. I have to sleep
Uh, have a nice dream. Well, thank you so much
For anyone who needs to sleep or needs to get a few things done around
the hoose
Or you need to get some water in you. Please don't be afraid to go do so
Keep yourself as healthy as possible
A succulent chinese meal
Oh, I should do a Scottish dub of that
What have I done wrong?
Just enjoying a meal a succulent chinese meal
Dubbing dubbing dubbing memes, but i'm scottish video
Honestly, maybe that would work out. I feel like that's got potential a wee bit potential not too much
Get your hands off my tajer
This is democracy manifest
Get your hands off my cuttlefish sir. Oh, honestly, maybe we might be on to something a little a little funny ha ha series
um
Unhand my hoose
Nah, hell nah gotta stay and see the end of the day
That'll be aam
That's so unhealthy though. You should sleep only I can do such endurance things because I'm a big girl
If there's anyone lurking who is perishing azur duly is on
stray
Oh it rhymes azur duly is playing stray
And mercy modeste is playing harvester part two
um
Azur is live mercy is live in t minus one hour 30. I repeat in t minus one hour 30 modi modi
modi mercy modis is live
What someone leveled up congrats
Ah, I see you know judo well and you are you ready to receive my limp
Just like the blue scottish power ranger meme honestly
uh
Pick the memes right and it's probably got a lot of potential
I thought about doing like reading the most bizarre
Reddit stories because there's a really famous one where this guy broke both his arms
But I can't say the rest of it, but I wanted to read it because I thought it was all right
But I'm not sure it would work out
Maybe it would be like a twitter series I guess and I'll be like oh go subscribe to my youtube
Time for work unfortunately have a good stream
No, you have a good work day. How dare you please remember to hydrate and look after yourself and remember
Boss makes a dollar you make a dime. That's why you take a big job beyond company time
Uh, please make sure that any stress levels you feel at work are uh at your pay grade if you get paid minimum wage
That's not your problem
Should have paid you more to care more
They haven't skipped it
Oh, is that the arm where he gets some help read the number 15
Burger being but baddest, but that's being boob on being burger being but burger
It's not fungus, but that's it burn foul bad bite be bought boob at
Burger king foot lettuce
The last thing I've already forgotten the freaking
What the frick I just said the b version of the meme burger thing burger king footless. So that's the thing you want in your burger king
Burger king
Bootless. Oh my god. What?
Um, do a five-part audio where you're getting paid prego each door see me each video around the crack door
How would I do that though?
Oh, yeah, give me a bro con
Oh, no, that's not gonna work
Maker ginger maker blue hair, but no, why
what
We can't make that
I've got a sea queen audio coming out where I share you with all my daughters
Um, I always take uh, hmm first thing on my shift if you're good at something never do it for free exactly
The joker was a kitten
That's what food coloring is for
Didn't you get mm-hmm with all the girls at the same time in the ASMR booth with the eyes covered?
Yeah, basically that's how it happened
Hmm
But yeah, I've got a sea queen audio. I don't I think it'll be a donathon reward like because the girls
and are all gonna like help each other out with their donathon rewards like as uh
As I like, yeah, let's go
Sea queen, that's the only way we can that's the new saying
Um
POV all the girl velour girls are fighting over you the one human left on earth that hasn't
Decided on which girl
I thought about Icy and Emmy doing something like that
where they're fighting over
Where the ink goes or who the ink goes to um
Um
Sea queen, uh, yeah, I mean it's pretty creative. I'll give you that
Yeah, Icy and Emmy would a hundred percent fight over it, but I find it really hard
to do
that kind of
Seven five hundred swordfish and I burned two k of them. I burnt so much swordfish as well. Don't worry
Where the ink goes. Yeah, if I mean Icy ever collab like that, I would be so happy
I mean they already got a collab audio on the way um of that nature
Um, but it's a bit different. Uh
Do you want spoilers or do you not want spoilers? I don't mind doing spoilers
I think it's coming up. Is it august the collab audio start off? I think it might be
Um
It's got to be really hard to do
I want spoilers no spoilers. Oh, no you guys are split
Go hard with spoilers. Mmm
So in the plot
But close your ears if you don't want any spoilers in the plot Icy and Emmy fell out
And you the listener and you can either be a pin pal or
A snowberry wherever when you want you force them to
To make up
by
Using a massage gun to relieve their muscle tension
Because their muscle tension is the reason why they fell out
Okay, um, then me and mersey have one
Where we're uh nurses that shouldn't be qualified because of what we do
And then Azura and sheebie's one. I don't think the masses are gonna like you
I'm not gonna change it because I I like the script. I like it, but I'm not sure the masses are gonna like it
Azura and sheebie
catch you in public
um
Cross-grossing
And the m word you
And I don't know if it's gonna go down well or not
It's a very unique scenario, but please
And before you're like, oh my god, I hate it. Oh my god, stroney
I hope you die in a fire because you wrote that do you honestly think they're never gonna do another collab audio again?
Don't be so silly
It's just the first one that I gave
Yeah, it's pretty but it was pretty out there. I don't know. It's just the inspiration. I got to write for them
So I wrote it and there it was and they what?
Holy moly, that's a spicy meatball a massage gun. Yes a massage gun. I'm excited for them
It's spicy. Oh boy that one does sound very uh, yes, uh
That sounds like something
Patreon would get no, they don't um, they don't care. Um, I know what's
Uh, good to go and what's not good to go on patreon. So damn. Yeah, really pretty. Yeah
I there's a few things I wanted to cover. Um
Having the freedom to explore a bunch of
Scripts is something the scripts
Yeah, like um, it's just different things we're hitting along the way like as I said, I kind of said it from
I'm not pigeon pigeon holding any girl into a particular
category because doing so will
Limit their income source and their income source and longevity are related to their success of yellow
And I do not want to kneecap anyone. That's not fair
It is what it is you're given spicy scenarios compared to anything else. I've seen this is some top-tier content. Yes
And literally when the girls do collab audios again, they still have three other audios going out that month as well
So it's not like, you know, not everything can be for you
We live in a society of burnt fish
I
Like to try different stuff. Yeah, literally just give it a shot either you'll listen to and you'll be like this isn't for me
Or you'll be like, okay
I'm reacting smile
There's there's only two outcomes. It's either no, thank you and turn it off or I'm reacting smile
We'll get we'll all get something at some time. Yeah, basically literally everyone is cared for
It's not possible
For a creator to come out with something you love 100% of the time
It's just not possible unless they do the same thing over and over and over again
But then that is like really pigeonholing and it's it's for the success of my girlies. Okay
They gotta succeed
Or what's gonna make them want to sign there the second year of the contract, huh?
Can't wait to find out what it is. I love
Oh, I'm glad
Thanks for reading it anyway, we would
They just misspelled something and I said it wrong or something. It's okay
I'm not into feet, but I like yours. Oh, yeah
I love everything viewers done so far. Thank you
um
you know, I had a year in the making and
Just everything is falling into place so beautifully. Um, I spoke to
Oh, I'm gonna say her. I'm gonna butcher her names so badly
The Vtuber obaki
That's definitely not how you say it, but um, she was talking about a project finally coming together and
You know, I was like, oh, I can completely relate to that. So I replied to it
And I was like when the puzzle pieces finally arrive and you can start slotting them into place is so satisfying
and
And I felt that to my very core
The everything obaki pump. Yeah, it's not obaki. There's no way that's how you're supposed to say it sounds like
I'm trying to say tobacco. Obaki. Obaki
That's exactly how you say obaki. Oh, wow
No, me accidentally being smart. I can't believe it
Obaki obaki
That is the say say it first try. Oh, I'm so smart with the heck and
Yeah, she put up a tweet saying like her projects are finally coming together and I'm like, oh, I can relate to that on such a deeper level
And oh, mommy's excited to be
Five moods ahead and her main chess game. Oh, I can't wait to one be one years in chess. Actually you guys aren't ready
Tobacco is true. No, no tobacco
I can't smoke I can hardly drink to the life of me. I get one beer in me and I'm gone
That's why I wanted to do drunk apex because we can all do salt lake city
Because no one's in it other than us
Uh, I don't know what drunk game. I wanted to do drunk game, but I don't go offline until we win type of thing
But I didn't know what game to do
If I lose I get to see discord, right? What? Um
Wait, what if you lose the one be one chess you get to see the discord where we all say inappropriate stuff to each other
Say no on that one chief
I've been a lazy refland. I haven't looked at any of your daughters. Yeah, you haven't. Have you not checked any of them out?
Actually the highlight
Reels are from debut or right around the corner. I think there's one more girl that needs to be made
Um, and then the debut highlight things can be made
Um can be uploaded. I know that everyone's monetized as well
What opening do you use in chess? Uh, I call it the twat move because I don't know what what on earth is my opening move
Probably the second pawn just shove them out by two. Have a wee go
I don't know nothing about chess
All I know is that I want a one be one you guys in chess and I'll put classical music on in the background
And I'll see if I can even win against one refling
It'll be interesting to see if I can win one game
I can easily recommend girls like a shopkeeper
I have a secret conspiracy
Strony allows a small handful of fans into the discord every month or so to be groomed by the girls
Then makes them forget and kicks them out
It's actually quite funny
No, uh, I sure there absolutely nothing goes on in the discord. Um
Mercy's ASMR was a banger
No, her is her meme ASMR. No, I didn't upload it. It couldn't be her actual ASMR stream got 25 000 views, which is insane
Insane in the membrane
Can you drill my dad? I'm terrible at chess, but he plays it daily
Are you joking me? He'd like smoke me in one
You can play checkers and connect four of his people here. What in runescape?
Play checker. What play connect four with me in runescape right now. What how do I do that?
Is that real?
At the grand exchange
Hold on. Wait, let me finish doing this batch of fish. We're going to the grand exchange like right now
Hello
Where's the grand exchange a little to the right?
Oh, there's a bridge here. Oh, but we don't have the freaking tunnel at the grand exchange. We're gonna have to go down in our wall
What we can break in one v one each other
Right, we're going to the grand exchange to play connect four. I'm not even kidding
I'll empty my inventory though. I don't want to go filthy
Stranny, I'd feel bad about beating you in chess. Oh, no, that's the thing. I like losing
You know dumb loss and all
You see now if I lose against you after you said you have never played would be such a sad and depressing thing
I would need something to feel happier
Get plopped get plopped get plopped there. You're happy
I'm joined listen to um playing overwatch in the meantime. Oh god. How is overwatch these days?
I know a new character came out venture, but
um
Folk weren't happy about or something. I've I've nothing apparently she eats rocks lamal
What rockier? Um
Right, how the heck right we're going if any reeflings want to follow me just follow my character
Um, and then we'll go down to the grand exchange to pledge to play connect four
Any reeflings want to come?
Uh
Right, okay, how's it right? We're going to the grand exchange to play connect four. No, I'm not trolling
We're doing it
Oh, wait, I should walk because that reeflings walking
Oops, no, no, no, we got the reefling car. Oh, no, wait, hold on. We need to help this reefling that's stuck
Okay, there that worked. Yeah worked. Okay, we got that reefing. We'll walk around these borders until we're out
And then I think it should be okay
Going to the grand exchange to play four in a room
four in a room
Me also me, uh, it's going to take me so long to get 99 cookies and also me. Let's go to the grand exchange
Just so we can play some bit. Yeah
Well, we already are
Look at all that raw fish that needs to cook
Is the grand exchange the trading hub? It absolutely is
Oh, wait, we can follow
We are following rabbit
There's an entry to the west of the grand exchange. Wait, I thought it was blocked for members only. I don't have any agility though
Yeah
Isn't this
Huh
Playing video on a video opening in the wall, uh
We're learning
Thanks for being in human history
Oh, no, we're playing chess and the loser must have be the winner for the day. Oh, what's gonna happen?
It's annoying tanking is but
All right
Okay, where the heck are we playing connect for? How do we do it?
This
No
Talk talk to who talk to them
Wants to play a ranked game of runelight two minutes per move
Oh, no, what does this mean?
Uh ranked
Wait, you have ranked chess and runescape
Uh, I'll be green nature rune challenge
Whoa
Oh, no, I didn't mean to place it there. Okay. Well, I'll put it there then
Uh
Oops question mark
Wait, we can like straight up. No, you're not supposed to actually win against me. What the heck?
Uh, uh-huh. Oh, no, I'm gonna lose wait, they can go like that
Oh, no, what have I done Franklin?
If I do that
And then that
Oh, no, wait, did I miss? Oh, no, I messed up
I lost
Okay, wait, okay, you win. Does it end?
I'm so bad at this
Did it win? Okay. Yeah. Yeah, it ended. Okay. Let me try again. Let me try again
Oh, no, my rank went down by 47. Oh, no, right. How does the next three film play me?
Uh, how do I send a request to refling or do you guys send me a request?
I don't know how to send a request to play
Uh, I don't know how to play either
Okay, you send me. We've not played drew yet. Right. I'm being
I'm being green. Did I get to go first? Okay. Do you get to go first?
Yeah, we'll take that then he's stinky
Okay
Uh
Take that
Um, okay take that
This is terrible. Wait, what are you doing? I'm trying to look at what the reflin's doing right a block them there
Oh, this is awful. Oh, no, you guys can see my thought process. Oh, no, I lost
I can't put one in one here
So head out win put it here
Oh, no, you guys can see how dumb I am
Wait, what does that mean? Okay. I need to go up here then
Maybe like do this. No, I'm just gonna do that
I don't know
Oh
No, you're gonna ruin it for me
Both of us don't want to play in these ones. Well, I don't want to play because it's gonna get blocked
What are you doing? What happens if you go there? I don't know one two three one two three
Uh
I don't know how to do this
This is terrible. Can I put one here maybe? I'll put one there
Oh, no, they can like win again
Reflings, this is so hard. I don't think I can win. I can't put any here or I lose
Or here
So I'm basically just stacking them to the ceiling
until we can anymore
And then do
No, wait, whoa
No
You guys are cheating right one more new reflin
Come on new refling. This is so bronze connect four. No, right refling do it again
Okay, you
Surely I could win one
Uh right i'm gonna go in the middle
Surely surely I can win
Okay, I'll go above, you know
Um, okay. No, you're just mimicking me
Um
Oh
Yes
Are we just mimicking each other?
Oh
I'll put it here
I don't know why I'm putting it here
Wait, why did you wait could I have one there? No, I couldn't have
I'll put one here
Oh, this is hard I'm like touching my face. I'm getting sweaty. I don't think I can actually win against any of you guys
Oh
I could have had it one two three
maybe
Maybe if I stack here that can do like this up here
Uh
Is he gonna try and go up there
Did you let me win
I can't tell if you let me one
Did you let me win?
Wait, wait, you didn't mean that did you not see that?
Huh, I can't tell did you mean that hold on let me check up my orders here
Is are you at the restaurant?
I'd be at the restaurant. I didn't see that either. Oh a little distraction. I have not played. I've not played tiny cars
Let me be green
So pretty okay, okay, uh-huh. Oh, yeah, uh-huh. Take that. What are you gonna do about it?
Okay
Okay, so drivers at the restaurant. Okay. Okay, you're gonna do that better. Oh, I'm gonna preemptively strike
Using them cosmic rings
Flash your opponent to distract them. Okay, let me get the bikini toggle
Oh
Okay, we'll do this
And then uh-huh. Oh, yeah
Um, we should do like speed runs. We just have to slap them down. Okay
Uh-huh
Uh
Oh no
Wait, have I fucked up a little bit a little bit, but I'm allowed to mess up a little bit
And if I put it here, oh, no, you put it there. Wait, I'm putting it here then get rigged
Mmm
Oh my god reeflings, why are you so smart?
Reeflings, why are you so high I cute?
Oh
No
Oh my god, do you stress me so every so much we're playing I don't know what to do
Shawnee go in the third column. No, he's gonna win
If I go in the third column, he'll go there and he gets four in a row
None of us can play the third column because if he plays wait, why did you do that?
Why did you do that?
Did I distract you wait? Why did you do that? Did you mean that you win?
Are you right? I'm blind
Oh, I think you guys are just letting me win though. I'm gonna be honest
No matter where I went you would have won. Oh really?
Just yummy. I've not played you uncle green
Ah, what's this?
What do I do?
What
What is this
Oh
No, I don't know how to play checkers
Can I just mimic what he does just to annoy him? I don't know play this game
Wait, how did you do that? How did you get there?
Yeah, yeah, that's right reflin what you gonna do, but I'm gonna mimic you. Yeah, oh get right reflin
Uh
How did you do that? You went back up here
Right, I'll change my pattern. I won't cheat. I won't cheat. I'll change my pattern. I don't know what I'm doing though
I think I think we're just playing like crisscross applesauce one of the coolest games ever losing all the rank and honestly
Yeah, you actually played well intentionally or not wait actually
That's so good. Oh god, um, you know what I think about that stinky refling
Wait, I'll go here. Wait, that's not how it works. Uh
Yeah, just like the the the or I'll go here then. Oh no here. Sorry
Oh
More of them went green. I didn't even mean that
I don't know what this is. I'm having fun
Um
Uh, are we drawing pee pee? No, wait, is that my turn?
Did he do something here? Whoa. Whoa, that was juicy. Whatever that did
Uh, okay refling made a move. I want to make a move here
Oh
Shit, I'm losing at me. Oh, no, how did what I do here?
No, I can't here
You know, if I just click the board, oh, there we go. There we go. There we go. Something happened something changed
Taking mummy over element makes her here. I'm like so dumb. You're all gonna know I'm so dumb
It's not your turn. Okay
Sheissa
Sheissa, yeah
Oh, no, it's my turn. Can I go here? Can I go here? I'm gonna go here. Okay. Okay. I can go there. Let him get up
You have to sign which the pieces of rent the player. Oh, no, what did he do? I wasn't paying attention
Can I go here? No, can I go here? No. Oh, I can how did that work? I don't know how I did that
I'm warning you now refling. I'm taking this entire room. Fuck you. I'm taking this room
How does this work? I don't know
This is the most confusing game. Oh, it's my turn. I didn't even see what you changed
here
Oh, that was the terrible move
Here, okay, that was good move
Uh
I'm not sure
He made that right up there. What does that mean to me?
I don't know. I'll do some points. Can I do this? Can I do that? Can I do this? I can do that
I'm just I'm just clicking on the board. I'm gonna be honest
Uh, Stroney, can you hear your sick accent for a little bit? I'm dying to hear it
We are country. Oh
Oh, no
I'm one here. I'm one here. Okay. Thank you. I got here. Um
Uh, I see your turn
God this checkers game is hard
Oh, I think I messed up. I maybe shouldn't have played that. Oh, no
Um
I
Both of us have no, I don't even know if this refling knows what he's doing. He probably does
If you are this cute when playing
Uh, I'll have that love heart solo
Corners are power spots when playing I can agree on chess and during stream
I'm too dumb for connect four. Is it my turn yet? Oh, no, it's not. Okay. Now it's my turn. Yeah, get rigged
I see you're still winning son. Am I? Oh, no, you two back. Wait, how do I take it back?
Get no, give me back. Give me that. That's mine
It's stop you're taken. Oh, no, that didn't do anything
Oh, no, I think I'm losing. What is that? Oh, what?
Like this does that do something? I don't know what I'm doing
I think I may I think we have to admit defeat unfortunately
Oh, I'm getting rolled everything's getting taken
I don't have the strength reflends. I'm doing so bad
Oh
Connect your pieces
Oh corner someone says corner
Don't play the corner. Oh sugar that didn't do anything
Oh, no
Near okay green green. I'll see green
Uh, but that turned green a little bit green
I guess it's like splatoon where you want everything to be your colors. Oh, that didn't do anything. Oops. I think I just threw that
You lose the board is filled. Oh, no, it was so hard. That was confusing
Uh, maybe we only do the other one. Oh, Amy wants to play. Yeah, sure. Amy will play
Uh
Amy's turn. I have never played it before either. I'm dumb. Okay, we just go
Right, Amy. You're getting rolled. I'm going here, Amy
And you're you're not gonna have an a clue what's gonna hit you because I'm so good at this game
I have to be a I have to peel lower
Uh
Here
Um
Uh
Me so
Nando desuka
Oh, are you thinking reflin? I'm trying to get in your head or actually you're a pen pal because you're called imbebizo
What were you doing pen pal?
Are you trying to embarrass me? Oh, I saw you were about to get that. I saw that
Oh, what? How did you do that? I never even saw that. That was like my fastest freaking law as pen pals are ruling me
I never saw that at all. I was too busy focusing on my little right side play there
I'm not played against you yet. I'm going green. Uh your turn first
Uh, okay, I'm going here this time and then here
And that no, you're not supposed to do that. You're supposed to let me win
Um
I'm
I'm in chic
I'ma just do this
Uh, I think I've already lost sweetie. We go start to do it. I think I lost
No, you're not supposed to see my mlg pro moves
Um
I don't know what I'm doing. Oh, no. Oh, no
Oh, no
I lost I never saw that
Womp womp lots again. Wait, you didn't see that. Oh, no, you can win anyway like double time
Yeah, I was gonna say you already won you could have won down here
Wow, this is so hard
I don't know how people play this anymore. We fling I want to play
Uh, I'm not played you again
Oh wait, I missed out you can't do that here. Wait, I need to come over here. I'm sorry. I need to like come in the area. Sorry
Hold on try that again. Uh, I'm not played you yet
All right, maybe
Maybe
right
You win another player resigned. Wait, what?
Did you mean that? I don't think you meant that we fling. Uh, do you want to try again?
Okay, there we go rank. Yeah, let's go
The other player's busy
All right, let me be green you try again. Okay my turn I will go here
Sugar I'll go here
No, you smell stop it
Stop it you smell
Okay, I'll go here then
I
What are you doing? What are you planning? No, where are you planning? What does it mean?
I don't know how to this
No, you're not supposed to go there. This is hard
No, don't win. Don't be selfish. Let me win. Don't be selfish. Let me win
No, I have to put it down
No, I don't want to put it down
Stop it. You're teasing me. Stop it. No, wait. No
No, I want to win
I want to win. We're both playing the same freaking stuff. No
Come on. Why is this game so hard?
Why isn't so hard?
This is terrible right cool again. There has to be one reefling in here that's called lower IQ than me. Come on
Let's I've not played through yet
There has to be a reefling that has a lower IQ. What the heck is this?
What do I do?
Examine what?
No, I don't know what to do
You just I click it? Wait, it's not let me do anything
Huh, it's not let me do anything. Hello
Examine board game piece
Huh, you move you move and jump diagonally
Oh
Okay, okay, we hold it you hold it and then drop it wait
I'm getting pranked why why am I getting pranked? What what what happened?
Wait
No
What?
I think it's a bit laggy
Can I just start moving them everywhere? No, they're tired. I'm sorry
Okay, wait
I can't move them. No, so I move you
What the heck
Uh, then you block me so I block you
What
Hey
Uh
Can I go back?
A legal move bro. I don't even know the rule book. I don't want to get jailed
And what like this
No, I can't, can I? Maybe
I don't, wait what?
Like this, okay, that was a load. Why are some things loaded? No
Oh
Hold
In the name of the checkers board. Wait, I can't do that. Hold in the name of the check
Hold in the name of the checkers board. Hold in the name of the checkers board
What this is crazy
I'm sorry. My little brain can't do this. Maybe we just play the four in a room
You can only move one tail if you're jumping over an enemy as many times as you can. What happened? I wasn't paying attention. Oh, no
Something happened
You can only jump a tail so here
No, it's not your turn. Oh, sorry. What and then do that
What the heck
Am I accidentally winning right now?
I might be
It's plausible. Hold on. Can you go back? Oh, you can't go back. You can only go up. Okay. Wait, that didn't do anything
Can you be like gridlocked in this game?
Yes
Uh, sure go up there then. Wow. What am I doing? I can't go back
If you reach the end of the board you get knighted
Oh, neither. Oh, no, he won
I lost again
Reflames. Oh my god
Oh
No, he won I can't go back and we'll let me go back on him
Right, okay, what can I do? I can't even go forward or anything. I just did that
Game ends when all the pieces are taken. How can they be taken? We can't go backwards
I don't get it. I'm so confused. He's not won yet
What?
Wait, so if he comes here, I can only jump forward one
This is too hard
Oh, no, what happened? Something changed. I don't know
So I can't go backwards. I can only go forwards
Well, then I might as well push forward then
Surely surely that's how it works
Okay, and now then I take you
No, I can't take you you're too far away from me
Then I push you forward to play I guess
No, I don't one at a time. Sorry one move at a time. Apologies one step
Oh, this is so hard
Oh, no, my guy got taken. Wait, how do you so I can only go one way
Then that would push what that pushes him there and then I can't push up so I need to do that
Oh, no, that blocks him. Oh, I didn't mean to do that
Uh
What is a knight do I don't know
I'm not sure can he take everything now
Hmm
And then can go backwards
Oh, wait, so I just need to move him forward like here
Okay, I'll push him forward
Okay, I'll push him. Oh, he got taken right. Hold on. I'll push him forward then
Wait, am I gonna perish? I think I'm gonna perish. I don't think I can win
And then you move up. Oh, no, I didn't mean that
Yeah
And then I could I never push up
And then what what happened then
In the head. No, okay
Yeah, I was no I'm not winning that one. Okay, let's try again. Let's try again
That was yeah, that was
I wasn't sure about that one. I'm sure about that one. Uh, Renry slaying. I don't think I've played with you yet
Okay, surely I can win. Oh, it's not my turn yet. Oops
Oops gotta be there. Okay you
You are getting
Can't handle it
Uh
Block you from doing it there
I'll take you
Oh, no, this refling's thinking you're not supposed to think against me
Monka, what's this refling thinking? I don't know. He's taking his time
I'm getting nervous. I'm getting nervous what he's planning
I don't know what he's doing. I can't see it if he's doing something
I don't see it
Here, I don't know what reason's planning
Well, I'll take that then you're not getting a four in the rule on me
I don't know if I do this. No
I block you
No
No, you weren't supposed to see yeah, you're supposed to be like
La-dee-da-dee-da strong. He's too dumb to figure this out
Uh
Okay
So now what you're gonna put it there
No, he's gonna put there. Wait, hold on. What would that achieve one two three three three
So if I put it there, he has to go there so yeah
Will she finally get the dub? I have no idea
There has to be a refling that's lower IQ than me. Wait, you block me
Oh sugar, I wasn't supposed to do that. Oopsies. I foiled my own plan
Literally, you don't even need to like counteract me. I counteract myself
Like a dumb dumb
You already beat me strong in my IQ is too low
This is hard
You're kicked is so bad. Wait, we'll have one two
Four you can't
So never
No
I'm so confused
Um
Are we both playing the same game right now?
We're both scared to play here because I win if he plays here
Oh, no
Oh
Bro, why is this game so freaking hard to win?
Honestly one he is all um. No, I've already played you all of us
Literally, how are you all smarter than me? This doesn't make any sense
How are you so freaking smart?
Bro, how is this game so hard?
Oh
You could have won just placed in the middle. No, he was gonna block me
Surely I can win one surely freaking temples. I can win one one faking
round
Of this. This is so hard. It's cuz we're
It's cuz we're men
Riefland you can't see that part of load. That's supposed to be the quiet part
Be honest, I was barely screaming by my brain's bright, bro. I'm like fainting this so
Like I'm gonna get ranked ranked
No
Are you squidding me right now?
Hello miss cuttles. How is your Friday night? It's going good, but I'm getting freaking rigged. I'm getting ruined
I was gonna do something here. Wait
Ah
Did you did you let me win?
Did I win
Did I win when I win I win out. Yeah
Okay, hold on. I want to do that again see when I win I get serotonin when I don't win I get
Ah
Who we got tiny cuttles? I played you. I haven't played you yet
Whoa, my tickle is here. Hold on
Give me one minute. I need to go answer the door
My bets that game leaves about to come flying
Oh
We ready are we ready for Friday?
Okay, I'm gonna be eating and doing this at the same time. So you must forgive me if I'm extra dumb
Thank you the ton of two for the two. I'm currently getting wrecked at runescape
And it's not looking good. How do I counteract this? I need to go here
Ah
And then I need to stop you from making a four over here
This is such a big
I got a chicken wrap
with
Sugar, why are you so tall?
I feel like I'm gonna lose this one. Well, you think I can't do it
Oh my god, I'm eating chips and it's so good
All right, so yummy
I
Chicken wrap with sugar
Wait, is that a thing? No, it's just a chicken burrito wrap
Oh, no, this is a lot of red. I don't like it. I see red. I see red. I see red
Uh here
I don't know what
Hmm
I'm too busy munching. It's not delicious
I said sugar. Oh, I said oh sugar. I say oh sugar instead of
Um, I'll stop you right there criminal scum
Hmm
I'm not gonna mess this up. No, you're gonna play there. What? How do you not play there?
No, you you smell my freaking connection. I didn't really do it on place it there
Ah, I wasn't even paying attention. No, come on man
Come on. I'm getting rolled. Are you squid me or else who dare please me? Please share
Oh, you guys not Ian. Thank you for the tip boy. You guys not Ian you want to go, uh
Hey, rest in peace. I'm not pleased you
Hmm
You win. Oh, you didn't mean that
Sniffer sniffer
Everyone's are gonna start and we're getting so distracted trying to win
Why didn't it work?
Okay, there we go
Uh here. Oh no, I'm blue
Abba di abba die. I'm blue
I would be off a guy
Now listen up. Here's the story about a little car. Oh fish in the deep blue sea
Everything was blue and this is the minimum. Yeah, nobody to listen
Um
Blue I would be double guys
Wow
Oh, it's cool on my hands that guy literally me. I'm blue if I was green I would
Hold on get my burrito at my wee box
Ah, yeah, um, I can't do that
I need to do that. I don't know
Oh, no, you're supposed to do that. I'm gonna hear them. You're wet far
No, you're not supposed to win against me
Okay, I'm opening up my burrito my burrito with no cilantro
Oh
He's doing that he's gunning for that
I can tell reflin. I can see right through your thought process right now. No, I was gonna put there
Wait, why can I not put here? I don't know. He puts here. I put there
He no I put there. He puts there
I win
But why would he do that? One two one two three he won
You could have had it spare um
You
Oh wait, oh no
Oh, no, I just I remembered like literally as I put that down
Oh my god
Bro, I literally just threw that game. I could have won that
Bro
I could have won it
Grimble law I will conquer the world reality connect for hard love you strongy
Oh
It is too hard. It's so freaking hard to win. Grimble. Thank you for the tip
Literally hypnosis is the only reason I can get away with it. Have I played with D reflame?
I don't think so
You go again. Boom. Oh, it's not know my turn
I will deserve loss. Okay. Look I have room temperature IQ. I'm trying my best
Um, right. No, don't do that
But I think you played them all at least once now. Yeah
go away
Our darling low IQ feature, but honestly more like our dangerously low IQ feature
I love
You want chicken is the mvp. I'm not even playing. Oh, no, that is a good one two three four
What if I go here then
I don't know what happened if I do
I freaking love chicken so it's like the best meat source ever
A girl's when girls are curious when they're almost reeflings. Uh, oh wait, is that matter? Oh sugar. Um, um, what did you do?
What did you do? Thank you for the game strong. Oh, you're welcome. You don't have to take me for that
I have no idea what you did though. Oh wait, or this reason
What did you do? Was it something here? I think I'm having something here
Um
Papago
Uh, right, what happens if I go here? I don't know. Maybe I need to go down here
Um
Here maybe
I don't know
If I go here they'll lose I hope no
One two three
So hard I don't even see it
I literally can't even see it. I like at all
This is so hard. Is there any reeflings that haven't gone against?
I have a lot of guys everyone here
That's so hard right have I gone against everyone here? I may have you know that
um
Are you a beautiful all fans all fans?
Uh, maybe they're just confused why there's so many people here
Does anyone want to go again? Because I can play while I eat
But beyond range I think we're on room two. I think everyone's having a fair share
Um
Look at all you guys have like numbers and stuff now because you'd be beating me
Hold on
Um
I don't even know my phone. I'll pass. I've been meant to do it in that one
Hmm
Yeah, yeah, that's the best corner in location. I'll pay out
You should both
The same thing is you actually could have won three times if you went play some tales random like
I'm trying to think ahead of my moves. Okay, it's hard
Oh my god, this is delicious
Reeflings do you want me to baby bird you because I'll do it
Yep
Uh, don't like the look of that. I'm getting nervous. I'm getting shaky
Oh, no
Why do I not see it? Why do I not see it coming?
Why do I not see it coming? I'm being so for real right now, right at the next one. I am not losing
I don't care what happens. I am not losing
I am tryharding so much
I am not losing this one. I'm so serious
Are we bimbo max I literally don't see it right you've placed it in the middle. That's fine
Is it I don't know we'll place it next to you then
That's fine, so I'll counter you from doing four in a row on the bottom and then I'll do this
All right
One two three so you can't go anywhere there but I can progress by going here
And that's fine you're allowed to do that
Right
Did I do it?
Uh, oh wait
What I thought I won there
Wait
Wait, why why did I not win there?
Like this did I counter them by going that way?
I will redeem myself. Oh no, right one two three four so drop it here
I'm tryharding I'm looking
All right, if you're there what one two three four fuck you
One two three four
What you try to do one two three here so I can't put it in this column
Um
Right you've put it up there, which is fine
Oh fuck you you blocked me
Uh
Right
So what happens now?
What did that do? No you're getting blocked. I don't know what you're doing, but don't do it
I don't know what you're doing there, but don't do it
What are you doing over here now?
That's fine
Whoa
Get rekt get rekt get absolutely rekt. Oh my god. I did it. I was like trying so hard
I was trying to see what you were trying to do. I was playing two characters at once on the board. Oh, we did it
I have lower connect for IQ
Okay, let's try again. All right, hold on. Let me take a bite of my food. Oh my god. I had to try so hard for that
Okay
Oh my god, that was so hard
I don't know how people play logic games all the time. I feel like my brain just gets so tired. I'm like, oh
I
Oh, shit. Oh, this is not looking good
Am I gonna throw I don't know what what you're trying to do
What are you trying to do
Don't feel bad. My brain is still at max capacity. Oh, no, what did you do? I wasn't paying attention, right? You get blocked
Oh
It's so hard
Bro, when you go back to cooking swordfish, this is so hard. How?
I never see it. I like physically can't see it coming
until I hear the
Bro girlfriend is pouty and frustrated and upset. She got destroyed and fucking
Not even just destroyed in runescape destroyed in runescapes like side player gate. Oh god. I'm sorry
Wait, how did I double down there? I didn't even need to find I'm tripling down
Oh
So I'm choking on my burrito in anger
Because I'm so bad at this game
No, you're gonna win
No
Look at freaking low my scores. Let's start on the third. Oh my god. You're so good to win. What are you doing?
One two three
I don't know what I'm doing either to be honest
Ah, what are you doing?
Stop
You're stressing me out. This reefland's gonna win. They're like genuinely stressing me out right get blocked
No, oh my god, I hate right we're going. No, I'm sorry. We're going back to edgeville. I'm actually fucking done
I'm actually I'm done. We're going back to edgeville. I'm not even I'm not even doing we're going back to edgeville
I'm so done. I'm so done
I'm going back to edgeville to cook freaking swordfish. This is so hard
This is so hard. I should surprise the exam get to fuck. I've got the lowest IQ in the uh
freaking lower than room temperature water. Oh my god
Why is that game so hard?
freaking the uh
To no one's surprise
The 1v1 chess stream has been delayed due to the fact that I'm probably gonna have to actually watch some chess tutorials
Because I don't know how the rules work
If she she starts speaking if you start speaking germy should really stop playing
I respect your dedication not to apply mind bullets to them to gain victory
To gain a victory is that what I should have done? I should just start like taking the bikini off and all that like bro
I was so hard for no reason
Take the random event. Oh, is it good? Sorry
Hello, uh, yeah, sure. I fancy an exam right. What's my oh, what is this?
Ah, she's got a fish. You've been slacking in your studies. It's time for an exam
They are thank you for the tip boy. They literally are though
There are two types of questions one requires you to find the next object in a pattern
And the second I will present you with 15 cards and a hint
That's so specific. What are we doing? What comes next shoes shoes shoes shoes?
That's correct. Next question pick the object that should come next to a pattern
A banana a dookie a pineapple
a slice of watermelon
Finally a pupil that uses her brains. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, sure sure
Uh, these are gardening tools. So we need a rate
To the exit. Okay. We did it. We did it. Please don't fail. Imagine if I did this
Oh my god, did you hear that the burrito just kissed me from the way I bit it? What's the book of knowledge to do?
Oh fishing
It took him
Wait, oh that wasn't to him. Oh my god
Oh
My god
Just when you think I couldn't get dumber
I just put
XP into fire making instead of cooking. Bruv
Can this get any worse?
I don't think it's any more obvious how low my IQ is holy crap. It's even a miracle. I can breathe and eat at the same time
um
Oh my god
Reeflings about to get jealous over a burrito for real for real. Did you not hear did it come up in the make it literally went
When I like bit into the burrito
It's fine. You're a fish. You are the goofiest of goober's. We love you immensely the fire making will warm up your IQ
Small brain after all that was that was so hard. I don't know how to play that. Ah jealous of a piece of
I'm just starting out here looking like process and brav
I was terrible
I literally rage quit. I'm like, no, I need to walk away. Thank you very much reefling for making the fire or
Any arsonists?
Absolutely. All right, let me keep eating this burrito before it gets cold
Oh are you squidding me right now?
Hmm
Strongly we're hungry. Can you get back in the kitchen? I mean level in cooking. Love you. You goofed
Thank you. I don't know man
Love you too little reefling. Yes, I will feed you well and good
That was thank you for the tip. Oh my god, my hand's covered in sauce
See I'm not afraid to like sauce off after reefing as I choke on a piece of corn
I can't talk and freaking
Uh eat at the same time
Oh my god
That was so hard for no reason. I've never played connect for like that at a very long time
Bruh, I suck at anything logic based
Oh my god
Is there connect for championships
Could you imagine? You know how you get a rank in chess?
Could you imagine? It was fun content though. Streamer gets absolutely destroyed by uh
Viewers live on stream rage quiz
Mm-hmm
Oh
Wow
Almost finishes for real. My hand is covered. I don't think I have a napkin
Reeflings you want to come lick my fingers and call me kfc?
Because I'm finger-licking good. Oh, hold on because I'm finger-licking good
Thank you
I
Had to lean over with my other hand to do that. Mm-hmm. It's like a call offering
I want kfc not imagine it almost
Cuttlefish pounded from four angles. Yeah, that could be the title of the stream because I played that freaking
Connect four more like connect my shite
I
Will finish the
We'll finish em and we'll finish the swordfish
and
Sniff it's 20 minute warning for mercy
Um, Azura, I think is still going to be live on stream because straight's a six hour game
Ah
If you're gonna do much you should do questionable ones like this is that questionable
Oh, maybe if you're like under the table, then yeah
Yes, Azura is still live. Okay, that's good. Mm. I'm eating
Architect bro's winning
Hmm
Hmm and do you do you want to know the calorie count of my meal architect bro's? Mm
Just the thought of my stomach expanding with all that food and sticking out going from a flat stomach to all big and
engorged. Mm architect
I'm sorry
I don't know why I'm just talking about that. No architect bro's
I hate it. No, I'm teasing you. I'm teasing your pickles
I do not judge
Don't be sorry. We enjoy it. Okay. I've to get a hydration. Hey, I'll say hydration isn't that's not cool of it
Wow
Wow big burp
Maybe big burp. Okay. We burp. We burp not much force not much first row dad behind that burp. Okay
Oh
Yeah, we're now munching on the leftover chips because I finished my burrito some of this the like filling of the burrito spelled out
So I'm like I'm using my chip as a vessel to spoon it into my mouth
And not the in-game rating of my burp
Mm-hmm strongy feeds everyone equally. That's why she's queen for it. Hey
Your interests are my fascination your curiosities are my challenge chicken or beef
Chicken
I struggle to eat a lot of red meat and then I wonder why I'm so ill
And it's literally got all the iron in it that I need
Um, I'm also a chicken boy. I'm a chicken boy
Do you know some Gomez person? No, sorry
Am I supposed to
I love vision. I think I've ever had vision before
I'm heading to sleep at 6 a.m. Oh my goodness. Please rest well as that 6 a.m. America must be
Because it's like midnight in the u.k. Roughly
Are you good oops who goes there and identify yourself
No, it's only 8 p.m. On the west coast. Oh
Sorry, I can't stop burping good night you
Thank you for absolutely reckoning decking me on connect for
I live in turkey. Oh, okay
It's 6 a.m
It's 11 p.m. For me and I'm midwest. Yee-haw. Nah 4 m in the u.k. Wonka
Sorry, I'm still really enjoying my food so I apologize for not talking too much. I'm trying to eat as fast as I can
I'm doing that I should click on the booth
Let's go to the booth
Am I dumb but can I ask what munker means munker
And munker s is a twitch emote where peppy looks really stressed out and he's like oh like like nervous
And and I reduce it to munker like munker
and
But if you type in munker s on google, it'll just show you what peppy looks like he's all stressed out
Hmm
Almost 4 a.m. And I'm so is it please go to sleep. Oh my god
Please don't worry about going to sleep like seriously. I don't want you guys like risking your health to watch me stream
Like I'm literally stuffing my face. I just got wrecked and connect for and I'm going straight back to cooking
Like you ain't missing out on too much. I'll show you
um
Time for a hypnotic slumber
Hmm
Sleep is for the weakest weekend now sleep equals exp wasted
Oh my god, we're like really close to level or not next batch. I don't know what level 40 f 74
Yeah
I hate arching on mobile
hmm
See we've got like a billion different things to click to do anything
Oh
76 oh my god, how much did wine boosters?
I thought we were selling like 72
Wine is faster, but I want to use all the fish that the reeflings gave me
Because I don't want it to go away
I don't want it to be like rotting in my in my bank
Former level and you can cook sharks. Oh
Hmm I have a good night. Please rest well
Uh wine got me 72 to 65 in like under an hour. Oops
Um only power
Only power to bring me back to this gone forsaken game is like cute fish
It's a good game, but
If you've got stuff to do, it's not the easiest game to like keep up the excitement
I think runescape I would say is probably similar to like people say like when you start up a minecraft server, um
Pardon me and you play for like a week and then you all get burnt out and never go on it again type thing
Wine got you from 69 to semi-fee feels good, man
Cooking endangered species when no
Not cooking endangered species. There's plenty to go around in the runescape economy
More than enough actually
In fact, the waters are so infested with shark. They're everywhere
Thank you boy boy
Can I say thank you anonymous for their other tips?
Love you. You're good for love you too. Love reefling or love you too. Yeah anonymous
I don't know if I'm supposed to guess I was supposed to call you anonymous or everything
I
Rainbow fish
Okay, I've almost finished eating. I'm so sorry if it feels like I've been chewing for ages. I was too busy getting
That's how many times have I done that now?
No, stop eating. What are you doing?
Jesus Louise woman
Okay, we've almost finished the
The fishy
Oh my god, sorry, I kind of think I'm just too busy eating
I'm almost finished eating. I promise I'll finish eating soon. I just take so long to eat
Walks into an eight hour stream. Thank goodness. I'm not late. I'm gonna
Okay
For the architect bros, this one's for you
I order two meals because I have the second meal the next day. So tomorrow I'll be eating my next meal
So I'm gonna go put it in the fridge
In the and wash my hands because they're covered in grease. They're covered
She knows about
So when Azura got released, I read up a little bit and people were like, oh my god architect chocolate and I'm like wait
I thought you were
I was like reading. I'm like, okay, right. I get it now. Why architect is such a random word for it though
I still don't get the origin but hey, oh wait, I'm gonna very quickly wash my hands because they're covered in freaking
Grease from the burrito that was absolutely inhaling and getting rolled on I'll be literally a millisecond
So
I've just stood up and I'm aware of how full my bladder is I'm I'm gonna go pee
I
Have
I've just sat down and I need to die mute
I'm gonna do
I'm gonna do I'm gonna sneeze actually
Okay
What are we
You're done
Am I getting sick I better not be
I am not getting sick when I've not even done a month full of streaming yet
I do not tell tolerate any sickness
I've not even done it a full month. Yep. I'm getting sick
The taskmasker for me
No, not for me
For any
Maybe better streaming hours would help you
What you mean don't do 12 hours naturally
What are you talking about refling? Don't say such nonsense
Are you trying to upset me refling? Huh?
You're trying to make me feel it's because you left us. Okay. I won't feel sick anymore
I
You're laughing but I have separation anxiety with you guys
It's been getting better, but I feel an immense amount of anxiety
um
at the
Before I click go live
And then it goes away when I am live
I'm not sure what that means. I mean I had it
last time wink wink, um
And then it subsided and it was back again
So I don't know if the plan is it's gonna subside off my body sooner. We love you too
Hey, scrawny, when are the elden ring streams when the dlc releases?
You've been playing for a while consider taking a break. Do you insult me jaggex?
Do you think me some prepubescent child that can't handle a little gaming session?
Jaggex please do not dare interrupt my flow
Do you ever get anxiety when it comes to ending streams?
I get nervous about ending the stream because of what I'm gonna see
And I know that seems silly because it's like well you say the same every time like I say like I'll see you tomorrow
Like I love you reflings a few kisses on that
But I get worried about it and I don't know why I think it's because I am saying goodbye
And it's like I won't see you until the next time I'm up, you know
and
Too much of a grimoire you somehow groomed yourself
Hey, here at viola, you don't groom us. What are you grooming?
What I'm what a slogan to have for
Every time I do that what slogan to have for a visa reasons
I can't believe I said that out loud with my full check
Ain't that true though
Yeah
Oh when I was lurking someone mentioned that they didn't realize we both have a nicotine patch on us because we're addicted to each other
It's not for the briefings are addicted to each other. No
Refling and strongy are addicted to each other
I can always ramble and procrastinate ending streaming call those for so awkward doing so. Mmm
Well, like when we reached the 10 hour board mark on that other stream
I can't even remember what it was the entire ending got caught
But I was like trying to say so much all at once just because like I wanted to you know
and
I wasn't expected to be groomed. I'm glad you did all that sounds terrible when you write that out in a sentence
I'm going to be honest. It makes me sound like a like a Chris Hansen. Take a seat moment
Yeah
Kind of true though. Hey
I think pre-stream anxiety is normal. You're talking to an auditorium worth of people
I actually don't get nervous to stream in that sense. Um, it doesn't
I don't look at the numbers like I don't I don't actually know. Um
It's not like on display for me. It's just me and reeflings playing multiplayer game. Um
And that's it like that's what it is. It's not like I'm nervous because I'm gonna have to go perform
I don't have any kind of imposter syndrome. I don't have any kind of like I'm not good enough
Um, I just like straight up have separation anxiety
Um
And that's it pretty much. Um
Like I don't get nervous to stream. I don't get like, oh my god. What happens if they don't like it? No, um
I'm just like
Just getting out of it. I'm like, oh god. I don't feel well. Like I feel sick. Like my stomach feels ill sometimes
But like like I've started up streams and I've said to you like oh guys
It's not gonna be like a long stream today and then it ends up turning into like six hours type thing
Um, when I only had the intention of two because I wasn't feeling well
But as soon as I start streaming it's like I get a second burst of wind
Like I'm super energetic. I'm super engaged and like I'm having like so much fun
I'm enjoying myself like right now. We're looking at pixels over and over again putting
Pardon me for being so rude. It was not me. It was my food
And like I'm having so much fun. Like look at all the reeflings that are in the bank with me right now
like all of us goofing off and like uh
Mac
Macer or maker mac maker
Thank you for coming to memba
um
It's just like
It's like me with so shiny. I don't want to go out but when I'm out it's fun
Yeah, it's kind of like getting over the hump if you will and
And like
I especially
Enjoy my endurance streams. Like I kind of spoke on it the other day. Um
Um
One time I was having a really bad time and reeflings were just hanging out with me and this isn't now
This isn't now. This is like way in the past. Um
And we played a song and it's called mr. Kitty. Um
I actually like a really depressive song or kind of slow tempo song
And I heard it and I was listening to and it made me feel a certain way
It made me feel quite negative. Like it was quite a depressive song mr. Kitty after dark. Yes, that was the song
And I listened to and I typed and I said is this what you guys feel like all the time
Because of the way the song had like resonated with me
It felt as rough as I had felt in that moment because I was feeling rough because you know stuff was going on behind me. Um
And it kind of like made me realize like
Like
If me hanging out having a carry on rambling
Coming up with all these like silly little ASMR ideas and like all these collab ideas and elaborate stuff and all of that
And like it makes you not feel like that when I stream like how blessed and how lucky
like we're on this timeline like
You know, you can feel
I don't like accepted to just like do your own thing
Like I always say the phrase you can be at arm's length. You can be attached at the hip. You can be on my head type thing
It's completely up to you V Flynn. Um
But I do remember that night because I was like you guys feel like that like when
Just in general like you have like such a rough time and then you come
On stream and like you come and you you make me laugh. You make me giggle. We tell terrible puns while going
like
And we're just hanging out type thing
You know it was like even when like you feel so rough
You're so willing to like come to me be so accepting of me like say such nice things to me and encourage me to do stuff
Um and all of that and it's just like it's such like a nice way like hopefully
I hope it's like a positive feedback loop where you make me giggle
I make you giggle and like we just have a fun time for what it's worth. Um
Sometimes you need a song like that to marinate in your thought
Yeah, like I don't listen to what I consider like sad music in the dumps music or emotional music
Like I listen to atarashi gako. Um, and like tokyo calling
Tokyo calling. Um, like I listen to hatsu and miki
I don't even know what's happening half the time when I listen to hatsu and miki
But like the music's so upbeat it's so up-pop like I never listen to anything depressive like I like goofy
Um, like literally I'm listening to a dutch song. I have no idea what's being said other than the lyrics suck my
um
type thing, you know
What was I saying?
Thanks for the stream strutting. I'm off to watch mercy. Yes. Um any snippets mercy modiste is live and she
Is playing with my willy. Uh, she's not. Um, maybe in another life
Um
Thank god no each one. Uh, right hold on. Let me check hatsu miki has become a legendary figure
Of making a homework right. Hold on. What is mercy playing?
Is zura still alive? Azura is still alive. She's playing stream live
Uh, mercy modiste. Uh, mercy is playing harvester
Part two. I already knew that because I said that earlier and yet I forgot
See you brain
Uh
I got a comment on the new the asmr video
And someone's like why is this being recommended to me?
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, you can't resist the asmr
The most I felt like that after dark was when that
Um
When you go in member to a members world, I don't know if we need to do a members world this stream
It may be next stream. We're doing members world unfortunately
although
Wine isn't members is it?
No, maybe not. I don't know if we're just doing members all the way to the end
It if we're doing wines all the way to the end people say wines is faster
I literally get algorithmed. Honestly. What did you miss? I stuffed my face and then
Let uh
Let the architect bros know I've got them in the back of my mind
Um, yeah, hold on. Hold on
The begging ASMR is peak ASMR. Honestly. Wait, what does it say now?
It's still going. Oh my god. Is that 23,000 views?
That doesn't make sense
Architect bros eating good just like strongy. Honestly. What does it mean architect architect is a
terminology used for people who enjoy
bigger body types or eating type of content
Or gaining weight type of content, but there's different levels to it
Um, so Azura delays body type because she's not like the default skinny malinky
I keep opening this freaking collection box. Um, VTuber, so
She would get referred to as someone for the architect
Bros
Look at all the swordfish. They're so purple
Why are you so purple?
A
Specifically vtubers, I think
She shuffled herself and then
Yes, uh, again Azura duly is live with a stream
Hopefully her pc doesn't explode. Um, and merci mondice is playing harvester part two
Which she never told me there was a part two because I'm getting a highlight reel of part one
Which isn't going to make any sense if I don't get highlight reel apart
I love strongy. I love reeflings. What are you going to do about it? Huh? You're going to kiss me on my lips
You know, let me hold your hand
Actually, I have something to ask
The reeflings are
You guys are like small enough to fit in the palm of my hand. Basically
Do you guys like that you're smaller than me?
Or would you like
A mascot that's like bigger. Oh my god. Why am I struggling so hard with this bank system?
Um, like you're so nice and tame. Yeah smaller than you is better
What is my size? Um, I don't even think I have a reference artwork. I can use that isn't toss breaking
Small is nice
Yes, you're if you didn't know secret hidden lore for the reeflings your tentacles can grow as long as you like
So you can interact with things as much as you need
Um, you have very very long tentacles if you so desire, but they're just nice and cute and stacked together
Whilst you are in oh my god the crisscross salmon the salmon are going upstream look they're going upstream
We are growers not sure it's exactly hmm almost like a previous lore strange
It small means when you cuddle as we feel you every yeah, I can put you in my mouth in my tummy
Yeah
Uh, we can go explore strony in the first sense. Hmm should I blindfold reeflings but let your tentacles do what they want?
Bank boost I'm not going to mess it up this time
Wow
Oh, wow, how do I do the fire? Huh? Okay, there we go
Strony subtly mentioned war. I don't mind it. No, I clearly I like giant ass like war
um
What else I like
Um
Try to think of other things that are considered like not regular
Hmm spelunking me no
Oh
I can't escape that word
It's like mongolian throat singing. It's everywhere. It's everywhere. Can't escape it
No spelunking
What does it even mean?
You cannae tell me it's not related to the bedroom spelunking. I can't wait to go spelunking with the reeflings
Oh, I can't wait until we go into a tight dark
damp
Cave and spelunk together like bro. Whoever named spelunking spelunking you knew exactly what you did
I mean cave exploring. Yeah
I literally
You've ever heard such a more ridiculous word. How dare they make such a word
Oh my god, you're still doing absolutely
Wakey wakey sleepyhead
Goodnight Strony send luck to my country tomorrow. I have no idea what your country's doing tomorrow, but please don't perish if it's bad
Good luck to your country
And rest well for anyone who do need to sleep. Please don't worry. We are literally just
going for another three hours and then
Uh
We'll redirect into a streamer. I don't know who I don't even know who's not online normally at this time
Uh, but we will find a vtuber that is live that we can redirect into
The euro cup fitba is on the new all right. Okay, right. Good luck. Uh, I am down for some spelunking right now
Uh, plunging is another fun one plunging. Please don't plunge me. That's not abysmal
Hmm
Spelunking in the cave of a giant ass
I don't know how to have far to go with the giant ass and the zero
I might not make her do the weird side of things. I may do the weird side of things
But yeah
No, no plunging not even a little
You can plug me up. Whoa. Wait, hold on. I was like so direct. My brain was like, oh
This'll this is fine. This is clearly beating around the bush. Nope. No, it's not. It's absolutely not. I just straight upset what
what I uh
Sorry, you know, actually I can tell you something that was really terrible
So if all the development issues hadn't occurred, I actually
fully
was going to
Are you squinting me?
Uh, hold on. I don't know what you think. Giant ass for content one day totally
Ah
I'm freaking happy to make it anonymous. It doesn't bother me. Like I like it. I don't mind at all. Um
I don't like the you die ones. I don't like that
I like the ones where you just kind of appear on the other end all fine and good
And maybe a bit moody because you accidentally got swallowed or something like that
um
She's letting the intrusive thoughts went honestly though
This is terrible. So if all the development issues didn't happen all the girls were posting like all these audios on twitter and I was like
Uh, I should probably do one as well. But like after debut and I thought wouldn't it not be really
terrible if
I may or may not have been
PLug
Uh during like debut and after and then once the stream ended I would go record
and like do something with it and then finish and then post it and you know
So that was my idea. But obviously that all crumbled apart. Thanks to development issues. Um
But yeah, I thought it would be pretty cute
But
That would have been amazing. Unfortunately. It's not possible. It's not possible
And there was so many developmental issues in time and I could absolutely strangle some people
But that's just what happens like literally
Um, oh, sorry. There was a refling that messaged me that apologized for
criticizing the company for saying like, oh, it'd be better if
The girls could make their designs. Please don't feel bad. I absolutely completely get where you come from. Um,
just for
How do I keep doing that?
I give up. Um
Please don't feel bad about saying that like you said it in a nice way. We had some negative criticism that was like
Oh pre-made model. Actually one of the most bizarre criticisms we got
um was
What was it? It was like, oh, they don't even have talents ready
When we opened up auditions and it was like, yeah, you're fucking Egypt
We didn't have talents. So we're opening auditions like every other Vtuber agency
But when we do it, it's bad
But when everyone else does it, it's fine and that was like, what?
It was the most bizarre thing I had ever read honestly
um
We have plenty of time for a future fun. Well, literally opened up auditions and someone was like, what if she'd be 2.0 look like this?
I mean, she's getting an update to our model. I don't know how much she's said
I'm not gonna say anything if she doesn't say anything. I'm not gonna say anything
Thank you for the tip as well anonymous. Sorry. I almost forget to thank you
Um, I won't say anything until she be says something but
Yeah
Outfit she said outfit
Right, I'll I'll leave it at that if she's not directly said what it is. I'm not gonna say
She said outfit
Uh, we don't have workers because we're not open yet many baffled honestly
It was bizarre like I remember reading it actually there's a reflin
It must have been a reflin
It must have been a reflin because you made me he haul my arse off
And I can remember the quote because I used to quote it because someone defended the agency
They must I think they're a reflin or possibly just someone who's enthusiastic about the girls in general
So someone criticized the company because they were like
Oh
Another agency where you have to give up your model to work with them and get their their pre-made models or whatever
And then someone commented and replied to them and there was like
No one wants your ugly as sin model like that was to the quote your ugly as sin model
Oh
I wish I could have interacted with it because it made me he
Ha so badly is that no one wants your ugly as sin model
Oh, my god
I
Literally was like getting so close to printing that out and putting it on my fridge because it was just so hilarious to me
Like it was so hilarious
um
Like I just oh my god
It vin miss vin san vin san vin sin vin sin
Vincent thank you for becoming a member that took me so long to figure out. I'm so sorry
No, not sin sister
It was just the terminology the guy used because someone was like
Oh, I don't want to give up my model type thing and I don't want this. I don't want that like basically complaining about the agency
And it was like rub one you've not even applied to you're not interested
So three shut the fuck up and then some reflin or just someone who was a good fan come swooping in
And replies what I was basically thinking no one wants your ugliest sin model and I'm like
It's so good
It's so funny. Anyway, so you made my day whoever whoever like came swooping under to defend the agency you have made my day
um
Hellscape. Thank you for becoming a member. I appreciate it the membership stream start next week. Uh, you've got plenty
Uh, it's a bit warm not gonna lie a bit hot in here. Yeah, but it's a bit sweaty out here
Surprise the bank hasn't caught on fire. Honestly
um
Forgive her. She's tired and forgot how to read. Oh, no, what did I miss me?
Oh, what are you yapping about strongy? She be cooking
So I think she be has allured to something which I'm more than happy for her to
Um, but I don't think she's fully said what it is and I don't want to ruin it because it's quite a nice thing
I think it's quite a nice thing and it's like the most basic common courtesy thing. Um
Allured she be alert to it
There were some abysmally
stupid takes on a flume
It's just the way the guy typed the message
I just constantly remember the phrase ugly as sin model. I was like, oh my god
Talk about like catching screwy like oh my god. I don't think I could recover if someone was like your ugliest sin model
Oh my god, love it. Love it. Love it. Love it
Then mummy you have broken youtube. We are going for 6.1 subs. Oh my god
The video was the video honestly that funny
I'm like, I'm second guessing myself. I'm like, what's the video truly that entertaining
Like I was just kind of seen please a lot by the end of it and started like breathing in the mic really weird
I only know one agency that lets their talents pick their models literally
I've only heard one other agency do it as well
um
But I'm quite happy for the girls like to design their 2.0 like emmy designed her 2.0 like I'm more than happy
If she wants that makes her happier and all that then juice. What am I gonna fucking say about it? Nothing
Oh guys as long as the girls are happy. They're happy. Um
I made mommy ink herself
Has my whole life been a mistake. Is this peak content for you from?
Uh, also the amount of people that could not read. Oh, I felt so bad
Actually, we had one japanese girl
Um apply and I felt so bad
Because she had such a lovely voice
But she could hardly speak any english and I was like, it's not gonna work. It's such a shame
She had worked for a previous agency
um
And I think google translate was helping her through the page and she inquired on the website and I felt so bad being like
Bro, you can't speak english. I can't have you there was actually a russian
Person that reached out as well. She was like, I know you I know your agency's english
But can I stream in russian and have a russian audience and I'm like
Ah, yes, let us the english vtuber agency come out with talents that where I can't even like moderate what you're doing or saying like
what
Some folk had like don't get me wrong. We're lenient, but
We do have to say like that's not even possible
Like what you're asking for isn't even possible
um
It was a shame. I loved emi's 2.0 design. I'm glad. I'm glad. I think she had a lot of fun design in her 2.0
so, yeah
How good was good as application? What?
Good is still a thingy. Oh, you want to trade with me? Hold on. Let me put my swordfish away. I'll trade with you. What's up?
What's up low leaflin?
Uh, maybe oh, it's so what is this?
Are these doughnuts to put around your
disc of returning disc of returning yellow boots yellow gloves. What?
Huh?
What have you given me? What does it look like?
activity
You can only enter
Thor dors black hole from the dwarven mains
Are you sitting literally? I thought this is a weebie ring as well. Are you giving me your weebie ring?
Am I putting shoes on?
Okay, I got shoes on
I got gloves on
Oh, now I look like I really work. I think it's a helpful tool that'll come in handy later. That's so ominous
This is a helpful tool that'll help you later. What do you mean?
That's so ominous. What am I supposed to do about that?
I
Get you miss 100% of the shots, but some people
Just don't get it. It was a shame like I felt really bad for the Japanese girl
She was nothing but polite well mannered
Um, and like obviously I can't say too much of the message
But basically she'd worked in another agency before it didn't work out
Um, and she was like really excited at the prospect and she already had all the experience type thing
But she just couldn't speak English and I can't be like
Given lead script examples where she mimics what I'm saying because then she's gonna end up just sounding like me type thing
When it comes to trying to mix it was a shame. It was a shame because it would have been a very interesting mix
You can stack donuts on it Japanese branch went no, there will be no spin-offs
absolutely no spin-offs that feel or
um
I am I am three gens and I am done. I have nothing else to produce or give to this beautiful world
I will give my daughters
um
My gen one my gen two my gen three and I am done. I cannot handle anymore. I am I'm at capacity
There is too much lights off
Plappening happen. I can't keep up with you as refluence. I can't keep up with you
um
Someone was worried about a male branch. I assure you that male branch idea is dead in the ditch
I am not even touching it with a 10-foot pole
um
Someone asked I did get a few inquiries
On the website saying are you interested in doing a safer work branch?
The answer is no
I don't mean to sound so blunt with that
But the answer is no
You might as well go to any other agency go apply to any other agency if you're if you're interested in the safer work
The reason why you don't get such a good cut in other agencies is because they're greedy cons
But that's okay though because you know is what it is and they point and
They point and beat around the bush
and
Safer work branch kind of defeats the purpose literally like at that point might as well just start like
A whole different agency and all that jazz
But I am done. I have experienced it. It's been fun
Um Vila is my child and so are my daughters
And the reeflings are the father and I'm also pregnant with the reeflings for that asmr
And I forgot to commission that art. I've still not done it
Vila to electric boogaloo
But strongy with enough power you can reignite even a dying star
No latin american branch. No, I cannot do any
Uh alternative language speaking branches because I don't speak the language and I
Don't have any trusted advisors that I could overwhelm with the amount of work it takes
um
Like the split couldn't be as high if I needed someone on call 24 7 to translate what these girls are trying to
Say to me like it's just it's not possible. It's not possible
Or it's not possible for me possible for other agencies. Not yourself out, but
After three gents. I am done. I am helping the girls achieve their dreams as much as possible at that point
I have no interested in
Trying to infinitely expand and have a billion talents out of ones and no, that's just no it's so disrespectful as well to the
To the girls um just being like oh, but we're already throwing out the next gen some mailers
I'm broke. Oh, wait. Sorry. Sorry. Refling was trade. I'm sorry. Refling. Hold on. Let me trade. Let me put this away
Oh, sorry
No refling branch. What is that?
What even is that?
Moles? Wait, why is it a million?
What are you doing?
uh
The drip the drip
Other players accepted wait, you're giving me a million dollar
Million gp freaking what is it?
Oh
Oh, emi's not gonna like that
emi's gonna have a word with that
Oh, those are awful. Do you want these back?
I gotta be honest chief. I think you can have these back here. Let me trade accept trade
Wait, how do I go back on the trade?
How do I get you flip flops? Wait, how do I give it back? I don't want them. They're scary
Emi's gonna be mad. Do you want it back? Where are you? I can't see you. Are you on me?
Oh, there you are. Here you go. You take them back. Oh, no, you're busy in the bank. Oh
Just sell it for more way in
Honestly vealer has me really wanting to become a you're cool and I wish I could do the same sort of stuff
Um, if you're a guy, unfortunately, I don't have much of you
But do you really not want these back? Where are you?
Trade give me take these things back
Definitely just sell it have like four of them
Via lure s on I can't I know how blow espagnol me
Hey, you know me casa to casa
Johnny la chanta is the more local right I've yanked the shoes they're mine now. Sorry
Never give a minecraft hole your diamonds
Or she runs away with your mall shoes and runescape
Oh, you're still streaming. Why are you sick of me already?
Please rest well. Yes. Anyone who needs to sleep, please rest well
We are doing a cheeky endurance today. So if you think you can
Hold on for another two hours
Then
If not, then
Sick from how sweet your streams are too much sugar make to me her
Yeah, I was like la chanta is the more local
And then there is that other one free those rats
Which is oh no free those rats. There's a me. Oh, she's shaking her hand at us
Why I order looking stance
At least this 30 minutes left for me. Maybe not much more though
You're gonna have to use hypnosis. Wait, I don't want to sleep though, but it's good for your health
Can't do it. It's evil
Fuck you. You tangled me. I tangled you. That was even ASMR. I was just me man
singing a little lullaby
I
Was streaming when I came a bed now I wake up and I can continue watching hell. Yeah
All of a sudden I feel super hyper
Well after the lullaby my favorite saying apologies if I butcher it
Oh as if I can read that
No, I'm trying to book
Serada
Flies do not enter a close mouth. Damn. They really said loose lips sink ships. I can't believe it
You almost got me
It was lovely though. Oh your whispers can tingle alone. I'll bet you like my whispers
I
I didn't mention then just made me imagine you as Gengar
Yeah
Gengar the epinosis
Might be the lullaby or the two kilograms of cocaine or just no, no, I'll sleep when moma sleeps
Just so lovely. Thank you. Thank you
When the stream ends emi and ac's memberships are gonna go
Live because I'm gonna put them live because I'm such a good little streamer
Such a good little streamer
It's dreamer. No, let me be a streamer
Manager, no, I'm a little manager
I just do the intern work and it keeps the stress off of them as long as the girl stress levels are low
And I will I will be very happy
The point is to consume hypno content so much it conditions you it will work eventually to me over a decade from when I
became interested in color felt my first return
It was drowsy
Yeah, I will my bed team is
5 p.m. Actually, it's 1 p.m. Right now and we've still got another
Two and a half hours. Yeah
So then that would take me to
4 p.m. So I have one hour basically to do all the
Stuff that I'm supposed to do. Um, and then I pass out
And then when I wake up I prepare for stream with a cup of honey tea
And then I open up crash bandicoot warped and make sure you guys can hear it and see it
And then we go again. Um, I believe tomorrow is eight hour stream. It's not endurance to finish the game. It's eight hours
Would it be mean to let you know you're 10% of the way to 99?
I
What
10% of the way
I thought I could get it finished this month. I don't think so
10% there. Oh, yay
Do you want to know the amount of xp required?
It's 13 million. Oh, I'm
10% of the way that so every million is like, I guess
Well, 1.3% is every million wait
Every million is 10.3%
Surely that's how it works. Is that how math works?
Break it down into chunks. Um
9 to 8 to 99 is like 1.2 million. Oh my god
Peanut the force is here. You should be able to do it
Every 1.3 million is 10% okay, so we're just over 10% now
Okay, that's not bad. We'll finish the sword fish
I think we can finish the sword fish before the end of the stream and then
We'll tackle wine. I'm going to buy a bunch of wine stuff
And we're basically gonna watch a movie
While we do it so we can all giggle and laugh at movie
Um, I think we'll do john wick
This is perfect zatsu content and rambling. Yeah
I did look at marshmallow. I don't know if I have many more marshmallows a lot of the marshmallows
I can't really read for obvious reason because reeflings are a little
Okay, let me check if there are any more
Marchmallows
Oh, okay, definitely a few more marshmallows. Hold on. Let's go. Uh
Oh, no, are you guys berating me because I lost four in a row?
Uh
I was split between giving my veal or membership
Cherry to emmy or to mercy
Because each of the girls are intense young dairies and don't want their fans to flirt with other girls
Then I remembered all the good times from hanging in your stream and I saw the third option you me
No, you're supposed to support my daughters
Strong eat sometimes during or after emmy's membership opening. I'm going to make a decision. You're a strong prick
I won't overlook you when deciding
Reefling or or pinpal or snippet whatever one you may be
Um, please always support my daughters over me if you can only support one at a time
Um, please pick either daughter if you struggle to pick between a daughter pick the design the default design
You like the most
That's the easiest the most simplistic way to do it because your brain will either go
I like this design the most or I like that. Oh my god. I thought Gimli was in the room there
I had a heart attack. I was getting nervous about spiders. Uh, I don't like them
Um, I'm also just a spider like a working in the room. Can we add pictures or videos to marshmallows? Um, you can via
cat box
um
If you want to show me something you have to do the link and you have to make it easy
Just remove the dot
And put dot in brackets because if you do it any other way, I'm too paprika and can't open it off
It's literally a logic puzzle to open up a link when you don't give me the link
It's okay strongy. We'll comfort you after this losses. They're there head pads. Good girl. Hey, wait didn't
Did you want us to help with those frustrations? Would you like to be on?
Whoa, I can't read that. Whoa, I can't read that
Okay
Can you read that in lads can you read that in? Hey, that's uh, that's the offline
That's the offline one. You know what I'm saying? That's that's that's between me and offline
Uh, right. Let me let me scroll down to the next one
Hey strongy, just wanted to thank for all the fun streams. You're welcome. We've been
I've especially enjoyed your ASMR streams. Your voice and accent are just so pleasant to listen to. I you like that
I bet you do
I also look forward to the fun ways that you plan to mind break it. Oh
It's coming
Hope you and the girls are having a great time and go far with your content
Bruv, we're all in cloud nine like all of us are so happy
Um our monetization streams are about to be done me and mercy are done
Icy and emmy are next then it's she be
Then it should be a zero whenever it gets granted. I feel like it should happen now
I'm sorry strongy, but I choose you. You speak to me on a whole another level. I love you. Kamiyoshi. No, you can't call me kamiyoshi
Will you do more twitter mosaic responses to the marshmallows? Yes, I've been wanting to do it
And update it terribly terribly badly for a long time
Because I really enjoy writing the scenarios to you guys like when you guys give me like a little prompt or something
And I just take it way too far. It's my favorite thing to do
Yes, I will definitely be doing that again soon. It's just
Every I say this every stream as the dust settles and all the little mini side projects get pushed out the way
Then I can start to like really catch up because like whenever I do those two-hour streams
I'm catching up and like I'm literally going to the doctors after buckshot roulette and then I'll be healing up for a bit
um
so
ASMR with the viewer viewer beats you in a board game a bunch till we let you win and so then
Spacey time to celebrate the victory. Honestly, that's quite funny
um
You being so silly not very bright and cute at the same time makes me want to
Run and tackle you under the bed and cuddle you
I would hug you and roll around under the covers and never let you go. Where's can I explain how much I love you?
You're my sunshine. Oh, you're my sunshine
Refling
You like when I'm dumb
You like when I show how unbelievably brain dead I am. Yeah, is that what you like?
Sorry, but you're being hard locked as my oh, she does
We sure do
Allegedly, why is it so hard to play fricking connect for?
I don't know why it's so hard
Uh she be just woke up and said I woke up a bit ago dizzy but wanting to be ravaged
Okay, she be she be doing better with her migraine
You are more of a mother to me than my own parents and I hardly even know you you are welcome
well, I didn't mean you're welcome like that, but
um
sometimes
It's a bit sucky, but some people might not necessarily be the best parents and sometimes it's easier to just
take a deep breath
and sigh and say
They did the best with what they had
at the time with what they got
and
Sometimes it's not easy to swallow the truth and be like, oh that really wasn't as
nice because
You know when you watch media, it's like oh the loving parents. They're so supportive. They're so this or so that
Sometimes it's a hard pill to swallow to say that you drew an unlucky hand
And that might not necessarily mean you don't still share a love for your primary caregivers
um
But there are some phrases in the english language that's like the blood of the covenant is thicker than the water of the womb
Which basically just means the connections that you seek out in life
that are
outside of your family
Can be just as valid if not more loving
than family because you don't pick family you don't you don't pick these aspects and
sometimes it's just easier to
It's not easy to swallow the pill, but sometimes it's easier to just take a deep breath
Let out a big sigh and be like okay
That's just how it is and
I hope you're doing okay. Yeah
is
It sucks, but i'm i'm glad um
You can feel a degree of motherly love. Um
You know, I don't think anyone should be embarrassed or
Uh, what's the word kind of like it's only human nature to crave
um
to crave attention to crave love to create to crave
These positive reinforcers
That show that you're a part of a community that you're welcome that you're wanted
So don't ever you know, don't feel embarrassed about that
Just you know, if you're needing kind of a way to to put it away
Uh deep down inside you just want like one big sigh and say
Yeah, you know what that's fucked that situation's fucked, but i'm here. I'm doing it. I'm crushing life
You know, i've gotten through
The worst days of my life every every worst day of every experience yet. You're still here and you're still
Trucking along a little reefland and you're doing body. You're doing a body good job. You are so don't don't worry about it. All right
Don't worry about it. You're doing great
Fantastic
Um
Will you for lack of better words recycle scripts with slight adjustments for the other girls?
I no longer am the script master, but the answer is no they're all being like created from scratch
um
Now they
Now it can it might like some of the sentences might be the same, but there's only so many ways you can say give me that
Yeah, um
Um, give me that schwanz. Um, there's only so many ways you can see it, so
Uh, there might be some repeated sentences, but yeah
Thank you strong
Hey
For sure in german you say schwanz schwanz conningen
oh my god
Ink for me written 500 different ways. Give me that
Give me that fire hose
um
Say strongy nothing lid here. I can't donate become a member or a patreon
Just want to say thank you for your streams and the content you provide. It's a fresh take on vitro bin. It's been so so entertaining
Everything from the wholesome to the unhinge
Just sharing random things, you know watching you as a whole has given me so many laughs and
That I so desperately needed in my life, especially the meme ASMR. Oh, yeah, you're like, please. Please. Please. Let me hold it
Please please i'm begging
Please
Oh, I didn't expect that 77 77. We're getting there
70 freaking seven. I thought I was only gonna finish on 70 today
Whoa, that's your man
Okay, uh, sorry. Let me let me continue
Um watching you has wholeheartedly given me so many laughs that I suggest wouldn't he especially meme ASMR
I wish you and the girl success of your dreams. Remember to take breaks. Ah
You are so funny remember take breaks
Oh, you're pouring one out for my tonial. Thank you pour one out for my tonial lived a good life
lived a good life did right and did fit and did me good well
um
77 you're now at my level and I played for like eight years
What there's that saying it was like took four years to do this
VTuber does it in one week
Took four took this man four years VTuber comes in and does it in a week. I say that as if
Reflings didn't like hand me all of the fish and everything
laughs in agony
Got that pop-up answer my question
Guess that pop-up answer my question you can now cook blood runes or can make haggis
Get this woman on rune crafting absolutely not we are not touching rune crafting when a 10 foot pole
Wow, let's see. Where were they?
Yes, please don't ever worry about not being able to donate give money all that jazz
Free content always coming rough life is freaking hard, especially
economically in these times
and
Where greed is just everywhere hold on that tin foil hat's coming back hold on no go away tin foil hat
Just in times like this it is much more valuable
and
much more
Much more valuable much more important that you look after yourself
That you look after whatever situation you're in if you have debts you pay them off if you need a sweet treat
you indulge in it and if you
You know after work you need to play video games to de-stress
Make sure your internet bill is paid and make sure your electricity bill is paid
So you have access to these abilities to de-stress
To handle the work day to handle the workflow or to handle any life stresses that you might be going through
Um, there are just countless situations where people are
Just going through hell on earth on the inside and on the outside
They look perfectly fine and you'd have absolutely no clue what on earth is going on with them and you know
the last thing
people want to be dealing with is
um
Just the stress that builds and builds and builds and builds and builds until you pop people pop people have burnout
people have breakdowns like you can pop so easily so make sure
And you know you're looking after yourself first because at the end of the day
You are the most important person in your life
And that's the fact for everyone's pov right now. You are the most important person in your life. It's the way it works
Okay, and you have to look after yourself first. You have to make sure that you're feeling good. You have to you have to enable yourself
and
To be on your prime like I'll I'll wipe out mazl's hierarchy and needs right now. Do not think I won't do it
I will start a psychology lecture or right this second
I'll put my teacher's glasses on and it is very important to meet your needs first before you ever try and meet the needs of someone else
however, uh, the exception is that a
The stupid sentence I've heard is a love yourself first before you love someone else or something like that. Shut the fuck up
That's the most nonsense statement I've ever heard. Everyone can share the love to any degree
That's my take on that sense. Um
You can share love at any point it is simple to share a little bit of love glasses
toggle no not glasses toggle I never got glasses on my model
Uh
This is helping me procrastinate my final. How do you oh no
That's not good. Damn. I fell asleep for 13 hours and you're still screaming. Yeah
Do you need iron supplements?
Sleeping for 13 hours
Indicates low iron. You might want to get that checked out or just start taking iron supplements. Go for it. Have fun
You can only take one dose a day anyway
Cooking was my first 99 in old school runescape. Are you gonna end up making wine? It's expensive, but the fastest
Yes, we are doing wine. I stopped doing wine
Reflings gave me a ton of fish. So I'm cooking all the fish first
Wine
It requires a lot of focus like I keep missing the fermentation
period for an xp bomb
and
I used to sleep when giving a ton of blood
And they said I had high iron. Oh, I don't know what high iron would be. How much red meat do you eat?
I didn't actually sleep
You just still streamed for such a long time. Oh, okay. I comprehend. I understand
Comprehendi
It's just sweet. Comprehendi
Drink less blood. Are you a vampire?
If you want the truth anything that might take you away from us
Makes me want to cry, but I'm not going what can take me away from you
Motherfucker. I am veiler
Nothing can stop me other than an internet connection. That's about it
You know, you don't have to worry about me going anywhere. Nothing
Nothing can perish me and we already know what we say to death. We say to death not today motherfucker
I've got refluence. Okay, and they've got me and we've got a lot. We've got a lot of time to make up for okay
um
Got another gym post. I don't know what I'd do without you. Don't panic refler. I'm not going anywhere
Don't panic stop panicking
The deadly tone fiction do you know how that's how bob marley passed away apparently he rejected penicillin because of his beliefs
And bob marley that this is love this is love this is love that's that feeling
That singer passed away because he rejected penicillin
Why do I keep opening that? I don't even know how I'm doing that
um
Yeah, like saws i'm snorting penicillin for free like you don't have to tell me twice if I need it
Advantage a modern modern tag and doesn't pay it bro. She's gonna reject pen- no i'm not
Other than my dad's allergic to penicillin
um
you
Mummy I need a countdown. Please let me in
Uh, I don't know if you're on the patreon, but there's a new patreon audio with that in it
Unending stamina. Good. I didn't try that
Uh, yeah, I was freaking I was
clapping
I was clapping without my hands asmr and then right at the end of it. I was like, oh
I was a little cheeky cat there might as well
I'm allergic to that stuff. Yes penicillin can be incredibly deadly for some people which is crazy
um
I'm pretty sure the guy who discovered penicillin did it by a complete accident as well, which was rather interesting
uh
There's just complete accident
casually discover something that saves literally millions of lives cat
Uh, you know, just get a little casual probably in the billions as time goes on easily a billion lives saved because of
little accidental petri dish discovery. Um
It's really fascinating fascinating
Should maybe go into the lore of biology. Uh, no should go into the lore the start of modern modern
The wonders of modern medicine. Nah, I'm mercy
Not yet
How many things can you take at a time? I don't know refland. Should we meet up at convention and find out?
I
Would you make us a hypnosis
To get as hard just by hearing oh
Sorry, I didn't mean to say that part out loud. Sorry. Sorry. I'm forgetting to censor. I'm forgetting to censor
I've been streaming for a hot second now
Sorry, I didn't mean to say that out loud. Sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm supposed to censor what I say
Oh
Wow
Okay, let me try again gas my nots might not say so Richard. We're on a list. Um
What would you make as a hypnosis session to get a the tentacle giving a standing ovation?
Uh, just by hearing your voice and have the strongest ink
When we hear you think that's an interesting one. I wouldn't mind giving that a tackle
Um
I'll see so the four part series is one of the first attempts I have ever recorded it is not very good
I'll just say that right now. It's not go away chat. It's my wife now
Um, I will say that the four free to access audios are my first ever attempt
I'm not very satisfied with them looking back on them already even though I only produced them like a month and a bit ago. Um
So do give me patience to kind of learn what works what feedback I get. Um
I'm very shy, but if you wanted me to
Mm-hmm in the middle of a crowded city in broad daylight, I would do it. That's how much I care about
You break the law for me. Do you know it's against the law to do that stuff?
I wonder when you break the law
Mm
Mummy I haven't inked in days because I've been spending all my weekend hours watching veiler boy
I can't help but support the girls because they make me so happy
And I don't
To well livestream it. I'm so pent up. I need mummy. Tell me what to do
Do you have any of the girls patreon?
Or if you're a pin pal emmy has a really good funny canton
Uh, I don't think I have a I don't have a full audio yet. That's accessible
Wow
Just ink into the board
Who goes yeah, oh did that do it for you? Yeah, you like that
I swallowed it all and then and then did a big old burp at the end
Day 10 of eating celery. No, we have a set up
Did I say that? I think I might have read that one already
Stop eating celery for me. It's terrible. It's it's just like better water in a solid form
Um
Parable
The sucky five bucks asking for a friend
Stony, I'm really sorry. I tried very hard, but I just couldn't I watched live streams and vods and listened to audios
None of our daughters do it for me. I keep coming back to you. Hope you understand. You're my community
I'll stop
I don't know how you're gonna come in with me. I still support them however I can forever. You're beefling all reefland
Thank you for you know, thank you for giving them a shot
I would say
Sheevy is like incredibly close to me like mentally and personality wise pretty close
Unless I'm like completely like misreader, but I'd say she's probably the closest
Uh, personality wise and easiest to consume
Uh, I would love to share some fanfics, but I don't know if it's appropriate even allowed you can
But if it is weird, I submit them. Uh, I think you can do pace bin links. I think those are safe
Hi strongy, hi reefland
Did you know the term architect and features and comes from the irish actor pierce
Ro Brossnan who is rumored to have intentionally made his wife
Gain
100 pounds over the course of 20 years the term itself is from a quote
Made on the architects of peace
Home page a world without wills is too terrible to imagine. He did not write a book and call it that
Stop is that why he did wait is that from a book he wrote?
Oh my god, that's a racist
That's outrageous, but really funny
Okay
I like how ac is sweet and emmy is false to the wall and same
I will continue myself right now. Go to sleep
Hi strongy your way of
Gentle talking is one of my favorite triggers. I think if you did scott's wobble bars, it would be amazing
Is there a way to control my who while on stream on youtube?
Funny you mentioned that I thought about doing that, but I think it would like to be on banjo
and
I
Have you considered using
Bitmosis to plant suggestions that are wholly positive and affirming for the viewer
Something to encourage them when they're down to give them that little push when they're low
Don't don't want to do the dishes strongy would want you to don't want to cook and just want to order out strongy
Would want you to cook strongy would want me to live my best life. That's interesting. I'm wondering
If I could do a put in you to sleep asmr
but it's secretly hypnosis and then
After you've fallen asleep, then I would do like that kind of
in
In in planting
You've got me thinking a little bit when you got me thinking the cogs are turning
You got me at help you go to sleep. Yes, I think
You could do it if you established triggers outside of youtube and then use some in you
I see is way more insane. I thought me was uh having fun
I see just yeah, she doesn't like sharing on g fog sans sense or something that uh has been sent somewhere else. She doesn't like that
That would be perfect imprinting. Oh my god
What is deceit too
I'm about to get pranked when I look off on us
Bank the banker
Why do you do that I'm getting
I
Is a real game
The c2 has just released its free to play update
So I'm making an updated guide for it as there are many new things around the map whether that be players
Points below about 50 sanity one grab from a terror will kill it
Is it where wait if I'm getting chased by a werewolf the streaming gonna end good that's on something
honey soaked
Is it am I getting chased by a werewolf in that game? That's terrible. All of us are gonna be freaking
Male on stream me. Oh, sorry. I'm looking at a how to play deceit to full gay 2024
My apologies. Sorry
Um, all right, that was loud. Oh, I'm sorry. My bad. My bad. I was just trying to see what the gameplay was about
There's werewolves
Bro sounded nice though. I mean we have every physical
Come come on. I was just loud my apologies. Don't need to jump serious
We're at 2000 swordfish. Can I do it? Do we have enough time?
Cutting it close cutting it close. I think it's possible
Science is a wonderful thing like the scientist Fritz Harba who with Carl Bosch invented the harbour Bosch process to synthesize
Ammonia since then it has been possible to supply millions of people with food and toxic gas and chemical warfare
I'm sure the government would never poison its citizens on purpose
No, that's it. Give me the tin foil hat back on. I'm about to tell you what american have done as people
Thank you iron reaper for the 20 my goodness
You sure you give a lot of money. Yeah, you sure everything's okay
um
You got figure out who the infected are and either kill them or do the task and escape without dying
You either try and portray your friends could be cool. I'm addicted to this
hmm
Well, if I'm getting chased by a werewolf, whatever happens. I'm gonna just let it happen
I
Uh, scrawny you're gonna get all logged out in 52 minutes unless you hot wait actually
Don't need to like purposely time out
Why why can't people be addicted to games
I'm an adult. I consent to being addicted to old-school runescape and playing with reefing
You can log back out in in as well. Yeah
I'll probably go for a tinkle break in an hour and make a cup of tea just for my throat
And unless I do it now
Carl Bosch not to be confused with Carl Bosch
You want some madness fuel? Look at the all all the times America has stuck its nose into
But did you ask her overlords? I know I never asked overlords for permission. Silly me. Silly me. Silly me streamer
Sure
Then you can just log back in I better
I better
What
Is
What is a pace been like? Oh, hey, oh, sorry
This sorry, this is what I said. It's my accent. You can't it's not your fault. It's my accent
The website is called paste bin
Off the bed rest well
Yeah, for anyone, please don't be worried if you need to say hey ho. I gotta go. Um, I am
I'm gonna keep
Hey, strongy day nine of keeping my tentacles off myself. Thank you for being you
I'm gonna keep going unless you or your audios do something for me
You're just having effect on me that I want to do better myself. I even think my mood has improved and I haven't gotten angry today
Uh, but flat out so again, thank you
I'll be too recent
Do you get frustrated though?
Oh
I think I'll get frustrated
The goodest boy around. Thank you for becoming a member. What a nice thing. We just boy around jack of blades
399 thank you for coming a member and supporting
The channel thank you for thank you for smashing that like button that subscribe button. Yeah, I'm not really good at doing that part
Never ask a woman to meet her age a man has salary or a country about the warm crime they committed literally
That would be a really interesting thing
stream as well talking about all the
You know the one story I really don't like
Is the the guy they kept alive that got covered in radiation
And they kept him alive and his body couldn't accept painkillers
Ah
They couldn't give him morphine and he was alive for like another two weeks just radiating away. Oh trade. Sorry. Sorry. Sorry. My bad. Sorry
Sorry, bro. Sorry, bro. Excuse me. Pardon me
Med's bad is your name isn't that dangerous?
What is this a bird
Are you giving me a bird and a biscuit a wooden shield and a shoulder stop can I wear that on my shoulder?
Oh
Reefling you're you're a cockatoo. Wherever these birds are called a toucan
Oh my god, we flings your toucan
Reflings are a toucan. You're so cute. I got a little birdie on my shoulder
Parrot no, you're a toucan
Oh my god, they're so cute
Wait, you want more or not?
No, oh wait. Sorry. Sorry. Sorry. Sorry. I thought I said it wanted to say more. Wait, you want more?
Trade accepted
No, I'm so cool
Every time I learn something nice from German history it ends and yeah, pretty much
Never ask why
Volkswagen is so popular such a successful business. Whoa. What's this loot chest? How have I not seen this? I've been here for how long?
You do not currently have any wilderness loot keys
Well, excuse you
Maybe some of us don't want wilderness loot keys
Our Fanta
What was it? Was it portug...
Portugal
No, not Portugal
Um, it was like, oh why I randomly have like German ancestry and I'm Argentinian and it's like rough
The chest is for loot killing. Yeah, we in out here the pk
Argentinian or Hugo Boss or Coco Chanel
Yeah, who is it that made the uniforms and they like never talk about it
How do you remember?
Me when I met my Argentinian friends great-grandfathers I was like, oh, hello big yes. Do be good. Yeah, okay
Yeah, do be good
Einhorn
Start repeating random German words that unknown phrases
Yeah, every every company have it doing a little naughty naughty. Are we the baddies?
Isn't there like a whole town of is there?
That's news 10
Uh, I don't think we're gonna get 20 by the time the stream finish. I got two hours
We're cooking up the swordfish. Honestly the swordfish ain't that bad
140 isn't that bad per-cooked swordfish. I'm not mad at that. I know wine is a lot faster
And I understand wine is a lot faster, but this I'm I'm being cheering danger man being cheering
I have to be up early for lab. Yes, please rest well anyone who needs to sleep or you've got commitments
Or you gotta go and do stuff. Please don't worry. You're more than welcome to um
To what to go rest or go get stuff done
I am literally cooking these and then doing wine until it's time to until the vod is ready to explode
Um
If mersey is still playing harvester 2 she might be we might get a successful redirect into mersey or
I don't know if a zero is doing a part two of stray or she's gonna try and just stray in one run. Um
Uh
I thought it was less than two. Yeah, no, it oh well is less than two hours now
Boo youtube vods fix them so I can do 14 hour streams
Boo youtube
YouTube
Remember to sell cooked swordfish when you're done. We'll get a pretty penny
No night cuddles rest well sleepy heads
Then it goes to sleep
To sleep to sleep
It's time to go to sleep and rest your little head
Rest well
24 hour stream no if youtube's
Vods didn't break on 12 hours. I would definitely push 14 hour streams
um
Can you convert them into bank notes?
It kind of looks like you can only sell in stacks of 20. Yes, you can make bank notes
Uh in order to make a bank note you go to the bank
Don't do why you click there you go to the bank and then it says withdraw as and then you've got no
And then you click on it note all and then I produce a note
So you have to do it via the bank to do that
But I withdraw as items because I'm currently wanting to interact with the items that I'm pulling out
Hey, but that's how you do it and you can sell them all at one time
And don't worry that you didn't know because you don't know until you know
Enjoy the rest of the cooking stream. Love you strong. I love you replay
Rest well sleepy heads
You're allowed to you're allowed to go to sleep. I how what how did I what?
What are you giving me?
That splodge of cum be honest. What is that? What did you just oh?
What even was that? It looks like a piece of an alien or something
What did you just give me?
Did you just give me ink?
It's not ink
Oh, it's a wolf clock dumbass
What on earth that looks like ink?
Wow, oh my god. I'm like get it out of the wazoo like I'm getting so pimped out right now. I'm not being funny
I'm literally getting dressed up to go like to valador and like who to myself out honestly
Oh, no, it takes off my parrot. Oh, I can't have both. No, I need a rifling on my shoulder
Do you want the wolf back? I'll give you the wolf back. Where are you?
trade here
Take take the wolf back. I can't have it
I can't have the wolf you need to take it back because I need to have the rifling on my shoulder
Rip all yours. Thank you
Oh, that's raw swordfish
Maybe 30 minutes, I'll make a cup of tea because my voice is really starting to
What do you mean talking for 10 hours straight means my voice gets tired?
What that I've never that's ridiculous
That's ridiculous. I've never heard that before
Hydration
Mmm
Wow
Yes, I think I might make a cup of tea and the heat should hopefully help my vocal cords
But they're starting to feel it mr. Krabs seriously how frustrating
I think they say like one of the worst things you can drink is like dairy and fizzy juice when you have like long vocal activity
I'm like, oh, yes, the two worst things that I consume constantly
I have fizzy juice every day and I have a honey tea every day
I finally got my painting desk cleaned off time a pain. Oh my god
We should do a Bob Ross stream. Oh the wolf caught me down the floor
Okay, boom
we're at 1.8 for the
a
The fishy I guess once all these fishies are done. We'll sell them and then I'm just gonna buy a ton of wine
Strongly doesn't like my wolf coat. No, I do like it, but it removes the reef link from my shoulder
I know it looks nothing like a reef link, but I want to be parrot
I'm just working on cooking on my airman. Oh
I'm going
Yeah, those are the two literally you're not supposed to have any dairy and I have like milk honey tea
And then we compare paintings by the end. Honestly, I'm down for that
I saw a tweet where someone had to do vocal warm-ups like a singer. Oh, you're supposed to go like
I got carried to that because my friends my
I'm out of stamina. I'm out of juice
vocally I'm
Who goes there? I'm out of stamina
I saw yeah
Why what an interesting number of marshmallows literally 9-11, okay, dude
What did this day? Please hold on your
Uh
Have we just gained a far anon
I
Read this out loud or is this gonna have everyone saying what wtf? I think we've just gained a far anon
Please hold in your fars until it starts to get painful
And then blast them onto the make close up so we can hear your cheeks clapping beneath the
the basic
burst of brass
Actually, did she be far in a stream that I don't know if someone told me she be my vaginal
I mean I don't judge but I don't think I need you to do that
Look, we don't really we don't kink shame around here. Okay
She be and emi both did wait
Wait, and I've not clipped it
Stop, please tell me you guys clipped it so I can turn it into a short for some reason
hiccups burps in fart clips of vtubers get so many views
I don't even care if it embarrasses them
I'm like, I will get you your play button one way or another and I keep farting down that make young lady
Yes, Johnny
Um for some reason hiccups sneezes any normal bodily function when when vtuber does it hilarious views
And I'm like what it doesn't make any sense
And
Astrony milk in the clips literally though, I wonder why
Rappers absolutely
The emi one there should be a timestamp in the comments for it. Oh, thank god. Thank you timestampers. You helped me clip my gen mates
No, the buraptubers. No, I think we're I think peeler is definitely what we're at
Hi, strony. I just want to say I love you and I think you're perfect. Stop everything. You're perfect
See, I kissed you. That's how perfect you are. You can't deny the allegation
I'm done
Okay, oh my tummy's rumbling, but I think it's digested
Oh
Pea holding stream when are you a pin pal? Are you the one who convinced emi to do that on her stream?
It must have been you must have been you pin pal
I can I can smell you a male away pin pal
Got my stomachs making really weird noises about the 3d or migraine. I even heard all
Smell a pin pal
I can't believe how well that stream once is it. I've not seen it. Is it bad. Can you get put kidney stones from that?
I went to bed get up and you're still cooking these swordfish
There was five though. No, there was 10,000 swordfish
If I make 10,000 swordfish one stream that means I can do 10,000
Wine in one stream most likely if not more it means bod is
Back up actually did she cut something out of it?
I do not know I've been streaming unfortunately
Uh when I stream all day I have no clue what shenanigans the girls are getting up to in all honesty
um
Oh
Wait that video is still getting recommended to people
24,000 views 2,000 likes I wonder if because people are liking it
Strone has the best boing boing
Azura has biggest boing boing or do you mean rump?
I have the biggest rump
Oh
The perfect all the better to smother you basically
She's out pealard anything that ever happened the audio after this it takes a day
Do you think you'll feel accomplished when you get nighting in cooking? I hope so
I'm in the trenches right now on this swordfish
She accidentally played the clip on stream she forgot to turn off this the audio
Oh
You can pass away if you drink too much water she accidentally uploaded it to me
Uh, okay, okay, okay
She already has a warning on her channel
Amy playing with fire, but then again she is the pyromaniac of
Vila, so right um right on par
Can't believe it can't believe I found such a lore friendly girls
smile
I have to admit I'm think I'm starting to lag a bit
It's not looking good for me
slowly perishing
I'm like dad make a tea, but I don't think it's gonna wake me up, but I think it's gonna
Oh, my stomach's making freaking weird eyes noises. Can you hear that?
What will come first heat death of the universe or full inventory no burn honestly
I feel like I'm getting so close to it and then I'm getting although the burn percentage is 9.4 it used to be 18.9
She cut it out from the vod. We're safe question mark. I'm firmly of the opinion. There's such a thing as
Being too big
What's 99 after cooking? No, we're just doing cooking
We might do some questing together because I'm not familiar with a lot of quests
um
But that would just be very casual and probably level up combat a little bit before that and
once we've achieved 99 cooking and
I am not 99ing anything else. I
Have severely underestimated how much this is
and
A strong aspect fill to the caboose
If you ever do the cat quest you have to feed it when it's a kitten or it runs away
That's so specific. I'm probably never gonna retain this information
I'm going to go for a full 99 account for the first time off your brave
And the other version of runescape levels go up to 120
Did they take even longer to achieve?
Oh, that's crazy. Sorry. Oh, I'm having a wee yawn. Sorry
Don't mess that update on that video
Oh my god, I'm in the money list. I'm sorry. I really don't want to flicks on you guys, but we're in the money
Oh
Look, uh, whoa fill inventory. No burn get ready to ever said no burn
Hold on hold on hold on
So this is what it looked like a minute ago
So that was the last time I shared it with you 19.8. Okay
And the money didn't register, but now the money's registered. Are you ready to get flexed on?
Where is it?
Are you ready to get flexed on how much money I made on that video? Boom. That's right. Get flexed on
To say that gen two has been funded is an understatement. That's how much money I've made
What are you gonna do about them?
It got limited ads
So it probably would have been like 20 bucks if it wasn't limited ads
But you know what 10 bucks I'll take you you'll be logged out in 30 minutes
Make sure you move to a safe area or log out now
Your mama
Right. I I'm gonna go make a cup of tea then if it's gonna log me out so I can come back in
And
Getting 120 is getting 99 about eight times. Oh pass on that. No, thanks
How do people make a living off of youtube? Oh, it's much better than this when you have like a
A lot of ASMR videos to offer and you make like money generated in the background
Right, I'm gonna go make a cup of tea and let this game log me out. Um, I will be back
I would just take me about three minutes because you can't leave the world
They're in the runescapes. Uh, gay Brooks Johnny
Uh
Right, I'll be
Yeah, three minutes and I'll make a cup of tea. Please do stretch your legs and all that jazz. Um, I will be back
In three minutes, which I've said for the eighth time now. Sorry. I'm losing it. Well, I'll be back
So
Oh, it's actually quite a lot louder than in-game audio. Sorry if that like completely destroyed your ears
Hope no one's sleeping through this
Her account is gone too. Wait, who's the count? Look at that
Um
What was I doing
Fish fish fish
Um, I I'm starting to pass out. I'm not gonna lie. I'm getting very tired. I'm a throats very sore
Which is why I need refilling tea
Not just any kind of honey tea
Well, I'll get a timer in five minutes. The music was pretty loud. Okay, my apologies. Oh, I've got honey on my freaking finger as well
I'm not the good I'm not my refilling honey. I need a special refill
The menu music apparently a separate set. Yeah
Monkey badness
Nice sleepy little reeflings who were already snoozed together honestly
Oh, I'm I'm getting tired myself
Oh gee Hermes, thank you for becoming a member as a reminder
All membership streams
No
Next week membership streams start because I've already locked in what happens this week
Next week is very busy
as next week when
Uh
Elden Ring comes out
It's today next week Elden Ring DLC comes out. Okay, so
The start of the week is going to be like a
multitude of different things going on. It's a little bit crazy sometimes
Refilling tea you mean ink tea exactly. That's what my refilling tea is
Passed it four times, but I got the tea
A bit oh my god, I love those stories where it's like my legs are quaking after a good session. I'm like, oh my god
Oh, no, that's not it is I can't feel my legs after
How hard I was beating in that session those ones always make me crack up
What's good
Uh
What's good, uh, we're going 10 and a half hour strong. We're wrapping up an hour
In less than 30 because of the void restriction. Um, I am going to see if mercy is available
to read into or a zero
um
Oh, my tummy keeps making noises because I need uh, did I end up going for a job?
No, it wasn't successful. I had an unsuccessful attempt at adobe, which is why my stomach's making
Uh, bizarre noises right now. Oh my god. I'm starting to get like full cooked sword run swordfish ones, which is amazing
Do your reeflings want your money back? Am I undet to beeflings?
Oh, no, is there any runescape reeflings that I'm indebted to?
But I don't have any money. How will I ever repay you runescape reefling for all the things you've done?
Get wrecked and connect for apparently
Left for a bit and you're still going. Oh, I'm a tough cookie
Hard hard to get me to crack
When I say, uh, I need to make up for lost time. I wasn't kidding
I wasn't kidding. Uh, literally next week we've got like four, maybe even five
Well, please don't be getting sick. I really don't want to get sick. Oh, I'm not gonna make it if I get sick
I'm not gonna make it. I really don't want to get sick
Bless you. Thank you. He's on high. I accept ASMR's payment. Oh, yeah
Yeah
Per little
Needing some tingles
One hour of agility treatment is payment because I can't be bothered
I need to maybe get the agility shortcut wherever it is on the map. It's like 21 to do the grand exchange shortcut
We formally request snitches
Thank you for being my sugar daddy on runescape
Thank you for making it super easy real me versus strony connect for
The real
Strony milkers warm and tasty strony milkies, please be hey stay. Oh my god, that's such a good
Uh, there's a connect for minigame and runescape. There absolutely is. Do you want to know how I know?
There's a connect for minigame and runescape. Uh, I got absolutely annihilated by all the reeflings unanimously at once
Uh, the only reason I think I won I won one game by tryharding and I won a second game by mistake
Because the other reefling wasn't paying attention
And I was literally eating a burrito and I was like what the fuck with my mouth full of a burrito
I
If you're going to do agility, there's a quest so you can skip a lot of it
I think when we do 99
Cookin will probably take a solid break from any runescape streams for a bit because there are a few other like multiplayer games
I want to like focus on like elden rings like the next big
Like a thing we're taking on
and
I don't know if you can hear my stomach
No, you can't the mic's not covered. It's covering it up
Just Johnny's milk tastes like jelly. I even know what cuttlefish milk would taste like
Would it be gelatinous or would it be silky like ink?
I think it may be silky
Worthing
Love these 20 things
Thank you for the smoothies
Also need to be on a members world for uh
I'm blamed when it comes to board games. I lost fair and square though. Okay. Okay. Okay
Well, actually who's got the higher IQ reeflings are strong in clearly the reef one clearly
Wow
We're at 1.4 on the swordfish. We may be able to finish it
Or
We might just be out of time, but honestly, it's not the biggest deal. However
You need to give strongy the monkey nut items. That's so specific
and
And could we solely if it's anything like squid ink you've eaten squid ink before
You've eaten your fellow reeflings before oh, we're in 1.6 k territory at 1,600
Monkey nuts 287. I blame all my eyes. I
I'm on you you eating your fellow reeflings. What's going on here?
Oh
See to be honest
You were just randomly placing the pieces, but I wasn't low
I was trying to counteract what the reefling was doing. That's the worst part
I was actually trying to win and I could never see what the reefling was making
I was too busy trying to like get ahead and make something for me that I couldn't see what the reefling was doing
Is worse than emmy rip of my jeans what I listen to emmy stream and if I recall correctly my glass prescription is worse than emmy
Oh, emmy cannot see. Oh my goodness bless her cotton socks. She can't see for
I reeflings gotta do what he got a scuba doo ba doo
Yeah, you literally saw what I was doing and then you forgot no because I was trying to like
I was trying to be like all the reeflings doing this the reeflings doing that right
So I'm not gonna place one here and then I'd immediately forget
Mods cruises jays
You really want me to believe that yeah
I was like trying to think ahead
I believe I can't believe I made it 10 us dollars. It feels good man
Wow
Okay, these swordfish are giving me like
What
7k a batch that's not bad
Honestly not bad. I know wine is more which is fine
But I think that's like 7k xp of inventory if I don't burn them all. Okay. Okay
Well spoke too soon on that one
Congrats on level up
It's time to beat on up on connect for strategy. It's like I'm beat strong the next time
What's my burn percentage? Oh, it's like oh, I guess it's not up to accuracy because I logged out
I got logged out against me will yeah, um
Right tomorrow's crash bandicoot, which is eight hours. So it's just a long stream in quotation marks
Not an endurance
Short stream is two hours. Um, which is buckshot roulette, but that's because I've got the doctor
And I'll keep you guys up to date on what on earth is happening with me toe
But it's pretty much decided if you guys want to hold a funeral during buckshot roulette
You're more than welcome to pour one out for the toe
It's been a good run, but
I'm just no fussed for it. Does they make a difference to me?
To me
Riptoe
It's a great lineup. Yeah, I do. Um, I want or probably can't do it tonight because I'm going to be shattered
I need to go put emmy and aces memberships live literally as soon as I end this stream
So I need to
What I need to do
I need to
Do that
I wanted to look up baltro more because that actually looks like a genuinely fun game
I just need to comprehend what on earth i'm doing first
I don't know. Maybe I need to play it offline like off stream for a little bit just to get the hang of it
Or is it better if streamer plays it for the first time?
Like I don't think watching other people play it is cheating
Rip the big gripper you will be missed literally both of them. No, no, just the one
Shawnee caught the da budus. Oh, no
People don't think I've got da budus
Um, oh my god a streamer tries american sweet loses toenails loses toenail within
one week
Diabetes hits hard on streamer
How many features do you see how many where we get no burns one?
Honestly
How many multiplayer games are on your to-do list multiplayer games are every week
um next multiplayer game is elden ring for a while and then
Probably jellybean
I love my jellybean. I don't know if they've added more stuff to it. Um, we never gave dead by daylight ago
I don't know how that would work
I think I would have to add you guys as friends possibly on steam and then delete everyone at the end
I don't know. I wanted to give fortnite a shot, but folk were rolling their eyes at fortnite
But i'm like fortnite's actually know that bad
As far as i'm aware they've like added in different game modes and stuff
um
I want uh, I would say mario kart but I suck at mario kart and it and
Like I don't I don't know how to do that new turn feature thing in it
Like we have to like turn left and right well
Called it momay win the jellybean game
It's a meme to hate fortnite at this point
It's just
Ever listened to rap city you want to sing it
Is this the real life?
Or is this just fantasy?
Caught in a landslide
No escape from reality
Look in your eyes, I don't know the words and see
uh
So you think you can stop me and make me cry
So you think i'm just gonna lay down and die
Oh baby
Just can't wait to go just can't wait to go here
Is that the word?
I don't know. I don't know
um
I was thinking about the in-game song oops
in my bed
What is, where does that go?
Easy come easy go little high little woe
Anyway the wind blows it doesn't matter to me
Hmm
I'm just a poor boy from a poor family. He's just a poor boy
Spare him his life from this monstrosity
Uh, how else does it go?
No, no, no, no, let him go
I can't remember how that freaking goes
Watch and lock it so you can listen to it
No, I finished these freaking swordfish before I fall asleep. I'm like so tired my eyes are bulging out of their skull right now
I'm ready to snooze although I might level up actually before I snooze
Best cover let me go. We will not let you go. No, no, no, no, no
No, it's important
Best cover. Oh, yeah, did you enjoy that me guess and all the lyrics was that entire thing because I completely forgot how it works
That's the whole level
Wow, we're gonna be 78 by the end of this feels good, man
Feel good, man
Oh, excuse me for yawning. I'm so going to bed. Oh my god
I
I'm just a perv. We fun. I need no sympathy
That wasn't I'm just a fool
Because I have a mummy I'm
Mummies losing the plot. That's what mummy's doing right now. I'm starting to
Uh, yeah, but h2o delirious often here
The bird outside my window the magpies are probably wondering why I have upset them today
and
I can do it. I promise
I can do it. I can stay up reefing. I'm totally not exhausted, but it's okay
I can make it happen
Yay
I didn't get any serotonin, but I think it's because I'm so tired. There's no serotonin left in my system
You don't have anything to burn on the fire. I do so
level 78
let's go
Well, now I gotta adapt the learn
Yeah, eventually serotonin only comes from night in it man. This game was rigged from the start
Reach for the stars
Yippee 78. Well, I definitely blew over my guesstimate for what we would be on
But uh, I'm still back at level 62
That's fine. Maybe wane cost a lot of money though. That's the only problem
Oh
Are we friends? I can do it. I can do it. You kid
I could also cook and not waste xp. She's passing out. Oh, yeah
Oh my god, I'm actually like this this sleep is really starting to hit me
I don't even have my tea yet. Can you hear it? Can you tell them?
Wow kfp with another 10. Thank you. My goodness
Are you squidding me right now? Are you squidding me man?
Congrats to those who caught the membership with their face
Oh, I wasn't even I wasn't even cooking them
swordfish. I'm getting so disheartened. I have my copper tea in my hand right now
I should probably go to sleep. I'm freaking ready to go
I'm tired
Strani sounds like she only has one hp left. No
Wait, I'll just I'll read some really naughty marshmallows. That should wake me up
Come on ovulation
Keep me awake so we can oh actually
and is there any snippets that want to ask if
Mercy is still streaming for another hour
Just say like strani wants to read into you, but she doesn't know if you're playing for another hour or not
Um
If there's any wee snippets that want to be a deer and pass on a message from mummy
A big bug
Zero gates zero grapes in vorkuto. Oh wait. Sorry. That's the the bolt from bluffops
Didn't make it sad
What's your take on leveling up without only to your little oh, no you can level up all you want
It's perfectly fine too. I'm not gonna let for me personally. I'm not gonna level up offline
Thank you again kfp spidey for the game tiff did mumber. Okay. Whoa. That was a big
Stagger star
I'm very tired
I will drink my tea now
Oh
The gifted membership was what I was supposed to say in english
The royal monkey kicking on top of strani
You
Mercy said that she will lately still be live in an hour. Okay. Thank you snippets for checking that out. Um
I can do it I can do it 50 minutes
Oh, mommy can do it. Mommy's just very tired
do everything
I'm ready to pass out. Oh my god. My bed time's normally five o'clock. I've got
Two more hours until bedtime and I'm perishing
I don't want to end early though. The whole point is supposed to be like endurance
But oh my god, this is like whacking me for the sight of my heat
Normally I don't do
Oh my god brain, please cooperate
My brain's not cooperating. Holy crap
Sleepy momy
Sleepy beepy momy
Almost there almost there. We just have to hold on and replay
Please hold on with me. Oh
We can do it
We just have to cook these billion swordfish that we were kindly gifted replay
Ah
Strani, what's your feelings about uh, you start sleeping the same way your girlfriend has happened to?
See on me. No me doing that to you. Absolutely
I will discuss more of that in the member stream. Maybe
Hold the lane
Hold the lane. I'm holding
Okay, so
Old school runescape is heavy doing insurance game only getting to challenge strani this much
Literally, I'm like so tired out of nowhere
I was supposed to eat that food and it was supposed to freaking help me
Get more energized and I just want to roll up into a ball and pass out
I'm like sipping honey tea. It's got caffeine in it. It's gonna do absolutely nothing for me
A sugar crash. Did I eat with that take away have sugar in it?
You can sleep early
Someone got a clues girl
Oh on me on you
A true strani classic
Honestly, I feel really bad, but like I wanted to like all these things see every fun, but you doing it to me
I'm like, I'm too scared
All right, like I'm not that's not really doing much for me
But me doing it to you
Like the terrible ones that you're not supposed to speak out loud
I
Our bodies are ready. Oh, it's happy to be your guinea pig
No, it's good. I love that
No, I'll be fine. I promise I'm fine. I'm fine. I can do it
Endurance endurance endurance. I will make sure I'm redirecting mercy in this next batch because it's not gonna work out
I I'm feeling kind of tired, but I'm gonna stick it out through until you get off
I'm getting off right now. I'm ovulating
Oh, no, my filler is going now. I'm sorry. I shouldn't be saying that stuff. I'm sorry
I shouldn't be saying that stuff. Hold on. Let me wake the frick up. Let me wake up
Wake up
Wake up wake up. Wake up grab a little makeup
Put the keys upon the table something something else. It's like a fable right. Hold on. Let's get mercy
Please
Live stream old-school Rinscape
Customization
And it should have picked mercy
Should have picked any kind of
I'm sorry for seeing it out loud
Mommy's getting tired
System of a donor friend. Yeah chop sweet
Meow
She makes a lot of random base references should have gone to Scotland spend a week
In your 20s are you an OG son?
There he makes you an OG son surely surely
You should stream more when you're both tired and I'll be like
Shiny, I don't know if you know I don't remember that till day they do it. Who does it?
The day who does what?
What does that mean? What is that?
But the game ends up going offline. Oh like the game updates for patches. Yeah, there he hikes that 31
So in death's door. No, witchy sons are supposed to be very
I don't know we ended up
It's all in board your tears or what I live for
Because you should have picked mercy
Should have picked any kind of girl of your
Yeah, my tummy. I don't know if you can hear those internal parts, but if you can hear the internal parts, I'm sorry
I had to be this way
Didn't I see this stream this morning 10 hours. Yeah. Yeah, you did. I'm a wee bit addicted
I'm starting to lose the plot though. So
You're welcome to watch my descent into madness
My filter is also gone because I've started to see things. I know I'm not supposed to see
But they're kind of just coming out just like you're angry, you know
Only so much I can do we're actually gonna get less than a thousand sorties
Listen, I mean that internal part. No, they are internal parts. Well, at least I'm a digest
But this must mean I'm disgusting
I
To make myself wealthy she's slowly dying from my
Oh
I came in at work quite tired and feisty wrote an entire world domination agenda on my calendar
Are we doing it? Are we taking down the big companies?
11 hour grinds that interests of thoughts are taking the wheel
Take the wheel
Man really?
Okay. Oh, I had to complete the start for that. Man runescape is really
Oh gee. Yes old-school runescape runescape 3 which is the new one. I think
Not really played that at all. I didn't actually understand
When it came out there was two different games
And I think I actually ended up playing runescape 3 for a little bit like a dummy
Because I was like, why is the game so different? Why did they do that?
and then
Or was it they made runescape 3 and then everyone was like oh go back and then they're like, okay
There's no two games
These are the golden hours. So this is the last batch. Uh, not quite. We've still got
50 minutes, I could have sworn it said 50 minutes 50 minutes ago, but
There's three. I thought there was like runescape 3 wasn't the new runescape called runescape 3
It's really ojisa
Get it because that's how I say ojii
Runescape 3 is the original server from that. It's mostly runescape is them
We've written the old game back. Oh, okay
Because they didn't world of warcraft do that as well. There's like an old world warcraft. Oh my god
My tongue is not even following what I'm telling it to do
Wow
You said three batches before this is what? No
Hmm
Oh almost just knocked over my cola everywhere. Gee willivers. I really should clean this
Oh, what happens if I feel not stop opening up the collection and stop eating the swordfish
We're gonna sell that we need that money
Okay, right 900 now
Wow
What
How big is an inventory for
8 12 16 20 24 28, okay
By the 28 that's like
four
for every hundred
Oh
Refling on time
Play both just where what did you see just play both it's not like this game is grinding or anything
Are you gonna disappoint us or not? I said I'm disappointed. I'm freaking doing it. I'm freaking
I'm cooking the
Swordfish I'm cooking my ancestors and my cousins and stuff because get it because I'm a cult
Are your refinements you're requesting
What
Are you
I think I'm losing the ability to read right now. I don't think you said that
Holy crap
As you're refling you're requesting me to go but okay, that looks more like english
Go to sleep. No you go to sleep
Go to sleep when
When something happens
Go I'm gonna I can do endurance stream. Literally. I don't want to lose my endurance title like two centimeters in of like playing the game
Wow
I'll only go to sleep if you come with me
Come with me. Oh, no, it's wrong one. It's that Japanese song
Stay with me
Don't have the rest of my clothes
I'll only sleep if you just
Yeah
Self hypnosis by exhaustion. This is working apparently. No
You've been streaming for 11 hours nobody's taking your endurance from your title from you
I'm just gonna eat this little cheeky little bit cheeky swordfish on a Sunday afternoon. I don't even know what day of the week is
You know what day of the week is stream day
I like it the beam all my way
Imagine if I could see me
Remember that time I got hired to sing
Right stop it. That's naughty
That's naughty. Okay. We're almost finished with the swordfish
You're beginning to feel very very sleepy
By your talking like a vampire
Stay with me
What are they even talking about honestly I feel like I'm eavesdropping
I wait for their new message to pop up and I'll start commentating on what the reef ones are talking about to each other
They'll never they'll never expect
Oh for goodness sake. I don't know how I keep doing that
Wow
Boom boom look at that nine third cheek. No
She collected again. Well, I'm not allowed to collect
It's because I'm a whammin my mistakes is I'm even in runescape. I'm sorry. That's not nice
You know, you just play the whammin card whenever you want. That's kind of funny though
I don't know why you're right-clicking it. I don't know. Maybe maybe I'll right-click you ring
Right click is funny
You collect here
Look into the mirror, you know
We're talking about time-spanning games
Is your rune crafting world still up? I remember the little rune crafting
I don't know what that means
But thank you for your question. The answer is probably no. Smile
I don't know anything about runescape
Good night throny and everyone. I'm gonna see
Rest well
I swear if anyone puts anything under 18 to that question your album
I'm gonna do it
Okay, we've got 45 minutes or something like that. Oh no, now we've got 50. No, we've got less than 50 minutes
We've got 49 minutes because the board breaks all of them
Wow
Should I write the girl's mirrors as a prank?
We could do that
You pretend to not be me and write the girl's mirrors
And say the most terrible stuff
Do it do extremely spicy one. Okay, who should we do for?
Mods, can I give you permission to speak so you give me the girl's links and I'll write some stuff and I'll wash my lips I shouldn't
Um
So I only mentioned things that only you would know the girls aren't gonna know who we're doing is zero. Oh my god. Okay
That's good
Big juicy chocolate
You are so beautiful
Your voice so beautiful
Your personality so beautiful
Beautiful
You are a blessing upon my
life and yet
You are the goddess who gives blessing
But I am already blessed
You didn't have to give them you didn't have to give me the blessing
God, I love your chocolate milkers
Good night, Azura
You are loved
Okay, this is already done
I like to keep my message private
Okay, okay, then we have done Azura
You'll never know it's me
More swordfish I demand more swordfish. Give me swordfish. Okay, we're done Azura. Who next? AC
Go to you no open up AC go to say
Wait, oh
You're so tanky
Oh my god, I'm gonna be an og sam
I'm a self identified og sam
and my god
You're so tanky
I want to care for you forever
I want to do what I can to make you happy little cub
I love that you call yourself cub
It's too adorable my old man
Og sam
heart
Can't take it as long as long as you're happy
I am happy little cub
be
Let me make
you happy with
With my with my og sam
Old man. Oh, no, you can't say that let me let me make you happy with
og sam spot
Okay, there we go
Oh
Okay, okay more swordfish
Who's next
I'd like to burn the swordfish, please
Uh Emmy. Oh, where'd I even begin?
I wish for you to perish me
Then laugh in my face as you raise me
back and forth this year
this year what is your
Your your powers your powers with your
powers
I want to be humid
Oh, you ate it. Oh god. She's gonna notice me because I can't spell how many
I want to be humiliated by you over and over
I want to see that
Shit
Shit eaten grin as I disappoint
You and take any punishment you just should
Love you whole sister
Like three
I need to send one to myself
I want to be with my sister
We've got mercy
Go to site
I can't wait for the day you break in and catch
me
watching
Another vtuber that isn't you. It's one big
mistake, of course, but you can't
help but
become feral
at the switch
Of a button. No, you can't help become feral at the site and completely
enraged
Before you know it we're
We're dancing we're dancing. No before you know it we're
We're well
I don't have clothes. I don't I don't have clothes clothes on in this
scenario
But you claim me as yours and
And it went and and we both had a good time. Thank you
I don't even think that's English
Okay, we're almost okay, sorry for school more surface
Okay, one more she be
Right she be
Um
Uh
Well, I was gonna say I'm going to bed
I'm so tired
She be
Mm-hmm
She's a bunny
Oh
I
Okay, we're done. I can't do it anymore
I don't I thought I got a good sleep
I think of all I think I'm done me flings. I can't take anymore
I'm sorry. Will you forgive me if I go to bed?
I need to sleep
You've done enough swordfish max and go to sleep a grand bit like that. Okay. Okay, we flings
I'm gonna
We flings I'm gonna
I'm gonna go and sleep
Um
Thank you very much for hanging out
If you're in a good giant test, would you send me lots of cake or whatever?
I
Good night. We flings. I'll see you tomorrow when I wake up
Good day, I'll dream I'll dream of us on the farm playing connect for and then I reach because I'm so bad
Bye
Oh
Okay, I'm gonna go sleep. Love you reef flings. I'll see you tomorrow
Bye
Go go see
Say hi mercy
Yes, merci modis
Goodbye mercy mercy
Good night. Bye reef fling. Love you
Bye
Yes, mercy time mercy