What's that? Hold on, hold on, you put the light on to the fucking tracking thing.
Ah, it's blinding! It's blinding, it's looking good.
Me? Hmm, why do I need to wear glasses? Also me, because blasted.
About, like, one minute late, she hates us.
You stop that. You naughty Nellie.
You naughty soft fans.
You naughty ballbags. Actually, don't say that word.
That's not, well, I mean, that's not the right word.
Uh...
Um...
Are we here? Hello? Hello? Hi! Hello, I'm Marika. Hiya! Hiya!
Oh my god, what's that? We get to do another full day of Assassin's Creed.
I get to, yeah, ease as much as I like.
Uh, I do want to say I am very thankful to PayPal support. Yay!
PayPal unblocked this.
Because if you didn't know, yesterday, you guys unanimously, at the same time,
supported, like, everyone with donos, and PayPal was like, halt, halt.
This account has been paused because what on earth are all these things?
And we literally had to go, oh, hello there PayPal.
Uh, we're streaming. Uh, we're beach homers. Please unblock.
So you can support my daughters.
Good morning. Good evening.
And most of all, good afternoon, Reflings.
Are you ready to fuck up your sleep pattern?
Do-do-do-do..
How are you?
And you did? It was Aisi looking after you?
Did anyone touch your tummy? Don't lie, Aisi's best design element is her tummy.
Her navel, if you didn't know a belly button is also a refer to as a navel.
I understand you can't hear the background music of Assassin's Creed Brotherhood right now, ask that meme-in.
I apologize for being a whole 60 seconds late.
Do you want to know why I'm 60 seconds late?
Because I was trying to arrange another Ace Markalab.
I've recorded one with Mimosa, I need to edit it.
I do not know how long today's stream is gonna be, so feel free to strap in.
If not, I'll be the one wearing the strap in this relationship.
That's terrible, absolutely terrible, just started.
But it's been fantastic.
I should hopefully not miss any freaking donations, like I did yesterday, because I was absolutely awful.
I just kept missing everything left and right.
Everything left and right.
Left and right.
Oh, that's not how I can read.
Okay, there we go.
Woo, five hours of sleep and eight hours of work, and we're so bad.
Oh, please rest, okay?
I can, I literally, I brushed my teeth, I had a shower.
Right, well I'll tell you something gross whilst we jump back into the action.
I'll tell you something nasty.
Why can I not hear my game?
Hello, headset?
Headset?
Headset, I know there's, hello?
Okay, I cannot hear any sound, and the game isn't coming out of my fucking desktop.
Are you fucking serious?
By the way, this game lives up to the test of time.
Are we being true?
Why is it not coming out of desktop?
Is this a fucking joke?
How could this have been so scuffed?
I can't hear the game either.
Okay, fantastic, fantastic.
No, seriously.
The tips link is messed up again.
Are you joking?
God, I'm so scuffed.
I am speechless on why the game is not playing through the desktop audio right now.
Ah, hold on, let me start clicking stuff and see what happens.
Okay, I need to start clicking stuff.
Why would the game not be detectable via the desktop audio?
I am totally not raging right now.
Let's check, let's check.
Right, okay, okay, okay, hold on, hold on, hold on, let me cook.
Rule one, if something doesn't work, close the game and open it again.
Because why would it not be detectable on desktop?
That's rule one of gaming.
So I've closed it, it's now closed, you can't see none of it.
Also, I listened back, I was watching a bit of my own brotherhood gameplay.
My voice actually doesn't sound that messed up,
but I can hear it and feel it myself how messed up it is.
Uh, yep, again, no audio.
If I have to go offline to troubleshoot this, I'm gonna be so mad.
Why? I didn't do anything.
This is, I, Mercy has literally made a short about this exact scenario.
I cannot make this up, Mercy has a short coming out later about this exact situation.
Um, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay.
Game, audio, output settings, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on.
Manage input devices, manage output devices, sound mixer, is it a sound mixer?
Input, yep, output, yep.
Why the frick, why the frick, frack, diddle-y-dack, tic-tac, pedi-wack?
Would this not be coming out?
I think I actually have to go offline to frickin' jumpshoot this.
I'm not even kidding.
I can't believe this. Are you joking?
Oh!
It only took me seven minutes to start the stream!
Oh, 49% total synchronization.
Oh, I guess we are doing 12 hours then, if I'm only at 49%.
Literally, Mercy made a short about this.
I cannot wait for the short to come out, so you guys can be like, oh my god, oh my god, she was right.
Um, if you are not up to scratch, please do not worry,
because we have successfully finished campaign mode.
We are currently playing Landlord Simulator 2 by all of the buildings at the moment.
We are now doing the kind of save quest-esque missions.
We are about to do a very sad mission for the Auditory family.
Auditory, me, I'm still here. Let's see, let's see, Auditory.
But gom, morning, good afternoon, good evening.
I hope, uh, oh, it's good.
I believe Asakul is the only other member live at this moment,
but as always, when another member goes live, I will force you to go insane to her stream.
Oh, okay, here we go.
I do not normally do this, so I'm not too familiar with what happens next.
Oh!
I think AC is going offline.
I see, in my old age. I did not know you had returned to Rome.
It's Leonardo. That's Leonardo's voice.
Hmm.
What's happening?
Etio seems to be remembering something. Something from 1506.
Desmond's heart rate is increasing. I'm administering a sedative.
No, the missing data may be there. The piece of Eden is useless until we have-
Oh, I don't remember much of this.
Let him continue. Yes, William.
Yes, William! Congrats if your name's William!
Any Williams and her?
Eh?
The Da Vinci?
Eh, Da Vinci- I'm sorry, I didn't mean that.
The Da Vinci disappearing.
Did you know?
Oh, I remember!
Leonardo!
Good friend.
I see.
I see you reading Super Chess at the moment.
You're- Wait, she got monetized?
She couldn't have. I didn't link that.
Sense accounts.
Do you mean Donation?
No, they were doing- I was gonna say.
None of us have monetized these.
Uh, I think one of my assassins came back for success. We're from a mission.
It's gonna be the Mona Lisa.
Acical!
My sleepy pee-
My sleepy acical.
How is strum?
I'm so sorry, AC. I never managed to catch any of the-
Snowberries!
Any snowberries?
Hi, snowberries!
We're currently talking to the historical icon, Leonardo Da Vinci.
He's a part of the campaign.
Get raided, get raided, get raided.
Get plopped, get plopped, get plopped.
Are you squidding me right now?
Thank you for the 20.
Bajinga. What the fuck?
There's no way that says Bajinga.
Did I read that right?
I read it in the top corner.
Thank you Bajinga for the-
What? You didn't even leave a message!
Why are you called Bajinga?
Oh, now I can't read chat.
Oh god, I'm so brain dead.
Hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on.
Bajinga.
Good morning.
I'm glad you like icicles.
It's the woman.
Did you see the guitar AC design for-
No, I didn't manage to catch her stream.
I was uploading everyone's Patreon audios.
I told you those guys were lucky.
Fortuna wishes she were as good as me.
John Jacomo.
I do not answer to that name.
Honestly, me is real.
Better, but not good enough.
Yes!
I'm good to go.
She designed one for everyone.
Oh, I need to watch that VOD then.
No, no, there's not new audios on Patreon.
Sorry, I scheduled up everyone's Patreon audios.
I'm really struggling to know how to tag though.
If you didn't know.
Of men.
You worship their misery?
No, mate.
I actually prefer holes and no poles.
Then he's swinging that way, but actually,
he's not an against a mate.
Wait, is this DLC?
Yeah, Pink's Hole.
It's not like main quest stuff.
This is like side stuff.
Okay, ready to kill.
No reactive model today?
Oh, I never put it on.
I've got this though.
That's if I make a joke, I can do that.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, combat.
Hold on, hold on.
Get the wee knife out.
Wee knife and let them attack you.
Oh, I can call them assassins.
So if I make a pun that I like,
I can literally do that.
Okay, the assassin's on the horse.
I'm happy.
Can you get off the horses?
Oh, that was brutal.
No, you can attack me then.
There we go.
Whoa, I missed that.
Okay, there we go.
Please God, do that as hilarious.
Yeah, so if I come up with a really good pun,
all you're going to hear is that all day long.
Casually kills a dozen people.
Apologize.
Any apologizers?
Man, let me burp.
No, sorry, let me raid the horse.
Jeez.
I didn't mean to say that.
Literally what I was about to do.
Why is he running?
Nothing.
I drink honey tea.
I have a lovely honey tea.
Just for me, some honey tea.
And a game full of nostalgia.
And I'll play and ramble all day.
So I can enjoy the game with you.
I'm not even, I don't know what the tone of the song is after that.
Come with me.
Yeah, there you go.
Wait, so what are you?
I am a cuttlefish.
I'm a siren and a cuttlefish.
But the problem with being a siren is I can't sing.
So I have to rely on my hypnotic abilities to steal the hearts of men
and then perish them in the war.
I did not make my lore, by the way.
But in terms of who's the most evil out of all of us in Vealor,
I'm pretty evil.
And then it goes Emmy, but Emmy isn't inherently evil.
She just really wants her brother back and she does stuff to entertain herself.
Okay.
What tea?
I drank some tea, so if I start hypnotizing it's because I'm drinking tea.
I would, oh you'd perish in my water willingly.
Follow me.
We are following, following the leader, the leader, the leader,
trailing behind the leader, going ahead of the leader,
the lead to lead to lead to lead to lead.
Oops, oops, oops.
I don't think I'm supposed to be at this section,
because they could spot me a mile away, but hey ho.
Somehow things work out in the end.
It speaks volumes about Vealor, but the most evil person is not the god of the fish.
No, Azura created you.
She's your literal mother.
She created humanity as we know it.
Like, so Azura is like the kindest.
Mercy's just misdirected, okay?
Mercy just, she just doesn't understand,
because she does genuinely love,
but sometimes that love results in your expiration date,
which is a shame, but she doesn't mean it, okay?
She's wholesome.
She's like a dorky yandere.
She lures your guard, and then before you know it,
the finishing act occurs.
And then, yeah.
Oh, we're learning about catacombs that we can go in.
Oh, this is the DLC called Leonardo's Diaries.
I just remember that literally eight right now.
I thought it was an auditory mission, but it's gone.
Um...
Taste my...
Oh, no, we're just...
For size?
Oh, I got a double A or something.
Rick, wait, I'm going to get a quick drink of my tea.
I apologize.
Don't let her deceive you.
It's all just part of her plan to lure us into her watery graves.
Oh my god, that was such a hard word to say.
Watery graves.
Yandere grapes.
Terrible.
Again.
We are jumping into the DLCs of Sasuke Brotherhood.
We've finished the main quest, and we are going to try and 100% this bad boy.
Think I can do it?
I have no idea.
I did not look up what the tank mission is, so I'm getting scurred.
DLCs.
Ah, delicious.
Not...
You're true?
Honey is very good for avoiding illness.
But Antelba...
And take back cereal.
Sorry, that guy's talking at the same time, and it makes it hard to talk and think.
Whoa, E.I.
E.I. Burger.
I'm a beautiful fish.
Oh, we should watch that movie.
The song is like...
I'm a little little fish in the deep blue sea.
Somebody help me.
No help.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, I've gone too far.
I think I'm about to desync.
Oh, no, they're just walking past.
Okay.
Walking behind.
Out my way.
Oh, I'm on the floor.
No help.
Strongly evil intentions through Cain's axe.
Amy, Cain's intentions through evil.
Yeah, basically, Amy just wants her brother back.
And she Cain to has a bit of fun with the spells, really.
That's how she was concepted.
Oh, the Yoink Leonardo!
I do not know.
Katso.
What does he say?
I cannot read.
Leonardo.
Depente.
Depente?
He wants us to examine art.
I remember when Leonardo.
He was Leonardo.
Back.
The every lovey painting's hung in the gallery there.
What do they have to do at their temple?
You're the cuff, you're the cuss.
Oh, it's Edgy girlfriend.
Hey, thanks for doing the watch alone, baby.
God, I can be the cuss cull fish that ever did cull.
Hope you're doing well.
Thanks again for doing the watch alone.
I appreciate you winking at you right now.
You got three deal?
a three-deal? You wanna do ASMR together? You're slayed in on my Twitter DM? That's terrible.
That's absolutely terrible. Please do not feel put on the spot. And anyway, I'm just, I'm just
moving around. I'm such a fiend. I'm a little ASMR fiend. Right, we're gonna keep doing a Leonardo
situation. So, if you didn't get any of that plot, Leonardo has been yoinked and he discovered
some sort of advantageous thing that would, oh pardon me, excuse me, come through. Sorry,
reading chat. I was reading chat, excuse me, I was reading chat, excuse me sir. Have you
heard about this? Have you seen this about chat? Yeah? Oh my god. Slayed in right now.
Yeah, slayed in my DMs. And then I'll, I'll do the rest of the work, okay? I got you covered,
babykicks. Biba, biba an ASMR fiend, you know? Oh, Catherine, not Catherine, Christina's coming
up. Oh right, we'll do Christina. So basically, we stalked her home and then we got a kiss. So
surely this isn't gonna get weird any further? Reading chat, obviously, a mistake to do. I
know literally doing it like in a game is so hard. Let's strongly lead my pleasure. I remember that
it's, yeah, it was a bit, it was a bit sus. I have to admit it's ill. It was a bit sus. Now, we, the girls
can do it to you. That's fine. You know, that's fine. By the way, around Christina, we're in
Firenze. Assassin's Creed 2 is like Firenze. Oh, this is so sad. Oh, this is so sad.
Mm. In Assassin's Creed 2, your family get hung due to treachery. This, this is really sad. This,
I don't like this one. This is pretty freaking sad, honestly. Oh, I can't remember the past though.
Mm. This is very sad. So the girls, yeah, yeah, so we can do it to you, but you're not allowed to do it to us.
Come here, you fanny. Bunk. Oh, I missed, I missed. That was really embarrassing, actually.
Imagine someone coming to punch. Oh, I did it again. I'm like punching the air. This
can't be one air that's going on with him.
Assassin's Creed 2 is actually very beautiful, considering how old it is.
Mm. I don't want to speak because I don't know, for a fact. This might genuinely be the imported
map from Assassin's Creed 2. Where the heck am I trying to go? Swinging at his family.
Sorry. To be honest, it was, it's his first day. Yeah, his first day, as you know.
What do you do? Only one thing to do. Kill them. No, don't do that. They did nothing wrong.
They follow orders unquestioning me. That makes... Unquestioning me. That's a very hard word.
I'll sneak behind their backs. That's a big word for scrawny.
Time if I have to. Carry them down to the river. Be careful.
Right, if I remember correctly, I can just do this. And there's one patrolling guard
that will desync you if you're not. Oh, he's up there. I can see him.
Oh, this is so sad. This is literally the bodies of my freaking family.
Oh, I've desynced already. Wait, am I not to kill these people?
Wait, did I desync if I kill them, Chris? Without killing any... Right, how did I do that?
Uh... Wait, he perished because he went in the water. Right, come in the water. Come in the water.
And you come. Come into the water. Come on. Good boy. Be a good boy. Into the water. Wee!
You love water, don't you? You love it. Into the water. Come on. Come on. He's a good boy.
He's a good boy that wants to come in the water. Yes! No! Jump in the water. Jump in the water.
Jump in the water. Come on. Oh, wait. Can I knock him out? Does it count if I knock you out?
Let me knock you out. Boom! Get in the water. Yeah, good boy. Get in the water.
Right, in the water. In the water. You too. You're next. In the water. Don't be throwing rocks at
me. That's no nice. Ha ha! Ha ha! Get pulled. Get pulled. In the water. Go! Good boy. In the
water. You go. Okay, we did it. We did it. Okay, now back to the sad part. This is my big brother.
And, yeah. This, honestly, it's pretty messed up. All things considered.
Poppy down there. Oh, his body just kind of ragdoll and...
It's so leaving their deaths to fate once again, probably. Oh, no. This was your wee brother.
It was actually so freaking sad in Assassin's Creed 2. So your mother, Maria,
she doesn't talk until you collect a hundred feathers because Pietro, the wee little brother,
was collecting feathers. And once you collect all 100 feathers, she finally speaks her first words
after the death of everyone. And it's just like such a freaking sad thing, genuinely. And then this
is your dad. Oh, it was so sad. Literally so freaking sad. Yeah, the feather quest. That's why
there's 10 feathers in this game. I guess it's a memoria. I have to leave the city. Christina, I
want you to come with me.
I want to. But I can't. My family.
So you can always be together, Christina.
It's you.
Actually so sad.
She doesn't... She doesn't come with those.
And Christina's ex, he was like true love. And then so sad. She's feeding corpses to the fishes.
That's true.
And there was no in-game map for the feathers. Do you want to hear the worst part about the
feather quest in Assassin's Creed 2? So my Xbox was in a different room from where the computer
was in my house. So I would have to scurry to the living room and memorize a location of a feather
and then scurry back through to my Xbox as a child. I was doing this back and forth.
My mum was like, what on earth are you doing, Strony? I'm getting worried about you.
And I was like, it's the feathers! The feathers, mum! The feathers! I need the feathers!
What do you need the feathers for? I was like scurrying back and forth.
And I did it once. I've never done it again. But we'll probably try and do it when we play AC 2.
Which is our DLC.
Allegedly, so the way I memorize things, I don't have a very good brain.
So I had to open my eyes really wide and order. Oh, it's the crit sale.
Wow. So after Chesery's date with fate, the crit sale got married off.
And Chanel lives on the countryside and hiding.
But yeah, I used to like have to, in order to memorize stuff, I had to open my eyes really
wide, which I know seems bizarre, but it's the only way I could do it. I just had to go like,
and then like I wouldn't blink and then I'd run to the Xbox and like where the location was.
It sounds really dumb now that I'm saying it out loud, but it was the only way I could do it.
Like the like phones weren't like, well, I didn't have a phone.
Because I was a child and like, yeah, phones weren't like that.
This is really dangerous because I actually don't know which way. Okay, okay, that was lucky.
Eyes wide must take all information. I was literally like, sorry, can't speak. Don't talk to me.
And then I'd get another feather and then come back through and look at the next one.
And if you like pick up feathers on the way, actually being set a bit harder.
There are guards everywhere. La Crescia is, is that just a straight jump? I think so. Okay.
You don't hear a grown man fall into here. Literally, oh my back.
Yeah, you don't remember which feathers you pick up along the way. So it makes it even harder
because if you go to the area you think it, it was that, um, sorry, I got nervous. I'm about to go
the wrong way.
You're stuck on that side. No one will hear you. Are you ready? No. Stay where you are.
Let me through. You must wait until the Tukesa allows you to pass.
I can reach that, jeez. Another wind. Skyrim logic must be the best logic.
Sorry, is there, I think, no, there can't be flags on the DLC. That's not allowed. Whoa.
So that camera angle change, sheesh.
Although I will say one thing about this DLC, this is so satisfying because, um,
you really won't get caught by the guards doing this. You can literally parkour your way through
it and the guards don't actually catch you, which I see is very satisfying gameplay wise.
What a satisfying yes.
Um, I do like the idea of, like, it so being able to, like, completely sneak undetected
without the fear of being detected.
Oh my god. Uh, I have terrible news, I need to pee already. Um, yeah, like, see, I love this.
This is, like, so satisfying. Like, I'm just quietly sneaking around.
Ooh. We're in the gardens of whatever that goddess name is and I've already forgotten
what the garden's called.
Okay, this is the bit where you can lose, I think.
Right, you can't climb the hedge, I guess.
Okay, okay.
As if they don't hear me fucking...
What was that supposed to do? I have no idea. Oh, I just went for it. Oops.
They are so dead. Oh, the cret. Honestly, this outfit, they're gonna...
Benesons.
Gentle.
Benesons Veechever?
History Veechever?
I'll redecorate that win.
Plop, plop, plop, plop, plop!
I'm sorry.
She is home. Yeah, do you like her haze?
Go, we are really a ladies, man.
And one for someone who was special to me, Patrizio. He spends his time near Ilvatica.
I'm not gonna lie, Riflin, if you did that to me yet, Mel.
I'll give it to you soon. Give it to me.
Guards!
Place the Vinci's Annunciation in a cart. Leave it outside the walls.
No.
Oh, lo bene. Now, close your eyes.
I don't remember what's happening.
There's no way. We killed her brother and...
No, we won the scene.
Oh. Oh, see, all you had to do was put your pole in the hole and now the guards are on.
So it was that simple. Come on.
You heard that doctor at the start. There's a cure for syphilis.
Oh, I don't know where to go.
Take up the stairs.
This is the most logical reason because why would you put the stairs at 12 o'clock?
Oh, I don't know where to go.
And there's a timer.
There's so many guards, so many guards inside.
We go back inside.
Ah, okay, okay, okay, okay.
Let me go, let me go, let me go.
Okay, across, across the chandelier.
Unfortunate.
Door locked down.
Okay, okay, okay.
Ey yo, ey yo, ey yo.
Sorry, I cannot reach out. I'm getting stressed.
This is a freaking time hard.
Okay, and then wee.
And then run across, run across, run across.
Oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah.
Okay, we can do it, we can do it.
Come on, I say, come on, I say.
Don't be scared.
Oh, sorry, I didn't mean to whistle that.
I just whistled because I was breathing like with a small mouth.
My pardon, my pardon, your pardon, I beg.
I don't say my pardon, you beg.
But you don't need to ask me.
Oh, did we do it?
Oh, was that it?
I was actually really quick.
What?
One out of five pins.
Okay, we nailed that.
We nailed that.
We absolutely nailed that.
Who's pardon now?
That was, that was scary.
But we did it.
Only one minute and 57 seconds is fair.
Okay, that went so well.
Honestly, can you distract on a horse?
Can you distract with me?
Whoo, yeah, you can.
Wait, whoa, whoa, whoa, camera angle, camera angle.
Relax, relax.
Ooh, wait, I'm funny.
Um, this is terrible, but can I go for a pee already?
I need to tinkle my winkle.
Please get up and stretch and get a thingy.
I actually generally do pee.
So sorry.
It's like so quick into the screen, but I just noticed it.
And now I'm like, huh.
Okay, I'll be, I'll literally be a minute.
Okay, stretch your legs and get a war.
I'm going to get, oh, I have a war already.
Actually, I don't need any more.
I'll be, I'll be two minutes.
Okay, I, oh, I just smashed your neck.
Take off if you heard that.
Ta-da.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa,
I'm so sorry to do a pee break so quick into shame normally I'm more organized I do apologize
I was a bit scared brains this morning I like put up so she be she be as much as we
meme about she be's concept art of like her looking like a horse she is a workhorse she's
already got like two months of uh audios like scheduled up and I was like dealing with all
that so I'm taking pink killers tummy heart unironically
and then I had to record I kid you know I recorded like a really quick ASMR audio
like two minutes before stream where do we post art on Twitter
I'm okay I'm just taking some more I still think I can like 100% this game um
unfortunately oh right okay let's see what we're working with here we've got 30,000
so really not to invest in the landmark at the moment we'll keep doing the Leonardo DLC
I will say one thing about the DLC was it worth the money like back in the day when it came out
where the heck am I supposed to go I'm like all over the water
you know also be apologizing for burping I feel so bad about people who like can't stand burping
it's just innate like if you've been like kind of raised that like you know burping manners like
obviously in like in person like if we ever do like a convention or whatever I'm not gonna burp
in your open mouth but like I am just quite comfy burping on stream like I'd rather not like do a
throat burp because it's like uncomfortable I don't know we're getting into the physics why not no
you're not gonna ask me to like intake like give me fizzy juice at a convention I mean please
strawnee please uh burping my mouth burping my mouth strawnee
but please no you guys are actually saying please but my burps always taste like whatever I've eaten
would I have to probably eat something that you guys like on purpose like fried chicken and chips
so like my burps are extra yummy that's disgusting I am so sorry
yes please burp on me
garlic oh you want garlic you mean to have garlic for it
excuse me I need how you say checkpoint
can you burp back no you're not allowed to burp on me only on the analyzer
are you Irish or Scottish pick one I genuinely want you to pick what do you think I am Irish or Scottish
what am I supposed to do oh it's a tailing mission
don't spoil it
don't spoil it let the gate Irish close but no cigar I am Scottish this is what Irish is
in the name of the dear father we're gathered here today and the name of the father the
son in the holy spirit we're playing it too old oried after and we're enjoying our game
I actually don't know if I'm going to do sink if I get caught by these guys what am I supposed to
do am I getting caught I don't am I supposed to kill them
what the heck is going on oh what's going on I'm so confused why aren't they attacking me are they
scared of me I'm tailing I'm tailing we will be glad to add it to our collection
as agreed I got you a fresh and cool I'm British please she thought I would be pleased with such
a gift after she married another man you're alert literally every enemy was looking at me and nothing
happened okay both may be brought into harmony doubtless I think I thought you were going too far
literally I don't know if that was just like straight up like streamer buff or something
is there a group ahead other than that group there I feel like they're about to stop and
turn around so I'm a hide in here
oh they're behind guards hmm can I climb that oh it's a three-story building though
oh
oh whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa I'm sorry I'm sorry oh don't use the rooftops I'm sorry
how is that what is going on with this mission why isn't everyone like so unresponsive to me
I'm genuinely like huh what is the game like being nice to me uh take this oh I wasn't to be
detected okay I was literally gonna smoke bomb them and walk past them oops okay I'm not to be
detected yet everyone is refusing to detect me what okay and I've already failed it
yeah so I can go on the rooftop right I'm not to be detected okay so I'll go around this part of the
oh am I gonna run out of time because I can't see them out my way no
that was smoke bombed yourself out of a whole mission literally abracadabra desynced
I cast evasion and I completely I roll the one how is this how is this such a
rather confusing mission I have to admit
I assume he's gonna come out here so I'm not gonna I just want to look at him so I don't
oh it's a bit too close for comfort I'm a lady I like shopping I like getting my nails done
makeup makeup makeup boys boys that's terrible I'm allowed to make these jokes though
what's going on Sam Vezins come with me
why is he coming backwards wait is he coming this way
no no he's not coming this way jeez la wait
drinks a lot of wine you're scaring me so don't get detected
oh you're so talented reeflings looky go look at that flexibility
you'll never guess what I can do with that
I cast itchy boons oh that's a nasty one
was that a little
brick
oh a little britain riff sorry what little brit I've already forgotten what I said
gon be on his truth you're gonna need to like sub quote everything because I always forget
what else I say okay okay oh I knew you were gonna turn around that's right I got that I got that
eagle sense yeah okay he's going he's going oh no okay okay okay okay let me cook one quick
let me get up this is like very close I wonder if they're gonna turn them around again like they
did earlier in that section because I'm getting nervous I do not remember playing the DLC much
pardon me excuse me oh we did it success though cast your boys sticking together
you will complete the sale of course run a nose that woman used false passion to
suppose the error lies in her Spanish blood I know it such untruth you so casually utter based
on little more than a name these countries these groups make such easy targets for the lazy
and ignorant you should tell her that the high and mighty duquesa putana I have changed my mind
that painting does not deserve to belong to anyone
I take the painting and examine it for clues be careful human hands aided by a fierce intelligence
made that treat it with respect go he casted London experience
no I'm not really good at run mission oh I'm to destroy him
refillings destroy that man
what he's so fast how am I desyncing
he's literally faster than the speed that I can run at I'm not sure why the game is telling me
careful you're desyncing yeah get arrow stormed get arrow stormed you deserve it you stinky stink
leave the Vatican district okay working on it's ill there was a poll there that you could have
grabbed to save the health of your ankles I'm not going to take responsibility for you being sore
because that was point blank it's ill that was point blank no excuse
I'm trying to escape this district it puts you like all the way into a certain section of the
map and then it's like oh by the way go all the way out of the section
and out and out shake all about you do the hockey pokey and you run around and that's what's all about
hey that's green let's start wasn't even I'm seeing viewer from your pentas have you
drawn your pentas a little too much the funniest thing I got a few maros I wouldn't say anyone was
like disgruntled I think they were surprised so out of all the four audios for sheebie three of them
are her in control and one of them is her not in the controlling position guess which one you
all voted well the majority voted for the one who was me and then I've got a few messages and I'm
like ah please I kind of maybe need to explain it a bit better and we are working on making graphics
so you know what content is coming up and it just takes time like we're we're settling into everything
and obviously Emmy got a warning recently and sheebie's lower video got 18 plus so I think
we're actually debating about deleting it to try and ensure she gets monetization I would be
mortified for the girls if they didn't get like they were rejected from youtube monetization because
of me because member the girls didn't pick their designs and I would feel like so upset like don't
get me wrong there's still stream elements there's still patreon there's still like tips on stream in
general which is perfectly fine um heck I'm not supposed to go but I would like be mortified if
like they had to wait an entire month for monetization streams all because like I didn't think I had to
get a toggle to like cover up the cleavage
hmm
what do you normally need to do to get monetized 500 subscribers and 3000 watch hours but your
channel can still be rejected um which is understandable like they need to go through the
content but like um hoping you know all things considered like if the girls are sitting doing
like game streams and all of that it's just another like yeah they're just gamers pass it on like
obviously before we could launch I could only spell out so much like don't be silly of course
like the girls aren't gonna be wait am I not to be detected I don't don't detect me I'm scared
get in here
who dares approach the bail of hey right we're just gonna go for it because there's no need to
assume we can just run right those guys are bugged out because that guy I literally couldn't
give a left a boot crack oh I'm gonna hurt my ankles thank goodness we have the armor because yeah
I'm just gonna run for the objective there's no point in to stopping and fight because it's
one of those ones where they just keep spawning in more guys and it's just a waste of time
we're trying to 100% this I say that as if we don't have to like redo all of this again probably
to get 100% I actually don't know what oh no 100% was don't be detected or something that's impossible
if they're gonna just constantly spam enemies may I sit on the bench please
it's him he was rude to Claudia come back down to the harbor when I return to Roma I will show you
the inside of my is he he's the bad guy from clothing instead of beautiful he used to harass
Claudia our sister good job that's a thing look around we hate to joke yeah he insulted
Chloe I am warning you well we are only talking are we not I see this place has worked its magic
on your system down all right she did not want to open her legs in Firenze but now she is the madame
of Roma
cut so why are you just standing there eat him no
good luck dude too you're gonna regret this buddy but that does not mean
they will take you back
he counters me you know what time it is later we're gonna remove his ability to have children
I cast no children I cast no lineage I cast no bloodline
I cast the end of your your family name
take this this is for Claudia
get back here
he insulted my sister get back here did you I'm not done with you but you can get it
ah
take this
give me those balls
a Templar Templar identified lineage deceased Timstones erased
women forbidden to marry it ends here for you buddy
the history books burned and most of all
the secular torches
nice try did you not today
terrible absolutely you hired these people you should try and get refund buddy
I have nothing to call please ignore me
oh he ran away oh I can't see the tree you're in the way tree
no I know
not had enough
yeah that's right mm-hmm insult my family will you yeah yeah that's what you get
you are going to shut your mouth and give me what I want the Frida Vinci paintings one is on the
boat the other two were sold to a gardener he is displaying them for high-ranking members
of the church how do I get in how should I know go ask your whore of a sister I am sure she has
slept with a couple of gardeners
ah
oh yeah oh yeah yeah that's what you get you know what I'm also feeding you to the fishes while we're at it
who's targeting me someone's targeting me right how do I feed you to the fishes
okay to speak things up I'll just jump down here excuse me ladies got some business to attend
to an ever insult my hard-working sister she is the madame of a brothel and high ranking
enjoy sleeping with the fishes
oh it's disgusting you will not insult the auditories
am I not to be detected well this is given don't be detected
oh wait don't be detected just feel synchronized
do I kill them one by one
right in my mouth
do I kill them one by one come back here come here come here
come here right there's two of them so I don't think I can do it right next to him
I mean there's we can almost come back and redo this mission
you can just
can I just arrow storm them I can't
okay so there's literally one more pair okay I didn't realize I could use our
storm for that no no go down please I'm just gonna make sure um the I think I'll just send
an assassin on this guy because I don't want to mess up if I can get a hundred percent right off the
bottom you know you won't wait it's already filled because I feel the earlier okay I must
already feel because I feel the earlier okay there we go yeah okay it's fine it's fine
my apologies he made a little oopsie whoopsie the pink you can already feel oops I didn't
realize it was like one big continuum nice my bad I gotta apologize for that one
ooh okay we'll definitely have to redo that one out later time but that's okay
we're getting close to finishing the
why would anyone carry armor like that
right now wow wait did I thanks I appreciate it a 500 uh 500 flora and uh bribery is actually a
lot of money you could like buy a lot back and then things really
I swear I could fish due to you out just to punch him again
literally an assassin's creed too he was absolutely horrible to Claudia so I'm glad they
brought him back but I didn't expect oh that happens every time I launch off the boat um I
never expect to what are you hello what
what
what was that
what was a jester why was a jester attacking me is this like a secret thing
kill jester well I did kill jester but
jet multiplayer character possibly I don't think I've ever seen that before
Elden Ring mentioned
mm he literally as I thought he was going to be like a fight fight but I just swung once and he
was gone we can't really continue the game if we kill kill jester sorry traveler we cannot
progress if we kill him don't just start okay the jester is killed you cannot progress
I literally just slapped him and he spun into the water hello my lady
bonjour hydration check
so is this before she's an assassin
do not lie to me all right no this is after
I need to get inside the private showing of the Vinci paintings there is a viewing at the castel
st. angelo later today you don't need an invitation fortunately I know where you can procure one
it would give you access to the lower floors only cardinals are not hired I know I could count on you
see see we love claudia
do not let guards discover any dead bodies inside the restricted area these are I'm starting to get
worried about me 100% in this game I'm getting nervous I'm getting a little shaky what have I
gotten myself into now I'm confident in like playing the game in general 100% in it I have to
admit my confidence levels are diminishing the further into the game we get because it's starting
to get pretty like the ones where it was like don't take damage fine I can do that please leave me
alone no they're so aggressive watch out if they pass with their camera and their glasses
and they can't keep a lid the Vinci says
I hope it's not get caught oh I've gotten sheepen
right you guys can all attack each other ah smoke bomb whoa that was cool
uh I don't want to stab him oh I am to talk to this pretty lady hello lady I would like to talk to
you hi darling you must believe she for promised me over here we believe that you can beat this
oh you believe in me oh I'm getting nervous I'm getting shaky
I'll try my best I mean it's not like we've like hashtag failed or anything
in all honesty right don't let our guards see a dead body so if I kill everyone
can I be detect oh it can't be to take you oh I always did it I'm like I did okay don't let
a guard see a dead body oops
right okay let's try that again so guard no detect oh
I'll try it but I feel like this is most likely a try hard replay section
because yeah his dead body's like literally ready to drop unless I'm gonna drop in the water
oh no right we're gonna put it in the
okay let's try that again uh we did get caught red handed holding a dead body okay one more time
one more time one more time for the back hit him from the baby
come on I can't believe it after one-twelfth a recession I'm washed up I can't be right
you perish first and then you're next because you spotted me
whoa you climb fast please don't okay oh come right we'll come back to it children me first
if I do not successfully do a double air assassination that's not gonna work
I can do this
but did it get the guard it did get that guy down there okay we're safe we're safe
ah
tiny spiny hey strony I'm off to working I'll be back in a few hours hope to catch more
later good luck with the game thank you so much enjoy your work and thank you for the tip
I yanked the tip did you guys hear that notification I never really heard it much in
sentence but as long as you guys can hear the invitation is not here oh I've been stood up
I will deliver it to seniority not another chase no more are you squid me right now
bro the finalized voice line that I used was horrific and there was one before on that are
you squid me right now and I was so monotone like I was like are you squid me right now I was
terrible absolutely horrific am I supposed to just grab him I'm not to kill him I'm to grab him
grab grab grab no you're wasting time it's you wouldn't be real for but out of my way yeah
bams out of my way out of my way no yeah they wonder the target was lost I was busy getting
blocked by everyone oh my god I'm a terrible brotherhood player okay I should reclaim right
let's try that again and let's not grab random citizens right we're locked in right so mm-hmm
right okay people are in the way that people are in the way but that's understandable
hashtag jump oh come on am I allowed to just send the recruits on them there's no
and I'm gonna lose them again I'm out of time I'm running out of time gotta go gotta go gotta go gotta
go I know I know I know I know what am I supposed to do
wonder if you parkour across the water at the start I also thought that we'll do it we'll do it
we'll do it we'll do it we'll do it we'll do it we'll do it we'll do it we'll do it we can't do it
there's nothing to parkour off of
please work with me it's you it's you stop jumping on people please
am I allowed to kill him I know he has a yellow symbol but it's you I'm not even chasing him
across the bridge like what's the point it's you I've never struggled with this
it's you guys are like wondering why I can't play like rage inducing games I just start screaming
I'm not sure anyone wants to listen to me scream and be miserable
I do have it as a donut on reward in case someone like really does want to
no no sorry arrow storm everyone's dying
he is literally coded to be faster than me he is literally coded to be faster than me
is this it is this where I'm supposed to do it on the freaking bridge right before the freaking
got it and I'm happy again because I got what I wanted
literally now don't just stand by the need to like chase mission stuff but
rub rub I I have zero faith I'm gonna be about 100% in this game
if that chase sequence included don't be caught by card
wait is it on the bridge I'm supposed to yeah it's on the bridge my apologies
bro are you are you sure you played this is get allegedly
complete 180 in temperament yeah like that's why I cannot play region just in games
because it's a miserable experience I do have one donut on reward is that but like you guys are
literally gonna hear me like miserable I'm gonna be monotone I'm gonna be mumbling swearing cursing
everything if you didn't arrow storm probably would no I got caught at that earlier like grab the
layer or you need to not get caught at any stage which is insane
it seems tackling random citizens basically when you see a refund me at cons just jumping on you
oh come back soon I hope
and just like that we sneak past
wait
hold on a minute I don't have to hide uh good evening evening I'm uh here to see the paintings I'm
can I run or do I get suspicious
uh evening evening how's it going yeah evening uh hello I too am a connoisseur
mm target locators target acquired oh this is a oh my apologies my apologies sorry I was just
oh no no no no no no no he's pushed me wait the people don't like how dare I have not seen an
annunciation from this angle before the composition suffers I feel the light of God is not proper
how am I supposed to mark it if I literally can't hide away
my apologies I was just so what was it hello
hello
how am I supposed to do anything if they're both looking am I going crazy
does he not like move at all
oh no
hello uh I'm so interested in this painting
hey boy okay wait what am I supposed to do
I'm hiding here
look I'm just really passionate about this one painting
they need to like get on me to do this
oh uh am I supposed to put no so I can't be detected but he pushes me off the painting
oh come on I'm having a stroke I know the good time try to figure out this what's going on
can I just strike them
I don't I don't have access to my
I'm like not being funny do I need to look up a tutorial or something
I assume if I do can I put money on the ground like a weirdo and then everyone looks at the money
oh excuse me I'm just a rich philanthropist oh excuse me oh no oh pardon me oh I'm just
coughing up money okay what on air oh excuse me a chew a chew no way that was it oh right
five is the smoke bomb I was like no way I go a chew and I can do it okay
okay guards shovels are the most op anime literally they're just actually like literally coughing up
money what am I supposed to do did they play test this use eagle vision okay I am I comprehend
okay mark the paintings without the guards I just stand here and wait for the guards to move
mm-hmm mm oh gorgeous look at the detail wait this isn't it
wait there's more are over here it moves every time
hi
a chew oh pardon me
I'm I'm being branded can can I get handheld moment chat help help any help
can you I'm trying to draw them like am I supposed to do it where he pushes me and then
a chew
right am I supposed to annoy him and then like bring him over here and then as he walks away
whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa don't touch me don't touch the goods man don't touch the goods
oh I'm just going oh you put me into the wait
I throw money in front of the guards so they're body blocking okay
okay you can try and poison them I do have access to poison darts hold on
because technically that's not killing them and I soon I get the checkpoint I'll poison
and then I'll get the checkpoint and then we'll take it from there okay okay we know
it is this time which is fine right the one guarding this one is this guy right
okay I'm sorry I'm sorry
excuse me pardon me excuse me come through
yes poison worked thank you refling poison worked oh my god oh my god checkpoint unlocked oh wow that
was so hard that was so hard genuinely I had no idea what to thank you for helping me
you guys fantastic that took me quite a hot second to progress
um enter the castello
how is it in the front entrance any front entrances are we back entrances online
no more hand holding no you're allowed to hold my hand because I actually don't bend it
I some streamers like really don't like it and I'm like but I'll miss things if I don't get help
oh okay okay how weird
um
this this this is the trade I have really no done this much
I do apologize so uh the the Leonardo missions and the DLC stuff yeah I not really had my time
okay please don't turn around please don't turn around please don't turn around
asking a lady for unprotected hand holding
are you allowed to do that in conventions I've seen like Japanese conventions
we're like
I fucked that up so badly
Jesus
we almost got caught
um I I've seen like the Japanese idol stuff where like you can just like straight up like
talk face to face with your idol and stuff and I think that's a really cute idea
there's an enemy up ahead so there's no way I can 100% this stuff without using ranged weapons
this isn't say hey hey like genuinely the same
fuck off
so any more enemies whoa whoa that's a big pain sheath oh
there's someone in here uh no no it's not true
escape without being detected okay why am I supposed to not be detected
there's two and a freaking guard up there uh hello
hello
see the killer
oh I can be detected okay it's fine I take it back tea I'm sorry I'm really dumb I don't know
when I'm not to be detected and to be detected pardon me coming through excuse me where did he
go the guy says because I'm still literally out here killing where am I just to leave the castle in
general I have no idea if we're looking north of the castle I need to go south of the castle I need
to go this way this is this is brutal I'm rubbish at the DLC honestly yeah I'm gonna yeah like
literally 96.96 I'll take that because uh yeah there's absolutely no way wait I'm still gonna be
outside the walls
if I claim to the top of that is it gonna take me outside the castle if I jump down
because I'm 99% sure you can claim the top of this so we're just gonna do it for the yule
me I'm the thief oh wait no I can't be detected silly me I'll just do that
jump it's okay well don't jump then fine let's just fight
we're going to jump off the top of the castello because I think it takes us out of bounds of the
actual area hello bye bye that thief me strongly not dying on sale oh boy
oh here I go killing again right oh wait hold on this isn't a jump point
I don't think is there I see a flag up here yeah I'm gonna be honest I don't really want to jump
into a bale of heat uh from this height is that a feather or a flag
the flag um I'm gonna be honest as oh that's the hay bale I'm supposed to jump into
the whoa this is a big map oh look there's the the thing and you can see the colosseum in the
background too honestly this map is humongous humongous wall do you remember that okay right
let's try this again I don't really want to be on the side of the castle but it's where it's taking me
so there's really more jump points oh it's the courtyard again okay okay we'll just go south
the humongous oh it was crazy humongous what what are you on about honestly
where the heck am I supposed to go to get out of this castle I'm so um like swapped about
I know there's a ledge okay I'll get down get down
it's left or right okay this way geez we got there in the end I am I've not woken up clearly
you know I think I might need to get a coal or something like I don't feel like I'm here right
now this is the most pathetic wait it made me go out of bounds only to tell me the map is right
the unfinished work by Leonardo portrays Saint Jerome in the Syrian desert where he
lived as a hermit why would anyone stop I don't need the lore and the paintings I need the map
can I have the map please map map map I need the oh wait it's straight ahead
oh oh it's because of the the bridge
you're really good at this game maybe yesterday yes but today rough very rough gameplay
I still don't think a man can jump 100 feet in at Hebele and be fine honestly
game please I don't care about your stinky pay I literally I do like that they genuinely put
like all that lore and I'm sure like others appreciate it but I'm so sorry I'm very like
I can't be there's only so much knowledge I can inhale no PewDiePie not the bridge
finished yesterday's Nike dealing before we say which is 4 p.m and it's kind of annoying
is Nike gacha I just know it's got pretty girls and people like the pretty girls
use your head more than your brain I'm literally like use your head how are we
gonna solve this problem to open the door yes you're right use my head I'll ram it against
the door until it breaks down that's that's how I am we are gonna hire because we are gonna try and
get the favor of everyone at some point so we're I'm gonna take that money at the bank because
your bank interest can actually get full and then you're kind of wasting that income free money
actually the Hebele should be as high as the jumping point to be safe to enter
I don't want to use my head okay last one of the Leonardo mission
not the war machine mission oh sorry I just need to click with the
I think there's like five for the court did you say get busy as distraction
it's the oh that's a bit on the nose don't you
now we need a did you know strong enough
I was like what some forgets a pitch fork in that he built
have you found anything nothing is there no no it's just nothing we're finding Leonardo
he's been taken we need him back think I'm done thinking these paintings are a blank slate
sorry the hammerhead call face well
can seal his research he frequently writes backwards
that's so he also experimented with inks including an ink that vanishes
because your ego says you can't see invisible ink can we that's you use your gift you know about
that too
oh uh discovered the location of the cat combs in under five minutes oh oh no wait interact
zoom oh shit oh shit for real for real oh for real for real oh oh uh uh uh
um okay okay look for something clues yeah mm-hmm oh yeah mm-hmm what am I looking for bro
hello oh okay drawings on the painting we were right scanning scanning scanning scanning
scanning scanning scanning as fast as I can found the northern scanning scanning scanning
oh we did it we did it okay I understand I understand this one has been searched entirely
five minutes five minutes five minutes let's go zoom scanning well just one already oh my god
actually so MLG pro scanning oh oh oh where's the others where's the others where's the others
use your eyes look alive look alive reeflings I need your eyeballs glued to the screen right now
scanning scanning oh was that one no I'm dumb I'm dumb I'm dumb do not scan do not scan
who is the missing put um rubbish at this honestly
okay okay uh huh uh huh okay we can start from the bottom
okay okay okay okay left right left right oh okay okay three more three more three more eyeballs
eyeballs get your eyeballs up where the head guard where's the other one hello oh geez why would you hate it
you did that on purpose oh this is my oh okay what can't be that one drawing here haha
oh what was that what was that a nice a nice no okay you're right
uh huh uh huh up and hey hey I'm actually just doing these one as well okay okay last one last one
five minute timer last one where is it why are you hating them from me oh it's a girl with a ferret
and it's schnozer it's emmy with her rat plural
wow wow wow wow so fast so fast so furious
we did it I found two drawings
checkpoint reached give me that hundred percent yum yum yum yum I have found all the images they seem to
fit together throw them already bring me paper and ink we get to find Leonardo and save him
where's nickel cage really is this how museums work scanning scanning scanning
it's not over oh no wait what about the burn paintings it's not over it is likely they missing parts
will not be needed care to bet on that yeah no I'm gonna have to use logic oh no I'll suck at this
ah okay uh okay possible outside right corner start with corners whenever you do a puzzle start
our corner oh north north corner we have a north corner let's go right north corner so you can't be a north
hold on where are you I don't know problem right you're a middle piece you're an outside piece
stick put the outsides on the outside I guess uh uh uh uh uh okay you have to be a bottom piece I guess
okay your corner piece oh there it's here I see I comprehend my apologies uh right you definitely
do not go there whoa whoa you fit you fit you fit that's good that's good that's good oh how about
you no no five-minute timer okay wait where's the corner pieces am I going crazy no some of the
pieces were lost in the villa fire uh what do you want me to do about that well you can't go there
you definitely don't leave the one there um oh but that could be a bottom corner could it
oh no wait how did I do that okay I comprehend why this is a five-minute like timer oh you definitely
don't go there actually do you fit there you do okay okay okay okay no maybe this
plausible deniability no no yes uh huh oh yeah uh huh oh yeah oh yeah maybe maybe here no no you
have to be an inside piece you can't be there uh huh oh yeah uh huh yeah wait am I just gonna do
in five minutes yes oh there's no way that was so good I'm so proud of myself I was like huh where's
the other corners because whenever you do a puzzle you're to start with the corners and the outside
pieces and then I read they're burned in a fire excuse me oh can't believe I did that I'm actually
so smart what the heck I deserve all the headpats and preys and a tummy stuffed full of who goes there
my dad apart yourself uh wait is the wait what where am I supposed to go am I supposed to go for you
no wow it's actually overlaps perfectly hi I'm back you uh we're currently rescuing
Leonardo da Vinci they have kidnapped him and we're taking him back he belongs to us okay one of us
one of us we're about to grab him I might get a cola oh we're going to a layer of
promulus I might get a cola as a reward for being so smart
there's no catfish but it's good to do yeah they're both cephalopods
oh you're gonna pet the cephalopod pet pet pet pet pet pet
okay we're definitely in cat combs
mm-hmm
um tang
it's been an hour 30 already what the heck I was about to be like oh shebe's gonna be on in an hour
I thought 30 minutes have gone by whoa that's scary how like potent you guys are holy crap that's scary
um I believe shebe comes online or she already online is she be online
uh or did she come online in 20 minutes
in 20 minutes okay a warning for
um the fan concept name was love bunnies but I don't know she
how dare you do such a thing to Leonardo you disgust me and I'll make it hurt
normally I am merciful that Leonardo is a dear friend of ours and you hurt him
I'll make sure your death is as long as painful
huh narrow thank you very much for the tip lot reward for having solved the puzzle no don't
give me money because I did a plate of video okay thank you though I appreciate it narrow
do reeflings have a mascot design absolutely did I not show you
with it I didn't show it on the debut you absolutely have a mascot design
I didn't show in debut together we will make mankind I've only made freaking wow yes you have a
mascot design you have a little love heart on your tentacles you have a nicotine patch on your head
oh my goodness I might go get that fail like right now when I go get that cooler
it may be on discord possibly convince our friend
to open the temple and usher in the golden age of mankind so I persuaded our friend by kicking him
or would you rather I used my knife on the contrary there is nothing I would like more than an amiable
solution help Leonardo see reason with the pedigree and unapar we will remake humanity together
not under my tree the revolution will begin without you
bring it I dare you I dare you straight bring no I'll strike heart in the fears of the man
how dare you hurt my friend Leonardo take this and this you're next don't grab me
don't touch me the goods aren't for free in this place
it's so fun watching them fall on by one this is what you get for hurting Leonardo
don't do it again I'll make you regret it yeah you better start panicking
oh yeah it's over you'll never guess what my dating job is killing people
you want to beg for your life now should have thought about that first before hurting Leonardo
you no no don't let them talk just right now me of knowledge one must choose to search for truth
forcing it on others accomplishes little these lost people
who are in kingdoms I would have ended their suffering I knew your element is warped we're
going down women you have fire feeling aggressive today
I will pay anything for your goods well they're free I keep saying I'm gonna make an audio I'm
gonna make an audio it's just so busy I'm a busy busy be come let us leave this come oh we can
sorry it's you not without reaching the final room of the temple you are hurt
Leonardo you have two black eyes right now you did not look good come on go to sleep Leonardo you
need to rest
oh
oh he looks so being off I hope he's okay why are we getting locked in we literally just
walking into our tomb I guess thank goodness I sent Massimo to look for my paintings he delayed
their progress significantly uh why is there a random treasure box I honestly don't need it
whoa I really don't recall much of this
the Pythagoreans behind the soul of the cracks in the earth like a beam of light
ignites fire which symbolizes knowledge
wow I'm going to say something controversial this reminds me of the blades um from Skyrim
quest when you enter their place
now before you're like brain rot gamer brain rot yes I know stone and leaves don't equal
level thing but I'm just saying my brain is tickled
that is cool
um
yes I know where to go uh the statue okay face statue okay okay the camera angle is
going to help us out that's what I like to see uh do we need a bit help she goes live in 13 minutes
I repeat not love bunnies because I'm pretty sure the name's being changed but uh she be
warning in 13 minutes two minutes working the blades do you mean the organization we all
kill because you don't do your boy for 30 her fans are called Haram wait for real for them
having like a Haram Haram a bunny boy thank you for cheering me on Leonardo
I'm gonna do it when it comes up
oh here I'm oh I said here I'm not Haram my apologies my apologies I hear them okay that's genius
a little bit to the left wait have I just gone down by oh no no I'm supposed to be here
it's pretty clever honestly I'm like you guys are named after Lord of the Rings the meaty half
why the half me
I do not know maybe it is because they give me courage we must continue onward
I suppose Salah is out having fun spending my ardent Florence
he is safe at home I am relieved about the Florence of course you do not need to lie to me
oh it still gives the blessing
I am Leonardo da Vinci at a loss for words that is a first
this room could you support
he is soupy now
the sound of wind
do you hear that the sound of wind
wow okay I said these DLCs maybe weren't worth that I don't know what their base price was but
wow
Leonardo just casually talking to us while we're literally doing like the
they just jump on the face oh yeah yeah I do
here rabbit aim
whoa that's really smart okay must have been the wind
now I can get back up here
wow
oh I didn't even I was like where the heck am I this camera angle is wild
uh oh it's so we're getting a bit dangerous here I'm not gonna lie I'm getting a bit nervous
I'm gonna be shamed
a little bit windy up here yes it is ah my tummy's rumbling oh I forgot to eat
I forgot
maybe we finished the wheel is turning you are channeling the air keep going
uh maybe we get cooler and I'll get my snacky wackies again and then that will refuel me
why it's getting laha
oh there's a bar right there I'm very struggled with the DLC I can't believe it where's where's
the yellow paint
what snack time snack time is the exact same as yesterday I am going to have I have one egg
today because I forgot to boil more eggs before stream so I have one egg left over
I will have two meat sticks and I will have pea snacks as well with a cola and water
um I don't think I'll make another tea I'm not really feeling like a tea right now
I had one before I did my very quick ASMR recording session I had one when I started stream so tea
maybe not right now wow I hope this is the right way I've just launched myself down there
without actually checking
strongy when was the last time you had vegetables I actually just struggled to eat vegetables
the problem with uh streaming long is I need snacks but on short stream days like I can make
myself an actual meal so don't worry about me I know I had takeaway yesterday I had my chicken
burger and my chickies I had um breakfast English tea I believe it's called oh she be eight minutes
harm harm hair and she be eight minutes kind of
uh but yeah for long day for long streams it's much
I am really struggling you can tell I've hardly played the DLCs my goodness
I was a bit blasted into the campaign but then the DLCs next to impossible
me flings and worrying is like people and breathing honestly whoa
oh that's cool
wait a minute didn't this not happen with the blades as well
that could help oh we know Skyrim came out in 2011
yes how enlightening very funny
oh jump cross sorry confused and it's like uh what do you want me to do me this is literally
a wall and I'm like a jump on it on a scale of zero to one how good of a cucumber
um for the foods that I like hundreds for the foods that you guys might like uh not so good
hey oh I thought I was having to jump on the fire there I was like this is really good
these sound effects are so different from regular assassin's feet as well
I am enchanted the music is different as well for the DLCs
I'm very much enjoying them how good am I King Ting uh I have an ear fryer
that means everything's so dead
etsy is currently setting up the most intricate game of the floor is lava honestly
I'm like really blown away right now like I keep saying to myself like this is such an old game
like it's it's 2010 like and all of this is in the game it's fantastic
fantastic fantastic
you can just pre-mix this for filming
oh
bejinga thank you for the tip go go bed now enjoy your
sleep thank you so much see you when you wake up
can you bake as well yeah I have my unity is achieved but the door is not opening my favorite
thing to bake is apple cinnamon muffin because I like apple cinnamon oh pardon me let me touch this
let me come in with the post
Leonardo come here
why don't keep the light source with us Leonardo yeah recognize these symbols
no wait these are the symbols that were shown to me by the apple
they're in the wrong order let me just stream when oh if I rearrange these if you want
I don't remember any of this this is so exciting
I like smiling like an idiot
wait
hey
is this the room
hmm
those are not Pythagorean symbols 43 39 19 and 75 27 42
W
I'm mesmerized the number is meaningless
you are leaving it's not for it's for Desmond
it's the the vault in Assassin's Creed 3 location for us
it's you what are you not telling me for Desmond well I have begun several dissection studies
oh my god it's for dance man as an engineer oh yes I'm oh my god I literally have tears in my eyes
that's so cool Salah you would model for it again of course then perhaps I will study a woman with
oh
when his body's all mangled it's where they take him
you can sedate Desmond now yes oh my god it all makes sense
yes and then you're broken in revelations
oh my god I get it I understand
that's right oh my god it's like all clicking like a like oh
oh oh my god that's so cool in revelations Desmond's broken you're stuck in the animus
and they can't take you out because you're so mangled
and Ezio understands that he's a vessel for Desmond to get information in present day it's
absolutely crazy
oh that's so cool
that's so cool oh spoilers yeah I'm sorry I'm just like I'm like re
like putting it all back in my head because I've played Brotherhood over and over and over
but I didn't always have access to the DLCs whenever I played them
and then it's all clicking in Assassin's Creed revelations you're mangled in the animus
and we had to go like in present day your dad William takes like Desmond's dad William takes him
to the thingy to that location because it's a safe haven and it's where one of the gods are like
the building things where and oh it's just so cool it's so cool
Desmond's stuck in the mangled in the animus
I have no idea who Desmond is but I'm happy you're happy so we're playing Ezio Desmond is his and
like blood lineage offspring and we use Desmond's DNA in present day to look back at Ezio in the past
Christina oh we just jump scared our oops
I only just send it back to financial
it's been two years
and I thought there'd be nothing but you oh but Ezio what is it I'm engaged to be married
my father kept asking me to choose I thought I would never see you again
it's Manfredo he's going to kill him what
he lost money he's dragged them out to the end of the bridge who the hell is Manfredo
no save Christina's fiance Manfredo from the freaking gamblers
I'll have a freaking minute no I'm just gonna let him perish so I can take Christina away with me
come on you've got anyone to hang a bit with look I've got 10k florns on my persons Christina you
just come with me let him perish to the gambas do not gamble do I kill oh I kill okay let's do it
oh I was going to have some money for you sorry mate but your time's up
wait I have assassin signals that's not right
thank you you don't know how oh no I'm so sorry what what are you doing do you love her
what do you love her Christina the woman you're about to marry yes I do hey I swear I do kill me
here and I will die still loving her you are never going to gamble again never the same you will be a
good husband to her oh why is this game so sad what the heck
I can't handle this
all right she's a wee bit of a slag but it's fine wait it feels really not going like I know
like he never ended up with her because of revelations but why is this game so sad why can't
it still have a freaking happy ending he tries so hard he's fine he'll make a good husband I made
oh
what
even Christina's confused
it's you you're supposed to take her away you're supposed to whisk her away
oh you're crying I've got tears in my eyes I'm just like can it see how one like happy end
and so I like I'm really invested in it so storyline I don't get it give this man catch
a freaking break is that the end of Christina's story I don't see a broken heart on the map
there is no way it ends there for Christina I don't see a broken heart on the map
that's it
that's freaking it
oh you can't do this to me you be soft come on
oh for folks it we're gonna have to do the plane I don't want war machines now
no happy ending for the best character literally like
there must have been more written I'm so sorry but I do not believe for a moment the
development team ended it there for Christina literally it's saving him from Gamba and going
do you love her do you love her and then that's it I do not believe one second the writers left
it there if there isn't more it must have been cut because I refuse I refuse I refuse
whoa what is a man to write all I know is
but it's you will have a hell of a happy ending I can't remember what happens at the end of
revolutions I really did not play it as much like I know he was sweet on a girl and then she got
kidnapped but that's not the true love Christina was
like ah
they saved it for the 20 bucks DLC honestly isn't that song miserable I have no idea
I just if it really never man tension to brag it was never man tension oh I can probably renovate
this aqueduct while I'm at it I'm like right next to it I mean I don't know I simply saw it it took
revelation I took the revelation look to this one he if you want the Christina should you just get
somebody's I feel sinking there's more wait what's her DNA sink 100 did it it was very low in the
battery on the bar right I'd oh total sink oh okay okay je comprende je comprende right we're
going to do Leonardo I think that brings up her total sink surely no it doesn't it didn't we were
like on fortnight right hold on hold on we're steamrolling this right in memory we only have
one thing we failed do not drop below a health score huh is this this one where they jumped me
out of nowhere from around the corner okay okay let's try again oh we got an achievement for that
did you ever okay we need 75 percent sick we need more I just felt like that was such a bizarre thing
to end on calm out the pain will end soon I think it's when the guys jumped I can't skip this
didn't know you could do all this in the sense of people here
and she be is alive by the way for anyone who would like to watch her modes you have permission
to speak momentarily all the music oh okay let's just play it all over again why not
so good so good
aroma yes or what is left of it since the borja came to power and the mausoleum unfortunately you
cannot sleep from here series of course from the top of that church yes but the stairs up well I
had to go by the Christina mission wouldn't show up in my game so you're welcome literally
first and only girl in the series I so doesn't lose literally okay
so someone said I didn't take the medicine like a dumb dumb dummy dumb dumb dumb dumb
jeez oh wow because I'm
okay I know I'm replaying it I didn't know it did it like this
doctor I like fully armored up fully healed up
uh okay I'll take it I'll take it
okay let's do this the totally hello mr. doctor may I please have oh my arm
salute I require medicine and you find a doctor you're 100 health mate
it's just speaking out literally he just needs a bit of attention honestly felt that
I needed a bit of attention I felt that over time
gracias four out of five doctors would suggest leeches but they have not proven effective
against such things however I can recommend several good colleagues around the city
do you need anything else no sir thank you very much for your help please
right checkpoint reached I've not
I think it was the guards uh the guards hit me remember when the guard hit me around that
corner I think this entire section is for that I don't have climbing gloves okay so I don't have
what abilities I don't have at that time
Chad doctor not prescribing leeches honestly
right
um
what's my opinion I was having to pee it was a game yeah
okay it must have been because they hit me around the corner when I wasn't expecting that
literally our storm would wait this yeah it was definitely because they hit me
we'll try and finish Christina or maybe we should do Leonardo
for well it would be nice to finish Christina but then we're having like backtrack all this way
right what weapons okay I do have my fast knife so hopefully none of them like
fly out of the corner and attack me because that was what happened the first time like they
started attacking me way before we even got to the gallow which is where it's supposed to start so
I'll definitely hold back a bit more to be cautious
like I didn't dislike Assassin's Creed 3 well
I wouldn't play it on stream though like I definitely wouldn't be like as excited and happy and all of
that and I really love how forgiving the counter controls are and brotherhood and revelations
I think it's roughly the same um but in Assassin's Creed 3 onwards they like change the controls
and I am definitely if it's not broke don't fix it and if you fixed it it has now made like gameplay
frustrating like I really strongly dislike when gameplay gets interrupted because of like
oopsie whoopsie you forgot to dodge this attack so now you're desynced and you have to repeat this
over and over and over again because we've changed the controls and we knew for a fact that the
controls on brotherhood were received so well because it's like our best well-received game
you know like that stuff just makes me perish all right we're still gonna stay back we're not
quite at the gallows yet but I don't want anyone reaching to attack me and I definitely have time
to react if I've kind of got this distance on them
sorry excuse me pardon me come through all right take your time actually I have smoke bombs I'm
wondering if that's probably the safest method maybe smoke bombing them if they turn on me
are we at the gallows yet I'm like getting scared I do not want to replay this if it's
literally gonna be like this strike from okay here is where they kicked off
I don't know if I should claim you know that
that's okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay
okay I have access to all my long range I am using it
please citizen do not walk in front of the crossbow bolt my goodness
oh wow this is did I just I don't know citizens please do not walk in front of the crossbow
okay there we go 100% yeah okay this is so much easier I did not realize we'd have access to the
older weapons for this stuff as well this will make it easy that guy had a death wish literally like
thank you for it's you did not kill civilians well because civilians certainly pop themselves off
right that's fine uh double oh we've got one missing from this one as well
don't be detected while reducing to a righty that's like super easy why have I failed these ones
fake game are clearly
uh right oh I need to do the whole thing over again
10 out of 10 reeflings recommend strutting for distressing
my door was this the game that had the terror defense no that was revelations
because you were super excited and borrowing them to a barrel thank you that man is a traitor
to our order your character design romancy of mesmer from subnautica is there NPCs in subnautica
I thought it was like you versus all deafish I'm not pleased
subnautica
but he is an assassin not a traitor you run into guards well oh that's right that's true that's true
the mesmer is a fish I'm a fish too I'm a photo fish oh I didn't sink my my cheeky iPhone
let me calibrate myself right now
ah okay I calibrated so now you can like really tell what I'm looking at yeah
okay we will rock you for one
it's a scary little fish that hypnotizes you stop it's actually okay maybe we will have to
play subnautica I didn't realize I was in the game
there are NPC messages okay that's great right how much ammo oh I need a restock ammo okay
I'm actually gonna do the the pouch upgrade so we can like hold a lot of stuff because the pouches
increase your ability to hold ammo like a lot more and it'll definitely help out in these
kind of rewind situations
wait you've never played subnautica I don't remember I think I've seen people play it which
is why I say like I don't remember playing it um I'm in my tummy's wumbling okay okay
after this one we go get food and fizzy juice
boom
wow that would hurt
we can play it together and stream as long as you guys hold my hands through subnautica
because I have no concept of what to do my son Claudio has been injured they are going to shoot him
not if I shoot first get the others because I'm a I'm a quick shot
I may not have an automatic but I'll I'll do it anyway oh whoa whoa what are you doing
yeah yeah yeah whoa they're like destroying him
stop why are you just accepting gunshots that oh okay we did it we did it quick I'd run the guards
can we hold hands anyway yeah I subnautica multiplayer imagine if you guys can come in and help me
oh we should have more games like that uh right don't get caught while reducing notoriety I'd like to
see you son oh my tummy's really yumbling whoa that was a good switcheroo words my stomach is really
rumbling okay as soon as I notice it all of a sudden it's a big problem but I don't notice it for
like hours on end are you sure you guys aren't the one hypnotizing me because I'm starting to feel
like it is going that way it's single player oh that sucks it would be so fun to play
there is a mod but I don't know if I need like whoa what's going on there's like three groups here
yo shouldn't be inter clashing the tree someone's taking the tree okay okay we're good we're good
we're good we're good yeah not suspicious at all no no
mutual hypnotizing
no I'm stuck okay and then we quickly run ahead and then we don't get detected whilst reducing our
notoriety can I just say shout out to the word notoriety you're so satisfying to see
no a rioting no a rioting good me good me good work good way there's subnautica and subnautica below
it would look into it and see which one you prefer subnautica is easy once you spawn in just swim
the deep part of the ocean okay I've had it oh I guess because I'm a cauliflower shed so straight
right don't be detected stinky stinky me got detected
okay there's no guards here so I'm sick hello goodbye is it literally this easy
yeah then go back to the thieves skill wow I suck at this game
but it's okay if I suck because you swallow it literally
oh there's a horse waiting on me get back to level okay
ready up bill say ready up giddy up giddy up what strange word giddy up
any giddy uppers
did you know the hip no tell you see on oh look around the eyes don't look in the eyes
look alert look in the eyes don't look around the eyes not around the eyes you're under
that was ridiculous that was funny hello love oh babe we did it how hungry I'm so hungry I could
eat oh right okay okay know what we saw but you have nothing to fear from Machiavelli
I am sure of it I'm a switch hey I have you to thank switch is probably the best
have a best thank you if you believe Machiavelli remains loyal to the order I trust you
so what is one of the girls dm'd me on discord if someone's freaking account just blown up
oh one of the girls sent me my wreathlings they linked me the wreathlings when I posted it
in chat like a dum dum uh right I can show you wreathlings
R E E F L I N U
and then let's pick the picture pretty pretty wreathling where the heck did I just save the
picture yeah there you are okay why is it on screen
look at my pretty pretty wreathlings look at you you're so adorable you're just like mommy
look look I scattered we both have our little tippy bits at the side
and look at your front facing tentacles if you look really close look there's a little
hit little heart but these are my wreathlings but Frank I will tweet this out because I'm a
dum dum I never tweeted it but you guys are adorable and you have a head nicotine patch
on your head because we're addicted to each other don't worry I've got one too hidden under my bangs
um but yeah this is you you have eight arms you might think you have eight legs but
actually we have eight arms a cephalopods
wait so are we wreathling or humans that you're hypnotizing so you can be a humanized version
of a wreathling so if you wanted to draw a human wreathling you'd technically have like a nicotine
patch on your head um type thing if you wanted to be humanized but this is what you are you're my
perfect little wreathling you're quite small I can't remember your official height and centimeters
but you're a small baby you're a small baby um your size is pretty accurate to the loading screen
um you can fit on my head and you can um like fit under my armpit or in between my butt cheeks
and I can caress and love on you all I want and your arms your front two arms you can make them
nice and long if you need to for whatever nefarious acts we might be doing together but you're you are
very you can be very big if you want to be yeah this is you I will tweet it out after the stream
because I can't believe I was a silly billion forgot to show you what you looked like on debut
I knew I was missing something over here honestly but that's oh you're so cute and look at you getting
all angry like me oh this is such a cute face you're like mommee mommee it's been four days
okay we finished this mission and then I'm gonna get my tummy's a rumbling
now that you and I are working together I would like to know what you think
reef flings and a man equals you unless I miss something sometimes all the guy
needs to feel cute in his subtleties a little simple applaud that looks like him wait the
quest is still going talk to the architect oh wait we'll finish this no stop summoning the
horse we did that last time as well mommee gift me i'm bruh actually do you know that really funny
Japanese meme where that guy looks like oh he's perishing and then the girl's like
smiling and all smug I want to do that and then like I've got i'm bruh on the side to like perky
up again there's like so many memes I want to make of us together it's gonna be so fun I cannot wait
to do my donathan like I don't obviously donathons are really good for like like making money back
or whatever if you want to see it like that but like I'm like yeah I want to commission this artwork
and then this artwork of this and then a meme of this and then us together in this scenario
and then this plot like this is amazing and like make this audio and do this
wait do you mean the guy in bed like drained and thin like the girl looks smug and I think
there's a rapper in that meme and she looks so smug and he's like oh and death looking like he's
been trained more
okay it's done
strongy she well strongy wearing one of sheebie's tops using two reflins to fill the gap
oh true true okay that was really good to get we're actually gonna go get more
ammunition for these uh so far we're actually not doing bad for the 100 run don't want to
drink to it but you know uh there are so many anime there are so many anime edits to
she's doing peace sign oh is there there's more of it oh I just saved my uncle so much
damage there I am gonna go get some food I'm gonna try and go to the bank wait why the bank
money for something
money for pouches so we can have more ammo I remember go there in the end should be
okay
guy tired after meme yeah we are in the
1498 or something like that right on the cusp oh do you have ammo in here or is it the other
place that has ammo it's you that has oh wait we know I should buy the pouches first and then go
buy the ammo yes that is a smart decision please do that I will get on you oh uh one of the
challenges are to grab a guard are you proud to wear those colors no into the scaffolding
your twat bag grab him into the scaffolding there we go that's what we needed okay there we go
one of the mission things is to do that right okay we need pouches my
I'm very slow right what right what do we want for medium quiver
oh
and then I guess just all of this
okay and then heavy complete a shop quest
okay whatever whatever I don't know what that meant I don't really know what the shop
quest meant but that's okay I don't have to know everything right I'm munition yeah give me all
the knives give me all the billets give me all the crossbow bolts and then we are stacked for uh
wait is assassin speed 2 that had the bug that made archer spawn indefinitely yeah that was assassin
speed 2 there is like a really major clock about it good night rest well thank you for hanging see
you when you wake up I'm kidding I don't know how long we're going for today oh we've got like
tons of level names okay I completely forgot we had done that
okay whoa whoa whoa we need like yeah we need like heavy hitting contracts because we're getting
to the point now where like I'm needing you guys to like level up and take these ones with you
yeah I do that wow it's only 22% rate whoa I'm smiling want to do that take you two together to get
level up my internet just died hello hello are you guys there did I just disconnect
hi we're checking you here okay my OBS literally just said disconnected
monkey please don't do that again that wasn't very nice OBS you scared me when you did that
you wouldn't want to scare me OBS don't do that again please wow okay I've sent all the assassins away
she be said that your butt superior I show it I mean I may or may not have showed the girls
my my butt in the discord I may have showed them some photos of me
um like it came up in conversation please don't think I was just like here you guys take this
no it came up in conversation we're all just kind of like oh this is how I look oh this is how I
look and this is how I look and I was like here's my butt um yeah basically
showed them the moon why am I not surprised literally everyone's like oh yeah these girls
gonna hate each other and all that and it was like all of us like oh my god you're so cute you're
so adorable oh this is so good you look so good like your hair is this like oh we just love each
other it's so it is so nice not fair they get to see it how exactly does that come up in conversation
honestly it was just kind of like wait wait wait wait wait is he gonna attack me
he is he's an enemy whoa whoa whoa I can't counter his punches
wait someone in chat earlier said five Harley Quinn's and I didn't understand what you meant
I think I understand what you meant Reefling there's five hidden on the map and I have to
eliminate them all I'm happy you're all bonding yeah I got a big butt me too no way show me
basically like so yeah just a boy sleepover parties it's like video games and all that
girl slumber parties oh here's a picture of my butt so yeah there you go
um I'm gonna see if I can buy these goodness gravy this is so far away
I'm trying my best not to take too much fall damage trying to get to this place
we don't when guys have slumber parties they do shogi biscuit when girls have slumber parties
where the heck am I trying to go sorry you guys are distracting me stop being so entertaining
stop being so nice to me and get me so distracted from the gameplay
I've been told that I inherited my supposed to be very nice from my mother's side of the
family oh well do you want to know what's funny my mommy has big bazongas do you want to know
what cup size my bazongas are my mom's like freaking double g's or something and I'm a cops
I'm like thanks mom so it all went to my butt instead I don't know where they went literally
they went all went to my butt instead so I don't know how
you got your yiddies from your father honestly
when can we get mum on stream stop she'll actually talk about it she'll be like I
strongly just never grew anything um like I remember when she got me a training bra
like so if you didn't know a training bra is like to get you used to wearing one because it's
actually really uncomfortable like I know I know it doesn't sound like it's uncomfortable
but like having something to strap down moving parts um it's kind of cut
how much am I missing is that like less than 500 florins roughly
oh um and like she got me one and I was like mum what is this for and she was like oh well
I've got big gibberish so you're gonna get big gibberish as well and I'm like um okay so like
I start training and then nothing happened no not like a sports bra like just like a thin
fabric to like get you used to it and then yeah nothing happened nothing happened with me for
but I'm not mad like I quite like my aesthetic some people like have struggles with their
bodies but I am really lucky because I I prefer being uh not having much up but having a lot down
like I really like my body
yeah like small buddies don't get in the way either
like all I hear like my mum will complain about like back pain and I'm like uh the only pain
I get is like I don't get any pain because of my physique I would say that sorry I'm trying to like
think and do things at the same time and it's not working out um I would say like my physique
just means like I'm always good to go basically uh right we'll be doing another DNA
bro but do you know okay there's quite a lot oh no only two only two
do castle crusher no I don't want to do you the burdens we carry no I don't want to do you either
right I'm gonna avoid any don't be I can do it in this one I know how to do that one
so I just went on a massive ramble about that milk milk and dump truck as I go oh mini milk is
yeah mini mocha oh no we don't have our sassan recruits but we should at this point
it's gonna be a bit painful wait where are you gonna get some food oh I was
okay we'll do it after this one see you guys distracted me
be fine stay alert
oofy I forgot to get up wait I have one sassan recruit thing
is that because I only had one at the time
oh no it's because they're all away on missions right now okay so if my sassans are way on missions
they're not available during recall that's yeah I understand that's probably like programming
would have been a nightmare so yeah no that makes sense okay I won't send my recruits away too much
anymore if that is the result I can send away the lower level ones because they do not count for the
assassin signal I'm just gonna do this right now because I'm pretty sure it'll count towards my
hiring the to lure the guards
at the end of every week each one of us I'm starting to get lightheaded oopsies
should have got some food bozos
yeah you put everyone else on quest literally I need to go around and find all these gestures
I don't know what happens at the end of the gesture thing like they get money or just something
happen where does that senator I'm wondering should I stall right now so all my recruits come back
for this mission right yes we're gonna do that that's probably the best idea right now so I don't
mess up this mission I'm actually gonna go out of range just so the event doesn't trigger
um please get off there we go we're just hiding here why not I'm going to go get some food I'm
going to get a drink as well oh did you see that street performer fall over there oh dear
I'm gonna go for pee and please do get up and hydrate and stretch your legs um because we
do not have hemorrhoids in the reefing gang I'll be back very shortly literally I just need to
like put it all in a bowl and then uh that's it really I don't recall if I need to do anything else
maybe make a hot water bottle because I'm a bit too late
bit too late I'll be I'll be like a couple of minutes
all right you'll need a beating
so
I don't want to die, I don't want to die, I don't want to die, I don't want to die, I don't want to die, I don't want to die, I don't want to die, I don't want to die, I don't want to die, I don't want to die, I don't want to die, I don't want to die, I don't want to die, I don't want to die, I don't want to die, I don't want to die, I don't want to die, I don't want to die, I don't want to die, I don't want to die, I don't want to die, I don't want to die, I don't want to die, I don't want to die, I don't want to die, I don't want to die, I don't want to die, I don't want to die, I don't want to die, I don't want to die, I don't want to die, I don't want to die
I don't want to die, I don't want to die, I don't want to die, I don't want to die, I don't want to die, I don't want to die, I don't want to die
Are you struggling in these holes, Arsh?
Come out and breathe
This is
I don't know what I'm talking about.
I don't know.
Let's go play on his own there and break the fourth wall.
My god the shibu shima's layer is hell yeah it's how you go watch her.
I could have sworn I was in that hay bale but whatever.
You were, a guard shoved me out.
I got bullied.
Yes all your flooring- oh how dear you.
A guard attacked me, how am I alive?
Did the mission just reset?
Right I can see that I've got three sassan signals so this is gonna make things a heck of a lot of you.
I completely forgot I bought chocolate covered raisins
and I have chocolate covered raisins and I'm sorry I had.
They just pushed me out I guess.
Make an exception for her.
Right I...
Oh am I allowed to be detected at this stage?
Do not be detected while escorting the senator so I'm not escorting just yet.
I know I said that wrong so I repeated it to seem like I said on purpose but the truth is I didn't.
I like how the senator couldn't like perfectly see through it.
By the way sorry I just noticed a mean tag in the reply under your schedule that Cephalophogre is that correct?
Have I spelled it wrong?
I probably spelled it wrong then.
This is what you guys need to tell me what to do because I don't know what the heck I'm doing.
Friends these days unfortunately I'm not one of them.
Cephalophogre!
He fights the guards and gives away money.
So honey someone on Twitter made a VTuber fruit tier list and they fit you in impressive.
Oh yeah they like my fringe tipped.
Hold on I'm taking a sipping to Nicola.
Did you guys get up and start to leave?
I'm so sorry.
I don't know what's going on with my tum tum I'm having to take more pain killers
but I'm having them with food so it's not going to hurt me.
I promise it's not going to hurt.
Cephalophogre honestly.
Oh burp warning.
I burp a lot when I eat so please brace yourself if you're not uh
not that you're not into burping but I understand that some people being rude that burping is very
rude but I
Oh I liked her scream.
Okay in order if you look away your assassin recruits will despawn faster
and then they'll re like start reloading quicker.
Did you see the art?
I've been locked out of my Twitter and I keep getting locked out of it to the point where
it's inaccessible and it keeps telling me to do these like stupid capture thing
and it keeps saying um
um
no
well
I did not see them at all and so it says like verification complete you're human
and then it says error submitting and I can't do anything I don't know what I want me to do
um so I've been locked out of my alt one I've not had a chance to check out my
current one it's the music's a load of my ears sorry I need to hear my headset then
then you turn the games on or is it just being a bit dramatic at this stage
on the appropriate width of women's league
not you you raise money for false causes to pay back the gambling debts
they're gang violence and I'm right now barfy a smart win
um am I allowed to confess I've already recorded it
this is the most significant I sat in my recording this for 15 minutes
I had one bottle of water and one can of cola and I fell ill after recording it
but I already recorded it I'm so sorry if it's not your thing but I it's the truth I already
recorded it I thought it was funny but I don't really have manners so I was raised in a bar
I've just gone oh management unlocked my alternative twitter okay I'll go I'll look after
stream and then I'll see what I've missed because I think it's very possible I've missed a lot of
fan arts or clips oh someone clipped me plain assassin's creed and someone clipped me um
um when me and the horse were beating up the captain um I was like giggling my little butt off
at the club it was so good I'm going to tweet it out um because like it was just so funny um
and like I really appreciate anyone that clips me because like clipping takes so much time
how long will the audio be I think it's roughly 15 minutes after editing because
um I'm doing a lot of what I call live ASMR where like I don't edit out all my mistakes and stuff
like I know this sounds a bit funny saying it like that but um
uh sorry um what was the same word of gone I'm sorry my brain's too small to think and talk
at the same time oh yeah live ASMR um I've really been enjoying doing it instead of like the super
hyper edited approach like if like I make a bump then I just lower the volume so it's still
acceptable for ASMR and like if not like at one point my cat um came in my recording booth and
I was like do you want to do ASMR with me and my baby boy was like so I'm just like going to leave
it in because it's just so precious and I really like it um like I've really enjoyed doing like
live ASMR instead of like try hard even more um like I've done like non-scripted ones as well
where I'm rambling out my butt like so much um if it's not scripted my ramble ASMR is ridiculous
like it's not even ASMR honestly like it's just me like goofing off talking about whatever I like
um whoa whoa I've accidentally hired this group when I'm how is the senator under attack
I don't even know he's under attack there's no one that patrols that way
as long as I don't get discovered I could me and yeah what happened we're addicted to the yapping
where can I hear the ASMR it'll just be on youtube I do need to edit it I've got a few
things first before I start doing my uh 1000 subscriber thank you ASMR's um like I've got
a few collabs that I need to focus on first like I really whoa whoa whoa why did all of that
did I not perish you guys
can you look at those guards maybe
okay they're gonna fight each other wait what yeah so this is true um
taser ASMR unlocked by she what is she doing ASMR right now
um but yeah my rambling ASMR is like always end up like non-scripted always end up in a massive
ramble that's not even ASMR like there's so many things in it out because at one point during one
of them I was like do you want to listen to how much like ASMR tools are like on the floor right now
and like I kick my feet around the mic and stuff like so you can hear it it's just a
beating I'm a silly belly honey
like whatever right do it 100 percent I should never have sent them to the ambassador
we get taser in the year like an actual taser I won't go
strong making ASMR
thank god he's not here we haven't found out about the letters what did you want again
and like I did an ear cleaning thing like a ear cleaning role-playing and and like the first
sentence I said was like oh the STD clinics down to the left mate I was like oh you're here for
your ear cleaning I'm gonna start cleaning your ears like I'm just I don't know why I'm just like
having such a good time she said drunk ASMR oh she's drinking I hope she's careful
you might actually give me hope okay I'm gonna eat my egg and meat because I don't like when
eggs are out of the fridge I don't want to get sick so eggie and meat stick
I feel oh she's steaming we say steaming like oh is she steaming
oh my god did you hear the eggs just bite me back let's us follow the money
I can do that one easy easy back and 100% this one I just bugged it
um
okay listen it's just so easy to make as well literally boil egg
I look forward to this drunk ASMR she's doing it right now
YouTube moderators you have permission to link please consider supporting
chibi cotton bomb she's doing live drunk ASMR
meat however we're trying to finish Christina's freaking story line
there we go
I'm a bit worried I don't have a napkin again and I've just touched egg oh
I'll just wait put on my hoodie sorry I'm gross but it's true
look at Emmy's alt monk on
can I see it can I see it see it see it see Emmy's alt alt I think I'm following it on the main so
she'll be able to
where is it
is it hidden and you can't see it unless you search out for it
where the heck is it oh there it is right up oh did she post
oh her tummy hurt is that what you mean do you have a favorite streamer snack no
let's eat anything oh why did I feel like I've heard it before strongy I'm strongy cuddles now
and I'd like to remain strongy cuddles thank you very much
underneath the tummy hurt message me when I can't kiss you 600 times a day
the retweet or her tweet tight you up and whispering in your ear that if you can make
it to 30 seconds without I'll reward you as fast as you can I'm watching you struggle not to
but in the end you'll still feel
please give me a kiss with what oh I never read the full thing I just read that her tummy hurt
oh my god Emmy that's outrageous that's so good Emmy you'll never guess what
itchy girlfriend in my dreams actually that is my club's happening by hooker by crook
I'm so bad with Twitter I'm supposed to tweet like when I'm going live and stuff
like but I just can't even ball out I just can't even ball it retwears for looking at pictures
and then doing your thing and then going off again you know I'm saying I only got to the tummy part
no I didn't read ahead I just thought she had a sore tongue tongue
they're like all the girls around their own social media I've told them do what you want
because like I'm so bad like I know you're supposed to tweet like oh I'm going live I'm
doing this in an hour and I'm like I feel like those who want to be here already know the drill
but I do get the reminders are helpful I'd say I'm going to use it for like oh my
youtube video for 1000 subscribers this year take thing
I don't miss the strong 10 that's so good self gatekeeping
huh
are we gonna react to the xbox showcase stuff ooh
what's my stream on sunday I don't know
I can't I think my stream on sunday is
is the sweets
Johnny's cute cute you're cute refling cute
okay I shouldn't munch too much but I'm so hungry
okay
foreign sweet okay
I kind of plan to do like one endurance game stream a week so next week is Skyrim for endurance
then we have Elden Ring for two weeks in a row after that so I'm playing the DLC with you guys
first and then I'm playing multiplayer with sin sister um
and we also have shot callers and heart rate winners and all that jazz um thankfully sin sister
is an endurance streamer so like if you ever get annoyed like uh I hate it like when streamers like
don't finish a game I don't like either which is why I would love to get endurance streamers first
borderlands too I would love to do a vtuber playthrough like you know the vtuber's the problem is
if people aren't endurance streamers that's like oh so long whereas if you can find an
endurance it takes maybe three streams max if you want to just blast through the campaign maybe even two
honestly
I'm sucking my fingers I don't know why my tongue's coming out oh it thinks my fingers are my tongue
that's so cool I love this I don't know if I've ever been
borderlands too is like a hoot in a hole or it's like a fun game honestly
oh maybe I should look at Marshmallow while I do this yes I will look at Marshmallow that's so silly
oh my goodness I have a hundred more questions than I did yesterday oops
any chance there'll be a full body pillow for sale in the future yes um
ubu market are like absolutely amazing to work with and they were like whenever a girl has a
birthday please tell us and we're happy to do like a new thing for you um so the more support like
they get on ubu market right now the more favor we have to like produce something new so for the
girl's birthdays I would love to do um at least booba mouth mouth mat and also possibly their
mascots in a plushie now I don't know if the designs for the mascots might be a bit advanced
um or they would come out quite expensive that's the only um issue hi good to hear you yeah it's
good to be heard didn't it um maybe a hundred percent open to any merch uh we are going to
establish ourselves first and then I'm gonna reach out to a very unique merchandise line
because I have no idea how to bridge a connection between that but I'll give it a shot you know
you can only do but ask if you do not ask you do not receive so I will ask I will see if it's possible
if it's not possible then we tried um would it be uh I'm not going to let you know what those
type of mousepad designs will be for the others I know what mine is my big badonk adonk I take
a bite of my muffin I'm just hi strongy I really like the Assassin's Creed streams wanted to give
you uh feedback that I've tipped in the stream elements paid around five times now between
the two streams but it never came up oh no wait wait wait wait wait why would it not come up
why would you get filtered I don't it was broken before it's fixed now but why would it not show up
I have bejinga narrow tiny spiny and bejinga again for today it broke yesterday please tell me if
your money didn't go through or did go through the PayPal was broken because you guys gave us
so much money you broke the cricket PayPal but it's unbroken that's what's fun it is a legal
requirement of all reeflings to love strong stuff um I also was thinking I need to find an artist to
do this one that's good with all body types I would love for our six month anniversary to have a mouse
pad of all of us together like one of those big flat mouse pads I would adore to have us all together
absolutely adore it
but I would need to get like a really good artist for that like I would not want to waste money
dicking around with artists like I would want an artist to like fucking smoke it
I know I adore it okay um since there's a notification discord server would it be possible
for you to upload the unarchive stuff the discord like a thread and unarchive stuff do you mean
like karaoke stream or the ASMR stream that went kaput um I think because we like can't we shouldn't
really host it because I got taken off so I don't want to like be the ones responsible if that makes
sense like archive annons shout out to archive annons like for saving everyone's butts I for me
I am open to suggestion if you don't like the suggestion please you're more than welcome to
give me your opinion again and marshmallow but archive annons if a broke don't fix it
they've been doing fantastic they've been catching um what's been put out there and yeah
hmm
our alternative stream is going to be free to access yes I do not personally believe in paying more
than like 10 us dollars to like fully support your oh she and get everything that they put out
there and the girls have shown an interest in playing alternative games and doing some other
stuff um but I would not like them to charge for it I'm going to say to them like let's not charge
but obviously I will never hold you back from giving any tips to the girls
and you can always tip as a thank you to content that you enjoy
but that's just me um like someone said um do I plan on raising the prices of what's been
established no I don't I think I think 10 us dollars per month for all the content that the
girls put out is fair and I think it's good value for money and I think it also shows that
uh like the end goal isn't great and again like 8 20 split comes into it type thing um
and it goes up in their favor next year type stuff if they want to hang about like
I think if it's more than 10 us dollars you're you're not taking the piss but I very much push
for value for money and I hope I know region doesn't always change the price of membership
regionally which is obviously a big thing that's hard to overcome because we don't set the like we
set the price but if the website doesn't do an alternative payment style then you're like you're
getting shafted in other countries like there is a streamer that talked about selling games and
it was like oh brazil because they lowered the price in brazil like it was fine and all that
jazz i'm sorry i'm rambling i'm not making any sense um by the way cuddles i sometimes make a
lot of clips as you probably remember from back then are you goober we may be goober i'm happy for
you to use my clips with whatever you want whenever but i would prefer to keep the clips of you as
gay can't is possible and i only share those with the reeflings really uh and i posted group clips
with the other girls i'm happy for the clips of the other girls in the group collab to be used to
monetize and shoot oh that's so nice of you whatever you want not like it really matters what my
opinion is yes it does you mean that you goober um and i would like to keep comfy streams to you
as long as possible while you go naturally and share well i've got good news for you
the nature of my content gate creeps me automatically do you want to hear why a little
my goal of a ASMR video every time i get like 1000 subscribers the reason why that naturally gate
keeps me is because someone will come into the livestream after consuming that content and they'll
go when ASMR when ASMR stream and then when they see me rambling my head off about a 14 year old
game having the time of my life they're gonna get bored aren't they they're only here for ASMR
five heads i'm playing chess in 4d already i already did it myself they're weak they can't
handle the strongy they want the they want the strong ASMR whisper in you they can't handle
the ramble and they can't handle the accent they cannot handle the so by default i naturally
get keep myself you're welcome love you reeflings always had you in mind
only the strongest reefling can survive
first time doing this listen to your audio through oh wait i don't think i can read this one out loud
it's a video link oh i'm gonna watch that after stream
hey i did forgot a scottish game show show them the name of places in scotland an asset pronounce
that's such a good segment love that idea i'm teal i'm stealing it now my idea now young
they tune into a stream expecting like a soft whisper with an accent i just sound like a bagpipes
i can't handle the scottish ramble also check to see if you're still subscribed to the other
girls some have been called oh i saw that i was like really youtube you're calling us after like
literally a 12 hour stream go and calm down it really should start to calm down now that we're
there is no way you're telling me like it's gonna keep continuing because this is getting
outrageous now like i'm not laughing no one's hee-hawing strawney it's not fair you give the
burp huffer so much good stuff but what about the fart huffer stop it is it terrible i have a
donathan reward where i took out my boot there's a really funny asmr outtake and i laugh and then
it comes out more with my laugh okay so i'm thinking about you don't mean i'm necessarily
and i swear if anyone starts complaining like oh my god but it's literally just a 10 second audio
clip of me laughing and releasing air like do you think i don't have a digestive tract do you think
that i'm it will i'm such a gamer girl no i'm scottish for one i take big steven jobbies
no such thing as an idol meeting and my piss is neon all right let's know let's get it right
let's get it right right off the bat i'm no having none of this no i'm strawney i'm scottish and i was
raised in a barn when a manners if a little 10 second audio clip of me laughing will i toot
filters you my guy enjoy the ooo because that's what you're looking for no me you're not looking
for me and that's okay if you're not looking for me i've got three a dot three i've got five adorable
doors waiting on you all right
sup oh i'm gonna choke sup less i feel they need to say something after that brotherhood part
one stream what are you talking about why you don't think you could be considered or oh she
why because they're creators that they were more experienced who you think are better so clearly
would prepare them have you not followed have we not followed and supported you for a while heck
i've been listening laughing relaxing sagging and straight jorgen has pentas for many a time now
what do you why do you think that is could it mean we adored the silly scottish gremlin who's not
afraid to be herself and treat her with love and respect no last kick that impossible shame
syndrome to the curve we love you oh you're oh she case closed doofus oh thank you evening i love
you replay is that a bag of chips no it's a bowl i'm like the p-snacks are really hard i can
like dink them on the bowl without them cracking oh there was a marshmallow you wanted to talk about
on the other stream but i forgot oh my god right hopefully i don't forget this time there's a really
brave refling who messaged me well he's not a reflin but he's asked for helps reflings okay
i i'm going to paraphrase it because i can't quite remember exactly what it said okay but
basically this person is struggling to brush their teeth and i think it would be very nice
if we brush our teeth together after stream like when streams ending will brush our teeth
together i know that sounds silly however it takes 21 days to form a habit and i think it would be
nice reflings if we could encourage and help people that might struggle with that so if you would
like to brush your teeth with me at the end of stream i will give a roughly 30 minute warning
so you don't have any sugary drinks or any food before because that's bad for your enamel to brush
and i think it can be a really nice thing we reflins can do for someone even even if together
we help one person hopefully if we consistently do it for 21 days we have helped that person who
was very brave by the way that was a very brave message to come out with um i won't say too much
about it but um you know you were very straightforward and said that um you don't you know consider yourself
a refling and that's okay um and you know we can't promise that we we can help everyone but we
would love to maybe show you a way that we can do something nice together and it's a lot easier when
you do something together with someone so uh yes thank you for being very brave and reaching out
i would like to brush my teeth with you when i end stream i don't know if you're out there
but uh we can definitely do that together yes it's
i see no problem yeah
yes unfortunately i don't have a consistent time where we cannot brush your teeth
i would just have to be roughly 30 minutes before my stream ends sorry i'm pushing in my chair
you're pushing my chair
hi strani congrats on debut i was wondering um nope you're done
uh any games coming out that you're excited for uh multiplayer the binding of isaac apparently
someone went data mining and saw that there was a new repentance after plus or something
so there might be patches to current items which would be very interesting
forming new habits with my oh she sounds like a tuition name honestly join oral improvement
she's getting closer to i am the urge to crack a british joke oh my teeth are mangled honestly
my teeth are mangled i'm like they're healthy but they're just all squint and it's like i like the
look of i oh my god there's apparently a pandemic happening in america with veneers uh veneers are
like these fake things you put on top of your teeth that are shaved down and it makes them look
perfect but i feel like teeth have personality like i like my wee squinty winty teeth um i just
i've never seen myself any other way so it's me oh yeah i do understand for people that do need
braces like there's probably something else going on but i like i was obsessed and i never got braces
um and yeah i just have naturally squint teeth like they didn't come out perfect and that's fine
that's just how it is um
mommy i really need a hug debut has made me really emotional oh a little reflame
trust me i know this isn't about me but i'm talking to you now you should be so proud of
what you've accomplished i am the girls have done fantastic and i'm having a good time with my
weakness you and the girls but i feel much more lonely than i did before oh watching everyone interact
with each other the girls respond into mario's maro's and such i don't even know why i suppose i'm
just envious of the attention that everyone's getting i feel so out of place i'm so sad i haven't
even been able to listen to your audios to sleep i'm sorry for being selfish it's not selfish at all
are you are you maybe one of the lurkers that are shy to say anything
or have i managed to successfully accidentally dodge all your messages and stream and i would
be a bit upset too if you were talking away and i accidentally never read out any of your messages
so i do apologize if that happens and well i'm sorry for a little reflame i never want to make
you feel lonely if you are a lurker and you're a bit scared to talk that's okay whatever your
comfort level is you're allowed to be that uh you can always say you can always be at arm's length
or you can always be attached at my head you can sit on my head if you like um and it's okay
but just i don't know hopefully it doesn't make you feel lonely like
oh by then i get to show you my childhood game you guys get to show me you get to suggest to me
your childhood game i want to sit on stroney's head yeah lurkers are beloved yes i understand
for lurkers sometimes it can be a bit nerve-wracking as well to like be perceived with my eyeballs and
like i i read out what you're saying stuff but um literally uh if you would like evidence from my
autistic diagnosis please refer to my first stream which was 12 hours long and the only
reason i went off instead of 14 hours of full gameplay is because of bod okay i'm usually playing
something and lurking yeah like it's perfectly okay to lurk and just do your thing not wrong with
lurking absolutely not um don't be shy reflame stroney isn't always reading my comments but yeah
it's um a gooberino so i do apologize if i've ever made you feel left out um and hopefully
it doesn't happen in the future um i can only apologize uh sometimes hi stroney want you to
know what i think it's very cute when you narrowed out about sasa's group brotherhood well i'm getting
rolled in the dlcs clearly i'm not built for the dlc
i have a little sip of cola a fizzy juice i lurk when i'm at work um yeah a lot of people
like lurking and listening to stroney podcast wait if you don't see the screen when i'm streaming
and like i'm beating up bad guys and oh you hear us oh take this oh like are you like oh what's
going on or can you use context clues i like to have the stream on in the background but i do like
to interact i'm like yeah don't feel don't ever feel forced to interact i know some people shy like
that hi coddles just wondering if you could forward something to management i know vealer or not on
holodex but you can still view the stream of the url but i think the girls have something set that
prevents their streams from being viewed through third-party sites well mine is fame
i can't be right people is true screen off pretending stroney is physically
throwing the refill and then around for sport um to be honest you talk enough that there isn't
dead air so i don't have to wonder about what's going on yeah i can't believe it wait was there
really no dead air in the last stream i must have been quiet at some sections there's no way
i had the video playing i just can't fully watch the whole stream yes the streams are a bit too long
for the average adult uh okay management's gonna look into holodex i think that puts all their
streams together we were thinking about hosting a website that showed all our stream schedules
but it cost like more money and it was just kind of one of those things where look holodex does it
for free we're just gonna let holodex take over who goes there i died for yourself there was almost
no dead air outside of breaks and they wonder my throat is sore honestly after uh after i've been
done with you i watched for about five hours and wasn't it okay you talked the entire time i do i'm
very passionate about this game very very passionate uh sorry if i missed it but what are we
yes your reeflings i was very dumb and never showed you what you look like that's you
i've lost some gnar twerk of a nature of us together and what's the old twitter check out
who i follow on strawnycuddles on twitter i don't use twitter much you're much better given a like
and a subscribe to this youtube channel i am not much of a twitter person okay in a gush i use twitter
now pretty much to reach out to other vtubers and be like hey want to make a samar hey sweet
cakes want to make a samar basically so i do i think your longest dead air was the sprint
section where you were against the clock and you're still monologued more like monomogged
because i'm just that good at being a yap or hey strawny loving the assassin's creed i was
wondering if you have ever seen or played lost planet one or two i haven't there are fun games
that i think you may like even if you don't play them i still appreciate you for beating
this message i have not i've never heard of them or i can't remember them being on the cover of
an xbox 360 so probably not have i ever played dragon age i played the demo of dragon age one
i think uh where it's like brother and sister at the star and then one of them perishes if i
remember correctly yeah that's how much dragon age i've done i don't know what it's like um
but yeah yes one take flamboyant cuttlefishes are highly poisonous okay well am i flamboyant
because of my watermelon candy here someone described as watermelon candy and i'm like
honestly true true uh will there be streams on other platforms okay
congratulations on your debut i'm looking forward to supporting all of the talents i must
apologize i said that's so wrong i must apologize but i find myself confused what you meant by
vealers collab restrictions and i'm looking forward to clarification you describe the
collab restrictions as the unwritten rule through other information do you mean for me
my collab restrictions are um i'm like if i don't know that someone is like me mentally then i can't
stream with them because i'm dumb i can stream with the girls though that's fine and the girls can
stream with whoever they like other than males they're not allowed to stream with males or interact
with males or follow males literally that's the only rule and so far so good literally none of
the girls have broken that rule scrawny slaps of each of us behind i can make you a star yeah um
it seems odd for me for them to be rules i've never heard of any other agency that has an
outright rule against them against who sorry i'm not read this properly uh especially value
and freedom doesn't it apologize if it comes off with really critical however i think clarification
were an issue oh and they can freaking go wherever they want oh this is asking about male collabs
the person has said wrestle tube collabs were like mixed would the girls be able to do that
i mean i would never stop them from an opportunity like would they be on the same team as a guy like
i don't think i don't think that's like advised if it was like that like i wouldn't advise it
however none of the girls have given me an indication to ever even do that like i think
we would be like sorry but uh we can't uh we are uh following japanese idol culture
and uh no male sorry sorry we sexist out here which is terrible don't say that i love don't
say that part of it keep burping don't apologize oh yeah oh yeah hello again friend of a friend
i knew you well the truth is just a rule that you can bet sitting my love on
i don't remember the words pick it up every time
hi stroney i think you've been one guy what does that mean saying names is okay as long as it's not
too much oh no so the way i i've been taught v tripper culture i'm so sorry but i've been taught
by the majority v tripper culture i'm not allowed to say your name unless you don't know or
membership however because and the reason why i can't do it when it's like just saying hi section
or in general is because like people think favoritism is forming or jealousy and i really
don't want anyone feeling put out um wait that's exactly what you've just said to me
we have just agreed okay we've just agreed yes we have agreed um uh at the start of the ASMR
stream i am going to try and say people's names just as a special thank you for showing up how do
you feel that you're no longer a v-tweeter well hopefully my first stream length really showed
how much i enjoy video being so up cuddles was thinking of a tag oh i missed the tag i kind of
finished them oopsie uh please do give us a guide for those script writing yes um i'm currently
getting a new manager on board that deals with all the scripts and thank god he is a male because
he can actually write scripts that guys want to hear because i can only guess what you want
to hear and so much um so like roughly the first three months of scripts are me and then it goes
to other script writers and then it goes to the script manager but we're testing script manager
but if all goes well my responsibilities lessen so much and i can stream so much more
well at the start of the stream you were 3.5k now you're at 3.3 heck yeah that means i don't
have to edit the 4k thousand anytime soon that's fine
hey i have to say that i think you amazing i don't get to interact with many scottish people online
that's because a lot of things had to go wrong in my scottish life to become a v-tweeter that's why
there's no scottish v-tubers do you know how i know i've hurt myself my finger is bleeding why
what did i cut myself on i've not touched anything sharp is there anything sharp in this room
ouch it stings hopefully i can still keep gaming
scotland only has one computer yeah yeah no like genuinely there's a reason why there's not a lot
of scottish v-tubers is if you genuinely like grew up around well like grew up around like normal
friends uh you would genuinely be like bullied so hard like bully culture like in america and
australia and the uk is so prevalent like if you show any enjoyment or being slightly different
from the status quo you get sicked on like a like a hound like sick um it's crazy pour some
zura milk on it honestly i don't know i can't remember how i cut myself my wee fingy i'm okay though
someone says hi stroney i missed all of your livestreams rip but i do have a few questions
what happens if one of the girls wants to leave they uh they leave question mark
they get to go we don't have a non-compete uh i don't believe in them i don't think they're nice
they are not kind if you no longer work for the vealer agency why would we prevent you from
making money elsewhere that is uh called being uh messed up will you retire the character yeah
also if you can work the plans for gen two will you bring in six new girls and retire the other
what what what what what what what what what what what what what what what what what what what what what
if gen two is the thing there will be six new girls on board um so well when feature agencies come
out with generations uh everyone can be active at the same time it's not a problem so generation one
all six active generation two all six active so that would be 12 total then if generation three
and everyone's happy with their cuts and things are all nice and swimmingly and then generation
three and there will be a total of 18 succubi and v-sucky wow i really that's very daunting to
think of but thank god i'm not the script master anymore because if i was a script master i could
not stream i genuinely could not stream um there are absolutely no interest for any generations
after three no spin-off generations no secret plans no save for work generation
none of that i and i am exhausted i took insane amounts of hp damage getting gen one out
i am ill i want to get myself better and i'm going to stream and i'm going to enjoy every second of
it um but yeah we we uh we are not having to retire gen one to get gen two out no um sorry
lastly and this may be taboo to ask and if you don't i'll read it in my head
that is controversial it's not controversial
and what's an item you would copy and steal from the other girls
shibis no i will be taking no further questions and why is everything in japanese are are you
weep nothing's in japanese actually this is a fully english stream there's nothing in japanese
at all here what's going on
how am i supposed to support the girls when you keep pulling me in i'm pulling into my
gravitational pull my can't escape this gravitational pull
the website oh why marshmallows you'll never guess what country marshmallow was made in
it was made in japan so it's all japanese so um google i use firefox which does have a translator
thing
someone says please will you wallace all over me oh yeah you like that
i don't know if this made it through so i sent it twice
it's a png do we open it and we're gonna open it live on stream
um
oh it's me with my autism huh i thought it was going to be something else
yay i had my autism huh
i thought it was going to be something else but i saw it was a png and i was like i'll go for it
um
okay i just quickly refreshed we've got a few more and then we'll jump back into the
uh someone says check smuttlefish hashtag oh hashtag set me up oh oh oh fish
it's on safe mode show me the good smuttle did i spell it right
it's been hating it's hidden for me check your search hate sensitive media absolutely no
show me the goods
there's two goods inside
oh my god i have feet
and my hair is so big and i'm sitting in a clam
yee
and there's a second one oh my god there's two
oh in the second one i say come closer to me have i got hypno eyes oh i've got hypno eyes
on the second one oh that's so good that's so good i love it thank you i cannot react to it
because i'm on my mannequin but it's so good there's three rs oh i can't see the third one i only see
two some accounts seem to be muted for me for some reason i can't see the third one only see two
oh i don't see it it's not displaying i don't know what's up with twitter it's like really having
a hard time oh i see it i
i see the
i have a tail it looks like three girls and veal are have a tail no i have a tail
i have a leash oh my god oh my god thank you i love
you i have a leash
oh it's so good and the tail goes green at the tip as well just like my horror
i'm gonna stare at it for a very suspiciously small amount of time later today
that's terrible what are you doing to me refling
shouldn't be that should be the one doing this to you
uh wait i accidentally thank you very much for that final i like all
fan art actually i need to put it in my folder i have a folder of all the fan arts and memes so far
um someone says i loved your audios in the part where you talked about
but her big ears and go squishy with it is the nicotine patch under the banks for real
i don't actually have it however i quite like the idea that we both have the nicotine patch
because we're both addicted to each other as we are each other yes yes yes it doesn't show up on
mine yeah it never showed up on mine for like
hi strongy i just wanted to say that's really great how much you care about the progression
of the other girls and your inspirational speech in your first ac brotherhood and you're a really
cute person and brist oh she i hope you have all great and long careers also now i have a thing
for the scottish accent oh i do you like this big man oh i am pure coming over to you like
i thought yeah that's coming to your house you'll be sleeping in your bed and then you'll feel my
hundle over here and that's right and before you know it you've popped our money and it's over for
you that's yeah is that what you want is that what you want because you got it with me baby
is they stream another endurance stream i have no idea i'm a bit nervous i don't know if we can do
100 assassin screes so we're just having fun strongy is just an industry plant from the
scottish tourism board don't fall for it don't fall for my tricks you shouldn't come to glasgo
and spend all your hard earned money there's totally not amazing lovely tourist cafes in glasgo
watching austin powers is gonna hit different i've never seen it i'm so excited to watch
austin powers you guys um i think that's all the lovely maros i have i is 411 maros
okay who's ready to replay this memory weirdly i haven't suddenly urged to visit glasgo
scotland has turned hypnotism
wait did we not finish that memory oh we didn't i thought we did i went away and got food
nori nori i knew it keep an eye on the politics of the city i want you to report back to maria
at the rosa infiore about targets you are helping the borja and what you'll make them disappear
the best so the mayor that may hate me but he's still family
babel we go i will follow you to the banker
okay are you trying to get achievements i'm gonna see where it takes us i don't know if i can do 100
percent it my confidence as we played some of the dlcs has gone down significantly because i don't
know what the solution is to a few hundred percent so bro if this game tells me i have a new
outfit unlocked one more time i'm gonna cry it's doing it so much how does my browser all come
plead to die right to lead to stories oh that's terrible i need to start retweeting
and stuff like i want to rule play with the r i'm sorry i said i don't care people find it cringe
yeah you know it's cringe your vtuber never having a good time that's crazy that's different
that's different the banker hypnotic scotish assassin go
brr you see anyone else here follow me for bakione for bakione is such a specific word
oh we are like so we don't actually want to kill this archer because if we do his body's gonna
drop down what did you see how they only got i i'm gonna pray the body doesn't fall right in front
of him don't do it ragdoll physics i'm gonna be mad what i may actually have to try hard during
the segment i'm not to touch the ground and i'm not to get detected i do have it's you are you
trying to give me a heart attack because it's working it's actually working me you're making me
i'm getting a bit concerned for how much of a launching you're launching yourself he's a rooftop
i have no idea if you guys can understand me when i start doing that like on purpose
like being super scots on purpose or does it just sound like it's just kind of like pleasant noises
for you uh i think we're just gonna do that
as long as his body doesn't go sliding down off but i'm fine with everything that goes on
i understand it no it's pleasant it's pleasant aren't we i'm just oh my god you're going so scots
if you can you're actually getting pretty scots
is it
wait is that your literal translation of scots there stop what does that say
you cherish sorry i'm like trying to reach out and play the game at the same time i'm actually
such a skilled streamer sorry i played this game so much i can do there are some bits and
pieces here and there but it's mostly understandable ah too compliant fuck it let's just go for it
it's surprisingly sweet i should i'm definitely going to do like a hard scotch accent ASMR i don't
know what i should do with it like tingle wise or maybe it should just be like go to sleep mate
they i'll i'll get these a these they're really cool and on your face and they go bloop bloop bloop
and it'll be really nice i'll put you to sleep real quick oh you still no sleep right let me get
the ear cleaner snake i think you call it a q-tip but it's actually called ear cleaners here
that's the kind of ASMR i want to do yes please i'll just call it super scots ASMR and then people
like don't be silly there's no such thing as super scots ASMR and then they click the listen and
they're like they click to listen they're like oh i understand now i get it
birds oh please don't rag doll physics do no drop they cannot get past those corousons huh
i feel like there's definitely more on the map i think that person yesterday was actually correct
and said the more favor you gain with the factions the more they appear on the map because all of
a sudden i'm seeing zans everywhere his body is tempted to fold over literally it's like giving
me a mini heart attack can i aim on you aim aim aim no aim bot aim bot aim bot no just don't want to
do it for me it's really annoying when it does that but i like oh that's not good
i really do not want that guy to be able to see me if i can get you back oh no no no don't
don't don't yeah didn't think so mate right he's just discovered that body do i desync
because he sees the body or am i safe i actually think i'm safe you know that i think i've done it
even though he sees the dead bodies that i that's fine
okay we did it we just have to hang out on this little edge oh no we don't because there's
freaking guards right there which i don't like hopefully they we don't have a problem
scottish mommy speaks commonly while you enjoy a heart meal
is it weird being scott's fine the scott's actually really weird no that's not weird at all
well well sounds like home the banker has a special evening plan
a body just another day in them honestly if you like told how many like for uh at seo's
yoink i feel like it's like a really considerable number on the side of the money
wait can i move on there do not be detected and do not touch the ground while tail in the center
uh
i can touch the ground now right that's definitely not i'm not i swear if this is
like we've broken it yeah okay i was gonna say i was like that's the silliest thing i've ever
heard if it's like uh you're not allowed to do it
calcic language is just assistant to me
oh this is scott's this is scott's we can get up please
it's not the serious scott
video embedding issues should now be fixed for all channels
we're not on holodex are we did you guys already get us on holodex there's no way
or are we i thought it was like a a view thing like you need to assign to my one
a assign amount of views ourselves or something
thanks we suck there's an endy say ah okay okay okay okay okay okay
hopefully everyone's viewable and you can see this up uh she'd be still alive i believe and we
don't have a zura today i think it's a race day for a zero if i'm not mistaken
okay we're done we did it hundred percent you're not but you can still use your
skills to create your own in my view not views so i've got any 20 key average on channel yeah
it means about to go live heck yeah what's in me doing the day
i will highly recommend in and out yeah the court is on blocked us from being able to
do the bench thing i know how to do the bench thing it's not a problem
oh she's meme reviewing
scott's east marastroni misunderstanding the listeners lack of accent we talk about we can't
go in you have to stall by the order of chesery fitty land fitty land
luigi has been killed we discovered his body at the pantheon
well you've succeeded in confusing me i'm back take a break to listen to music hate yeah
help claudia that the banker is here oh i have so much money to hire these lovely ladies
i'm too good literally okay any live and when
can't take the name of the music
don't want to get them on that silver
oh he's staring around
no one's actually named it luigi
darling brother sister
darling brother darling bratty sister
say that five times fast darling bratty sister in me darling bratty sister in me
darling bratty sister in me darling bratty sister in me
but they are giggling away and gonna start blushing right so take them and then go back
to the fuel stack because i don't want to get in any trouble
i think we just got 50% DNA so i think we might actually have
i think we might actually have a new pristine memory unlock if it's 25 percent then 50 then 75
that reason said then should we help
i can't protect him
speaking of smoking before to my friend lu you want to smoke go for it no nothing for me to say
i'm trying so hard not to lose them to a guard right now i think we're okay with the render
difference i have no idea what we're missing and not done yet we're replaying easy missions that
i failed in order to get higher dna sequence christina's story doesn't unlock until you have
high synchronicity so i'm having to go back and redo missions that like are easy and they'll
raise our overall percentage and then we should be able to finish whatever happens with christina
because it like ended and it didn't make any sense like at all
right okay we're done this part we just need to do the benchmark night
how far are you planning on taking vila or dominate no not domination i just want the girls to
achieve their dreams and achieve what they want to do and um have a good time you know it's kind
of like what are vila's dreams vila's dreams or whatever the girls dreams are because we want
them to be happy
interesting what about alcohol oh i can't have alcohol
if you guys drink it's fine i'm gonna stop you um
but yeah like uh alcohol and me don't go well um it speeds up my heart rate it makes me feel
uncomfortable and i get i'm very late wait even though i'm Scottish i'm so freaking late wait it's
so annoying i'm stinky like why
um so i just can't really handle it i don't do it also there's been like tons of reports that come
out where alcohol is really bad but i'm not gonna say no to like drunk karaoke streams or something
like that um i kind of learned that um so when you feel a buzz from alcohol you don't have to drink
any further than that point to keep the buzz going that's not how alcohol works i only recently
learned that back anyway and but like i won't be shy of doing like drunk uh karaoke i'll drink for
the both of us honestly there's less of you to fill alcohol with oh please please excuse me i'm
i'm holding b please excuse me geez whoa whoa whoa whoa ladies ladies sink with me my goodness
work with me here
no Guinness for starting i actually like drinking beer it's probably the only thing i can handle
at the moment please remember to drink water if you do drink yes i do not want any issues
what's the way to celebrate my purchase than to join in the brotherhood of man
soon we will be here once more celebrating and you'll like to eat well because i don't drink
and then the feasting will last for 40 days and 40 nights not even the girl eating come in
um i mean she's live right now doing drunk ASMR so i don't know i just never i never had like
going out friends that go like um i'll like nightclub or rave or any of that which is where a
lot of drinking culture comes into play in the uk um like the aim when you go out with your friends
is to get like plastered which is like just not very pleasant um
she has her own full plated armor if only we had a very strong kneecap
sure would be a shame oh i did a challenge
right let's do this without getting in trouble this time
right you go away thank you very much right and then you stop so i can go in this blend
sport no you're right in front of me this is what we didn't want last time
ah i have my friend group love getting hammered and half did not yeah like i didn't really
experience any of that so it just never really became a thing
and like obviously hang up right i definitely can do it this thing
yeah okay easy easy hundred percent right there
i visited the Disney driver on my 21st birthday oh that's right 21st day drinking age in
i do not regret your country the power must be contentious i'm gonna happy to hear
i'm going out or getting good at it it was going out or getting good at ac brotherhood
literally i like i just play video games all day i'm sure it is fun if you're into it but like
i just have no interest i have an interest in like doing like tipsy streams or like drunk
review of movies okay
not again
did it twice i'm sure there's a freaking hay bale down there or something
drinking with good family friends is probably me well you're getting hammered
well you were out there getting hammered i was so out of the story himself right wait
those missions only went up the sink to 51% so didn't you christina get unlocked at 50%
oh
what do you mean i've only done 50% of the game
uh right those ones are difficult so i actually don't want to do them
what's this one the baron de voir gatekeeper 50 50
what are you don't lose any health squares
okay this one's super easy we can do this one i'm literally doing it easiest to hard
and then we'll get hard at the end
how should i beat your first try and get glue sorry i need any sub saying that because it's not
very nice because like i completely understand
i did it again it makes that noise i think that must be an audio mistake or something because
i was studying the hidden bleed i was such an assassin's creed fanboy
i used to think it would be so cool if i got like the assassin's creed logo branded on my finger
i was so impressionable as a child you're truly a man after my so impressionable not very smart
it's kind of character i will get the armor my troops will gather it from the dead
what's been streamed tomorrow is a needy streamer overload needy streamer over than that's you
it's actually a pretty good tale for me to kill them without a fight the armor has to stay clean
next small fish the ac logo in tattoo only refilling assassins allowed inside
okay if this is just don't be actually well i am here
no not while i'm here we have to do it outside of a mission no i always go that way and it's
like the longest way to find anyone
that's the good reason that young people can't get tattoos yes i would like to be
sitting here with like a freaking branded fingers probably the sega logo on me at one point as well
for um for don't get detected for um sonic heroes i always loved it when i was like
did that not alert anyone they're actually so efficient at fighting that didn't alert anyone
you guys get okay our assassins are pretty high level i'm pretty sure they can handle
what's about to happen oh there's a patrol route oh there's a big old fight going on
okay we're at five costumes they're still going for it whoa they're getting beaten up by the big guys
oh they're they're fighting back they're beating them up four to two oh she lost the health bar
wow i actually thought the uh oh they're going for this they're doing it they're doing it they're
going for the patrolers as well oh we got 10 and that one that was that was a really good one
uh what's over here another french patel thing
when needy streamer overload okay uh i think that's definitely going to be a shorter stream
however when i do have shorter streams i'm going to like be working on ASMR collabs and stuff so
there's no homie more content coming america here can oh that's actually for two assassins to
take on that big old group that's quite a lot yeah one of them just lost the health bit
i actually think i'm gonna have to send in more assassins you know
oh they've lost two health bars this is getting this is getting juicy this is getting juicy
oh the other one's lost one as well oh it's getting juicy it's getting juicy oh oh there's
losing three i don't want to get detected because that will ruin this little sequence but uh i will
call in the next card there you go there you go oh i have no idea what's going on over there
i don't want to get detected to ruin it but oh he's on two okay so
oh
help him freaking
she's okay definitely need to level up the gang because they are still not strong enough for this
stop oh my goodness no don't pick on a guard please
oh right everyone despawn right this instant
my heart right they'll heal up so whenever your assassin is low they'll heal up um
i thought we lost them oh my goodness
i thought we i was like i was like what i called in another assassin on that guy that was in
particular is harassing them i was like where are they where are they like why aren't they
coming from but i was like oh wait i can shoot off my horse like i can still attack technically
i just need to not be discovered that's also i'm gonna wait to call in my assassins to do this
i really don't want to actually only get caught i'll be annoyed at myself if i do
there's another guard post all the way over here
excuse me pardon me come through
oh wow yeah there's a big one over here
maybe big like mine okay let's just send in guards and guards and like this
fill health already there you go hold on super simple super easy got 100 let's
literally that's all i had to do last time i wonder if i didn't have all a say a signals um
doing oh no my track is bugging out again please stop what's this one don't take any damage
don't lose any health squares that one's not easy because of how many enemies can just swing
at you and that first one i'll try it do i plan on unlocking all the endings on needy streamer
i don't know how much i'm gonna like it i'm gonna play it for the first time
i think it's like a click game which honestly might make it super simple
if i like it then i'll try and get all endings if i don't like it then i'll probably just do
a few runs and then uh have a short stream and then i'll work on a smart that sounds like a deal
that does not surprise me the french puttani have us under pressure tell me about their general
these baron de valois some major is just like the option and over and over again where can i find
watch the bed wait i need to censor the stream is it safe to stream it
they seem to be getting closer the situation is under control close the gate needy stroney
overload oh i should have named it last time i'm taking that thank you no you can do it okay
right don't take any damage
i'm gonna do that so that stops them okay that's what i'm nervous about them doing that and i
don't have a freaking smoke bomb i have i don't have any more smoke bombs
uh right oh i think i might need to oh i can call him my recruits
oh my god please don't attack me i really don't want to lose health over this
oh i can't see because of the camera angle
i'm scared i'm scared i'm going for it i'm sending it i'm sending it i'm sending it please
don't attack me please don't attack me please don't attack me okay my assassin recruits are
going ham that's what i like to see they're stuck outside
assassin please jeez do you try and make me lose
jeez is there anyone else
oh wait what on air i've never seen this before
i guess i'll just wait they keep seeing me though they can't so the the ai can't actually see me
but he keeps claiming it it's not i think i'm just gonna shoot them no
oh i can oh i can okay that was okay we did it we did it we did it
it's just heavily implied it's more of a way to do nothing okay
please did it too well it would mask your barbaric
Humpty Dumpty look at us
blame them with your ink
maybe i should have had an ink toy so what would have been funny is anything like i just go
oh no
in your ear
i believe another lady might object to that
didn't the developer also make another game a whale after
come on down on your wife says no my downs and come out of the door
that's practically your stretch
all of Italy will be speaking it i'll get you
yeah i can't speak none of that
okay i think we just need to go back and forth and not get attacked by anything which is super
simple
maybe part of a 2.0
why is your french so good no
i actually don't know any french i'll literally no phrases and i record just hate the same phrases
if you would like to order a ham and cheese baguette you say
i would like a good ham with
i forgot what cheese is
well that didn't that didn't work out very well
well it sounds good coming from my friend to speak up
uh
Oh wait that was
must have french post word
I enter and don't bear in gifts and hope that
I can not see offensive of Rima, but did I say
call your man back to the max. I will explain that.
You better have something good.
Hold back!
Yeah, that's like, I'm literally just regurgitating.
Do I have higher education? That sounds like I have higher education.
That answers me.
Reason a barn, uneducated in the barn.
And became a gamer. Hell yeah.
Ray, I'm a bit scared of this one.
Don't lose any health squares.
I actually don't want to do that one because it takes too long.
Ray, we're at 52%. So every time I do a memory, I'm getting like, up to 5%.
Use assassin recruits to do your targets.
Okay, we're actually, factually going to upgrade our assassin recruits.
Which, sorry, I just closed this, but we actually needed to open it.
If I do this, they get...
Okay, we just need to send them on missions.
If we get 5 assassins level 10, the assassin's recruit signal replenishes so much faster.
I think it takes off like 20 seconds, which, in the grand scheme of things, adds up so quickly.
How much money do I have on my assassins?
13k, right, I don't have enough right.
We'll just go and do...
We'll send them on missions.
By the P-jones.
Oh, it was like, dead ahead, dead center.
I remembered an Italian swear. I'll use anything.
Show us your thrones!
I didn't even know that.
I know, cazzo!
Oh, we put 50 grand in the bank?
50 smacaroons.
Right, we're going to send away our agents.
Because I want some of them to level up so then we can get faster.
I have no one at 10 yet.
What, how are you guys...
Oh, you're getting close!
Right, I just need to send them away.
Maybe do a mission that doesn't require them.
And then we can get that...
5, 1, 2, 3, and 4.
If you guys all go...
I think...
1, 2, 3, 4, 5.
Oh, I don't want to risk the room.
If it fails, I'm like 99% sure they come back all perished.
If it fails, which is like, pretty unforgiven.
Eh...
Honestly, your openness and no manners is one of the reasons why I like...
That's funny.
When I live at Cleveland.
Eh...
Right.
Missions, missions, missions.
Wait, they don't have...
17 minutes for that mission?
Is really not.
Is there not another level 5 regular contract?
There's no...
Oh, these are all level 5s.
Okay.
All four of you go together.
And you're humble, little thing.
Alright, as an Italian myself,
I have to say here in the dub for Italian phrases another...
Languages is cringe!
Oh, you don't want to hear me say...
Spinji, spinji!
Aiuto, aiuto!
Aius mius!
Wait, no, that's Spanish.
Alright, we're going to go to a bank.
As an Italian myself, please say more Italian words.
Ai, ai, ai, aius mius!
To say...
I don't think I have any Italian words.
I'm ready for a little nap after eating almost this little snack.
I still have pea snacks left over.
I forgot to eat any of my reasons.
I'm going to have to put them back in the fridge.
I need to buy paintings.
Wait, do paintings?
Question mark, go to DNA.
52, 4, 7.
I just spent all my money on that then.
Oh, excuse me, you're in my way.
I just need to access the bank over here.
I don't mind getting a little wet, why not?
That's my favourite food.
Chatting, has to be chicken.
It's too tasty, I don't know, I just did something.
I like savoury foods over sweet foods.
Savory is just dab on.
Flags, feathers and chest.
Do they, do flags go to the percentage?
Because I feel like the DNA sequence doesn't, is like so...
Rough, colonel standards.
I can't do that, just do it.
Don't be detected.
Like, I don't like to...
Beat chaserie to the apple of Eden, don't hurt anyone.
How did I do that?
Because they're all attacking you.
Beat chaserie to the apple of Eden, don't hurt anyone.
I have my hand over my mouth thinking.
Oh, I don't have any smoke bombs!
I don't have any smoke bombs on my person, so I can't get rid of that.
Fried, oh, fried by far.
Yeah, for sure, would you?
Like, if you heard Nataline speak your navel image.
Sure, it might not be some bad, but you know, the accent can pack a punch.
The layers of Romeo, the war machine.
The war machine.
Wait, do these have a percentage?
No, these don't have a percentage.
Okay, this is why our thing is so low.
Okay, okay, we're gonna do Assassin's contracts, wherever the heck they are.
That's why the freaking percentage is so low.
These symbols, the pigeon groups?
Like, these ones, is it that?
Assassin's contract, right, okay, okay.
I was gonna say, because it's not making a lot of sense why the percentage is so low.
There's only a few missions that I haven't done 100% on.
I'm gonna be honest, and I don't think we're gonna 100% it,
but we definitely finished the game and I'm satisfied.
After the stream, we don't need to hop back on Black Ops on Brotherhood.
Because I'm satisfied with the playthrough.
Because I don't actually have much faith.
Okay, so I just need to kind of do all the black markers on the map, really.
Maybe factions also, half of it, if I get 100% favor in the factions as well.
KFC Yummi, honestly.
It's been very cozy.
It's more of a cozy day, I think.
Yesterday, I used up a lot of my energy on our replay.
Just being gushed in about this game and being like,
it's getting so cool, it's getting so awesome.
Today, it's definitely cozy.
It's definitely have a little blanky on you, make sure you're comfy vibes.
Yesterday, I was screaming my head off, just loving everything.
So energetic.
But I get to be like that unapologetically,
because nothing's worse than being excited for something,
and then someone's like, you're being really loud and obnoxious.
They're just like kills.
Oh, that's what I mean, I'm having such a good time.
You never met someone who's genuinely excited before?
Yes, faction challenges are also part of the peer-centered contract.
No, not that contract.
Mission.
Chesery hopes that our rebels will stumble into his line of fire
who's expected to come and wait and structure the...
kill the three targets in two minutes.
Oh my god, these have freaking things as well.
Oh.
Okay, I'm starting to understand why our DNA, I think, is so unbelievably low.
Oh, he's just out of range and no more.
Wait, under three minutes.
Three gunmen and under...
They're not that far away.
Okay, I guess the assassin's contracts are super nice,
because this guy's not that far away.
Oh, that was super reasonable.
Oh, I can't reach that.
Eh, that quick.
Okay, I was like...
Oh, oh, oh, oh, ow, ow, ow.
Me ankles.
I'm out of medicine.
Ugh, and smoke worms.
Oh, there's a doctor over here, that's perfect.
What was out of medicine?
See, the thing is, I don't look soldiers' bodies,
so I don't get anything from them.
Heal me, you should heal myself, no.
Sure.
Do the feathers count as DNA?
Oh, possibly.
You don't need ankles.
Right, so literally just do the pigeon coops and then it's going up.
Oh yeah, 53%.
Okay, okay, okay, okay, let him get up, let him get up.
53%, how do I go up there?
That looks like a hell to me.
That looks like a bit of an enslave, a bit of an incline.
Eh, I think tomorrow I'm going to save.
Which means I need to take a shower.
Put deodorant on.
I need to pretend I'm a normal person.
I'm teasing.
I do not stink all the time.
Wait, what was 100%?
Assassinate three guards with a hidden blade.
You do not have to tell me anything more, I assure you.
Hidden blade is a way to go.
Oh, they're on horsies.
I love when they're on horsies.
Hello, would you like to die?
Okay, hold on, let me try the game.
Would you like to die?
One.
They're all on horses.
No wonder the game's like, they're all on horses.
How am I supposed to do this?
Hello, would you like to die?
No.
Yes, wait, I did it.
100% already.
Skill?
Okay, wait, wait, hold on.
It's fine, don't panic, don't panic, don't panic, don't panic.
Let him get up, let him get up.
Oh, no, no, no, don't spank the horse.
Wait, wait, wait, get him, because he's got a bow.
Why does it not...
Do I need to like jump up onto the horse?
Ow, you're hurting me.
Okay.
Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay.
Let them cook, let them cook.
Yes, they got off the horse by automatic.
Okay, easy peasy lemon smoothie.
You're next.
No, you're not.
Are you coming?
I've lost sight of him.
Yes, there, get him.
3, 2, 1.
Oh, I missed it, I missed it.
I missed the timing source.
I sniffed for you too late.
Well, the weather's nicer for you.
It's mild.
33 degrees.
It's too much for me.
I'll pass.
Right, I guess we're gonna do Leonardo as well.
Oh, right, there's another one.
If we do that, the assassin missions seem like super fair.
Some of it buys for them right now.
And we can generate more money by sending our wee assassins to get more XP.
Oh, I'm gonna need a horse for this.
I said I'm gonna need a...
Wait, I'm blind.
I just passed off on the horse.
Sorry mate, my apologies.
If it's super easy to do the assassin contracts, we'll just do them.
Get them out of the way and then...
Hopefully that's like our percentage raised by like 5.
That's pretty good.
Actually, I could also use these mercenaries.
Well, I can't right now.
Hello chat, hello.
We're just trying to do what we can.
It's very unlikely we're gonna 100% it, but I'm enjoying myself thoroughly.
I'm actually gonna go get a blanket because I'm putting my legs on the table
and I'm killing circulation to my leg.
I'll just be a second.
I don't need to mute so you can...
What's that saying that's like, I love...
I hate to see you go, but I'd love to watch you leave or something like that.
Okay.
I'm returned already.
I'm gonna have my lovely blanket to protect my leg
because my circulation is dying because I pressed them so hard against the table.
They ain't sitting on my feet.
I'm cutting the circulation out of my leg.
All right, my chair is like so quicky.
Right, have we got any level 10?
No, we don't. It was a smaller mission.
I screenshot that.
That's an interesting scene.
I'm supposed to close my eyes before I leave.
So the thing looks right, but I don't think there's a soul here.
I'm just gonna keep sending people away to do more.
Oh wait, I'm a dumb dumb.
I was supposed to accept a assassination contract.
Missions.
Choose company.
Kill both targets for your hidden belief.
You do not have to tell me twice.
I'm loving these assassin missions.
Are you joking me?
I assume I don't have to get on a horse to reach them.
Where are we getting pretty far?
I can't tell which one's closer.
Eh, where is this?
Oh wow, they're like...
Let's do that.
By Austria and Switzerland, it's 26 right now.
Literally, the assassin missions are so easy.
We may be 57% once by the time we finish them.
If they make them this easy, then...
If you die, your assassin role before promoting them at max,
their cape match will be that colour.
I have no sense of colour.
Wait, that...
Assassin contracts are so easy!
I love it here!
What the heck?
Don't be detected and there's 18 billion guards looking at you.
Shout out to assassin contracts.
Hello?
I can't believe how easy these are!
Excuse me, Mr. Horsey.
Yet, in Maui.
6 and 8% finish.
Is that where we'll end on 6 and 8%?
I'll give the Leonardo missions a go.
It would be nice if 100%, but my goodness, I didn't know.
I'll see what happens by the end of this stream.
I thought I was only going to do 6 hours today.
Hi.
I'm sorry.
Bye.
It was nice meeting you.
What percentage are we on?
54?
55!
I love it here!
It says 55.
Oh my god, more contact please.
They're so easy.
Is there any more?
No, but there's Templar Agents.
Okay, we're going to do Templar Agents.
I'm totally not stalling on the Leonardo missions because I know they're a bit tricky.
Last Christina needs 75%.
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
We're going to do that.
We're going to do it.
I mean, honestly, it might be one of those things where I'm like, we'll do what we can.
I actually don't know how long we're going to stream today.
As I said, I was only planning on doing 6 hours-ish, but I mean, we're already getting close to that mark.
It's already been 4 hours and a half, and I'm like, I don't really feel like I'm out of stamina right now for stream.
Especially tomorrow, depending on how much I like the game, it might only be a tour stream, which is a bit meh.
I believe in a thing called love.
Just listen to the rhythm of your heart.
Yeah, literally, it may be one of those things where I end up actually getting so close that we do just go-
Oh wait, the bank, I can collect money from it.
Oh no, I've already collected my money.
I suppose once we buy the last, how do you call them, touristic locations, then we'll shall.
I'm trying to do the faction challenges on the way there.
Yeah, I need to hire thieves to lure people away.
You need to do it 10 times to their question.
I just need to find enemies.
Yeah, just like that.
We need to complete Christina!
Literally.
Right, what's this? Hi!
Are you a kitty?
Oh, it's not looking good.
She's beating up!
I will not touch you. What happened here?
Auguste, my beloved husband, he owns this neighborhood.
That Borgia have given it to him.
He once made signs for the shop's nudistic, but now he post lies for the Borgia and hurts those who stand in his way.
Like you, where is he?
He spends his days locked in his workshop, but I may know how to go them out.
What are we doing?
Kill your target with the hidden bl-
I love these missions, what the heck?
Aw, that's so easy.
Yesterday you said 8 hours and then end up being 12.
It would have been 14.
I don't know, maybe one day they'll fix the VOD issue.
If the day comes where they fix that VOD issue, please let me know because it is over for your sleep schedule.
I'm talking, we wake up, we brush our teeth, we get our food, and then we stream.
14 hours, put a vidyag in.
Wait, what am I supposed to do?
What?
Him!
Wait, it's the doctor? What am I supposed to do?
Oh no, it's the sign!
Interact.
Oh, we're pulling down propaganda, my apologies.
I didn't know.
Can you at least reserve the weekends, yeah?
Aw, you needing a break from my stamina?
You're so adorable, refling.
There's no breaks on this tree.
I was gonna say something else there, right?
I was really bad shouldn't have fallen out.
I'm not even naughty.
Alright, we're pulling down propaganda, it's useless posters.
Sleep is already ruined, what's a lot more ruined?
Choo choo.
Japanese man drained me.
I like them trying to do this.
Obviously they did the poster grabbing thing when you got no variety, but I didn't realise they reused it.
I quite like the concept, because obviously whenever you think of the past, you're like,
how did all these people even get caught for crimes?
It just seems so...
Kill your target within a move.
Can I rip it down or are they gonna be mad at me?
Okay, that's exactly odd-up smoke bombs.
I'll just do that then.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
I wasn't even...
Yeah, see that's what I get annoyed with.
If you don't enter combat before they whack you, you can't counter.
And I literally can't do a boom-boom, but here we go.
I might be able to get a smoke bomb off of this guy if I loot him,
which I would actually really appreciate in case...
Ancient Rome graffiti was here.
There was a Pompey.
We're at...
Oh, yes, he does give me a smoke bomb.
That was lucky.
I'll definitely try and remember to...
Oh, anti-drops!
The other guy drops smoke bomb too?
I don't know.
So when we pull this down, I assume we get to meet the guy,
and then we...
Oh, we lure him out of his workshop
because we've filled all those posters down.
Okay.
We can definitely do...
Other fanbases be looking at refills
like a man dying of dehydration.
Watch another man drowning!
That is so good.
What?
I predict.
I'll friggin' just say I've got Santa Man now.
I'm actually...
At least he well in this house.
I do feel bad when people have a streamer
that maybe struggles to stream.
I know, I just find that a really good time.
A good time!
Is that a multiplayer character?
It kind of looks like it.
It might actually be.
If it is,
then that's another compliment to the game
would be on how they incorporated
multiplayer characters into the game campaign.
I feel like...
Drowning is standing in this house.
Wait, did I not say that?
Did you ever play the multiplayer for this game?
I don't really think so.
I think I was aware of it.
56%?!
Okay, hold on.
I'm starting to have hope.
I'm starting to have mild hope.
I don't want to get anyone's...
I don't want to lead to anyone on,
but it might be possible.
It might be for the 100% run.
Because that's going up way faster now that we're...
Sorry, I should be riding horse right now.
Because literally I was so confused
why the percentage was so low.
Okay.
So let's...
Let's see what happens.
Let's see, we're at 55% I believe.
I've gone the wrong way.
Oh, no, not.
Oh, I remember this one.
That's stupid.
You go all the way around in order to...
Oh, actually, I'm going to send off a sassan with roots.
I need to level them up
and we need money, money, money for tourist attractions.
Wee!
I know, I know.
Knowing that a streamer you like is on most of the day
is a god time for viewers.
Yeah, I don't really get burned out.
I'm happy to talk about it, but...
I just don't seem to experience...
So don't get me wrong.
I absolutely can have days where I am
ready to go to bed,
but I wake up on the other side of bed
and I'm like,
yeah, let's do it.
What are we doing?
Let's go do this.
Let's go do that.
Send them off for 200 type thing.
But actual burnout,
I always wake up the next day
wanting to do something more...
Oh, there's actually a contract right here.
Wee!
Is that inside?
There's a killing contract inside here.
Oh, it's fantasy there!
Hello, madam.
Madam?
Let's talk.
Hard part will be the last 5%.
Yeah, I agree.
What's the hundred percent?
New assassin contracts on lot?
Say no more, my lady.
Say no more.
Okay.
Let me get up.
Okay, we've got more assassin contract,
which means the percentage will get even higher
very shortly once I do them.
Send away my assassins to level up and...
Oh, pardon me.
Excuse me, come through.
My ladies, would you like to distract those?
More ladies!
Would you like to come...
and distract some guards?
If there's any guards ahead.
Unfortunately, I'm on a horse,
so I'm much faster than them.
And the horse is stuck on the hill.
That's the only thing I don't like about this game.
Right.
There's no guards,
so we're just gonna...
We'll be fine, it's okay.
Where's this guy?
I'm on the wrong side.
Hello?
Oh, there you are.
What are these contracts doing?
Merda.
He would kill us if we stayed here.
Listen, I will run to the next pillar to draw his fire.
He's swinging her huge percent in her face.
Kill the target using the hidden bleed within 45 seconds.
I don't like times, but let's try it.
They're so bastard.
45 seconds, run, run, run, run, run, run.
He's gonna close that.
Okay, I can tell.
Okay.
45 seconds, hidden bleed.
45 seconds, hidden bleed, hidden bleed, hidden bleed.
I love hurting people with a hidden bleed.
Okay, we did it.
His name is Laquac.
What's your take on the best AC game regarding story-wise?
Exio's story-wise?
Like all of Exio?
Uh, like especially Revelations when-
Well, why am I under attack?
What's going on?
Come here, man.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, where did you even come from?
I didn't want to hurt anyone, though, as you're doing.
I saw that, so we'll grab it.
I didn't even know where those guys came from.
They're no station here, right?
Uh...
I don't know if I'm going to go longer on.
Hmm.
You know my favorite part of these?
Exio's killing a lot of the multiplayer characters.
Yes!
Definitely.
Okay, we'll go get this assassin contract.
We'll kind of just spin around the map again, like how we did when we were renovating everything.
Spin around the map.
Why is he whispering in Italian to a French?
I don't even know how you'd say rest in peace in French.
Dormez-vous!
Dormez-vous, mate!
So la-vous!
C'est n'est pas la vie?
No, no, it's not the life anymore.
My French is awful.
I get very confused with how these structure, like, words in French.
It's pretty...
Do you ever think about if Exio was really here to be an insane serial killer and probably
the highest killer?
Oh, yeah.
Actually, who does have the highest kill count?
Oh!
Don't answer that, actually.
Yeah.
Not necessary.
Thank you.
Okay.
Hmm.
Okay, I'm going to grab this flag right now.
Yeah, no, I asked the question and my brain then flashed up the answer and I was like,
ah, mm, mm.
Okay, we're not doing this.
Now we're just memeing along.
We're not really talking about each other.
I've discovered why my percentage was going up so slow, so we're currently in the question
mark stage of, is this going to be a 12 hour marathon to 100% the game or not?
Because I couldn't figure out why the frickin' game.
Oh, we need...
Okay, you guys are like so close to being maxed out, it's crazy.
I'm not going to send you away for 20 minutes.
So do you like that after doing that?
Yes, we do.
The other two, we don't even need to send away anymore.
More.
Do you need like 24?
No, you need a bit more XP than that.
Got a level 82 XP for you.
Yeah, that looks like quick math.
That looks good to me.
My brain was still explicit in the context.
No, no, I don't need me.
Oh, I need to accept the contract.
Actually, oh, I'm going to send the thieves on this person over here, actually.
Actually, factually.
As long as you set them on someone, you don't actually have to stick around or anything.
I'm going to grab this feather while I'm at it as well, because I'm really close to it.
Right, as well.
It's also a feather on the Colosseum that you go back for.
That's 6 out of 10.
Wait, why are you guys still following me?
Did you not lure their guards?
I guess they didn't activate because they weren't close enough.
Wait, do you only lure away stationary guards?
Can't he be?
Oh, wow.
I did not know that.
I thought you could lure anyone.
So I have to pick stationary guards?
I have not bought the Colosseum.
I actually might have enough.
Right, there.
Right, they're luring him away.
I'm going to go and get this nation.
Oh, a maestro.
I saw that, I saw that.
I need five assassins to be maestro and then we'll do some more reblet.
You just have to be good at the game.
I say you're done.
Wait, is this funny?
I'm coming for you.
Constantinople.
Wow, you actually...
Right, I'll send them two together because they're not ready yet.
No, I keep forgetting to accept the fricking contract.
Hi, hi, hi.
Yes, yes, yes.
Right, what's the mission assignment?
Make a nice and easy peasy.
Finish the memory within two minutes.
Where am I supposed to go?
Do I need to go by horse or not?
Yes or no?
The thing is, you take...
If you just directly sprint...
Yeah, see, this is the problem.
All this stuff is in the way in order to get to them in under two minutes.
Gallop, please.
Yeah, okay.
Faster, faster, faster.
Yeah, okay, the horse was definitely the better bet.
You could not run that.
And just says do it in under two minutes.
So...
Yeah, what are you?
They're on horseback.
No, that makes fighting so annoying.
Oh, sorry, I've got a nitri nose.
So if my tracking goes away...
It's a running face.
Okay.
Okay, so glad I took the fricking horse.
Holy crap.
Okay, that's...
It's just so easy.
It's so good.
Like, I love these missions.
Holy crap.
I had no idea how easy they were.
Oh, excellent.
It's like that.
Literally a minute to spare.
Let's go, let's go, let's go.
Another one.
Oh, do you want to come with me and we'll distract some guards?
I should be so close to doing the distraction on...
Okay.
There's a guard over here.
Actually, I need to walk around.
I might distract.
I didn't do anything.
May I ask that?
Time to perish.
Are you ready?
Oh, is it because I had the weapon out maybe?
Yeah, I literally did not know.
So the good thing with the mercenaries, if you walk around with them to the next location,
you can keep setting them on new people to attack, so I'm just going to bring them with me.
And once they've attacked 10 people, then we have done that section of the mercenaries challenge.
Do you think Margaret Thatcher effectively utilised girl power by funneling money into the gold?
Parliamentary death squad?
Oh, jeez.
I'm just here to play video games.
I'm quite happy to admit that this topic of conversation is completely out of my knowledge realm.
No, I've never played it with monsters.
I prefer to play games vanilla to appreciate the way that the development team made it.
A lot of people don't like vanilla Skyrim, and I'm so sorry, but I just enjoy it.
I didn't know, because I played on Xbox, that on vanilla Skyrim, because I was on Xbox,
that the little dots on the floor were daisies and grass until I played on PC for the first time.
Oh, is it? Am I pooping or is that mud?
Why are they insisting on walking into me, honestly?
I just tried to watch A.G's stream, E.B's stream, but I'm deaf on my left ear,
so it went silent for 10 seconds on my right ear.
But you heard that? I'm like, I don't know.
Oh, bless you.
What happened?
Were you born like that, or did you get tinnitus?
Are they still not done with that fight?
Oh, the guy went back on his horse. I was actually going to send him on him.
Oh, they're still fighting? Come on.
It's just one guy in armor.
Come on, you can do that. I believe in this.
Horses kicking, literally. I've never had the horse being pushed into the floor.
Come on, mercenaries.
Come on. Yeah, there you go.
Right, we're going to send him on this guy now.
Thank you, sir.
The Guardia?
Oh, they're beating that horse up.
I don't know how many mercenary challenges are completed.
All their stuff is weapon-based. They're doing something impressive, a weapon.
We're going to say, do you guys need help?
Do you guys need help with him?
Okay, definitely. Do you need help with him?
Yeah, I'm done.
Thanks, guys. Glad I hired you.
Bought stone, bought things, taken so long.
I know.
I've almost done sending the mercenaries on people, at least.
Is this, like, five, maybe?
If they could just perish some a bit faster, you know, we can be there.
And they tell him, like, just hooded man on horse since four men to fight.
Ten years working around engine rooms.
Oh, no, that's, like, the quickest way to lose hearing.
It's, like, works like that.
Okay, moving up.
Fire messages disappeared.
Mozi, y'all feeling okay?
Am I going crazy?
Rubber room.
I'm rubber roomed for the rest.
Stop.
Right, we're almost there.
We're almost there.
Right, fight him.
Fill him off the horse or something.
This is going to take forever.
Is there, like, another mercenary group right here?
Yeah.
Okay, can I have you?
And then can I send you to fight this group that's already fighting?
Oh, it works!
Okay, there, they're completely outnumbered.
That must be, what, six now?
Only four more to go.
I'm born deaf in my left ear.
Perfect for sleeping because I sleep on my right side.
Okay, now, follow me.
So this will be seven?
Oh, for goodness sake, that's taking forever.
I'll do that, though.
Because when you send them, they don't have to win the fight.
It's just when you send them on people.
Actually, you know what?
I'm just checking.
I can't take this anymore.
Gale challenges.
Mercenary?
Nine?
Okay.
Ugh.
That must be done from a certain location.
Yeah, double assassination.
Three out of ten, I can hardly get it done.
Court is on, nine.
Oh, guard's poisoned.
It's fifteen, so I do need to go poison.
There's kind of more guards.
I assume if they hate each other down, it doesn't count.
Okay.
These, honor, honor, and spread.
Leaves of faith, I need twenty.
Guards are assassinating from me.
Okay.
Oh, there she is.
I just need to find one enemy.
Hello.
You are enemy.
And fight.
Okay.
Finally.
That took so long.
Hiring discount earned a little bit.
Hello.
Man, look at his fresh cut on that beard.
Look at that angle.
Is that even possible by then?
I was really dumb, but, like, before razors were invented, did guys just, like, shape their beard on rocks and stuff?
Like, I know that sounds really silly, but did they, like, fashion a rock to be sharp?
And then that's how you got rid of your beard?
Or did, like, everyone just have beards back in the old days?
The razors weren't a thing.
Maybe glass?
It was a hundred percent.
Kill by air assassination.
I can absolutely do that.
Shave with swords.
Not, like, before that kind of effect.
What the heck must we do on this stuff?
Oh, wow, that's such a good faraway.
Um, maybe or something?
I'm tired of thieves.
They may be able to keep up, if I can do a little way to guard things.
Yeah, yeah.
We're getting there, we're getting there, we're getting there.
Here is, oh, I'm getting stuck on a rope.
They shaved with knives.
They just got the homies to scratch their beards off by hand.
That sounds painful as anything.
Shave with obsidian.
The guy's still dead.
Okay, what am I supposed to do?
Oh, air assassination.
Okay, I'm gonna go out on a limb and say the guy's probably up in this building then, since it's all red.
Not gonna be discovered, am I?
Hello, goodbye.
Actually, I need to start looting bodies, cause I'm getting low on supplies, cause I'm wasting them all.
Mid.
Okay, air assassination.
Let's give that a shot, where is he?
Gee, I wonder where it's air assassination.
Oh, I just called him a horse doing that.
I need to get away, that's why I called him a horse.
Having strongies mug on two monitors is overwhelming.
Wait until I make hypnosis.
I'm so excited to make my first one.
I don't know what to do.
I was gonna do a, like, free thing.
God, these missions are so good and easy.
I can't go over it.
I'm not doing the Naruto.
I'll keep doing the Templar Agents, cause it's starting to get less and less.
Copernico is a nightmare, if I remember correctly.
Copernico is, like, throw yourself across the city as fast as you can type missions, which I despise.
And, like, it really does not give you, like, much time at all, so I'm not looking forward to doing Copernico.
No, I don't need the body, but thank you.
Hello, horsey.
Are you ready?
Mount.
Mabos.
Well, the horse, please think of Mabos.
Okay, I think we're gonna pull one way around.
Speaking of, are you gonna collab with Secret Subject?
I haven't reached out yet.
I know Secret is, like, super busy.
Like, she's got, like, the new VTuber model and everything going on.
And, uh, I don't want to be, like, a bother, like, harassing anyone.
I might get the boss to reach out.
But at the moment, like, I've actually got quite a lot of people that are interested in collabs with me,
and I'm gonna try and, like, not take too much time.
Like, as she says, as she plays on stream for 12 hours,
and literally has, like, folk waiting on her right in the script, so it can be sent off.
Well, that was fun.
Um, but yeah, I don't want to leave too much of the pee.
Send you away.
Can I send?
I'm so sorry. I think I need a drawing.
I think it's time.
The problem is that I take, like, five minutes to generate one.
I really don't want to go.
I know it didn't happen yesterday, which I'm really happy about,
but I think it's happening.
Oh, wait, sorry. Oh, sorry.
I need to go into an emergency meeting with one of the girls over something.
But I'm, like, 90% sure I can feel my organs shifting around.
I have no coin on my corpse.
Ah, I can hear them behind me. That's actually pretty scary.
Nah.
Oh, no, no, no.
I will take advantage of the smoke, because we need to kill enemies in smoke.
Right, they can all just fight each other.
Oh, I need to go into the smoke.
Any idea when the first hit in the stream I'll do my job?
It's time is my biggest problem.
Like, if we end up doing this 100%, I don't know if it's possible.
Then I probably won't do it tonight.
Needy streamer, I need to go out and buy American sweets for this hand cam stream
and clean up my desk, because it's an absolute mess.
And get a nice cute outfit and all that.
It's just time, honestly.
I hope it doesn't sound like I'm not interested in making it.
It's just time I've got these Ace Mark gloves and girls are waiting on me.
And then I'm sending away shorts of the girls to be made to Clippers,
because I didn't want them being stressed out having to organize this stuff.
And, like, I guess it's just trying to settle in right now,
but I hope to have some consistent stuff that's free to access.
Like, I do want at least something decent free to access on the alt,
because I don't think it's fair, like, especially for, like, people just,
they just simply don't have the money, like, I completely understand,
like, don't ever feel bad if you're unable to, like, just straight up give money
to, like, streamers or anything like that, like, any of the viewers.
Like, I am 100% can say right now that, like, all the girls feel the exact same way as me.
If you can't afford it, please don't feel bad.
Like, literally watching, liking, commenting, flipping if you want,
liking a tweet, like, all of this stuff is free to do.
Like, that helps us beyond words.
So don't ever feel inclined and, like, thank you for respect
and that there, like, is a paywall on some of the content,
because, obviously, the girls need to eat and they need to thrive,
because if they don't, like, thrive monetary-wise,
then, obviously, they're not going to stick around at VLR, why would you?
So, like, I do appreciate everyone's, like, complete understanding around it.
Um...
Nope.
Right.
Okay, where's the source?
I am actually, unironically stuck.
Where the heck am I going?
Over the bridge?
Over the broken bridge?
The girls are doing great, don't worry.
No, not over the broken bridge.
Do not be fooled by the map.
It's not that old.
How do I get down though?
I always have that problem whenever I come up to this section.
You have to, like, all of your breath around me.
We're already lucky and spoiled with what you've done for us already.
No need to rush yet.
Like, I know some folk are noticing, like,
oh, all the girls aren't posting anymore.
And it was, like...
Yeah, the girls are live streaming now.
They're preparing for streams.
They're thinking our heads, like, like, that's stuff to do now.
Before, the only stuff the girls could do
was meme in the Discord with each other
and muck about on Twitter and pre-record audios, you know?
And now they've got so much to deal with and contend with, so...
What am I doing?
What am I doing before I mess up?
Kill your target?
Why is this game so good?
These game missions are so good!
It's actually making me angry.
Have nice interfaces.
Some... No, I do understand that some people, like, complain to complain.
That's okay. That's just how some people are.
Like, it's how they, like, get, you know, like, stressed out.
It's therapeutic to kind of have a mop or whatever.
It's a lady killer!
Okay, I need to chase...
Stop chasing me!
No, you like it, you little rascal.
You're teasing me.
You're a leaky.
I don't know what that means. They didn't put the subtitles in.
Stop it!
Oh, oh, oh! I love a good glitch.
I love a good glitch.
And that helps me get the objective.
I love that.
That was gorgeous. Do that again.
Honestly, Renaissance outfit starting to grow in me.
Kind of Renaissance influence outfit, maybe.
Someone suggested a design...
Which was...
Ah...
Was it an aristocrat?
Vampire?
No, it was a smug aristocrat.
Mmm.
I'm very, like, posh, hoity-toity looking.
The only problem is they would have to be British,
because if there were any other...
I was about to say if there were any other gender,
it doesn't work.
If they're not British, I'm going to...
Oh, Christina available!
Wait, what's her DNA if Christina is available?
I'm not questioning it.
To Christina we go...
Mom-
Any other gender than British?
Let's- I was like, okay, thanks, friend.
Stroney?
Yesterday, don't follow Lady Hoon, also me.
No, no, no, no, I like that.
It's a lady assassin, though.
Only I am allowed to raise lady assassins.
Okay.
Something, Christina, because I have no idea
what the heck that your fricking story line is.
Alright, I need you guys,
because you guys...
I need to lure away guards with...
Can I technically get you guys to...
Well, why are you...
Right, I guess not.
There should be some guards coming up.
God, they can run fast.
They're keeping up with a horse practical.
Lure them away.
There we go.
Aristocrat with a Jordi axe.
Wait, I always get so...
spun about when it comes to this section of the map.
It's terrible.
I think it's on this stage.
Stuck their anger.
Watch out, watch out.
No, no, no.
No, no, I missed something there.
Goodness me.
I just can't even get this right.
Can't I just go on the wrong way?
On the wrong way?
You're the one that's right.
Oh, excuse me.
You're on my way.
I could have sworn there's a cape
that makes guards ignore you
unless you, like, straight up attack them.
I need to get into that.
I don't know what cape that is.
Oh, wow.
I think that's 5-1-2.
I'm just going to send them away for money
because I think we actually might have enough now.
No.
For...
For what?
For buying everything yet.
Right, Christina, my love.
Thank you for unlocking
because we were genuinely also confused
on what a bizarre ending your storyline had
because that didn't make any sense.
And you know it didn't.
So what on earth are we doing?
Oh, no.
I think we're going to the fair.
Do you get an AC monster?
Maybe put, like, an assassin's screen.
Hold on me.
So there'll be an assassin's screen.
Oh, I've never thought about that.
Maybe I should get AC's outfit
and, like, but, like, you know,
get the, like, red, lazy underwear and stuff.
Leonardo!
Aww.
He's not over her.
He's heartbroken.
That's so sad.
I can't remember what we have to do here, though.
Oh, there she is!
I'm to tail her.
There she is.
With her other hussies.
Oh, Christina.
I'm just so interested in these masks.
She just got a circle.
Wait, what was it?
Am I supposed to do something?
Oh, plan a letter on her.
I beg your pardon.
I was like, why did she just go in a circle?
Okay.
That makes much more sense.
Way more sense.
Okay, the rendezvous?
Don't mind me.
Wait, she reciprocates.
Um...
It's you, that's wrong.
This is...
It's you.
I haven't seen you in eight years.
It's been eight years?
You're right.
I wouldn't have.
It's you.
The last time I saw you,
you kissed me in an alley
and then left me behind to be married.
It was the right thing to do.
We loved you.
Who cares what he wanted?
I love you!
You have your second child.
Please, Edson.
It got worse!
Why did we do this?
Why did we play that memory?
It got worse!
Is that where it ends?
That was even worse.
Why did we go away?
Why did we go further?
There has to be another one.
There's no way.
It got so much worse.
That was terrible.
Aw.
Shot through the heart, true.
That got even.
I don't know why...
I don't know why I thought that memory would...
Oh, that's going to be so much better than the last one.
No.
No, no, no, no, no.
That's terrible.
Well, she said don't find her again.
But I'm left unsatisfied.
I feel like that's such a short memory
that's not like the true ending.
Right, we're going to upgrade our assassins
just because...
we have the thing.
I'm a ballard about the seas, honestly.
I have quite a lot of money, though.
Good on Christina for not being a cheater.
Literally, like, when...
Oh, when she was like, oh, husband's name.
I was like, wait, Ezio planted the lair and...
What a mess, Ezio.
What a mess you've got yourself into in a pickle.
Yeah, he sucks when it comes to romance.
Everything is permitted.
Goodness, gravy.
Mm-hmm.
Whoa.
Welcome to the Brotherhood.
Yes.
Did I get the thing?
Mm-hmm.
Suspend points.
Assassin's Guild challenge is complete.
Okay.
Uh, is that...
Oh, Guildcrest.
Stop, is there something new around here?
This?
We get little things.
We get trinkets.
Oh, my God, this game, I'm sorry.
This game was made for girls.
You're telling me.
I get a little sim.
And I get to put it in my little house,
my little assassin house.
Okay, sorry.
I love this game so much.
How did it know?
How did it know I was a girl?
Good night.
Rest well.
See you in the morning.
Mm-hmm.
Oh, this game.
Gender norms go hands, my goodness.
Ah, right.
I don't really want to start Copernicus.
We'll go by the Pantheon.
Augusto, my Pantheon.
We'll go by this because we literally do have a...
I'll check the bank in case any interest is made.
Accessories, Claire, I can't believe it.
I can't believe I get to decorate those assassins' freakin' hideout
with my Guildcrests for all my hard work.
Ah.
We know the target audience.
Honestly?
Is Assassin's Creed Brotherhood a girls' game?
The only reason I say that is because it's, like, such a good game.
Like, it doesn't...
It's, like, so hard to get, like, genuinely to get stuck in, like,
at any part is next to impossible.
Mm.
Oh, I need poison guards, actually.
I'm just gonna, like, muck about.
I don't want to poison, like, anyone in front.
But I think they need to, like, pass away from poison,
or it doesn't count, because I'm pretty sure I've poisoned quite a lot now.
Um...
Game's so good it breaks the gender barrier.
Why is this one so goofy looking, honestly?
Wait, are you saying if it's easy to...
I mean...
I don't know.
I feel like whenever I see, like, a guy review a game,
it's always, like,
I love the challenge of this game.
I love having to repeat the same thing, like,
12 times over until I got, like, unspanked.
And, like, I figured it out.
And I'm, like, I just want a chill experience,
like, make it through the story mode,
and have a good time.
And, like, yeah.
I'm just a bad gamer that wants indie games.
Not if you're a game journal.
I feel like Brotherhood is such a great game that boy's angry.
Yeah.
My little cousin played it after watching me play it.
So who is?
Someone's gonna get beat.
Then you gotta love Dark Souls.
I mean, it's basically what you...
No, Dark Souls is the opposite of what I described,
and I know for a fact why it is.
Because I have had the pleasure of playing Elden Ring with the Wreethlings,
and the truth...
You want the truth? I don't think you can handle the truth.
I would not have been able to complete that game on my own,
like, I just don't see how I could have done it
without all the help of the Wreethlings.
That's the truth.
You think you can handle the truth?
I need Poison Guards alone.
I'll just poison them when I attain.
I think I need to wait until they expire as well,
which is the biggest problem.
You just like your hand being held, didn't you?
What?
What do you mean that all these people are being so nice to me
and helping me through my game and I get to reward them?
Maybe I should do that.
Like, every time we do a game where you guys hold my hands,
like, I do a reward audio for it.
And then, like, when I'm doing the ending part of the reward,
I'm like, thank you for helping me, thank you for helping me,
thank you for helping me!
And then, then I pop.
You know?
That's terrible, I know.
Can you poison on horseback?
It says shoot.
No, you can't poison on horseback.
A spank in that horse, jeez.
I'm not gonna hang around until I need him to expire.
I wouldn't be able to...
Wait, we played what?
Elden Ring.
Elden Rings are really good game to carry.
Hmm.
They're all looking in opposite directions.
So I can maybe do two.
I can maybe do three if I get this guy.
Oh, no, I can't, they're both...
That'd be amazing.
Games should have some challenge, though.
Yeah!
No, I do agree.
There definitely should be, like, some consequence.
Or else, if you don't feel like any pressure to do anything,
then you don't enjoy the game.
Like, it's really hard to nail what kind of dynamic
that you wanted.
Like...
Oh, I'm in trouble, I'm sorry.
I am a naughty assassin.
I didn't hide well enough.
Unless...
Dun, dun, dun!
Oh, don't push me.
Get poisoned.
Plop, plop, plop.
Get poisoned, get poisoned, bloop, poison.
Everyone's getting poisoned around you.
Oh, please spin that pole around.
There we go.
Okay, I managed to replenish.
Oh, like, a ton of poisons, which is good.
Oh, hello.
You're going in the well for thieving from me.
Goodbye.
Um...
You can come out now.
It's okay.
I'll come get you.
I did not mean to do that.
I don't think his life should have been forfeit,
but...
I mean, was it kinda deserved?
I don't know.
That was a bit morbid, so I'm going to be honest.
I actually didn't expect that.
Please, mommy, don't poison my iron brew.
I have a can of iron brew in the fridge.
Look at this!
But it ages ago, and I'm still not sipped up.
I need, like, the perfect meal.
I miss British fish and chips so much.
I'm sorry to any Aussies listening.
Your fish and chips are rank.
Okay, I did the court exam.
Can I poison?
Can I poison all you guys, and then push you all away
so you don't do that fighting thing?
I hate when they do the fighting thing.
I think if they, like, hit each other with the swords,
it doesn't count as poison, so I'm going to try and separate them.
Oh, he just did it there.
Mmm...
No, I tried.
I don't want to leave the vicinity too quickly
before the poison's out somehow.
Hey, I'm not going to find it with fish and chips around here.
Yeah, Aussies use shark.
Like, I think it's called gummy shark.
It's not actual shark.
Meat.
It's just a fish.
How do you call Germans Scottish?
Oh, there we go.
We did the poison guard.
Rank five.
Court is on...
Did I say court is on poison people now?
Ladies.
I didn't know that.
Am I in Australia forever?
I highly doubt it.
It's very good to run a business from Australia
compared to the United Kingdom,
but...
Oh.
Well, you're saying get down to me,
but not to this wife over here.
What's he going to say?
No.
Are you joking me?
Yeah, it's good to run a business in Australia,
but I can't see myself being here forever.
Lance.
Ooh!
The British use haddock.
It's a delicious fish.
Are you in Australia?
Yeah, I am.
I'm doing a...
I'm making a corn.
I'm going to do a V-Tuber meet and greet
in Australia.
I did not look at what the 100% thing was.
Oopsie.
What's 100%?
Kill your target with a hidden blade.
Why is this mission tape so...
so perfect?
Hmm.
So, Ironberg was well with fish and chips then.
Ah, kind of.
I don't know what the best takeaway...
maybe unironically a Chinese,
but like a British Chinese.
Oh, I think I need to chase this guy
from the rooftops.
I think, yeah.
It's giving chase from the rooftops.
Hmm.
Merda!
What do you mean, merda?
Get bonked.
Hmm.
Hidden blade.
Lock on to him at least,
Exio.
Don't be afraid.
Water!
Exio.
The only thing I despise
is when you have to do, like,
assassin.
Can you come here?
Yeah?
No.
Come back.
Can I knock him off?
Why are you trying to hit the air?
Oh.
Goodness sake!
Stop moving a bit!
Just accept your death.
It's over for you, buddy.
Stop it!
Oh, actually getting teased.
Stop it.
There we go.
My goodness.
My tummy hurt.
No more food.
No more.
Have you eaten too much?
Can't forget.
Have you had any encounter with local fauna?
Ah, magpies.
I have befriended wild magpies.
Although I saw my first snake
in a cockroach.
Oh my god.
There's no such thing as cockroaches
in Scotland.
And I met my first...
And a possum.
Oh my god.
Possum are terrifying.
I don't like...
I thought they were cute.
The noise they make at night is like...
Te-te-te-te-te-te-te!
Very scary.
Not a fan.
Yeah, I had my first cockroach encounter
and I'm like,
I want to go back to Scotland right now.
Thank you very much.
Because...
Oh my goodness.
Possums are harmless if you leave them alone.
Yes.
I accidentally ran into one.
That sounds really dumb.
But my cat escaped the garden
and I had to go into my neighbour's garden.
And it was one o'clock in the morning
and thank goodness I'm no in America
because I probably would have got shot on sight.
Oh, I'm in trouble.
And it was absolute nightmare.
It was freaking so dark
and I had to run around
to get into my neighbour's garden
and there was a possum that was eye level in the fence.
And both of us basically,
like, both me and the possum were like,
eep!
But yeah, I had to dive into my neighbour's garden
at 1am to throw my cat back over the fence.
Yes, Gimli, I'm talking about you.
Don't do it again.
I never want to be in that situation again.
I had to stick a letter through the freaking mailbox
being like, I am so sorry if you heard any of that.
The ruckus last night, that was me.
No one tried to steal from you.
And I had to sign it with my freaking address and everything.
Her name is Gimli.
Yes.
Because she's Ginger.
She's got Ginger on her, so I named my cat Gimli.
So when I pick her up, I go, that's my wee lad, Gimli.
Hmm.
Excuse me, you said, well, the thing was,
it was literally 1am.
And like, they had the creakiest gate ever.
And I'm like, I'm like, Gimli, Gimli, get here,
Gimli, get here right now, Gimli.
And because she had never been outside the garden before.
And she got really confused.
And was meowing at the door of the neighbour
instead of coming back over the fence to me.
Like, I had been calling on her for ages
and I was trying not to wake up any of the neighbourhoods,
like the neighbourhoods area.
And I was like, Gimli, Gimli, Gimli, Gimli, Gimli, Gimli, Gimli, Gimli, Gimli, Gimli, Gimli, Gimli, Gimli.
Kill only Donato, big Donato.
Nobody, no, like, unironically, I had to toss Gimli back into my garden.
And yeah, she's not here.
Oh, the music's gonna do the thing.
I love the pickup of the music.
Oh my God, veterinary care, though, in Australia is so fairly priced
and so good.
My baby boy, he ended up injuring himself on something mysterious
and he had a cut on his leg.
And I phoned up a vet and they were like,
oh, we offer up a pickup service for animals.
And I'm like, well, I don't drive, so that's perfect, thank you.
I don't understand how you can do that, though.
Wait, I need to kill only him?
Simple.
You can bowl a cat.
What?
Where are my pills?
But yeah, I phoned up, I'm like,
my baby boy's got a cut on his leg, I don't know what happened.
Can I book an appointment?
I was gonna have to put him in a taxi with me.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, just becoming anonymous.
Don't hurt anyone.
Excuse me, good sir, I need this horse, I need the horse.
Please give horse, horse now, thank you, bye.
Ow, ow, ow, ow, horse, horse, come, horse.
Let me on you!
No, don't hurt anyone, don't hurt anyone, don't hurt anyone, don't hurt anyone, don't hurt anyone, don't hurt anyone.
Nice, I'm coming in my own horse, this is gonna be ridiculous.
No, don't run away, don't run away, I need the horse.
Right, let's go.
We're safe.
We're safe, are they chasing?
Oh, they're chasing!
Oh, okay, okay.
Sorry, sorry, sorry, I know which way to go, sorry, sorry, sorry, pardon me,
excuse me, pardon me, come through, excuse me.
Uh, right, which path does NPCs not normally take?
That's one, I guess.
Okay.
And we lost them, we're going pretty far now.
I'm still going, still going, can I go down here?
Oh, we did it, okay, I'm fine.
Let's go.
We took a neighbour cat cat since she got on a fight in Toril Fathom,
and I was like, give it away to her.
Yeah, like literally, the health, the veterinary care in Australia is so cheap and good.
And they were like, oh, we can like pick up your animal, and I'm like, oh, yes please.
And I was expecting like $800 or something, and it was like super cheap, and they were so nice.
And like, it was so quick until when I adopted him, that I was like, I'm so sorry,
I have absolutely no idea what the temperament he's going to be, like please be careful,
he might be aggressive, like I don't know how he's going to act, and they were like,
oh, he was just like a sweet little angel, and I'm like, oh, thank you, I'm so glad.
So what happened next with Gimli?
Oh, well, threw her back over the fence, and now she's not allowed outside without me being with her,
because she is a silly, silly sausage and gives me a heart attack.
I unfortunately live like on car roads.
Actually, one thing I'll complain about Australia is residential areas don't like have a speed limit,
or the speed limit is ridiculously high, and I'm not being funny.
The speed of freaking cars is ridiculous over here.
It's very Americanized, sorry, sorry to be mean and stinky, because I should be really thankful like that.
I even have like the ability to like, basically like check out another country type thing,
like I should be grateful and all that, but it doesn't mean I'm not allowed to complain, so I will complain.
But I'm trying to think that once, hold on.
So you did, literally, what she did was climbed up a tree and jumped over a fence.
So I basically, now she didn't get hurt before anyone's like, oh my god, you're,
was it a linear or whatever her name was, 2.0 or whatever.
No, I put her back on the tree, like I like sugled her back on the tree,
and then I knew she was back in the garden, and then I had to run around and go back in,
like in my garden and bring her back into the house.
And obviously she was on time at like, she wasn't not allowed outside for a couple of days after that.
We know you never helped me, yeah.
Oh, sitting in the chat for me.
Why you gonna go home?
You go into a car crash, listen to the sheebie, you're joking.
You're joking, you're in a car crash.
You heard it here first.
The violor is causing people serious damage to their health.
You've heard it here first.
Oh, we've done all the missions.
So we can do courtesans, we can do these.
We can do Copernacle.
What's our DNA percentage now?
62?
Wait, the treasures count as 100%?!
Ignoring the treasures?
Hope you're okay.
Did you have to like call the police?
I think you have to report it to the police if you get hit.
I'm gonna cry.
Oh.
Why are they doing that?
Okay, Leonardo says 18%.
I think that's holding us back on the DNA.
Right, we're doing it.
We're doing it, Leonardo.
Oh no, Majobi's came back.
You know, sometimes if you hold it, it goes away again.
It's coming back.
Where's Kaka Ann on when you need him?
I had a really funny story for him, but I don't even know if he's here anymore.
And it's the one that wanted to hear me fart in the toilet.
I don't know if he's still here.
But if he is, I'll tell you a really funny story.
And it's really gross.
Shit!
Yo-yoing your poop?
No! No!
A little bit though.
I feel like, oh, I think I've said this before,
and this is the dumbest statement I'll ever say.
But I feel like if you're a guy, if you're yo-yo, can you not like...
stimulate your pee?
Doing that?
Use a smoke bomb to stun the overseer?
Not overseer, sure. I can 100% not.
Easy peasy.
Yes, I do have a stun bomb on me.
Locate the overseer.
What? No comment.
Literally, like, isn't that a thing that guys can do?
Still surprised no one said, I'm doing it right now.
Right.
And then...
Oh, we got a double assassination out of that.
Oh, the others just disappeared.
Right, we'll do any Leonardo.
I've never felt good from...
Well, aren't you in luck?
I have a four-part trading series.
See if it's for you, and if you finish the series,
and you don't like it,
then actually, you were right.
It really isn't for you.
Whoa, that's a lot of money.
So...
You stay away from the back door.
I mean, I don't know if once you've done all those things...
If there's really much of a point of sending them away,
other than one, one, two, three, and four.
Yeah, that looks good.
Did she be heck on wheels?
Not? Yeah, I might not have even done it,
I don't know, honestly.
Oh, I think I need...
I think I need toilet time,
but it's gonna take me like five minutes,
because I'm a nervous poopo.
I'm a nervous poopo when I sweep with some wheezing.
That comes flying out of my nose.
I remember I felt more embarrassed by a streamer in my life,
because SUV man went,
what was that?
And I just went, listen to a podcast.
Oh, are she bees in your ears like,
like spitting on you and that?
He's like, weren't you listening to me?
Flying machine...
Oh, I think I picked like the hardest one.
Do not get shot while using the bomber.
Okay.
Do not get shot.
So am I allowed to be spotted,
or is this a classic warning being detected
because desynchronization?
Okay, I need to go poopy.
I'm nervous.
I'm scared of this part of the section.
Do you guys want it?
What happens if we all take a job at the exact same time?
I'm having lots of water,
so I need to make sure the organs are all ready
for this ball man about to drop.
Okay, I'm gonna mute.
I will be a few moments,
so do forgive me for this.
Who said link up or put mods?
No, I'm just kidding.
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah.
Okay.
I'm ready to poop.
I'm pooping around.
Okay.
Okay, so we're going to start with a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little
little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little
little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little
I don't know about you lads, but I came flying over me.
I'm grabbing my cup of tea and I'm gonna make a honey tea, I'll be back in like literally
a minute.
Okay that was already boiling.
Well, I have absolutely horrific news, I've not got any tea bags left, there'll be no
honey tea for me and this has shot me, that was a moment for me to, I'm so sorry if you
dropped in on that moment, we all collectively went for adobe, I can't believe I'm fricking
out of tea bags, I'm so annoyed at myself, I'm gonna like, the one thing I do like about
Australian supermarkets, they have big like stuff, oh my, calibration is off, hold on,
there, that's my calibration, I don't know why I was looking all the way over that way,
I have no idea if we're gonna be able to do this, do you want people to tell you when
the other girls go live or when you ask for it, please always tell me when a girl goes
live, I can't always keep up and I suck, right, I am not to be detected, interesting, if I'm
not to be detected, wait what am I supposed to do though, locate the architect, but don't
be detected please, okay, I, there's two together, how am I supposed to be able to navigate, you
play some games where you versus the chat and hypnotise them so you win honestly though, I
wanted to do an IQ test and then I want a chat to do an IQ test, like we do a poll for what
the answer is and see what like the results are, are they gonna spot me, wait, wow, I love all the
bugs in this game, full stop, I just love them all, game don't be detected, then why is that man on
the roof, how bizarre, wouldn't work, we make you work the victory, oh no you guys are allowed to win,
I wouldn't cheat to do it on the IQ one, but I think it hit me in the stream where I make
y'all dumb, really good, where the heck am I supposed to go, I assume I'm allowed to kill folk,
I feel like I need seven bolts, am I going crazy where, is he over there, is that him over there,
I'm having a, I don't have a choice, yeah I was gonna say I don't have a choice because he was
coming into the hay bale anyway, lower score is better right, I'm gonna be number one, chats IQ's
room temperature, but that's why we're so good for each other, we're so bad, is that tracking funny
to me, I think, oh my tracking is funny, I fucking hate this iPhone for some reason, sorry that I got
really aggressive out of nowhere, whenever it is horizontal it does not track me full stop, horizontal,
vertical, no when it's vertical it works, when it's horizontal it doesn't, but I need to charge it
while I stream, and it's awkward to put it vertical, it's not tracking being rubbish all day,
I'll just over enunciate my word, so you guys, I don't know where this enemy is genuinely,
can I, oh it was me, pardon me for being so rough, I guess I can do this kind of stuff,
and loot the bodies,
could you get some sort of tool to grip it and hold it in there,
oh, so it's on like the world's tiniest tripod which is adorable,
I'm so confused, honestly, I don't know where this person is, I'm supposed to be trying to find him,
I'm gonna loot these bodies and hopefully get more supplies,
because one poison, one medicine wasn't a deal,
I'm not good, the position of the arms is all wrong for the saltarello,
please expire so I can loot your body, sorry, okay there we go,
to be honest it's hard to tell if the tracking is off or not, since we don't have a reference,
all right let me build my webcam lets, where is this overseer, is he like in, is he below the
church or something, is he in it, is he the one by the hay bale, he can't be,
um,
have I been everywhere yet, I don't know,
so those were the ones that caught me on the outskirts, is he in the center and that's why,
no, what,
is he like walking around and I just can't tell, yeah the game's telling me to stay in this section,
I'm on podcast unless as long as it's your voice it's saying,
love cuteness is smaller they are, the cuter they are, true,
I'm, I'm one confuzzled girl,
okay, look at that, I think we're just gonna have to literally go around the map and clean it up,
because this is,
use eagle engine to differentiate, yeah but I don't know what to tell you, nothing is being
highlighted, oh there's guards coming, no they still, we're checking the hay bale,
they're like, those guards from down there come any closer or no, yeah, we will shoot them with
poison, like the game keeps telling me but I don't know what to tell you video game,
I've literally been to all sections of this map,
wait that didn't happen, okay, I hit them that time, I'm gonna loot their bodies to get all the supplies,
oh they'll meet them first, closer to the larger area, is your target in the building?
more poison there, the one thing that I'll say is a bit funny in this game, NPCs will walk into
guards that are like flailing about and it's like, bro, hopefully I can get more ammo off
these guys and I'm not spending more, I just get, I'm getting more poison back which is fine,
if I'm spending poison it's good to get poison back, but am I getting,
okay, I didn't, so he does just roam the map,
okay, all those guards, don't want to be these things because I stopped,
I didn't really see it turned back, I'm very confused with this mission, so like I had to
find him walking around and there's guards everywhere, I'm gonna go on the roof because
there's that rotating jewel here, there's, oh maybe a desync if he notices that people are ill
with poison, I don't know, beat up the architect, okay, fuck it, I'll do it, hopefully this gives
me like a loading point, give me the plans, right now, oh yeah, honestly me,
that took so long to progress, I do apologize, that must be painful, right, so what happened
now, I'm notorious, okay, I can deal with that, I've definitely progressed to the next loading
screen, so again we've not failed 100%, do not get shot while using the bomber,
surely I will do this first time when I get on the bomber, surely I will not have any issues at all
and I'm not going to be frustrated with this game mode, I'm already preparing for it, can I launch
on that, oh it hits you with a ver, oh sorry, I need time to perish like right now, so don't get caught,
no I have no interest, surely absolutely health and copium, right, next loading point, yes please,
oh I'm at,
I'm to not be detected by the two guards that are across from each other,
yeah, I'm not to be detected by the two point blank guards,
I can do this if that citizen doesn't get in the way, and then he will be distracted by him,
I said he will be distracted by the poisoned guy, can you, oh and now everyone's in the way,
get the fuck out of my way, Jesus, I know why they make the minstrels like that,
but they've made them a little too well, okay, they've made them a little too well,
okay yeah my tracking is like bugging out because it's horizontal, I despise you,
there's no way, or maybe it's the iPhone, hold on, give me, let me click for the
my elaborate set up from yesterday, I removed all the cups from my ring, look at them ass,
when I had the perfect set up,
that looks much more,
okay and then we'll look for supplies, the poor NPCs, I just know we're gonna fail this and I'm
gonna be so mad, because I don't know what to expect,
okay, these poison darts for distraction is absolutely gorgeous,
these NPCs in my fucking way, not gorgeous, okay he's gonna start attacking, I can see
the ones coming down the hill, I don't know if they're gonna, oh no, oh no they got attracted,
I'm just gonna hide in here, unleash the archers, good evening skulls, I'm nervous, I don't know
what to do here, I'm just kind of waiting around, waiting for the EI to kick in, so I don't know
what to do now, oh yeah that, must have been drinking the good stuff, must have been drinking the good stuff,
okay we're just gonna poison them both again, like literally poison darts are,
yeah you know don't be afraid to lock onto them when they can see us, no it's fine, honestly
don't be afraid, no I missed shit, we cannot be missing poison darts, no next one, use the other
guys, okay there we go, we're gonna let these two bodies so we can refill our poison, we're taking
it nice and slow, should charts start logging every bird, nah, okay these are both poisoned,
again we're gonna pick up, we're just gonna take it nice and slow, you know we don't need it too
fast, just relax, calming, cozy atmosphere,
but remember don't get shot when we are in the glider and I know I'm going through do you think,
I'll still finish it anyway, but
no, oh yeah, wow you get a lot more from them, okay I'm quite happy with that,
she be redirect, oh no they're all gonna see my terrible gameplay and me getting mad now,
I'm gonna be region, they're gonna know I'm a terrible gamer, nice cozy atmosphere, remember the
guys gagging and choking on the background, literally, I'm gonna just need a whistle to my
teeth, whistle while you work, your gameplay isn't terrible, it's rough on the dlc stuff because like
I don't know there's anyone up here,
oh my gosh,
I've just remembered how humongous this is, we have to get up there but we have to go like
and do all this dodgy stuff constant back and forth, oh no, oh no, no he can't see us again,
he needs to forget about us like right now, he needs to like okay, wow that was dangerous,
hold on, I think we'll be investigated by another guard, right there's one in there,
yeah and he's moving out, oh there's two of them, we're investigating the bodies,
I don't want to go down, I'd rather stay on the walls and go around to this tower stuff,
oh my goodness, she be caught and bummed herself, thank you for the wait,
how is your stream, are you steaming, please drink water, please drink lots of water, my dear,
we don't want any hangovers, she be and Emmy,
wait, both Emmy too, you both spend a stream at the same time, oh my gosh, hi guys,
oh my god, you both ended stream at the same time, I don't know, maybe you should like kiss or
something, geez, I don't know, maybe you should give each other a little kiss, if you're just like
so in tune with each other, please, Emmy ready to she be, she be ready to do
please get lots of water and food, she be, don't want you having any hangovers,
hi Emmy, hope you both enjoyed your streams, hope you enjoyed your streams, we are currently doing
Leonardo's missions and I'm currently debating if I'm actually capable of 100% in this game,
unfortunately my answer is it might be, it might be a no, I don't actually think I have the
thingy, just guarantee the vods getting nuked, okay, guys I'm trying to get you monetized on
YouTube, right, I can get him, I need this archer over here done, yeah, okay, I'm glad that looks,
that's good, is that a flag over there, I don't know, maybe just a treasure,
sorry it's fine, I'm teasing, you guys can do what you want, but I'm not, I need to go there, what?
Oh goodness me, que cosa, I actually think I want that guard to forget I exist,
she seems so grown up, it's fine, we're playing Assassin's Creed Brotherhood 2,
which is a very beloved childhood game of mine, I believe Mercy's coming online in one, two,
three hours, just under three hours, so if you are a snippet, you are welcome to hang about
till it's mercy time, that's very, oh that guy up there, I don't like him,
I think I'm gonna have to start looting bodies as well, because I'm running low on ammo,
so that was actually rather humus, oh what a post to be left on, POV, you're a harem,
that's the position she'd be gonna leave you in at the end of the night,
yep no bad, it's already dead,
wait it already got a warning, that was pretty quick,
that was pretty rough, Jesus, I private it over here, ah I should have gone,
ah let's see, let's do poison,
oh let's not do poison again,
oh she'd be making a smart move, five head move, this is so sad, I only got to see half of it,
there's always more ASMR streams to come in the future, don't worry, it's not one and done,
we're not, we ain't one and done around these parts, hopefully YouTube gets this stuff missed,
there's a few things going on with YouTube right now, this is a very slow based mission
by the way, because every time we poison I have to wait until they're perished and then I have
to loot them and then I have to go for the next part, I don't know if I can reach anything here,
just outside but I need him gone,
I need him gone or I can't be jumping around this tower,
he's out arranging these guys, but I'm not gonna do it,
Strani you're always streaming, are you okay, ah yeah it's called, I am sharing my childhood games
and I love them and I want to share them, it's a bit more cozy the day yesterday, I was a bit,
can he see me?
He can, man needs glasses, I mean Tuarev will literally let you upload, true,
lovely, lovely stuff, we will be taking this very easy,
I am not sure how to get
out of safety, we're gonna be doing a lot of poison right now,
I'm, I don't know if I can leap from there to that and I don't want to risk it,
that looks like a leap over definitely, like that 100% looks like a leap over so,
right they're currently poisoned below me, so I should be safe to make my,
there's a lot of red there, I think this is definitely what I'm supposed to do though,
a 12 and a 6 hour plus stream on your first week is all inspiring, I just really enjoy
these video games, I definitely will be focusing, please don't think my streams like are all gonna
be 18 hours, like tomorrow's needy streamer overload, I've never played it before but
it's definitely gonna be a shorter stream because I don't even know if I like it and
whenever like I have the, whoa, it's so careful, what happens if I spin around a beam
and a, no need to poison these two down here, I'm not risking it,
not risking it at all, we have come too far, right onto the beam,
I'm just going poison route because poison stops them from being able to see me,
and yeah, I'm gonna loot this guy's body because archers normally have a lot more stuff on him,
called fish are venomous, there is one called fish is venomous but my ink isn't venomous,
it's an aphrodisiac, it puts you under my alluring spell,
that's so, what is bro doing, poison them,
the lead artist for needy streamer overload is one of my favorite artists, I'm a sucker for
oh his and she booty's stuff, right, we need to be super careful because this is the most
ridiculous thing for trying to spot enemies, there's like guys all the way up this tower
and it is so hard to know when one's about to see you and I'm not freaking redoing this all over again
but I'm getting scared, okay I can see one guy up there, it must be there all on the roof
under your lure, not your visa, you might have a streaming edition, I can't believe it,
oh almost fell there,
you said you might not be able to 100% it, there's a few 100% that I genuinely don't know
and I'm worried about not being able to do my, like I just simply cannot do it and I can't
like call, I can't tap one of you guys into the game to do it for me and so I've still, I'm still
not sure this is going to be a 12 hour stream or not, I can hear music, how am I supposed to hurt
them all at once, I don't think that, is that a flag this room, no what, the sun's getting further
um, why isn't it, what am I supposed to do, no, oh, okay, okay, I understand, I thought I was about
to be exposed right at the end there, right, in order to 100% this mission, do not get shot
while using the bomber, okay, we have been at this mission for like 20 minutes now, all I have to
do is nail this off the bat and I don't even remember freaking doing this, oh I'm going to start
sweating, okay, don't get shot using the bomber, oh why can we not get like a little tutorial first,
destroy the workshops, I can do that, I can do that, it's fine, tactical camera, no not tactical,
that was awful, don't ever do that again, press retreat to fire, R2, oh no, oh my god I'm going
down, this is not good, this is not good, oh my god, I don't know the controls, I don't know the
controls, oh I don't know where the closest one on the map is, it's the one, if I take a right,
I don't think I'm going to make it, just go for the one that I'm hitting at, oh my god there's
archer towers, no no no no no no no no no no no no!
I didn't even hit that tower, yeah, see this is what I'm afraid of, that I can't 100%, I'm under
After the impression, I now have to redo this entire mission again.
I missed that again?
I'm trying so hard.
I think I'm going to have to go further away.
I don't think there's a checkpoint.
I never gave an indication.
Okay, there we go.
Shoot workshop twi- Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, my controller, Jesus.
Oh, please, my goodness.
I almost didn't make it there.
I did that.
Okay, then do this.
And I missed, so that's okay.
We just need to do it go around a bit.
Oh, well, maybe we're going to just straight up attack this one.
I missed.
Whoa.
Hopefully there is checkpoints because that does seem very harsh.
I completely, I did, I will admit, I twided it all up.
I'm going to get my own.
I need a fire right now.
Oh, goodness me.
Goodness, gravy.
They didn't even make this game easy.
There we go.
Destroyed that one.
Honestly, this section was a lot harder on paper, I think.
There.
All right, now what?
Only if you die, you have to repeat home missions if you play a port.
A checkpoint at the start of the bomb.
Destroy the bomber.
Where?
Oh, I see.
Speedrun over there.
Can we aimbot it?
Three, two, one.
Oh, I think that was a miss.
A swinging a miss.
Swinging a miss, swinging a miss.
Hold on, let's try again.
Wow, I cannot control this right now.
I'm completely looking in the wrong direction.
I...
Bruv.
Yeah, okay.
Controls, please, thank you.
Oh, no, there's more.
Okay, okay, it's okay.
It's okay.
I'm just trying to set a fire along the way.
I am... Hello, game?
Respond, please.
I missed, and it's okay.
It's okay.
We're gonna bomb that, get a bit of speed.
Whoa!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Whoa.
Hello, game?
Relax, relax.
Game.
I don't think...
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Game?
What was that velocity?
It was completely unnecessary, are you sure?
Game, up, put me up.
Put me up, put me up, put me up.
I want uppies, so I can aim.
I missed.
Oh, whoa, I actually hit that.
Wow.
That was crazy.
I don't think I was supposed to fly that high.
That was insane.
Oops, played it out of order.
Where's this, a horse?
Okay, turn around.
Every now and then I get...
Oh, I was too early.
Maybe there then?
Yes.
Yeah. Okay, that wasn't bad.
That wasn't horrific.
Whoa.
That was a crazy boost.
I don't think I was supposed to go that high.
I think the game mathematics...
It's way...
I don't think I was supposed to go that high.
Okay.
Because cool guys don't look
back at explosions.
Well, we did it.
That was not easy.
That was not fast.
I am going to open it up in the DNA sequence
to see if it's like, replay that section.
If it is,
then 100% is still on board.
If it's not, then 100% is like a much less likely
because this is getting hard.
This is getting tricky.
The whole thing.
I was worried it would say that.
I was so worried it was going to say that.
Look, we'll do what we can.
We'll finish the other Leonardo missions
and that.
But yeah.
This is going to be...
I don't...
That has just like dramatically
decreased the odds of being able to
100% it.
To go through all of that section again,
I was taking my time poisoning guards
along the way so I didn't have any issues.
That one attempt
and we got hit immediately.
That was the only time we got hit as well
which was just so unlucky because I wasn't sure
what the controls were.
That was so rough.
Come on, that hurts.
And that is why a late game gives more check.
Literally, that is so...
punishing.
Wait, can you 100% this game without being online?
Yes, the DNA sequence is what we're 100%
doing 100% of the memories and stuff.
I'm currently
63%
which isn't bad at all.
However,
I was under the assumption
the game was a bit more forgiving.
However, we've just kind of
discovered
the replayability checkpoints aren't
necessarily all there on certain
missions and
that is just so...
I don't know.
Let me see that.
Okay, go ahead.
Remember trying to
platinum the game.
Achieving wise...
I don't know if you need 100% DNA
for the achievements.
War machines
are infamous for a reason.
Yeah.
There's a difference between 100% and 100%
achievements.
So, yeah.
I thought we could maybe attempt
100% the DNA sequence
but, yeah.
It ain't looking good.
I mean, how long? Oh, it's already been 6 hours?
What the heck?
Okay.
Yeah, I didn't...
I thought I was only going to...
What was I supposed to do?
Use a kick attack against
the overseer. I
literally thought...
um...
If you don't do it in a movie,
this should be a thing you come back to
at a later time. I think so.
I think 3 days of Assassin's Creed Brotherhood in a row
is a bit too much.
But I'm perfectly happy to
come across the save fail. That's not a problem.
What was I supposed to do? Kick him.
Oh, no.
No, we're not doing this.
We're not doing this horse feature, but leave me alone.
You're scaring me.
Whoa! I actually dodged that successfully.
But the game said no.
So...
Oh, there you go.
A true lover of this game with 100%...
Oh, steady on. Have you seen what the requirements are
on some of the missions?
Oh!
Is there a wee bit of a...
Is there a wee bit much for me, honestly?
Like, I love this game.
But, I think
definitely
wouldn't mind coming back to
it. But I think 3 days of Assassin's Creed Brotherhood
in a row maybe ain't the choice.
We'll try Needy Streamer
and it'll be a smaller stream tomorrow.
Which means I can
go get the
sweets that I'm using
for that hand cam stream. I need to, like, prepare
for it and saw.
I don't even know what to wear.
Hee hee. I'm actually gonna have to put clothes
on for one. See ya, pee.
I don't even know.
I don't even know what to wear.
And one achievement
requires you to reach level 50 in multiplayer.
Oh, yeah, no, no. Not those achievements,
like the DNA season.
I'll be girlin' up neek.
Pants, sewer, cry, mutually.
Have to is a
strong word.
I think I have to.
Open one of the first three games.
The Borgia have constructed a deadly
naval war machine based on Leonardo's design
and must be destroyed before
Chesery.
The jeans.
Talk to Eduardo.
Ed Uardo.
I assume this is a don't get caught.
It's giving don't get caught.
Yeah.
I'm just a little fish.
Look, look, look.
No, I'm a fish.
You didn't see me.
I'm just a fish.
Fish, fish, fish, fish.
Swimming in the deep canal.
Canal.
Fish, fish, fish, fish.
I'm excellent.
If you hold the block button with the
floor ball and the horse coming out,
you can knock the raider down.
Oh, it says gasman prayer.
Me, through, through.
E.
Clothes strong.
I have six.
Oh.
Baby.
It's you.
Hello.
I would like you to take me on the canal.
Oh.
You are the assassin, am I right?
You must stop Chesery.
I will help you.
Let me take you to them.
Oh.
Like I said, I chose life today.
Thank you.
Uh.
Interacting with the gondola
will cause desynchronization.
I scratch my nose.
How tall are you?
162 centimeters.
Um.
Taller than
smoke bomb
disables guards. Assassin or sleep
fort wears off.
Um.
Excuse me.
Am I not allowed to kill?
No, I am.
So why not?
Uh, the gate.
What am I supposed to do here?
Nothing.
Oh, he just jumped on. I saw that.
I thought I saw that.
Oh.
Uh.
Okay.
Okay, okay, we're getting it.
Taller than a smoke bomb.
What's that?
Banana or freedom? Uh, 5-3?
I've not played Assassin's
orgy, no.
You're like me, also.
It's just a weird class.
It's just no flood me.
Okay, something's a flood.
I'm so sorry.
I just pushed that man in the water
and he drowned. I will say one thing though.
If you're a gondola pusher
and you don't know how to swim, isn't that
a bit dangerous?
Isn't that a bit silly?
I didn't even realize I was supposed to be up here, also.
Whoa, wait, why can he see me?
I thought we'd purposely put these beams here
so you can't get seen by the guards below.
Hmm.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
My pard in my bag.
Look at that. Just so you know.
Where is it?
Oh.
Pitching him wasn't the problem.
It was like you touched the boat.
I can't believe it. Fending Nemo?
I touched the boat.
How many slower, mate?
Okay.
Are you coming?
The frickin' twat
from across the street saw me.
Yeah, you do that all the way again.
You'd be surprised.
I was in the Navy and it only passed the swim test
because the
Proctor wanted me to go home.
Jeez.
I think if you're Scottish, you have to learn to swim.
You're forced to go swimming.
Let's just run ahead of this guard
because he can't see me at the corner of his eye.
But I get out of range,
which is good.
Gondola logging.
I've only got five poisons.
I could probably just
do that, man.
I've got 19 crossbow bolts.
They're quiet. I don't get it.
So it's all good.
That's fine.
So who?
Okay, so this time the frickin' guy doesn't notice me?
Yeah, that's what I thought, mate.
I'm such a wee liar, honestly.
He doesn't even spot me this time.
Sting.
I'm set to Scotland.
We've got school soon enough.
Oh, I need to go up.
So you're going to see me?
He is, so I kind of need to deal with you.
Sorry, but you're in my way, son.
You're in my way.
Poison, huh?
Just to get around the corner successfully.
The Bluetooth device is...
Why did you not go up?
Go up.
Go up and along.
There we go.
Much better.
How's your gaming going?
We MLG gamers out here.
Unfortunately,
I believe the 100%
will not happen this stream.
I did not anticipate
how hard this game is.
Because I've never attempted it before.
I genuinely don't know how it goes.
Right, I'm going to poison him and the other...
Eh?
I almost deseed,
but I think I hit a checkpoint.
I didn't...
I'm going to show you now.
I don't even know how you saw me.
I'm up here.
They're not supposed to be able to see you from up here.
Yeah, like that guy really...
There's like more to go.
Oh, that...
Get me in the war!
No!
I like that.
That's a pretty good detail, huh?
No...
It seems literally drowning right now.
He needs to catch a breath of
frickin' air.
Making him go under.
Oh, goodness me.
I don't know what to make of that.
They're not making this one easy, are they?
Oh, my goodness.
He took his sword out.
I heard it, but he needs to breathe
or else he pops up for too long!
He needs to breathe.
I need to breathe just thinking
about how long he's holding his breath, honestly.
Please don't do that animation
where you can't breathe.
We did it.
Oh, for goodness sake, there's more!
Breathe, exhale, breathe.
Oh!
Well done!
One, two, three...
One!
Okay, I think maybe I can
kill those ones
because that was really rough, right?
See, that was too much breath holding.
Any breathers in chat?
We stayed around.
Mm-hmm.
I'm going to Scotland in 2D.
Whoa, wait, how far back are we?
Huh.
That's pretty far back.
Okay, that guy doesn't care.
Oh!
I've just wasted so much time
dropping myself back here, but who...
Breathing is overrated, honestly.
I know the game's telling me to swim under this,
but, like, it takes so much freaking time.
Like, that guy is going so fast
in his wee gondola.
Like, he knows that I'm literally trying
to swim behind him in time.
He's such a lot, like...
You know I'm freaking behind you.
Slow it down!
Literally, I'm trying to, like, silently swim.
It's not even possible.
I think if I just hang off
the pier and assassinate him,
this is the best way forward for this.
Sorry, mate, but time's up.
Okay, yeah, that is far more easier.
I just need to do it to the other guy on the pier.
Sorry!
Oxygen addicts, honestly.
Can't get enough of it.
You're so greedy, huh?
So greedy for more...
more oxygen.
Okay, let's dive.
And then breathe.
And then dive.
And then yank.
Ezio, please do not go on the platform
when it comes to assassinating...
freaking gods!
Ezio.
You knew!
Fine well. I was asking you to pull him
into the water.
Not get on the platform
where the freaking AI
is so sensitive
and on the lookout
on freaking...
YOU FREAKING FREAKS!
Right, I'm just a serious
assassinating spam, honestly.
Game knows... oh, and he's gonna
fuck you.
Mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm.
And I'm out of honey tea
and I'm sad that I can't have
a freaking honey tube.
Gonna have to go to the shops.
Okay.
Right, I can take my time to this segment.
I've never been caught at it yet
so let's not go caught now.
We swimming!
Any swimmers?
You got any swimmers for me?
Shopping.
That's how it is, just that, honestly.
I feel like if I fast swim
I might alert him.
Now, if I am correct
what the problem was
is that I assassinated here.
I need to hang off and then assassinate.
Yeah!
But you knew exactly what I wanted to
achieve, so don't even look at me, okay?
Don't interact with the gondola.
Me swimmers!
My story.
Alright, let's...
Okay.
Why is he gulping?
I'm not even diving in.
Okay.
Hang off the ledge, please.
One assassination, please.
Back in the war.
Dive.
Dive over the ropes.
Don't be afraid.
Don't be afraid of the ropes.
That was very talented.
My life flash before my...
Someone say ropes.
She's still alive.
Especially not past that drunk.
I don't know if you're drunk.
I was not supposed to...
That's all I want to see, baby.
Okay, there we go.
Detection is now permitted.
Yee-haw!
Time to perish, boys!
Yeah, yeah, yeah, you want some of this?
I kicked it.
Actually, I need to disarm guards
and kill them with their own weapon.
Let's do that.
Give me that sword, please.
Yee, thank you very much.
Drop object.
And then we're going to do it again.
Can I steal your weapon?
Oh, it's not fighting over the weapon.
Okay, there we go.
He wouldn't go over it, honestly.
I wouldn't go my weapon to if I had one.
Now I'm chilling, cleaning up and watching
because I love these people.
Azura said she played it as well.
Emmy said she got it as gifted,
but she never played it.
Good night.
Those who rest, thank you for hanging in.
I love when I can be detected.
It's so fun.
Come on, who wants to first, then?
Okay, there you go.
Oh, no, don't grab me. Who wants to first?
You!
Ugh!
Take that.
And this!
And you're another one!
I love the crisscross kill.
It's so cool.
Oh, wait, I'm actually going to loot because those were pretty high.
Guard.
These guys act like they understand you're the main character
on a flittle.
Okay.
I thought I got more poison holdings.
Once we've done other Leonardo missions,
I think we'll do all of the factions
because I want to dress up my Assassin's Creed guild.
So it's girly pop, you know what I'm saying?
How do I get up there?
Or do I just leap?
Do I do a leap?
Oh, that was a big leap.
I don't think you should have been able to do that.
Hey, ho.
You can't see me because you're dead by the time
you process it. It's me!
Daddy's home!
Let's loot.
He may have poison on him.
They accepted that.
I'm going to go see you in the morning.
Oh, that's hilarious.
I'm focusing on that now.
Literally, good night. See you in the morning.
I'll still be online. Sweet dreams.
Have a good rest.
I'll still be here on Assassin's Creed on my knees.
Daddy's home.
They're more like guidelines than actual rules.
Oh, I do love this game.
That reason I did go watch
and get him out of it alive.
What's this?
What a switch.
Wow, I have to switch between rowing
and aiming.
I mean, I guess I comprehend that.
But, sheesh.
Oh, we're taking down ships!
Boo Templars.
Stinky Templars.
Switch, fire!
Oh my gosh, that's so cool.
Okay, sales destroyed.
That makes sense.
Won that one?
I only hit one of them there.
I'm getting wrecked right now.
All done.
Bye-bye!
Okay, okay, I like it. I'm digging it.
I'm digging it.
Oh my gosh!
They're like ragdolling off the ship.
Okay, that was cool.
I enjoyed that.
Yo ho ho.
It's a pirate's life for me.
A tweedalidum.
Tweedalidiliwi.
I don't know the words. I just know the shanty.
Yo ho, yo ho, yo ho!
Okay, it looks like there's just three.
And I have plenty of health, so that's fine.
Give me fuel in my fire.
Give me burning.
Put some oil in my land.
Eye free.
Okay.
Can I do it from here?
Possibly.
Can I do all three though?
I think I'm gonna have to go a bit closer to this one.
At the back here.
I think that's it.
That should be good.
No? I didn't hit it?
Oopsies.
Okay, there we go.
I don't think you can go back through,
so we're just gonna...
do our thing.
You are now notorious,
for throwing high alert.
I should hope so.
Because I'm still here.
Oh, they knocked me off my gun.
I don't even know what to do about it.
Hold on, lads. I need to rotate before I destroy his.
Dude, give me a second.
We just need to rotate.
I actually don't think I can hit it from this distance.
You know that?
Ow, I'm...
Wait, whoa, what's happening?
Okay, hold on.
Hold on. We need to do a big old circle around.
Cause...
I'm like...
too close.
To even hit this stuff.
Honestly, black flag will take through.
Going reverse is so slow.
Can you go backwards?
I don't even know if you can.
I'll try. We're just in the old spin around.
Did that hit?
I hope so.
Almost.
There we go. Beautiful, beautiful.
And last but not least,
let's not get too close now.
Let's not get too close.
We've still got some momentum.
One more roll should do it.
Get us front row seats to this pirate ship going down.
Oh.
Ow, ow, ow. They're hurting me.
They're hurting me.
Just out of range. Hold on.
I'm like just there and no more.
Ow, you guys are hurting me.
You're giving me a booboo.
Just out of range.
That was so close.
A little bit of a push.
Get too close to the point where I can't even fucking aim.
There we go.
We got it.
It literally is your tank in all the arrows.
That was kind of comedic
the way they jumped off the ship.
How are they not lunch on you?
Honestly, there's literally cannonballs.
Literally BRB.
Sorry, I can't aim at your shields. Let me just do a little spin around.
Ooh.
Oh, we're shooting at itself.
Wow.
Splish splash.
I was ticking fast.
Oh, we actually got 100% sync for that.
Okay, I'll take it.
I used to love this game.
It has a fantastic taste.
This is my number one game of all time.
And I suck at it.
Is there one more Leonardo mission?
Yes.
How are they always on the opposite place?
There's one.
This is Leonardo.
And then we'll get the Guilds Faction Femme.
Tank tank tank.
You are good at sucking.
Sorry, I'm making an animated shot
of your reference sheet for the meme tag.
Should I bring in the tweet?
I don't know when it comes to
memification of something.
You don't have to credit the original artist.
I don't know. What do you guys think?
You're probably better known than me.
I did credit her right under the
thingy so people know
it is by her under the reference sheet
at all times.
I don't know.
These hay bales
were so confusing actually.
One of the games I love the most
is called Dynasty Warriors.
AC Brotherhood was the last game I
truly played in the series.
Yeah, Revelations was alright.
But
it wasn't Brotherhood.
If I had to rank them as Brotherhood
then AC2 and then Revelations for
Exo's storyline.
I went on an adventure trying to beat
all of this
but I stopped at Syndicate.
I think I've played Assassin's Creed 3
maybe unironically three times.
It's just no fun.
ACR had
a fucking turret defense.
Literally the turret defense.
Do slash credit.
Yeah, maybe do slash credit just so it's
not like
bothering.
But the credit is there for people who do
want to use it.
Yeah, people say they love Black Flag.
I struggled so much to get into it.
But I'm wondering if it's just because I'm a
little crybaby because AC wasn't
in the series anymore.
Which is very plausible.
I wouldn't mind to try and get
Black Flag. One more big hood.
Yeah.
But I just
really seem to struggle with the controls
but it's probably because I'm doing
the, well I've already played Assassin's Creed
so I don't need to sit and read the controls
well obviously they have changed the controls.
I'm
you're being a crybaby.
I wish they would make
more like story multiplayer games.
Like
it takes to
is like such a good story
thing and I would absolutely love to
play games like that on stream and be like
okay after the first chapter we'll get
someone else in, okay next chapter we'll
get someone else in but like they just
didn't do that. They just didn't do that.
It's so annoying.
It's so frustrating.
I can't believe I can't play video games
exactly the way I want to
play them.
It's such a baby.
Kill the Templar overseer to recover map.
Use the pistol.
I can do that.
No.
Yes. No.
Yes.
Yeah I was going to say you sure you want to
fight this. Oh wow
it's always you guys that want to fight.
Stop this.
Fuck it Sam.
Not really.
I'll see if I can loot a smoke bomb back.
I've been having a blast
watching a veteran on a newcomer play the
Halo.
Oh yeah the Halo campaign
is going to be playable.
Where am I supposed to go?
Okay last one question mark I think.
Is it like
safe to do
a Halo campaign?
That would be really cool to do a
refling. It's not going to lie.
I'd be pretty hyped for that.
But I don't know how safe it is to like add
people.
Because I don't think I can just instance and
have you guys in.
It would be pretty cool to like
I don't, is it
duo only or is it four man?
Favorite game combat of
is it evolved or
evolution?
Oh my gosh
it's John Halo from Fortnight.
Laying out his tank
is an ambitious and devastating war machine
capable. Do not take any damage while in
the tank. Yeah good luck for that.
We're not doing this one.
But you know
I have name poison
which is decent.
Is he going to come see me?
Oops.
Yeah we're not doing that.
Literally everyone's getting poisoned.
I don't care.
I only have name to watch.
I should have bought some more at a healer.
Yeah maybe if
it's safe to add people like on Halo
then we could do
playthroughs of that but
I guess you
do it mission by mission so like we would do one
mission and then
kick out and then add
and then next mission kick out
you know.
You see nothing.
How did you guys not shoot?
It's a poison dart so it's supposed to
just be like a little swing
and no one knows.
Literally poison is so OP for like when it
comes to don't be detected because you can walk
right in front of them and
obviously the crossbow does the exact same thing
but I don't know how to say it.
Poison's cool.
Oops sorry.
I was pulling down my sleeves
I'm getting a...
That's right I'm wearing a hoodie.
You'll never guess why.
Wait how am I supposed to see him?
I love how as soon as you go sideways
they just don't care anymore.
Beat up the architect.
Oh okay.
Hello.
You're so aggressive.
You just ask before beating up.
We're helping people.
Go home.
Checkpoint reached.
Amalo to be seen yet?
No.
This music is so dramatic.
Checking my heart for that.
You can go first.
Sucks to suck.
Sorry but if someone had to bear.
We could do two poisons here
just to be doubly sure.
We could probably do...
Can you? No I really...
Oh my god that alerted him?
No.
I need this guy to par...
Stop hurting!
And then in order to unsheathe my...
Right you're next.
You're freaking next.
Now that I can see you.
Jeez you're such a pain in my butt.
Not the good kind.
You're next.
You're all done.
And everyone's perished.
And my ankles are sore.
But it's fine.
We did it.
First thing I checked
was she still screaming for me.
No.
I would have gone the 14 hours
but it didn't work.
Free the mercenaries.
Can I still be...
Can't be spoilers?
So I don't even hear?
Doesn't look like it.
Hi mercenaries!
Where is Dabinchi's machine?
Follow us. They have hidden the path
but we discovered the entrance.
There you come lads.
Three mercenaries?
Oh not two.
Follow and protect them.
Well maybe if they didn't
jump right in front of the enemies.
Then sure.
Wait wait wait you're done.
I'm farting.
You're done.
Oh it's good to see me.
Hopefully they can actually fight a weaver.
No! Why are you fighting one of them?
Why is there...
Please stab them in the...
Oh and yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah.
Stop it.
I hate when they do that right.
Where are you taking me?
Step eight Rizzo.
Fart in the guards faces.
Get him first!
Get him first! No you missed him!
You were supposed to get the other guards.
Right right we're farting again.
There we go.
I should have got that guy first actually.
Oh and he's right around the corner.
I'm just attracted to the tent.
Please just perish your one HP
in a freaking dream!
And it's not even registering
my kicks probably.
And that guy's getting beaten up by a brute.
Yeah they're done.
Can I loot in time for another
fart bomb because
we're needing them.
I got one. Okay I actually got one needed.
Let's go for it.
What's that?
Open inside?
Hold still.
Wait for me.
A little bit parkour.
A little bit parkour momentum.
Okay there we go.
Open for you.
Open sesame.
Did I just say open sesame?
No.
Remember that time
I got asked about open sesame?
And I said open cumin.
Good times.
I'm such an idiot.
I don't know if anyone remembers.
Saved!
Jeez it's you.
I did not think I would get here.
I don't know why my brain blank.
I think it was the way the question was worded.
I will lower the bridge.
Can I lower the bridge?
I guess I can.
Open sesame!
Or open cumin.
I don't know which one seems better than me.
I don't know.
Is there a lever?
I don't think so.
The way you recalled that.
Literally my brain was like
recalling memory loading.
Memory loaded.
It's open cinnamon.
Music?
Oh my god.
Hello?
Can I run people?
I must be able to run people over.
There's no way in heck.
Oh my god.
This is adorable.
Yeah, POV come.
Take that.
This is so cool.
I love this POV.
Maybe not.
I don't know what's behind it.
I assume that's what hurts me.
If I take damage.
I don't know.
100% a bunch.
That's unlucky.
Oh well.
Sorry, that's a lot easier to tell
what's coming up.
I'm sorry, I have to change camera angle.
I apologize.
After the 100%.
Are you squidding me right now?
Thank you for the tip.
What did you see?
Hold on.
I'm destroying things.
Wait, wait.
Thank you for the tip.
Why are you?
There's no way someone is standing up to a tank.
You have to be crazy to stand up to a tank.
Did they even do damage?
Oh, so you can dodge.
Let me pause.
I don't want to miss that.
I'm really dumb.
I'm going to forget.
I don't want to forgo.
No way.
Okay.
Hey Australia.
I'm back from work.
Yeah, I got tank tank.
Thank you for the tip.
I appreciate it.
Oh.
Man, just tank that whole cannonball.
I need help setting up alerts.
They barely work.
It's a bit of a nightmare to instrument elements,
but once you get it set up,
you never have to change it again.
And you can set up custom
things like if someone
donated like $69,
for example, you can get it to do.
Are we going in a battle dome?
Yes!
Oh my god, tank battle dome!
Take this.
And this.
Hold on, I'm reloading.
Yes!
Oh my god, I love tank battle dome.
This is amazing.
More tank battle dome.
There's something.
Let me in.
This is why I think of your factories.
Take this, capitalism.
Tanks! Tank battle dome!
No, no, you're not loading the tank.
You're not loading it.
Tank battle dome.
I'm stuck on the cylinder box.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
Wait, wait, wait. Let me in, let me in, let me in, let me in.
Let me in.
Okay, there we go.
Tank battle dome.
Battle dome, battle dome, battle dome, battle dome, battle dome.
Yeah, I don't know how I'm going to
think that. I'm not going to lie.
I ain't going, there's no way I'm 100%.
We can try and layer
streams, but
yeah, there's no shot. I'm doing it tonight.
Arrivederci.
Little tank.
No, I wish I could keep you.
I see we're so real for that.
That was fun.
I like tank battle dome.
Just don't take damage.
Five hits, honestly.
Someone was like, have you ever played the game modded before?
Me who mods it so I can't take damage
so I can do the no damage hits.
Runs.
Some of the
freaking 100%
are a bit outrageous, honestly.
Rest builders who have to go, if you need
to go sleepy, bye bye.
Strongly, I'm up for almost 36 hours.
I'm going to get some shy.
Oh my God, that's dangerous. Definitely get some rest.
My goodness.
Yes, we will have a wonderful stream.
It's dirty underwear.
Okay.
I think I know what we do with that.
I think I know
what we do with it.
99% sure I know what we do with it.
Y'all don't mind
what we go do right now.
That was Leonardo da Vinci, you're right.
You're not wrong.
Maybe I could have gone off that surface.
I think it's just one of the guild
requirements
to use
the parachute.
Oh, there's a bank actually.
I'm going to take my bank money out because
it looks cool.
I can faint the bank.
Good evening.
Good afternoon, Mr.
Bankman.
Can I have my landlord simulant?
Whoa, where the heck is this thing?
Can I have the landlord simulator
part of this game?
Is he counting coins?
Why is he leaning over like that?
He looks so insidious, like, ball him.
My coins.
12 never came, so me and the SUV
just went away. Lol.
Hello bank, I was like
I want one zillion dollars.
We're rich, we're rich.
Right, next
we're going to do challenges
to get
our guild
to play decoration,
to play room decoration.
So we've done landlord simulator, we're now doing room
decoration.
Uh,
and then
after that
I
think we actually have
done, like, the main
we're going to take some of the layouts
of this place.
He actually just gave you
sheets to take. It's his laundry.
He's like, here it is, it's all for you
buddy.
And why not jump with me?
That's such a smart, I wonder
he only says that line
if you jump here.
Butcher. It's not a butcher.
Why do you keep saying butcher?
I don't know.
They both begin with the letter B
so
yeah, maybe that's why
instead of blacksmiths I say butcher.
Up next, animal crossing
decorating rooms.
I
personally will never
stream animal crossing.
I don't
know.
Whoa, they boarded me
out.
Oh
bridge.
Like I don't know if I can make
animal crossing fun.
Like
maybe as a
I don't know. I couldn't make it
fun. I don't mind watching other people play it
but me, I'm like, I ain't that creative
to make it entertaining.
I love all the games that
start with AC on full.
Right, so I guess the only way to get back
into the castle is this way from now on.
Whoa, we have over a hundred
thousand forums.
Right, I can
can I walk through that gate?
No.
That would be too easy.
I wonder, actually, probably post-game
they should actually open that gate. I said what I said
because like chaseries won't do a thing.
Yeah, oh no, guys, I've got a DM.
I was getting nervous.
I'm like, oh no, is there something wrong with my babies
if I've got a DM?
Everything is
really cute.
Oh, we have the thumbnails
for our first group collab.
And that is what I knew.
How interesting.
I'll let it be a mystery.
Rest well, those who have to go.
Thank you for hanging.
Mercy is going live
in 2 minus
1 hour and 45
for a
how the heck to get up. I've completely
forgotten all over again.
Just go straight up
like that, I guess.
I do have my assassins
so I suppose I can just signal them to go
get rid of them.
Yeah.
Wait, wasn't there?
This way over here.
Relax, Hen.
Why are you moaning
about the place? My goodness.
Alert the guards.
Good night.
Sleep well, those who need to sleep.
Good morning, those who are good
morning.
She's getting me acting up.
Oh, literally, I don't know what that was.
Okay, this is what I was going to do.
Let's do you.
No, that guy actually
can see you here.
Morning.
Europe's waking up.
Okay, the assassin signals being able to
do that is like amazing.
It's 3 a.m. in Europe.
Oh, I'm a bit early for European streamers.
I apologize.
Can I not go up there?
I don't want to go too far.
Okay, it's the next one I go up.
I need to go down in order to go up.
European's perishing right now trying to
wait.
I'm losing it.
Yeah, go down to go up.
Okay, I'm starting to kind of remember, but...
It's always 3 a.m. somewhere.
Last and ESP.
I have no idea what time zone I'm like
perfect for.
But then again,
am I technically not perfect
for all time zones if I stream really long?
Hmm.
Yeah, I don't think we're doing a 12 hours
before anyone is strapped in.
So some people will be relieved to hear
that we're not doing another 12 hours
at this floating home.
I think when we do Eldon Ring,
it will be a few back-to-back 12 hours.
Yeah, you fit all time zones.
Heh heh heh.
Bad healthy sleep.
You'd be perfect for New Zealand.
I thought it was 4 a.m.
Sorry, I didn't have my weapon out.
Sorry, I'm not paying attention.
I'm Jerry Jack.
Why have you got your...
Put away this thing?
Oh, my thing's glitched out.
It's like...
What are you doing?
Oh, that was kind of badass.
I wouldn't lose it all.
Something's not...
I had it up here.
That was...
Now my...
Assassin...
What are you doing, Lady?
Classic woman moment.
Can't make up her mind.
That's terrible.
Don't make too much of that.
Don't do that.
That's my next.
Heh heh.
He has two goons.
We're doing it!
We're doing the thing!
Oh.
That's on the way.
Oh, it was on the wrong side.
My Assassin's still having de-spawn.
They're freaking out.
I don't like it.
Right.
So I don't mess this up.
How do I tell the parachute to come out?
Uh...
I'm being propaganda.
How do I tell the parachute to come out?
Did I just launch and press X?
Right.
I don't...
I don't want to go that way
because that won't activate the jump.
Look at that thing.
The Assassins are really struggling.
Should prompt...
Do a flip.
Okay.
What were we doing?
Did I go that way?
Or that way?
No point in going in the back in the street.
Uh...
Whatever the prompt is,
bloody hope it comes up because...
it is...
not on the wheel.
Oh, there we go.
Oh, thank God.
Right.
I need to do like a ton of distance.
I guess I'll just go over the wall.
I was really worried that prompt wasn't going to come out.
I think I need to glade like 500 meters.
Uh...
Am I going to make the glide?
Hello?
Am I not going to make it?
Come on, pop.
Pop.
No, I don't want to climb it again.
Please pop.
What was that supposed to do?
Why did that not pop?
I was supposed...
something was supposed to pop there.
Not the achievement.
What was supposed to...
what did I do wrong?
It was an assassin's.
Was it thieves because they're agile?
Glade...
and a cumulative total of 500 meters were a part of it.
Is that what I just said?
I'm not to turn at all.
Okay.
No.
I hope you guys have the same patience for me.
Because I need to do that all over again.
I don't know...
cumulative.
Alright.
I'll just do it again because it should pop then.
Just do it multiple times.
Yes.
Alright, we're going to zoom it because at least I know exactly where to go.
Wait.
You can do it cheeky sometimes.
I thought you could do it in one jump.
For some reason.
I went for it too often.
We're so rude.
Slanted.
There's not a star in heaven that we can't reach.
If you're trying.
Oh, I'm breaking free.
I can't remember the rest of it.
Does it still have a parachute?
Yeah, I have four more inventory.
I can't believe it.
I can't believe this castle is full of guards.
Shot and behaviour.
Get out.
Anyone wants you here?
Oh, my ankles.
I didn't take any fall damage.
Okay.
I love your...
Yeah, you're like when I burst into Scott swinging.
My wee accent.
I should do a Scott or some cover.
I don't know what to do.
I wanted to do an M&M one,
but I was like...
I don't know if it's bordering on cringe.
She was like...
I don't know what M&M song I wanted to do.
I don't know what song.
I don't know.
I've got any clue.
You've got any clue what's going on there?
No, you didn't.
You've gone back.
Sorry.
You threw me.
I don't know what one to do.
I'm beginning to feel like a wee bit of a rap god.
I don't know.
Yes, who's back, back, back, back again, again, again.
Strony's back, back, back, tell a friend.
Oh, everyone report to the dance floor.
It's your season to be butt squeezing.
That made me snore.
I'm so sorry.
Touch my body.
I mean, is it boy just touch my body?
I mean, girl, just touch my body.
Because this is the part where the rap breaks down.
No one moves.
No one makes a sound.
I'm just mixing into a ton of different songs, I think.
Back to reality.
There goes gravity.
There goes...
Doesn't have any.
There goes gravity again.
I don't know.
Okay, that was very lucky.
You can actually go backwards.
Are we a big fan of M&M?
No.
Not like...
Oh, I know all the albums and stuff.
It's just the goofy songs.
I like it.
I can't believe it.
I love Scottish M&M.
That one's good one.
The spaghetti on this shirt.
No, there's vomit on his shirt.
Mum's spaghetti.
I'm a jukebox.
Okay, now we need this as a carry, okay?
Oh, there goes gravity.
Oh, there goes a rabbit.
That's not the lyrics.
You're teasing me.
Scottish Kendrick Lamar wins.
I don't know the words.
I don't even know if that was Kendrick Lamar.
I'm going to be honest.
No, that was Denzel Watt.
No.
Wait, hold on.
Hold on.
Brain farming.
Sitting here repeating YouTube work on my Scottish accent.
I really know many other...
Right.
I was in the 212 on the Uptown A.
You know what's up or won't you?
That's not really...
500 accumulative meters.
I don't want to fly up off that fricking building again.
500 accumulative meters, please.
I can't believe it.
That's it.
Put the tunes on.
We're rapping in Scots.
Because how on earth was that not 500 accumulative meters?
500 accumulative meters.
I only ask for 500 meters.
Hmm.
Talk to my assassins.
Because Exio ain't listening.
We suck at rap battle.
You want us to rap battle each other?
Honestly?
Right.
This is going to be really obviously kind of spoilers if you'd be here.
Well, it's not really spoilers because it would have to be discussed anyway.
I really thought it would be fun to have diss tracks made.
Like make diss tracks on each other.
So obviously they'd be like,
Strongly cuttles can't even see your name right.
Because you're Scottish, you know what I mean?
If I don't know how to do that,
I would have to unegronically commission someone to diss each other.
But I think a diss track on each other would be so funny.
I know it's brain dead, but I don't know.
I just want to find out the content that's funny.
Like interact with each other in that kind of way.
Words, yeah.
Like she be caught in bomb or like pretending to be your mom.
Oh, you know, because you know, she's a male.
But she hasn't spawned in a child from her loins.
Like, oh, like, oh, what this, what this,
but I don't know how like this tracks work.
I don't know how you make them or anything like that.
And like Azura Dooley, more like Azura Doo-Gay.
Oh, I mean Beezoo, more like, I mean, your brother's dead.
Oh, I see snow paws, more like a brat with just claws.
Oh, this is awful.
Merci, modest.
Yeah, nothing.
Yeah, your dress wear isn't modest at all.
You just slagged your dress like a slag.
Like how do you make diss tracks?
I don't know.
That didn't even rain.
I just don't know how.
Like how do people think of it?
Like, you have to go right away and write something.
I was like that.
I don't know if you've seen the meme where it's like,
you're deadly.
You're deadly nails out of the garden, the scruffy nose.
Like that's how we end up doing a diss track
because I feel so much pressure to like say something.
It's like, it just doesn't make any sense.
Like, I just don't know how people come up with like actually,
like, you know how epic rap battles is like so good?
Like, whose rap flows the dopest Marilyn Monroe's
upthrown pharaohs, like opposes like Moses or something like that.
Um, like that is so good.
And I'm like, how do people know that?
We can do epic rap battles.
VTuber style.
Come on.
Oh, stop reading my mind.
Literally though.
I should.
Yeah.
Yeah, they spend more times on the like,
get idea wrong.
Maybe VTuber should do rap battles,
but like the problem is I don't have any music or lyrical thing.
So I would have to like go out and commission to do it.
I don't need to grab VTubers.
I'd be willing to like let us diss each other.
Like, oh, I don't even know how I would diss myself.
Oh, I don't know.
Probably like, oh, schizophrenic personality disorder.
Oh, but you're like, that's probably how you get me.
She's been streaming seven hours.
That's what you hate.
Yeah, I am.
Right.
Repeat after me.
500 accumulative mirrors.
Accumulative mirrors.
500, please.
500 accumulative mirrors.
Because I don't want to do that anymore.
I'll probably do something else if we don't hit it this time
and that's okay.
But we're asking for 500 accumulative mirrors.
Yay!
We did it!
Okay, it takes three times to jump off together.
Okay.
Oh, let's do a cheeky air assassination.
Oh, I can't.
I'm out of bounds.
Sorry, just dropping in for the third time today.
Oh, I just looked up my own scout there.
We did it.
Right, now we need to figure out what on earth these guilds want from us.
Let's see.
Guild challenges.
Assassins.
Like, fully done.
Yeah, okay.
Okay, it's done.
Cheeky Flash.
Right.
Brutes killed.
Scaffolding by guards.
PayPal guards.
The PayPal guards are back there.
Guards killed while on horseback.
Guards on horseback air assassinated.
Double assassination.
Five guards disarmed and killed with their own weapon.
I'm going to be honest, I've actually already done one of that.
I know for a fact I have.
I have a five-man kill streak.
Mm, okay, is there anything easier?
Oh, we've actually done quite a lot.
Evade enemies using the crowd or other hiding spots.
Enemies stationed at a guard post while using a crossbow.
I actually know how to do that.
Horses belonging to guards commandeered without killing the rider,
and guards killed in a smoke bomb.
Right, we'll do that right now because we can do the smoke bomb.
Hello.
I'm going to kill you.
Oh, that was...
Right, take your time.
Right, and then I'm going to get rid of this one.
Oh, well, I'm going to get double assassination,
and then I'm going to take his sword.
Oh, he can.
He's not weak enough.
Sugar.
Uh, right.
We did the smoke bomb, which is fantastic.
Um...
7.68%.
Is it actually?
No more kill.
Actually, I did the coppers kill.
That's terrible.
Kilty, kilty, cold bum.
Did you know when you were killed, you're not supposed to wear any...
Greeks under it.
Mm...
Did I need to write these on a note?
I think I actually have to.
Uh...
Yeah.
This is like so much.
Right, the papal guards are...
actually back across the bridge.
You know that.
Excuse me, how about your horse?
Oh, fine.
Right, I'll call him on.
What item do you steal from the other guards?
I answered...
Oh, I answered that.
But it's a bit inappropriate.
I'm not sure I should say it again.
Right, here.
These are where these guards...
These ones spawn.
So, we're going to need to like come back and then...
Oh, don't shoot me.
That's not nice.
Whoa, you weren't even aiming at me, bro.
I don't want to...
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Right, okay, okay.
Okay, okay, okay.
You're done.
Well, because I am, you're dead.
Don't waste my time.
Stinks.
Take that.
These are the only location...
I know these type of guards spawn.
I'm like 99% sure.
I don't think anyone else spawn here.
Right, and then you.
Here you go.
Here's some money.
Me.
Here we go.
That's my money.
I don't know.
This beast is beautiful.
Beautiful?
I don't know how to respawn those guys in without like going around doing something else.
Should we do Quarters on Assignment?
No.
I need to do a lot of horse activities.
That sounds bizarre.
Out of context.
Have I got a pen and paper for my brain?
I don't know.
I'm literally going to write this on the discord.
So the girls are like, what the heck are you typing about?
Right, let's see.
I need to...
Right, I've killed four more people.
I have to like open it and then show it in the next.
Killstreak and then...
I need to evade...
Evade four times or something.
I've already forgotten the other freaking thing I was supposed to do.
One enemy stationed at Guard Post.
Okay, we're actually going to station Guard Post.
We're actually going to do that in a memory because there's a memory that enables that.
Horses belonging to guards commandeered.
Horses yoinked without killing.
Do you want me to screenshot and post on the discord?
I just need to do the last one.
Oh, I can screenshot it.
I don't even have to type it out.
Can I screenshot it?
Did that screenshot work?
I don't even think I did.
It did.
Okay.
Okay, that worked.
Okay, it worked.
I am so smart.
SMRT.
Okay, let's see.
Put that there so I don't miss any donations if someone tips.
And then put the discord there.
And now I can...
Oh wait, no.
I can't see it.
Oh, the screenshot makes it so tiny that I can't see it.
I need to type it out.
Six.
Six thieves lured.
I did it for anyway.
Now, that's the picture.
It's because if it's a picture, I need to have the discord in small.
Sprint uninterrupted.
Sprint for 300.
21 leaps of faith.
I need to do 40 leaps of faith.
So you don't really do leaps of faith anymore.
Guard's heir assassinated from a beam.
Unless, but certainly not least,
jump from a horse to a beam.
Jump from horse to beam.
Yeah, there's actually like so much horse related ones.
This is surprising.
I didn't actually expect...
Oh, Azura just messaged me.
Oh.
What's she saying?
Ah, okay.
It's MRT.
Oh my god.
The girls are posting in the not-safe-for-work section of the discord.
Now look at it.
I think it may be...
Oh, it actually may be my gifted artwork.
Open it.
It's MRT.
Oh wait, I've just closed the discord.
Oops.
The discord actually holds everything that I need in order to play the game.
Look at dum-dum.
It's MRT.
No, that's Samarty.
Wow, I can't believe it.
I might unironically need a third moner for this kind of stuff.
Okay.
Someone at Ubisoft is really proud of the horses.
Honestly, it probably took like a heckish and hellish...
Oh, wait.
I'm freaking dumb.
Why am I so dumb?
Dum-dum-dum.
Okay, wait.
Hold on.
Hold the freaking telephone.
Okay, there we go.
I definitely need a third moner.
Honestly, I felt that right now as I'm currently trying to like arrange so many things.
Okay, hydration check.
I am going to do one...
Yeah, one of those portrait moners.
Yeah, definitely like chat-orientating.
Right.
Because there's so many horses once, I'm actually going to take us to the thieves district
if I can find a fast port, which I can at the...
Rosa in Fiori.
Merci.
One hour, 20 minutes.
Merci didn't know what countdown was.
Yeah.
I...
I'm like...
All our...
All like, Merci's senpais are more deceased.
Oh!
Merci just catches the street a little bit.
What?
I'm dissing my...
My fellow gen mate,
but I'm so bad at like dissing because I just...
Like, I...
Oh, I need to put you in the scaffold and please let me grab you.
No, no, no.
I don't want to fight.
Please, can I grab you?
Can I grab you?
Wait, I can't grab them when they're in.
Right.
That's two of three.
Ah!
Leave me alone!
Is there any more scaffolding?
If there's more scaffolding, now's the time to reveal yourself.
There is!
Please come this way.
Oh, look at this lovely scaffolding
that someone's put up for it.
Damn, she cooking.
Merci, what's she doing?
Zero, I'm trying to diss tracks,
but I'm absolutely rubbish at them.
And I'm like, trying to pretend I know how to
frickin' diss tracks,
but it's plausible.
Now, you're not coming over.
Come here, right now.
Come here.
I'm wondering...
Oh, this is terrible.
This isn't going to work out well, I don't think.
Tell these two.
Right, we've got a double assassination out of that.
No!
It's you.
You're a bit too efficient at your job.
I didn't actually want to assassinate them.
I'm talking about a third monitor,
and I still only have one.
Ah!
If you're going to be sure, you might need three.
Momet and Mummy are here.
Yeah.
Or Mommy.
Wait, what do I need to do?
I need to go do horse missions!
Right, we're going to go to the Thieves Guild,
which I totally know the name of.
The Thieves Guild.
Why is it all the way down here?
I feel like the last one.
You know what?
Yeah, you're dumb.
Mm-hmm, you're dumb.
She would never diss me.
She would love me.
Oh, I can't remember what my diss was on you.
I thought I was like Azuridule, more like...
Oh, that's what I was like.
Azuridule, more like Azuriduke.
That's really like the most rubbish thing.
Like nonsense.
What's wrong with you?
Visual number of hurricanes.
Are we allowed to recommend?
Yeah, you can always recommend stuff.
That's not a problem at all.
Right, horse activities.
Right, I need to run 300 meters uninterrupted.
You can do it at this section super duper easily.
Definitely recommend going to the Thieves Guild
in order to do this.
Azuridule, more like Fontal Abyssum.
Your third monitor should be used exclusively to ignore chat.
Why would I ignore chat?
It's literally the best part of streaming.
Other than, like, when the gameplay gets intense,
then, uh, some things need to be slowed down.
Is there, like, a perfect circle here?
Can I just go in circles?
If you get motion sick, close your eyes.
Mercy, look away.
Don't watch stream here, man.
What would happen if Ezio had to turn for the feature bar?
I think he'd have a lot of fan girls.
Ay, hold on.
Alright, what do I need to next?
What?
How have I got the Thieves Guild crest?
I didn't do it.
More like Stacey, these Milkretains, literally.
She'd be calling herself a dumb winner.
Winner.
Protide name was literally cotton bomb.
Yeah, get wrecked, yeah.
Your dedication towards Ezio is highly respectable.
It's a good game, what can I say?
Right.
Am I supposed to kill from being on a horse?
Guards killed well on horseback.
Let's go!
Oh, hold on, let's try again.
Hold on, let me get back on the horse.
Sorry, sorry.
Let me quit, excuse me, excuse me.
Let me literally get back on the horse.
I kid you not, literally let me get back on the horse.
Stop, I know you're scared, but we need to try that again.
I messed that up really badly, hold on.
Okay, let's try that again.
I've been destroyed, decimated.
Just like how decimated your skin is when you interact with rabbits,
because you're allergic.
Ha, ha, ha, you're allergic.
Yeah, I'm so good at doing this.
This is awful, I'm so sorry.
This is absolutely horrendous, I'm just gonna stop talking.
Oh.
I'm a horseback.
Showing it on an old space commercial.
Wow, low blow, just like the hate of rabbits.
Oh, ooh.
They just make my throat close now.
Literally put you in anaphylactic shock.
Oh, nothing measured though.
Yeah.
Okay, retconning the model we gave you right now.
Holy crap.
Double air assassination.
Oh, it actually worked.
Wow, okay.
Owie.
Wait, hold on.
Horse, come back.
Stop being scared.
Where did the horse go?
Is it?
Oh, right, fine.
I'm just calling my recruits in.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
We don't do this.
Get me here, get me.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, the people are fighting back.
Take that.
And this is stinky, stinky.
Wait, that missed?
Oh, well, I'll let this guy control that.
Where's my horse?
There's my horse.
Okay, we did this.
We need to just go around killing more guards from horseback.
And then once that one's done, we'll move on to the next one.
Hello, are there any guards?
It seemed quieter.
I get turned into a horse because they get...
Oh, would you want to be a horse feature?
If I would change into another animal,
I'd maybe make you...
What would I make you?
Thank goodness I'm not on the development team anymore when it comes to that shiz.
Don't worry, you're not getting any more bad names.
No.
Hi, Jack.
I'm to commandeer a horse without killing.
Okay, so that's one for the commandeering.
Oh, my horse has like a little backpack now.
Got a little backpack on the horse?
Okay, so that just need to like keep running around, hoping to run into...
Okay, here we go.
Okay, that was one more.
Okay, we're going to call in the assassins.
As soon as they get on a horse, I don't like it.
I get scared.
Ooh!
Oh, that was guard on horseback assassination.
That was good, that was good.
There's only been like three surprising ones.
Let's see if we can do another double, maybe?
Yeah, okay, nice double.
We're racking up their numbers really quick.
Alright, I'll let the assassins deal with this.
I'm going to get this guy.
I'm getting out of here.
No, you're literally in my way.
Horse features also have a very big buff because of the horse.
Alright, we need to get back on a horsey-worsey.
Hello!
And then...
We're getting there, we're slowly whittling it down to not much...
Oh, I'm stuck on a rock.
Alright, enemies, enemies, enemies.
Oh, who we got, who we got?
I just need to hijack without killing.
Thank you, so that's two for ten.
That's two for ten for commandeering a horse.
I need to do the hide spot things, so maybe I'll go into the spale here in time.
I don't count.
Oh, rush.
What was an enemy back here?
What was it?
Oh, right, you.
Right, you're three of ten.
Thank you very much.
Appreciate it.
Actually, I'm going to go for these guys because they're just easy.
Oh, pardon me.
I'm just calling the assassins in.
No, stop running away.
I know it's scary when I start.
Oh, hijack, thank you very much.
Wait, if he keeps going on horses, can I just farm him?
Farm him?
Oh, no, my assassins are going to get up.
Okay, I have learned.
Today I have learned.
Let me get this guy here.
I think I can just farm him over and over again.
And because I jump off my horse to do it, he jumps on main automatically.
Right, what, what was that, like five?
So he's going to get on the horse.
Six.
Okay.
Oh, my goodness.
Seven grand theft dressage, but I didn't get the thing yet.
That's funny as anything though.
Oh, my God.
This is actually really funny.
Eight, I think eight.
Nine.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
Hey, there we go.
There we go.
Beautiful, beautiful.
Right, a few more kills from horseback.
That was good.
All he wants to do is ride the horse on his horse.
I just kept yanking over and over again.
I mean, did he really want the horse if he just made it that easy for me?
Okay, we're at the bath house.
I recognize this part of the map.
I think we're going to have to go in a bit more to find more guards.
I'm literally just going on the outskirts there.
On the map.
A few more assassinations from a horse while on horseback.
Well on horseback?
Oh, no, hold on, let me check.
Very quickly.
Stoney has DNA, DNA.
Is this the horse one?
Guards on horseback, air assassinate.
Guards killed while on horse.
While on horseback.
Okay, I'm going to get my crossbow out and we're literally just going on a spree then.
I need to stay on horseback now.
Oh, I'm going the wrong way.
I need to go to the wards, the Colosseum, which is this way.
What's that?
You've played assassins, creeds so much that you recognize which way you need to go.
Maybe, maybe not.
There should be four enemies here.
I'm surprised how casual this is.
Don't peel me off, don't peel me off, I'm scared.
Stop, you're scaring me.
That's four.
Okay, there we go.
Oh, wait.
We need to do the beam trick.
I think this is the beam trick.
That was the beam trick.
Right, we need to do that 19 more times.
I'm not even kidding.
Hold on, and we need to lure the guards.
Come here, come, come, come.
Lure these men away.
No, lure them away?
Yeah, there you go.
Right, we basically need to go back and forth over and over, jumping on this beam.
No, you didn't do it, it's you.
That wasn't it, that wasn't the trick.
We needed to do that flip you saw, literally 19 times more.
Do a flip, it's you.
Right, and I want to...
No, it's you, try again.
Do I need to jump on a specific part?
Really specific.
Jump, hold, flip.
Okay, jump, hold, flip.
So I need to tap A and then hold it.
So 18 more times.
Jump, hold, no.
Okay, I think we needed a bit more speed that time.
Give us a bit more energy, a bit more energy.
Little bull's eye, a little horsey-worsey.
Do a bit of run-up for it, hold.
And that horse just blocked us and jump and hold.
Why did that not work that time?
I'm not sure why that didn't work.
Yeah, but while talking with those, it's not bad.
I'm doing it in the corner of my eye.
And jump.
Okay, I purposely did that a bit later than when I would have selected A.
So it's 17 more.
I can do it.
Bitly, hold.
No, okay, right.
You're gonna have to bear with me, bear with me.
A is in this room right now because you're gonna have to bear with me.
Bear with me, let me take a few seconds.
Ready, steady, jump and hold.
Yay, 16 more times, let's go.
I definitely seem to be able to do it coming from that way.
I'm wondering if I can't do it this way.
Maybe there's like a hidden bug.
And a jump and a hold.
Maybe it's a one-way type of thing.
We're getting there.
70 more, let's go, literally.
It's like, oh, I'm so glad you guys put this.
Really arbitrary.
Okay, really, really premature with that one.
I'm not even gonna, no, no.
The horse.
Let's try that again.
I wish the NPCs would actually calm down about my rely.
Hold, no.
I honestly, I'm not sure how I'm getting it sometimes
and not other times.
My only guess is that an NPC is making it so like
this pathing mess up.
Jump, hold.
No, why?
What is going on?
I'm not actually sure why sometimes I'm getting that.
Right, we'll do a really big run up just because we can.
Okay, so run and then stand.
And then jump and hold.
Okay, okay, it's speed.
It's speed. We need a bigger run up.
15 more times.
Okay, big, big long journey.
One, two, three, four, five.
Jump and hold.
15 is still the number.
We can't do it.
This is not at all.
A bit of a grind.
A bit more of a grind than I was expecting.
Run.
Jump and hold.
I honestly don't understand what's determining
the number.
Maybe do the middle one.
Like jump late.
I think you may be right.
We'll jump late on purpose this time.
Okay.
Not doing it.
We'll jump now and hold.
No.
Thank you for at least coming back.
Hmm.
15 is better than 20.
And 14 is better than 15.
Whoa.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
No.
Is the appropriate response
after seeing that out loud?
Oh, right.
No, that didn't work.
I think I'm getting speed blocked or something.
Because this is...
What?
13.
No, not 13.
Close to 13.
We can do it.
I literally feel like Bilbo Baggins when he's like...
He's like trying not to be like a bit
disgruntled with like
the dwarves showing up.
And I'm like, ooh, ooh, it's fine.
It's fine.
No.
This is very pun.
There is a war going on.
Maybe you have to be under the beams.
Okay, I'll definitely...
Like, I'll super delay it this time.
Like, genuinely super delay it.
No, he just jumped straight on it.
If you do it, like, super delayed.
Okay.
Hmm.
Curious, curious, right?
I'll try again.
Because 14...
Like, I can do this, honestly.
It's just so...
I'm trying to avoid that guy.
I'll try to avoid that guy.
I think I just need to let the horse
maybe directly steer,
even if the horse is a little off.
Because the steering...
As soon as I stand on the horse's saddle,
the steering...
Oh.
What is it? I don't know.
So, I just realized since you're in Australia,
does that mean you've been streaming since 3am?
4am is my stream time.
Daylight saving and stuff.
But it's healthy...
It's healthy.
It means I can do stuff during the day.
Oh, 13, 13!
Okay, I don't know.
I genuinely didn't do anything different.
I think it really is just luck of the draw or something,
because I did not do anything...
Ah, I thought I was going to say, hopefully,
I'm going to get two in a row.
This is such a bizarre,
like,
challenge-type thing, honestly.
No!
Why, why, why, why?
30!
No, not 30!
13!
Mmm.
Spreads build up just straight up and...
Ah!
All bits are so, like...
Neaxanoid in the moment.
See, yeah, that was, like, hardly any build up to it,
so I think that's why that one's on the wall.
Mmm.
Let's not be knocking down women.
I only want to knock up women.
Thank you very much.
Oh, wait!
I don't want to knock down women.
I only want to knock them up!
Please laugh.
One more time without doing a massive thing.
I have a little thingy.
Yeah, I forgot.
I forgot I had it too.
Okay, I forgot.
Literally, I'll need to add a laughing track as well.
Oh, brother, this guy stinks!
Yeah, I'm going to have to add a...
I'll add a laughing track.
I should add a laughing track.
That's, like, one that's good,
and then one that's, like,
it gets a few coughs and, like, a giggle,
so it's, like, a bad joke.
I'm definitely going to need to get that.
I need to hydrate.
My goodness.
Trying so hard to figure out, like,
what's determined in this jump or not?
I need some crickets, yeah.
Do the joke again.
I let my laugh in my other jacket.
Oh, you left your laugh in the other jacket.
Ha-ha, you spelt it wrong.
Everyone pointing laugh.
You spelt his thing wrong,
and I read it out,
and now he's embarrassed.
Ha-ha-ha, streamer,
read out your message with a spelling error.
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha.
Oh, that was just gross.
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha.
Right, okay, we're going to try Gallop now.
The only issue with Gallop in
is if you Gallop through a crowd too much.
No, that was far too early.
Okay, I kind of struggled with this.
We'll try the Gallop from this side.
Life's over.
It's over.
You'll never recover.
Your social credit has been determined.
No, okay.
That Gallop doesn't seem to enable that jump whatsoever.
I like how the horse is so responsive.
It's like, where'd you go?
Please come back.
Oh, is it the degration?
Degoration.
Degredation?
Degredation.
Degredation sounds correct.
I said a degredation.
Ooh, 12!
I'm just so surprised when it does happen.
It seems to happen in that direction
more than it happens in this direction.
Nope.
Well, close.
It's over.
Not quite.
I do want you on the beams,
but I want you to do that
with fancy flips that you do.
They should have made it 10.
No, they actually shouldn't have done this at all
because literally, how would you have discovered that
Exo can even do this?
I'm sorry, but I would never have naturally discovered
that he could do this.
Good night.
Rest well.
Thank you for hanging.
We're, uh...
Oh, I actually can't see how long I've been streaming for.
I've accidentally covered it up
by a little list of things that I need to do.
Oopsie, oopsie.
Oh, that was like...
Really?
Nope.
It feels like it has cooled down, honestly.
The brain rot took over.
Yeah, it took over long ago.
I apologize.
Eight hours.
I've only been streaming eight hours,
and I've got a few more in me.
I want this one over
because I never want to have to do it again.
I don't want to have to come back to this,
but I know you guys have been literally watching me
do a backflip on...
Do a flip on a horse for like ten minutes now.
It's gonna be just...
No one's laughing.
Getting aggravated now.
Great.
I am running.
I am holding.
Oh!
Hmm.
Eleven?
Okay, I think it's eleven now.
I don't know why.
Right, I'll run up for ages.
Hold.
Nope.
Oh, we're almost 50% of the way there.
We're almost there.
No flip.
Absolutely.
Only eight hours.
Oh, well, you guys are gonna feel at a place
when you see me only online for like two hours tomorrow.
You're gonna be like,
what's wrong?
Is she sick?
Where's my horse?
Oh, I'm sorry.
Oh no, you have done.
Ten, ten.
Right, I feel like it always happens
come in this direction
instead of the other direction.
Skillshare can't even do a flip.
We're not flipping out on you.
You're not flipping out on me?
Insert laugh track here
that I still haven't added yet,
but I will add the laugh track soon to you.
Please get the heck out of my way.
I'm trying to do flips.
Can you leave me alone?
No.
No money is worth this, he said.
I do need to kill from horseback.
So maybe just do that real quick.
We'll just do this one
to add to the horseback one.
So we're still making progress
even though it's very good.
Let's try this.
I did it!
Okay, that's the sound
I need to add right now.
But if I do the flip, it goes ehhhhh.
Don't worry,
I'll get a little bit for you.
I'm dead.
Flipping on a beam off a hole
or is this sucks
and I don't know
why they asked for a twin.
stop taking people's horses.
It's really not nice.
I'm looking to see if there's like a
prompt that's like double tap to do a beam or jump or whatever
but there's no happening.
There's no happening but we're halfway there. We can do it. We can do it. We can do it. We can do it.
Well, that's probably not going to work now.
I have lost my mind.
Literally I've been doing flips for so long. Please.
Free me. Free me from the beam.
Oh, nine. Finally.
Wow.
No, it's still below the beam.
You could have easily sat back on the horse, I'll be honest.
The skirt looks so funny. You mean has killed.
He's killed to kill to pull fun.
Eight. Eight. Eight. Eight. Eight. Okay, that was
excuse me. I think I need it. I think I can kill him
and it'll count for the horseback.
Oh, I'm getting a spank. I'm getting a spank. I'm sorry.
Actually, I should probably do these guys from horseback as well.
There we go. One.
Two.
Three. Or I'm going to throw rocks through
your window.
Okay, let's try this again. Oh, no, don't jump.
No, stay. Try again. Try again.
You mustn't offend the left.
You wouldn't like me when I'm angry, can you? Oh, seven.
Seven? I think seven.
I still have yet to
figure out what determines it, but once it's over with, we don't have to do it again.
We got a double. We got a double. We got a double. Oh my god, I've not done that.
Can we do a triple? Can we do a triple? It's like my subconscious understanding
what I need to do, even though my brain, like, my actual conscious doesn't...
No, we got a double though. So it's six.
Only six more to go. I've never done back to back. That's fantastic.
I was literally like, is my subconscious knowing what's up? But my conscious
is like, can't... mmm, that was far too early.
I need to put my glicks on for that one. That's terrible.
Wow. Oh, baby.
Top 10 moments of 24.
Welcome to WatchMojo. Well, we rate the
worst little
side quest things that Assassin's Creed Brotherhood randomly give you, because it is a bit
arbitrary.
Yeah.
Only six
more. Can you hold on?
I'm starting to lose
a little bit, but that's okay, because we got five. We got five.
I was going to say it would be a triple. Get out of my
hand. Look, I wasn't kidding when people were like, why would you
describe Shubi as like, everything you should have been?
I wasn't kidding. Was I kidding?
Oh, four! Four! Four!
Cheat run.
F-f-f-f-f-f-f-f-f...
F-f-f-f-f-f-f-f-f-f...
F-f-f-f-f-f-f-f-f-f-f-f-f
Wow, four, that was too slow.
We're sounding so country.
Wow, the sound of the ice cream.
Three, three, three, three,
three, two, two, two, two,
two, two, two...
All the two, two, two,
all the two, two,
all of that was gonna get the Truffle there.
Two more. Two more. The people listening in right now that are like waiting on
Mercy to start they're like please for the love of God mercy start early.
One more. One more. One more. One more. One more. One more. One more. Just one more time.
We've got to celebrate. Oh yeah jumping on the horse beam.
Do the random say thing for the guilt quiz because it's so silly. Just one more time.
We've got to celebrate. Oh yeah.
Oh don't don't ever be such a silly sausage again and
your daddy your dad tells everyone don't ever give me such a silly thing again.
That was absolute torture. Lower guards leap of faith guards air assassinate from a beam.
No guards.
Okay the only thing I can think of doing is attracting these guards over here to
no because they would have to be below me. Where is a beam that a rider goes past because I think
that's what I have to assassinate. It's enough horsing around. No dive on.
I think if I do this I might get the horseback kills.
Uh uh please come under this beam over here please harass me under this beam please
harass me under this beam I can't believe the game literally just trained me for this moment
please come under the beam please come under the beam I take all back I'm sorry these guilt
these skills I'm sorry these skills I'm sorry I didn't believe you these skills I didn't believe
you I'm sorry where the heck is this mystical beam that the enemies pass under I don't know where
it's located it's not up here it doesn't feel like it's up here at all
ah mission failed you get I'm next time literally where the heck are these beams
are there any beams anywhere the only beam around here is me having a beamer because
of how freaking embarrassed in this gameplay is to have a beamer means that you are embarrassed
and have scarlet face or a red face
um
just to be like
uh levope does have missions I am going to buy ammo and I'm going to do this stationary guy
one because it's really easy to do it in this quest so I'm going to go buy ammo and we're going
to replay a mission that gives us one of the thieves guilds requirements
yeah Claudio yeah she does as well um I'm trying to do sorry who goes there um
oh goodness me I think I'm actually gonna have to get rid of my rating from a very
what is needy smear overload it is uh unfortunately I actually don't
know too much about the game but it might be a good thing because we get to play for fun for the
first time um I don't think it's gonna be a very long stream if you're wanting an endurance on that
I need to go to the shops to buy the sweets for the hand cam swing stream why am I here just to
suffer yeah sure how much was that oh you're no cheat oh I need to buy art I just realized that
yeah I need to buy like tons of art in all the different districts two three hours yeah that's
like the perfect stream deep gargling didn't overstay as well but uh okay okay I do it
young man with an apple man
he looks so dumb he's like I have an apple posing oh that's a cool one
hmm right we've got all the art for here oh wait I'm like 90% sure you sell feather locations
can you please resell me then no yeah the feathers we'll grab the feather I'm another
there's one on the Colosseo are you gonna 100% avatar no I've never played the RDA side of avatar
I don't like the RDA side it's speaking can I still visit Leonardo um I don't play the RDA
side I only play the navi side um I will just be doing the navi I think the campaign's like
six hours on that one if I can remember correctly um we'll be strange not seeing you before bed and
waking up after yeah it's gonna be an interesting day but I do have endurance streams every week
kind of planned as long as all goes well and I'll see what the clipping situation is uh
hi Leonardo
it's you the people apartments are in turmoil cesare is ill and the pope dead it was your doing
was it not Leonardo I swear to you he did not die by my hand
this world gets stranger every day I shall have to focus on my painting I work on the small
portrait of a woman I'm growing rather fond of it hmm do not let a beautiful girl distract you
from constructing my designs I have no worries women provide little distraction wait I don't get it
he's a gay boy so it's pride month doesn't he be like that man
doesn't he be like that that's nice oh I have everything
if you decide to buy something look for the chalk outline on bench I don't have anything to
purchase Leonardo about everything wait if I talk to him again you have all that I can give
now you're on your own ah Leonardo give back you
give me some of that good day for catching up on clips and bars and things and no endurance
yeah um so the clipping situation I don't want the girls feeling stressed out thinking like I have
to click like and stream at the same time and like deal with all this and try and do collabs
all the girls and all that uh and deal with audios and blah blah blah so I don't want to stress them
out so when you guys like do a make a youtube clip I can go on their accounts and see what
someone's clipped and if it is like clippable worthy I can then send the timestamp onto like an
actual clip editor to make clips for them um I just need to see how it works out in theory
obviously when I do endurance streams I can't do any of it like right now for them um
but we will see how it goes I don't know if I need to like put out a little ad saying like I need
more clippers of this particular style because there's a particular clipping editing style
that I'm looking for the most recent mersey shorts the blonde hair short and the other
short a forgotten um is the clipping style so if you really can do that editing style
you know don't be afraid to hit up the website uh because that's kind of what I'm needing at this point
good thing I got a few clips already my job is not nice either if you're a general clipper
uh we just I'm still interested in doing the clipping enterprise that like idol end done
which is really good um obviously need to get monetized first and set up and see whether my
funds and the money looks like and all that um because will it tell you a really embarrassing fact
you know the earlier uh like um the earlier uh clips that came out shorts that were on the
girls channels um emmy made two of her a couple of shorts on her own actually
but I was editing them and I hated them so much and I was so embarrassed I was like I'm so sorry
girls this is the best I can do because we had quite a few issues behind the scenes production
wise with timing it was a freaking nightmare um so like all my attention was elsewhere and
like I didn't have time to be like hi clippers here's this these files like please wear them
um which that's where I did fail like looking back like obviously I'm happy like talk about
like where I failed the girls and like I definitely feel like I've failed with them
on the clips because the actual plan was the count school live for two weeks before stream
and there'll be a clip uploaded every day and like I kind of failed the girls like doing that and
I feel really bad about it like I feel wrong um but like the dust is kind of set off already done
this but the dust is like kind of settling now the only bad thing is that for now time zone only
you and I see stream at normal times okay you may be not in a normal way yeah
no like it definitely went well like absolutely no denying like
where am I trying to go
um I'm definitely not denying like debut went well and everything just like I had planned
things to just be a lot better and obviously it's not realistic to be like all my plans are all
I just realized I need to leave the face uh we're going to be jumping off this building for quite
well um like I understand it's not possible for everything are you serious it's for everything
to like come out the way of my head um like the girls trailers didn't come out the way I wanted
them to um but because of like production issues I couldn't get things like fixed or altered in
time for anything really and it was just like ah but yeah yeah are you winning strong absolutely um
are you winning excuse me I'm using this hay bale I'm so sorry if this makes anyone motion sick
I'm needing to do leaps of faith and if you jump off a pigeon thing it counts as a leap of faith
no it's ill into the hay bale no it's ill into the hay bale
yeah it was a timing issue um we love artists in this house we do but um
I had given very I feel I had gave incredibly fair deadlines for what I was asking
and pretty much across the board the majority went over and if you are an artist that worked
with me and you did go over deadline like please don't worry um like it's not like a big deal
anymore because obviously now everything's out there and everything's all good and we debuted and
like that's that's the facts but I had a lot of delays and basically I had planned every month in
advance being like this month I'll be focused on this this month I'll be focused on that and what
happened was everything had to be done in May and like I'm not gonna lie I like cried a few times
out of just like pure frustration of like feeling I can't do enough because I have to wait for
someone to send something back in order for me to progress and give feedback like I had a lot of
like issues with um people not checking what they gave me the first time around and being like
hey the reference sheet looks like this or hey um like the subtitle that you put here um like it's
quite clear that she didn't say this but you've literally put it in for some reason or like hey
the audio literally cuts out in the middle of this can you re-render like I don't know what like
it was it was rubbish and at the same time like obviously the the girls know a bit more in detail
exactly what I'm talking about um because like I showed them like we are like I'm constantly
sending back like please fix this please fix this please fix this and the days are going by and the
fixes are taking 24 hours the fixes aren't done within 20 minutes and I get a new rendered version
of something it's like no 24 hours I'll do it in the morning I'll do it later and I'm like I have
paid premium rates I shouldn't be the one who is quality checking your work you should quality
check it before you send it to me and like bro it was just a cascading effect and it was pretty
horrible um but yeah but we're here now so and there were so many lessons learned like um
ripped to future artists if you're interested in working with Veeler but like everyone's getting
contracts like conscripted and stuff like um and being like if you miss this deadline like
you know it's just there's just it's not fun being like that like I love giving artists the
benefit of the doubt but holy is this even counting for leaps of faith uh yeah like deadlines are so
important and having that like oh wow we're one off of leaf of faith um literally in the end we
made it everything worked out fight wait did that guard hurt himself I don't remember hurting him um
like we made it in the end but yeah rough rough not fun but I'm now like I just want to stream
I just want to have fun I want to show off my games I want to have a good time I want to make
ASMR I want to do everything that I've wanted to do while I get to do it alongside like these
amazing girls type thing um and I want them to see them achieve their dreams and see how it goes
like obviously the the the current goal is YouTube to please stop calling us and like
admit that we're real like streamers and stuff you don't need colors like there's plenty of content
on the channels now but yeah like it definitely like everything works out in the end
absolutely is everyone max level
no three people aren't max oh I didn't mean to do that but hey yeah like the worst part is over
wait what the heck oopsies I'm to kill the mailman not to be confused with the sand man
that blows literal dust over your eyelashes or some shiz that was ridiculous
never heard of that first time I've ever heard of that nonsense before I heard the song but like what
oh for goodness sake
okay they're open oh I love how easy that stuff is wonderful
oh uh excuse me am I not your mentor that's got pushed off of them
oh no the PayPal got fixed um so you can support any of the girls like right now
I think I need to update my link or something because people say it no work or something
oh you're using the new info I can't believe it YouTube on softwares
it's old european folklore of course it's nonsense true
a little retrieve
right I don't really know what the plan is
okay we'll finish the guild people's requests but I have to admit I'm a bit lost on what next to do
um
get all the guild requests buy everything and then I think we might be done maybe the feathers
um and we'll revisit it at a non-profit question mark
uh mercy 30 minute
did I get the feather from this location I must go
shit then
cause a little chaos why not
Christina oh I forgot about Christina oh right okay okay okay
oh I've completed all the renovations
wait so what's my DNA
it must be high enough seriously six to eight
is there anything I could do that's really easy
no no
I didn't want to do do you know be to take
it
wait a minute did this one
that was rubbish that one did not look like I discovered it no that was rubbish as well
that was rubbish as well
that was rubbish
and maybe the missions
I've never achieved that that's not even possible
no these like so aren't possible maybe I need to do
wait the assassinations are only uh
oh the assassinations are like only at 41
okay okay we'll do assassins that'll raise us that'll raise us really quickly like they're
super easy super nice and uh consider it so we'll do that we'll do that
just climbing up ladders don't mind me
hey
you all excited for my first day some more stream
I'm doing something mildly special in it I'm a bit concerned after what happened to me but
he apparently she was jumping up and doing on the bed like a monkey
yeah were you there did you hear about this did you see this
what was my cute little sister doing on the bed hello
hmm
one little in me jumping on the bed and she jumped off and bumped her head
how is she jumping down
oh let's see the board you have unleashed their interrogate if they cannot find us we'll
burl us people do not let your targets call for reinforcements oh I don't know what that means
kill wait does that mean like don't get detected
she had to fall and land on her ear somehow yeah I remember reading someone's review on it and I was
like no I want all my children to succeed but apparently apparently we were spitting and
licking it back up how do you plead to these accusations in me how do you plead to such accusations
actually
pin pals how do you plead to the accusations that you egged your little sister on
to do such devious acts
a guard is running for backup who who they're all highlighted
no I got kill bruised
I don't know where that guy ran I'm not really mad at it because I'm still gonna get DNA anyway but
oh there's scaffold in there I could have grabbed him
not guilty I plead the fifth egged Emmy on oh that's funny what is she egging you guys on
these accusations against my little sister I will not stand for such things
right okay let's keep doing
these
she knew what she was doing my innocent little sister has no concept of what even a double
meaning is you are looking at her through your your lusty eyes how dare you
have no how dare you labeling on the innocent the innocent target yet it because that's what
the name of her goes it's all true she's always egging us on
right I'm gonna send away those assassins that aren't ready to level out properly
I'll send you on a big big contract big big big big contract
one two three four five of you
she turned a guy into a tree like he was asking for okay
yeah she needs to level up okay she needs to experience what she's doing
it's not hurtful right we seem to be about 42% use the assassin recruits to assist in
diversion kill the merchant while remaining undetected easy easy let me squeeze
gotta get that XP somehow you know what you're right her latest
alt tweet probably is a misunderstanding exactly you're just reading it wrong okay
can I like lock on to the guy
well let me recall my recruit
is it bugged out oh
oh wait what was the mission use the assassin recruits to assist the night diversion
oh well that was easy peasy lemon squeezy what's going on here we are discussing how
how pin pals have you so misunderstood they're looking at you with
they do I'm trying to tell them that you're innocent okay and that they're not comprehending
that the you jumping up and down on the bed during your ASMR stream is completely innocent
and you were literally just singing that song three little monkeys jumping in the bed one fell
off and bumped its head first game the doctor or something like that i don't know something's in
sure
all right i don't get
we'll do the feathers
i'm not innocent that's for you
who among us is innocent truly
if i were making them among those reference to emi's lore there
i was like did you like that uh oh wait i don't need to go off and go down
you leave me sucking out of this you know it has potential don't tell my other one
i won't accept such
right you need to jump up here in order to get this flag
i named him to come across more thieves to do the lure i think i have like two more
thieves need to lure the guards away i'm sad i missed on these i mean i don't good i'm
like 99% sure yeah emi's probably gonna do it and it is some more streaming in
just uh maybe a little less uh a little less ump perhaps you know we can't escape
the suck it could be another brand of ruler it should be for the the innocent uh the innocent
side where i just make them do like girlfriend roleplay audios or like that kind of stuff but
like it's nothing it doesn't like go any further you know
safer work side that people have been asking for i did get a few emails um management showed me
them and people were like uh is it required to do that and it was like yep that's very sadly
kind of the the whole point of the agency um that's where the money is um
oh oh wait no there's not bored your people here anymore i was getting nervous so i was
gonna get caught and i'm like wait a minute there's no border oh the books are so good
eye contact roleplay teaching you eye contact proof i don't know the best way to climb this
maybe on the outside of the policy that looks up man
give me that feather
true love
girlfriend roleplay something what could a hand-holder roleplay blessing yeah like so i did have a few
variations of like would there ever be a generation that didn't require that part and it's like
what's the point it's just a real agency at that point
um where the hype was that other feather oh it's literally split perfectly in the middle
where there is the jump off point oh wait we have a parachute all right we'll just use a
parachute off the coliseum
temple popping roughly where you can hear audible oh in me
right we're just gonna do this
here assassinate
group roleplay is a few uh group roleplay is actually seventh as well i'm coming out
uh it just came in each time to sell i only want them to come out once the calling has stopped
because literally it's like such a shame that it is still happening even though like we're like
getting into the stage where it's like yeah we've like got proper streams now so i'm not really
sure what the deal is like the meme asmr's are literally i'm too scared to even upload them
at this point because i'm like what's going on with asmr i think there may have been a stealth
policy update or it's about to be introduced publicly uh feathers up here um
this is a little sister you argued has an innocent name yeah i'm not arguing in what's
innocent it was oh cool okay right we're gonna use the
yeah there's definitely something going on at youtube headquarters when it comes to asmr because
there's a lot of channels left and right getting yanked for content that previously was fine
and they're my guess is that youtube don't want to publicly say it because asmr is such a popular
category on youtube like it's an insanely popular category and they don't want to come out and say
it so they're just tackling it like silently basically so it's not arguing this thing um
i i think the uproar if they publicly said like we're doing this would be so much because asmr
i think they like said it's like one of the top four categories sorry like in the top 10 searches
a variation of either like foodie in or asmr medicines like whatever you want to kind of
really get into it um it's like such a high watched category that if they publicly said like
hey we're drawing the line here now i do think there will be a post at some point
but at the moment it's kind of stealthily being done so the content is no longer available so when
they do go publicly like hey we've actually changed this people are like oh that's fine because
like no one's been uploading it anyway because you know you've been deleting channels less than
right and uh handing out warnings willy nilly so yeah that's my guess by the way this is absolutely
not factual this is like just what my genuine like what i think is going on um youtube is
just like i see yeah it's literally just my guess what's going on it seems the most probable to me
um so unfortunately i think like you're looking content it's just gonna have to be like
just straight up upload it to twitter or put on patreon solution and i know a lot of people are
like oh like just put it like not behind a paywall on patreon unfortunately in order to link your
patreon successfully um everything must be behind the paywall for like even if it's a fine audio that
is not wrong with it um it has to all be behind the paywall it's bizarre it's bizarre the rules get
very arbitrary in memoria now you're wrong youtube's wrong
all right let me see we've done the feathers i have no idea how many things i've done right we're
getting close to doing the courtisms
yeah like we're supposed to enemy stations right we're gonna do that now because i know
how to do that you have to replay a memory from the french one
no
yes this is one can you stream to x i wouldn't stream on twitter no need money
like i hate to i hate to be that one i know it sounds really sucky we're like money money money
but it's like the obviously the girls need my support and the thing with youtube vods is like
you always like make money on youtube vods and like oh yeah once inside your men can
overpower the camp's patrols correct made money around yes especially if they're patrolling
i think it's fine saying like yes we're not an agency for greed but at the end of the day we need to
liberate several suits of french armor and don't and youtube vods is like a fantastic way or the
youtube adds on like a smaller video for example like this kind of stuff is like free to make
content like it's free for me to scream right now you know troops will gather it from the dead
and people underestimate the value of ad revenue via advertise like the free like add
the armor has to stay clean
right if you use your crossbow ball in this mission it accepts that last thing like
oh there's a horse right there oh there's another horse right there
business is business can't do everything for you unfortunately yes the world does run on
no i'm not going now because really peace forever to get to these days
um we'll go this way instead yeah this way is like so much better you basically for some reason
if you snipe the guys in this one um they count towards that court is on thing but if you snipe
in general it doesn't count oh sugar i'm sorry no i didn't want to do that
actually hold on hold on i'm gonna disarm and kill with this one weapon there we go one of five
nine percent of all my problems from silver money it is a terrible
okay we might have to do this place place i'm not sure well that guy's coming over to
investigate thank you another free kill is that guy coming to investigate oh these guys are
I'll take it.
I will loot them just so I can get some of them back.
That's how the next one might be.
We appreciate that thing, but please do always consider supporting the girls.
We should get crossbow bolts from this.
Hydration check, hydration check.
I've been yammering, but I've not had much water today.
I don't know when we can submit for monetization yet.
As I said, the stats are no update.
So it's kind of just...
They're very casually like...
Oh, excuse me, sorry.
Okay, I'm going to help.
I'm calling the assassins and...
Oh, I just teabagged them as they died.
Okay, that was a rather unit.
Let's not do that again.
That was really not a move.
Mm-hmm.
But yes, once the YouTube calling stops, then please do look around for very fun ASMR collabs coming out.
Very, very large ASMR collabs that cost a lot of money put together by Heihou.
Um, sorry, I'm trying to bramble and think and get this done.
I like how he's suspicious even though I literally just perished that guy right there.
God, I wish there was a way to pay for all the girls' patrons at once.
I just got 16 months back to back.
Oh, you support them as patrons?
Thank you so much.
That's very kind of you.
Thank you.
Yes, actually, special thank you to literally anyone who has supported the girls on Patreon.
I understand the patrons that you have one audio and it's very kind of you to like, you know, reach out and do that even though there's literally one audio.
And there are coming because the audio is released on the first.
The girls are going to have a consistent day that their audio in particular comes out.
I really hope this is counting towards the challenge, actually.
Um...
Grave, I'm having to go all the way around.
Wow.
Okay, that was it.
Right, I just need to redo that and then I think that'll be it for the mission.
Eh, for the crotch design.
Right, let me just check the DNA sequence.
I say that as I literally just close it.
That should have counted quite a bit towards that one.
Two?
That came in as two.
Why did that not work?
Is it because I kept getting detected?
Oh, brother.
Guards on horseback ears.
Guards killed Will on horseback.
PayPal guards, I need to go all the way.
Guards air assassinate from a beam.
Actually, we're closer to getting the thieves done.
I need to find a beam.
I don't know where the beam is to assassinate them.
The mercenaries one is like absolute killer.
So we got a patreoner just paid for you.
Oh, thank you so much for the support, I appreciate it.
Y'all are expected way more hate.
Honestly, I think we all did, but I think everyone's just on the same page.
You're probably tired at this point of your reach over just teasing and teasing and never giving anything.
And then it's like, yeah, we're just having a good time.
If you want the goods, you know where they are.
If you don't, there's also free stuff coming out.
There's a free video game coming out.
I think it probably helps without the greed out.
I think if it was a greedy looking corporation, that probably wouldn't help.
Right, I'm going to bump into guards and then run away from them and hide in spots.
We'll do the bump because there's a hay bale right here.
Excuse me?
Oh, sugar.
Oh, I don't think I can hide in this.
Okay, let's see how fast can I hide now?
Oh, no.
Oh, no, they're right next to me.
No, don't check it.
Don't check it.
That shouldn't happen.
Oh, there's more guards up here.
I thought this district was like, there's no guards here at all.
Oh, yes, the bench.
The bench of safety.
Okay, I can't go on the bench because it's not like...
Oh, for goodness sake, how many of you are there?
Oh, right, I'm hiding in here.
Can't get me.
Does that count?
Did it count?
He seems still annoyed at me.
I'm just going to check that counted because if it does...
Not the poking.
If that did count, I'm literally just going to keep upsetting those guards over and over to do that again and again.
I think it should have counted those.
I did it!
Right, time to keep bumping into them.
I'm going to kill this guard up here though because he's going to keep ruining it.
Yeah.
Woo!
Oh!
Ow!
Right, let's go upset some guards.
You smell so bad!
Tee hee!
Now you have to chase me.
Miss me, miss me, now you have to kiss me.
Oh, is that supposed to jump off?
Where's the bail hay?
Oh, there it is.
A...
Six.
Yank!
I've got to get out of here!
And then we just dive into this again.
Oh!
I'm not sure that counted.
He was like so close.
You guys should know.
No, I'm sorry.
Please excuse me.
Ah, please excuse me.
I'm scared.
There's a table in the way.
I got nervous.
I'm sorry.
Oh no, I can't claim this way.
Okay, he jumped down again.
Ah!
He's gone a long last.
Please leave him.
Leave me alone.
Ah!
Jump!
They're like instantly giving up.
I'm like really worried that it's not counting, but...
No, it is.
It just doesn't look like it.
It looks so silly.
And Mercy online?
Heck yeah, Mercy's online.
Let's go.
Is there any mods still even awake at this point?
You're more than welcome to link.
Mercy.
And please enjoy your stream.
I think we're going to wrap up the guild's challenge.
Oh!
I hit C.
I'm just going to squat in the hairball.
See you in the clip.
Can you hear that?
Or am I going crazy?
Am I going...
Did I hear that right?
Yeah, okay.
I'm going to...
I was like...
Are you all hearing that thing?
Literally.
I wonder if it's left over ambience from the party sequence with the banker.
Last one.
Okay.
I hear it again.
Is there like people here?
Or is it just SFX?
More like SFX.
Yeah, there's not even coded people to be here.
I must just be background ambience.
That's left over from the party sequence with the banker.
Let's get notoriety down a little bit because guards are getting really aggressive.
There's still asset, literally.
The party ended many a day ago.
They just played an operation.
Crazy.
That's crazy.
Right.
I'm starting to get a bit delirious.
How much should we survive though?
Mm-hmm.
I don't know why that did so little.
I'm watching all the girls, right?
A long watch strategy before...
Isn't there not too much noise?
Like, there's too much noise going on.
Like, focus.
We're all blabbing away at once.
Blabbing.
I'm not too sure what to do.
I'm kind of getting...
I'm not, like, stuck.
I know we can do those things.
I'm just, like, I don't know where the beam is for what we want to do.
Um...
I'm just, like...
Do we call it and then the next thing come on?
Am I gonna...
I'm like, I'm saying it myself.
Am I gonna be annoyed at myself if I call it right now?
Is one.
Think I'm...
I think I'm in back yet?
Oh, in 19 seconds they come back.
Right, let me find a group of thieves to hire at least so I can get rid of that.
I can only focus...
It's hard to multitask.
I'm watchable script, right?
But Mercy is alive.
If anyone would like to watch...
Mm, Mercy Modis.
Oh, I saw that.
Okay, there are...
There are thieves somewhere on the roof up here.
No.
I'm just coercing.
Um...
I think for simplicity we'll just teleport to the thieves guild in order to hire them.
I struggle so much to find thieves.
I understand they're on roof tops, but they make it so freaking hard.
Run Vods of...
Run Vods of all six at once and let it just fry your brain.
Most of that is four, but only one audio.
Yeah, like I understand maybe for like a collab stream you like meet everyone but one person and then get saved once POV.
Mm...
I have teleported to the wrong place.
I was not paying attention.
I apologize.
Oh wait, there's somewhere I can buy.
Hello?
Would you like to be purchased?
It would be a shame not to do Christina though.
Like we're actually so close.
Ah!
What's the percentage we need for Christina?
Why is your accent so cool?
Spondin' Scotland!
And...
Always be Scottish.
It's very hard to unlearn that accent.
I even think it's possible.
Truly outlawing it.
Um...
Why was I here again?
Oh, to hire thieves and there's literally no thieves hanging out here.
I need to hire one group of thieves.
Is this for real?
For real?
Like for real?
Well, I need to find a beam that enemies pass over.
And it's kind of in this general area.
I'm at...
Unbelievably.
I'm at 69%.
Um...
Like...
I don't know why.
Locate memory and world.
Insufficient data to accent.
Go to memory start point to synchronize with animals.
Gotta go to work.
Have fun at work.
If you could have any other accent, what would it be?
Ah!
Copernacle might have a lot of percentage in it.
That's missing.
We'll do Copernacle.
Um, as for accent...
I can't imagine myself wearing her now, honestly.
Like, to pick one.
The Italian accent can be really nice.
Although the Japanese voices are so nice and pitched.
Which I really enjoy.
But I guess it's pitch and no actual voice.
Uh...
Her accent.
Honestly, I don't actually mind a Polish accent.
If you've ever listened to a sweet Polish accent,
it can actually be really soothing.
Just a little hint of her words from that.
It's pretty good.
Apply the Scottish accent to any language.
Any language.
Oh, you might apply it.
I want you.
I want sex now.
As you believed.
Volgmae.
That's Scottish Dutch.
That's pretty awful.
Pray rough.
Right, we'll try Copernacle,
but this doesn't like dramatically raise the DNA.
I think I'm gonna...
I think I'm perishing.
Unfortunately.
And it might be wiser to redirect into Mercy
and kind of have a break
and deal with these ASMR collages
and see what I'm looking at,
because I think someone might be waiting on me to edit.
The world itself is unchanging.
We must change to understand it.
It's secret.
Scottish is the best accent in British Isles.
Who is this man?
He comes from Russia.
The Welsh accent.
I hear his studies at Iboticalo,
but his words are unlike any other issue from that place.
I don't buy it to put Scottish accents first.
Scottish is magical.
Hearing German speaking with songs that we're in.
You're not good at the spheres dancing around the earth.
You know you have a good source accent
when people can't even understand you.
I could use an excuse to go to bed.
Yeah, I'm kind of like,
I think I'm actually lagging.
I can't believe it.
You're me saying I'm an endurance streamer.
I'm a liar.
How long did we make it?
Take no damage during the ambush.
Right, get the wee knife.
Two minutes!
Let's get the wee knife.
No.
Yeah, that's what I meant.
I'm going to call in two of my assassins.
That was way too early.
You saw the way he was wiggling that knife.
Whoa, why are you...
You know the guy that's right in front of us?
Maybe focus on my guy.
Oh no, my assassins...
Okay, my assassins are sticking around,
which I'm quite happy about.
I don't want to call in the last batch of assassins.
Just because...
If they kill them too fast,
they actually might all be spawned
and not help me at all,
which is quite funny to think about.
I do wish citizens would stop running
into the middle of the fight or near it.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Don't hurt me, please.
If I take no damage, I win.
Oh.
I'm scared!
He's got such a long, frickin' pole!
He's gonna hit me with it!
My assassin is trying to chase them,
but it's not happening.
I'm just hiding.
I'm letting my assassins do it.
Copernicus is fine.
His health bar is fine.
Oh, I got fined.
Oh, they caught me.
I don't want to get hit.
I'm so close to doing no hit.
Please, please, please.
Please.
Literally 13 seconds is all I ask.
Don't change up.
Don't do anything else.
Just four more seconds.
Okay, we did it.
We did it.
I think we can do it.
I'm still running away
in case it counts.
I think it counts,
but I'm just gonna keep running,
running and running
in circles around the fountain.
Okay.
Yeah!
That's right.
I did that.
What did I do?
I didn't go up that much.
Right, I have terrible news.
Fake endurance streamer.
Absolutely horrible news.
100% poggers.
Yay!
You said 100%!
Now, we may genuinely return
to Brotherhood again
at a later date.
But I'm actually quite satisfied.
Literally, we did the campaign.
We've done all the DLC stuff now.
You did that so hard
that other people didn't find it.
Strolling it, if you don't finish it,
just means you need to do it.
Yes, I actually wouldn't mind
revisiting it at a later date.
I would like to play a bit more
Variety at this point.
I'm going to redirect
into
Mercy, so we can all enjoy her.
I can't believe it.
I'm not a real endurance streamer.
I only lasted
nine hours this time.
Gee willa curse.
Oh, I'm kind of basic.
I can't believe it.
Please do consider giving
a like and a subscribe
if you enjoyed.
YouTube may have unscripted
but don't worry,
I'm going to redirect you
into Mercy.
Into Merchandise.
Redirect, select stream.
Oh, she's playing Omori.
Omori.
That's Omori
when
Mercy plays
the tippy tippy thing.
That's pretty good.
Yeah, that's pretty good.
I got a copyright
on my Assassin's Creed Playthrough game
yesterday.
What?
Sorry, I just spotted that right now
and I'm like,
what?
I apologize.
Thank you so, so much
my lovely beflings
for watching.
Literally, I just checked it out.
I'm like, I'm pretty sure the game
has no copyright,
so it's a false copyright thing
going on.
But thank you so, so much
for hanging out.
Yeah, maybe not 100%
for the first time,
but we'll give it a shot.
I think we'll come back
and we'll feel refreshed
at a later date
because that was a lot of
jumping about.
I think that's brought
20 hours
combined
at this point.
So thank you
so, so much for hanging.
Tomorrow we're playing
Needy Streamer Overload.
I haven't played it.
So I'm not quite sure
what to expect,
but it is a shorter stream
for me.
So for those of you
who like the endurance side
of things,
I apologize,
but my stamina
is lacking tomorrow.
But nevertheless,
it's always fantastic.
Thank you so, so much.
My little beflings
or those who are watching,
and I will see you tomorrow
and say hi to Mercy.
I will talk,
I will talk in Mercy's chat
for a little bit,
but I do need to go
for the big P.
I'm not even going to pretend
otherwise,
I need to pay pass.
So I'll see you tomorrow.
Okay, bye-bye.
Bye-bye for now.
See you tomorrow.
Bye-bye.