Once the people in the camera
Action!
You break the microphone on Discord every time you do that
It's like
What is that?
You're so sister everybody
That's awful
I don't know what a freaking voice is
Awful
Ebi's root?
I'm checking
It's not
No, it takes like a minute to load for some reason
But once it's loaded
I'm being itched
No, it still considers streaming
Like when someone looks back in the VOD
They'll still be able to see this
Shit
So don't say anything
Don't say anything weird
Okay, okay
Okay, there they are
Hi Reflings
Hi
And Implings
If you're out there together today
You make Implings
Good morning, good evening, good afternoon
I'm Strongly Calls
And I'm joined by none other than
Ten sister Yakunts
Oh no, not Seepo
Hello, alloy to both gifts
Mambochka here, hello, hello
I have the streamer who never streams
Because I left streaming to become a strongy
Full-time strongy fan boy
She's a full-time clipper of me, thank you
Full-time clipper
Get the subs
Stop it
No, stop
Strongly Farted In My Ear Before She
No, I didn't
Did you hear it?
Right
At about time
You got paid back
Because you exposed me for my dirty chair
Okay
You're getting exposed for farting in my ear
Before she was away
I just farted in the mic
Before we hit Gola
She apologized
She had the audacity to apologize
I was like
Have a wee whiff in a sniff
And why don't you
Right, so
We are playing a game mode
Called
2vs
Stop
Stuff in the background
There's a temporary game mode
In Dead by Daily
It runs for two more days
If that's your thing
It is two killers
Versus eight survivors
The perks are already decided
The killers are limited
So if me and Sin want to pick a different killer
It's not a big deal
Hello, Momay and Mambochka
Real and true
Mambochka
Do you need a lesson?
It's Mambochka
Mambochka
As you can see
I am a faker
There's a way
There's a way more
Sin
Myself and Sin
Have quite a lot of history
And I'm going to finally tell you the story
Before we go into a game
Just so we can
We can tell you the story
Of how me and Sin became friends
Long story
Oh my God
Sorry
I know you're not streaming Sin
But I literally just got 50 gifted memberships
Literally big Jeff coming in
With 50 gifted memberships
Thank you L. Jeff
For the most cursed mobile picture ever
Congrats to those who caught it with your face
But thank you so much
Big 50 bomb name
Done anything
A lot of people want to know
How the heck did me and Sin become friends
If I told you
That me and Sin were rivals
Would you believe me?
If we were rivals
Cause that's true
Okay
So long story short
Back in the old college outie days
There was this girl
Ruining my win streaks
There was none other than Sin
So I hated her guts
I knew it was a girl
Because in voice chat
Like when you get a killer
Like at the end of rounds
And S&D in particular
Literally
Like she would
You know say stuff down the mic
And I'd be like
You fucking slag
And she'd be like
You slag
But she
She'd be like
You got no arms
No arms
No legs
And a pillowcase
There we go
So we were rivals
I hated her
And we would play the same game every day
And we would
Freaking get into each other's lobbies
All the time
And then eventually
A truce was formed
Do you want to know what the truce was?
It was
Look
We both have a high win record
Will we go win
Some games together
That was the truce
It was for the win-loss
And then we became acquaintances
Then we became whores
I said it on you've skipped a few years
So then we became acquaintances
And we would play games together
And as often
Love prevails
I didn't shag her
Relax
But
Basically
As you play with anyone
You form a friendship
And then lo and behold
Many a years later
We both beat you first
Oh
To the sun
Oh yes
So literally
Now we're enemies to friends
I've literally met her mum
That is how fantastic
Maui, mami
Hadwi, mami
Hadmabi, mami
Yes
So
That is the
Bizarre adventures
Of Strawni and Sin
Please tune in next time
For a secret behind the scenes
Lore, if you like
But
I am going to throw us in a game
Because I don't know how long it's going to take
So if you'd like to
I'm not ready
Are you ready?
Are you ready though?
You don't pick anything in game
All the perks
Are you joking?
What's going on?
All the perks are locked in
You can only pick between the killers you paid for
I was just wondering if you're ready though
Oh no, no, no
It's all by default
But
Okay
That is literally
An in real life friend
I'm jealous
I've literally touched hands with Sin
Did you not know?
Touched hands
We've touched hands
We had a sleepover
Yeah, we've looked in each other's eyeballs
Oh man
Oh, we did
We did
Oh, actually, Amala would say this
Amala would say this
Wait, type what it is
What is it?
Amala type it
Go on then
You're making me nervous
She's going to laugh
Oh, she's typing
She's click, click, click
There we go
Amala would say that
What the fuck?
Amala would say it
Is that true?
Are you joking?
Yeah, it's real
It's true
Are you a direct show?
You do
Amala would say it
What it is
Well, if it's true, then you need to fucking tell
You must be getting fucking tell
10 years later, practically, I'm only finding this out now
Sin has really bad eye contact
She's terrible eye contact
Terrible eye contact
She really struggles to look me in the eyes
Look
She just can't even look me in the eyes
She'll look everywhere else
She'll look at my hair
She'll look at my nose
She'll look at my lips
When I'm talking
She'll look around the room
She'll look at my strontism herself
Coming from strontism
You have to practice eye contact
You literally have to pick an eyeball
And then every, like, roughly 10 seconds
Look away, break for 2 seconds
And come back
That's how you do it
That's how it's done, okay
You leave me and Mali eyeballs alone
I know, but
You leave my eyeballs alone
It's endearing
It's cute, Ellie
Yeah, I like it
Oh, for fuck's sake
Even my frickin' feature book
I'm looking in the right direction
I'm raging
I'm pure for you, men
I'm for you, men
Absolutely for you, men
Well, can I use some practice, then?
A wee bit of practice
You need to practice on the ips
Oh, yeah
Oh, my god
Staring into the basement
I'll make you a hypnotist like me
Because you need eye contact to be a hypnotist
I mean, getting like
I've just broken all my tools
Oh, my god, you do know
When I actually go out in public now
I'm going to be pure paranoid
But my eyes are
No
That's all that's going to be going
That's all that's going to be going through my head now
Oh, my god
My eyes
My contact
No, to self
Don't leave the hoose again
No, that's not what I'm saying
See what she's probably did to me, guys
No
Oh, my god, they're all posting eyeballs in chat
That's hilarious
Is that my practice?
Okay, I'll try
I'll try
I'll get the whole contact
I'll contact with your chat
Okay, I'm staring at the chat
She sees you're making
I'm watching you
I know people are going to be confused
Like, guys, okay
I'm half Russian
I grew up in Scotland
Okay, that's why I go Scottish
When I hear scrawny
Yes
Okay, I soap up the accent
That's funny though
I left Russia a few years ago
And because we're doing the chair thing
Sorry about that
Okay, so when I was like leaving Russia
I had this office chair
That I used for gaming
That I accumulated a lot of my postures, right?
Like, because of my vaginal pH
It was pure white
And I used to be stitched to it, right?
Because I've been using it for years
Like, you know, you farted in that chair
You leaked in that chair
Because, let's be honest
Most VTubers game of me pants on
And then I took
I had to wait until 1am
To take my chair out into the streets
Because in Russia
You don't have your own bins and shit
So I had to
Everyone in the street shares a dumpster
So I had to wait until 1am
Until everyone was sleeping
To roll the chair
And then I was like
Okay, no one caught me
Thank fuck
I went in
I went to go to the shop the next morning
There's a gypsy's rolling in the street
Stealing my postures chair
I was mortified
Because I was like that meme
Where the guys in the corner
Like, they don't know that
They don't know that's my postures chair
Oh my god
I was mortified
I was like, oh my god
And I've also thought that was rude
Because it's like
The imps could have had that chair
Why are these random folks
Stealing my chair
They've yanked it
They could have cloned you
They yanked my chair
They yanked anything they can find
In the bins
And unfortunately it was my postures chair
So I was like that
Because that just amazed me
I was like, they gave her a chair today
Because like, they gave her a chair thing
Right, so what we were going to do
We were
I suppose Stony's got
Her fucking time in the month today, right?
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa
I don't tell them
My tummy hurts
I don't tell
I don't tell the reports that
Sorry, that's payback
You sent back my eyeballs
Right
Stony's leaking red
Stony's got the red rivers of blood
Red rivers of blood
Note it in the calendars, boys
Note it on the calendars
Keep track in our most fair-tile weeks, alright?
I don't tell them my hymen time
Because I'm thinking
I don't tell people
I can't even cry
Okay, okay, okay
Okay, right
Fuckin' 1v1 the unnec-time right now
I think
I think we're gonna
I think we're gonna have to look for a lobby
Because I don't know if you guys
Do we have to be survivors of this?
I think so
We're gonna have to cancel
I'll get us another
Just like how you're canceled in a
Leader
You're can-cancellated
I'm gonna fucking cancel
No sudden black ops to this
There will be blood
Either way, there's gonna be blood in this game
This stream, sorry
Yeah, so it's only one of us
With her clam on the-
With her clam hat
Stop! She's got-
Bruh, I'm being fucking ringed out
I've never been more exposed in my life right now
What the heck?
Same
Oh my god, I'm so-
That's two things
You called me out from my chair
And my eyeballs
Okay, we're not equal yet
I need one more thing
Oh my god
I thought I'd die
I'm like, uh
I don't even know what else you can make fun of me for
My flat chest
You're welcome, refund your welcome
Literally, now you know my fair-tile window as well
Rip enemies to lovers that enemies get
Yeah, I've done both the flow app
The flow app is really good
So get Strawny's date put right in
Don't
Which started today on the flow app
I've got that
Is that why you're both bloody?
Stop it
Stop it, bitch
Tisker
Don't tisker that
How dare you
Right, is there literally no one playing this game?
I think we're actually gonna have to do a regular
Schmeigler to Survivor Lobby
This is awful
I know, I actually saw maybe earlier that
People are struggling to find lobbies
Okay, right
Well, just a regular Schmeigler
Oh, no, I don't want to go to the store for you
Hold on
I've already paid a base fee to get on your game
I'll pay, I'll pass, okay
Right, play as a Survivor
And then invade
You're welcome, sweetie
There's a momma, she's always here to help
Let's just get the fuck out of here
Um
Senni's playing on another League Mummy
You should respond
I'm not dogging on Senn, what the fuck
I mean, I already dogged on her
Wait, who's dogging?
Because you were going on about my hymen
That hymen was after
Afterports, alright
Okay
Annihilate
What is Tisker?
So, in TSKR means Tascaru
Which means like, I'm blessed I needed that, etc
But because I was such a noobie noobie boobie
To VTubing, I was like
What's Tisker, guys?
But it's Tascaru
Oh, it is what it is
So it just means like, thanks
So that's why we say it as Tisker here
Mummy is getting defeated
Bro, I asked the where, I've got my Pepsi
If we actually cannot find a match
I'm gonna cry
There's no way there's no one else playing this game right now
The one time I wanna stream on it
And there's not one
What the heck is this?
I might have to get
Oh, alright, we've done it
Oh, I was about to say to me to get a pub background
I'm gonna need to have a fucking
Just chatting shit
About each other for a two hour stream
I remember that time
Oh my god, I have no perks
I have no perks
Wait, how does this game work?
Oh my god, how does this game work again?
Oh, look
Oh, I'm Meg, I'm Meg
Alright
It's been a hot minute
I have terrible news
I literally have no perks
So you're on your own
If I get downed you're legit
It's over
I'm so sorry
But we're literally gonna have to get carried by these two people
Because it's not gonna be me that's getting carried
But they look dripped up
So I think I have faith we can get carried this game
They look ripped
We're in our little default outfit
I'm a little bit too much
It's been so long I played this game
Some was like
You should play Chucky for more immersion
And I was like, eh
Chucky bastard
Wait, because you're small
I'm like, yeah, shock and behaviour
See, I should be Chucky for an immersion
Since it's quite a little bit smaller than me
Yeah, well, that's true
I can't even argue it
That's true, yeah
Yeah, it's actually really cute
Sorry, but it's really cute
I don't know why I don't
Like, you don't invite your friends
You're like, I'm no small, are you?
That kind of thing
Like, nah, she's small
But it's cute
I like it's endearing
Like, I'm taller than my mom
Okay, you leave me alone
Okay
That's all you need to do
I'm taller than my mom
You need to be taller than this
Oh shit
Are you already under attack?
I heard it's hard to be
Oh my, oh my God
My accent's changing
Wait, hold on
I'll do the rush on that now
Hello, how are you?
My pronunciation
What are you talking about?
You're speaking Russian
I don't understand
Well done
Come on, come on
So since sister's pocket size
Literally, I'm putting her on a lollipop
I'm getting a lollipop version
Of since sister right now
I'm paying for it, I don't care
I want to see it
Oh my God
Oh my God, imagine your boob toggle
And a lollipop, sorry
But you would destroy the feature
Oh my God, do you know how many spines
I need to hold myself up by the way
Because my model's like real height of me
Can you imagine
My tits, literally
With these size of tits
My nips are getting scalps
From the floorboards
I'm dragging along
Because how can my midget ass
Hold up these bags of milk
I don't know
Oh my God
Literally
Talking
I don't know
You don't get it
I didn't forget you
I'm on a gen
Right now
There's someone else that's
On the hook right now
Oh, blyat hamukha
Bitch
I just get to watch from
What you want
My safety
Oh, bozhe
Oh my God, he's trying to find me
Oh my God
Oh
Ah, get fucked
Ah, you go the other way
Oh shit, he's back
Oh my God
Okay, so wait
I'm gonna start a gen
Someone's getting the save, at least
That looks like
Okay, I totally did a gen
Because I'm such a good
You're such a good little mummy
Aren't you?
You're a good mummy
I'm not protecting my young
Where is the killer?
Oh, they're getting absolutely shredded
Right, they got saved
Sorry, not my problem
Shit
Oh, fuck, I just blew it up
Oh, it's a chainsaw
No
Yeah, I haven't seen him in so long
Oh no, our teammates are a little worm now
Oh no
A little wormy
A little wiggly worm
Oh my God, wait
Two people have already been on the hook
Sorry, we're not getting out of here alive
I'm so sorry
We're not making it out alive
Looks like an actual red
We're not getting out of here
Are we even gonna win a game
Before the end of the stream?
I don't know
Would you still love me soon
If I was a worm beach of her?
Oh my God
I'll make a fucking crib for you
I'll get some dirt, some plants
Oh
You can live your life out in a sandwich tub
Oh my God, I love
Oh my God, can I get orange peels as well
While you're at it
Oh my God, yeah
Yeah, every night
Every night, I mean
Fuck, where am I going with that sentence?
I'll give you some playtime outside for you
Oh, yeah
Oh, he's come back to the
Oh no, I just got
I just got
I was freaking
I was like
Fuck
I'm gonna be so smart
And hide in this locker
The first thing the killer does
Opens the locker
Bruh
You couldn't
That is
You couldn't make that up
You honestly couldn't make that up
No way
Our teammate's down
We are
We're not making out alive
Yeah
We ain't doing that
He here
The locker was too close
It's already closed
I don't know
I feel like it's so far away
Trust and mummy actually never mind
You know what?
You're in trouble
Fuck, she was
She was slick
Literally
Mamuchka, mamuchka
It's me
How do you say help me?
Mamuchka
Abagibia
Abagiciu
I'm sorry
Yeah, I do
Oh my God, I'm help
I'm help
I'm safe
Run!
Where are you, bitch?
He's chasing me
No, I'm just glad she's having fun
Oh my God
I need to stop
She's getting chastened
Oh my God
My med kit literally doesn't have enough to heal me
You have to be kidding
I should have put self-care on
This is fucking PSDS
Oh my God
Oh shit, they changed
They've changed the struggle thing
Hen, I don't even know if I can come save you
I'm literally doing it
Don't even bother
Find that fucking hatch
We're not making it
It's not even unlocked
The hatch hasn't unlocked
You need two generators done
Oh yeah, I need to die first
Fuck
Well, just let me die
Oh my God, no
Oh my God, sorry
I need to save you
Oh my God, we're all worms
I'm coming soon
Oh my God, worm v-tubers are real
I'm coming
I'm saving
I'm ready to run
You need to go
You need to go on
Oh fuck, he's going to like
literally chain saw over
Yeah, relax
I'm going to switch off this hook
Oh my God
Oh my God, we aren't going to make it
Run
I'm fucking running
I need to get that gen done for you
So you can escape
Oh my God
Oh shit
I hear a heartbeat
I think so
Oh no, he's doing that weird move
where he like swings left and right
I don't know what if
I'm taking him away
I'm sorry, I'm taking him away
I'm taking him halfway across the map
Okay, I don't know how to get you
Oh
I don't know how to
Oh no, I'm walking into you
Shit
All right, I'm going the other way
I'm going the other way
All right, it's fine
I was actually walking into you
He's waving at all times
Right
Oh my God
I don't even think the
things unlocked for you
Unless you've changed it
Right, I'm just going to die
and pray that it's going to open for you
I'm just going to pray
I think I'm bleeding out
I think I'm mourning
Oh my God, I'm mourning
I'm trying to die as fast as I can
How could his heartbeat already
I don't know
Maybe he has a pair
This map is awful
Literally the first game
we got one gen done
That's not looking good
I'm just going to heal myself
Right, I've perished
I don't know if the hatch opens up or not
Please
It's any death by day
like frozen here
I've been taken up to the entity
The heart
I think you saw me
It appears as soon as
there's only one person left alive
They might have changed it
Hold on, I'm going to spectator
You fucking found me
Spectator
Just run, don't look behind
Run, one more hit
and I'm down
Where's the pallet?
I don't know
Oh no
Bro
No
He's doing a goofy laugh
It's really scary
Oh no
I don't like it
Oh my God
Well
I don't
Well, he's won, so
Yeah
Last set GG
Absolutely
GG, that was the worst GG
We barely had a chance
Bro
He has to be feeling good about himself
Oh, I'm slurping my breath in like that
Must be stabbed in the abdomen
A little but fucking
rolled in smoke for any reason
Wait, what was this pair?
Great start
I know
If that's going to be the mood of this club
it's not looking good
I know it's going downhill
We're on a downward
Sorry, I'm going to be a weirdo
What was this pair?
Unlocks potential
Any survivor performing a brush action?
Oh, everything is like
What's surge?
Putting a survivor in a dying state
with a basic attack
All gens explode, bro
We never even did anything
Iron Maiden, you open lockers
50% faster, bro
I'm too much of a noob to understand this
Sorry, it's been far too long
It's been far too long
Yeah, I can't read
But then again
Girls are made for seeding
not for reading
So who cares?
Anyway
If that's your interview, you're in
I'm in
Right, okay, let me try
Call me Fondle a bosom
Stop
I thought that was amazing
Sorry, I thought so
I thought it was though
It just made sense
Fondle, that's because
Fond, like a goat
Right, Fondle
Fondle my bosom
It just makes sense
You're shocking me, bro
In short, his perks
Someone says if you fart
he knows exactly where you did it
Bro
Right, I'm levelling up my perks
Oh my God, I'm going to be so MLG for this
Oh my God
I'm level 10
I've got two slots unlocked
Oh my God, I've got an achievement for that
I'm such a real gamer
Oh
It's just
Oh my God, the entity's stealing from me
Sorry, but that's theft
Don't do that
What's going on?
Wait, wait, what do you mean the entity's stealing from me?
It, like, joined the weak spot from me
And when I was unlocking the blood web
I'm currently spamming all my blood points right now
Into the blood web
And it freaking stole from me
Can we fight that?
We bastard the entity
Literally, who does he think he is?
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight
I've got, oh my God
Oh yeah, yeah
I've got another achievement
I'm not even doing anything
I'm just buying stuff
I need to burp, but
Stronny's burps are another breed
and I'm scared because it's like
my burp's just a little bit
She's worried about being outburped by me
I'm literally holding it in
I'm like, I can't burp on Stronny's stream
because it's hurting me
No, you should
Reflins, no, your burps are
absolutely insane
You should be in the Olympics, those burps
I'm waiting for the first burp compilation
to go up
and if it doesn't go up in a month
I'm actually making my own burp compilation
because
there's a reflin that clips all my good burps
and I'm like, thank you very much
free content for me
thank you
because I will literally make a short
of just all my burps
and then I'll be known as the burptuber
thank you very much
Gather up, gather up
Hear that, hear that
Any burp compilation experts in the chat
you know what to do
Get Stronny Vegas bootied up
Once on our desk by 9 o'clock tomorrow
Actually, speaking of clips
in the Clipper program
I'm working on it
for any reflin that's getting edged
in their seat when I keep saying
it's about to launch
My goal after this stream
I'm doing a membership stream
of ASMR
and then after that
I'm legitimately
getting that program launched
sorry, but you're all getting paid
to clip us
and you're just going to have to accept it
you're just going to have to take my whole money
you just are
so, yeah
we've come full circle
you're now
you're being forced to work for hoes
that's terrible
if you say it like that
oh my god
I'm pimping you out
why?
I'll get the entity
okay, I'm level 21
we sweat
level 21
wait, what level am I?
I might level three
I'm trying to like get
my freaking perks to be better
I've got spine chill
so I know when the killer looks at me
self-care, empathy
I can see when someone's injured
that's kind of shit to be honest
I guess it tells me where the killer is
so I can just keep doing my thing
I'm sorry, that guy
like, no
I could never escape from that guy's heartbeat
everywhere
in my ear
I'm like, what the fuck
I'm sure there was a parrot called
agitation or something
that makes your heartbeat louder
artificially
I don't know, maybe not that
ooh
I'm so glad I have this slippery meat
parrot
the parrot that I will literally never use
I'm sure you reeflings don't mind having
a bit of slippery meat
here we go again
and we actually bet it's true though
why do your own work
when you've got like
reeflings to do the work for you
you know
why get randoms
why pay randoms
you know
the viewers are here
off you fall
reeflings take the money
take the money
magic and paid by your whole
to do work
like to clip her farting
like
isn't that just such an amazing deal
oh my god
actually that reminds me
she be sent me a clip of her fart
and I need to get it clipped
I've been
I've literally told the girls
I was like
if you guys
like send me clips of you
doing a really big burp
or a really big
fart
please tell me
for some reason
they always artificially
get really popular
and you
want no proof of that
Emmy has a fart clip out
and everyone was like
oh my god
this is the best clip ever
in the comments
I'm like yeah
that's right
I'm on to you fart andies
I'm on to you
right inside your gossip
I was like
totally like
in the interview
and she was like
if you can't burp and fart
loud in this decibel
then you're not in
and that's how
she was like
oh she's exposed to truth
you're sacked
so
oh my god
the truth has revealed us
that's actually what happened guys
so
yeah we were
we were in a voice call
and wasn't satisfied
with her interview stage
because she said
she wasn't willing to fart
down the three deal
that was it
I was in just in
sorry but
that was the end
that was it
can I have you in
can I have you in with that
should
should amazer sign an NDA
your saints can't have you in
can't have you in
sorry if you're not willing
to fart through a walkie-talkie
and
ASMR art it imps
stop
that's actually a really funny
concept of a name
if we get something
that can we still
farting down the mic
I might just call her
an ASMR forest
because that's amazing
that's actually amazing
we're in saw
I fucking hate this man
we're all together though
right where's the gin
that makes it even worse
I hate when we're all together
ASMR conness one
okay
I've got a fart pin saving me
but I'm too embarrassed
everyone's just going to point
and laugh at me
I'm just sitting in my throat
I'm not gonna judge
I can't
I just
chill not come off
I'm with you
I'm body blocking
don't you worry baby
cakes
fuck
I don't know this map that well
oh my god
do you mind
she smells the blood
I don't know what to do
against this killer
I don't know what kind of killer
it is
I'm sorry
I don't know
if I need to do anything special
sorry
I'm sorry
she's gonna wallop me
and I'm gone
but damn it
damn it
I don't know what to do
against this killer
she's so skinny
yeah
doesn't she like
put hex
I don't know what it is
no no no
that was a witch or something
she's like
the teleporting one
she can like
teleport away
oh not a teleporting
oh
and doesn't
her bones crack
and shit
while she's teleporting
her lore
was that
her dad
like threw
it was really abusive
and threw off a balcony
so she was all mangled
at the bottom
I don't know
she's mangled at the bottom
but
like she now uses
like her rage
with the entity
um
haha
I said the word too
um
excuse me
oh my god I got saved
oh my god please heal me
are you healing yourself
alright alright
oh no don't heal me
wait wait
don't heal me
oh the boss
oh that's
uh oh
wait I think I might be able to heal faster
you do the gen
do the gen
and then I'll join in
they're all getting struck
I don't know
I honestly literally thank god
we're halfway across the map
leave us alone please
we're trying our best
okay there we go
and then
I will do this gen with you
and then we have literally
outdone our last game
within like one minute
if we'd finished this gen
cause we just
we already had better game
I will literally
look we're MLG pro at this game
ahhh
bro
all I heard was
ahhhh
and then
she appeared out of
freaking nowhere
am I getting chained
bro I'm literally getting chained
okay tell her for it's no heartbeat
oh my god she's destroying pallets
what the heck
you're not supposed to do that
or something
I'm supposed to loop here
or something around these
I don't know how the pallets work
please stop it
I don't know where to do
did I just bring her over to you
I'm literally
I'm on the
oh my god
oh she's sniping
oh she's breaking the gen
she's going for me
she keeps it
she's ran away from the gen
she's after someone else then
oh my god
it'll be fucking me she's
ahhh it's me
it's me
it's after
six
six to the tenth
you'll hear a heartbeat
but I'm underground
okay you'll hear a heartbeat
I'm underground
fuck off
I'm just running around
I'm running around
get out of my way
oh my god stop
did she find me
I'm getting healed. I'm getting healed. I'll keep moving. Oh my god, that guy is so pissed off.
Plop, plop, plop, plop. Get healed, get healed.
Plop, plop, plop.
Are you still? Is she still?
She's still going for me. Oh my god, sorry.
Talk about hashtag tunneling.
Talk about hashtag tunneling. Like, oh my god, if you love me that much, just say...
Oh my god, stop. Oh my god, she's got me.
Oh my god, you're so rude. Go away.
Sorry, but you're getting tunneled.
Oh my god, I'm talking to James about you, so that's totally funny.
Well, literally, I'm like...
Oh my god, she's getting...
I'm literally...
I don't know what to do. I don't know what to do.
I don't know what to do. Reflins. Reflins. I don't know what to do.
I'm accidentally... I don't know. I think she might have dropped me.
No, I hear a heartbeat, so that can't be right.
I hear that hissing noise. That means she's coming after me.
What does it mean?
Oh shit!
Okay, sorry, I stalled so much time.
You guys are welcome. I stalled so much time.
You actually did stalled so many times.
I'm so proud of that gameplay. Sorry, I don't care if we lose.
I'm so proud of myself for that.
I'm literally so proud.
If everyone finishes the gen they're working on with one, I think.
Yeah, it means she is invisible and after you.
The panic roll. Literally, I was like, I don't know what to do.
That was good for stalling. Thank you.
Oh my god, Reflins. Sorry, you're boosting my ego.
You're boosting my ego.
Take that.
Who's she even lurking off to?
I don't know. Someone's getting chased.
But I'm getting helped by two people. Don't mind if I do.
Oh my god, I'm getting double healed up.
Give me them juicy heals.
Wait, where is she going?
I don't know why she's not healing now.
She really said I don't care.
Right, I guess if we bum rush this last gen.
Yeah, I guess. Okay, I'll start in this gen and I'll do the heal.
And then we all bum it up.
If mommy was the killer, I wouldn't fight back.
What? I wouldn't hurt you like that.
That's Mercy's job to hurt. I don't do that.
Okay, let's fucking bum rush this gen and actually escape.
Imagine if we escaped in our second gen.
We're so good at this game.
If we did the 2v8 kill, I was like, what's that?
Do you smell that too, Stranny? That boy you smell?
Wait, why are you running away, sweetie?
Why are you running away?
Aw.
Well, if we finish it, I don't know.
Maybe they're going to the gate to open it.
That might be wise.
Oh my god, they're pros. They're actually pros.
They're so smart. What the heck are teammates?
They're so smart. We should not question them ever again.
They're so good.
Okay, I think they're opening.
I'm going to pray they open the gate wherever it is.
Right, go.
Oh my god, where is it?
Right, there's one there and there's one right there.
Should we go for it? Oh my god.
Right, as long as it's upstairs.
Right, I'm going to do this one because it looks like she's chasing.
I've got empathy, so I can see that per person getting killed right now.
I can literally see them get chased halfway across the map.
They're downstairs right now.
Her thing.
I swear if she comes up on her side of the map, don't be selfish.
Maybe I should open it on her side by the way, guys.
Oh no.
I don't know if I can save.
I'm on too, so sauce, but because I've been on the hook twice,
I don't have to save. No, you've not.
Wait, there's a red thing next to your name.
Have you been on the hook?
I think so.
No, I've not. I don't have it.
Oh no, I need to go get them, don't I?
I don't know.
You and the Barbie person hasn't been on,
but I can't do anything like literally sorry, but...
I'm gone. I'm away. I'm away.
Where's the hooky?
She's pushing me out.
I'm lost.
Oh my god.
I just opened the gate.
Oh fuck, where's the other gate?
Oh fuck.
Fuck.
Wait, let me speak.
I'm lost.
I'm so scared.
I'm not going to make it out.
Wait, how do I...
Oh bled.
Oh no, this is not good.
You need to go upstairs.
Both of the gates are upstairs.
I'm going back up.
Yeah, go upstairs first.
Both of the gates are upstairs.
I don't like this.
And then take left.
Left, left, left.
Yeah, that way, and then it's a little to the right, I think.
Left.
Yeah, right, right.
Right, right.
And then...
That's right.
Left, right.
I don't know.
Is it not there?
Where's the gate?
There, there, there.
Left, left, left.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
No, no, where the killer was.
Where the killer was.
Sorry, there's a freaking delay.
Go, go, go.
You can make it because even if she hits you, your full health, you can still go out the
gate.
The gate's not open.
They didn't open the other gate.
Oh my god.
No way sin died because of my fucking...
I'm so sorry.
I did it.
I thought they opened the other gate because the other...
Oh my god.
No way sin died because of my fucking...
I'm so sorry.
I did it.
I thought they opened the other gate because the other freaking person disappeared.
Game over.
Oh my god.
That's so sad.
Wait, they're so nice.
What the heck?
Oh my god.
Go in.
You need to type GG.
Oh my god.
GG.
That was so nice of you.
Thank you for a lovely game.
We love you.
Kisses you all over your nice face.
Oh my god.
Thank you.
Kiss.
Oh I...
Literally we love caned killers out here.
Oh my god.
We love you.
I was actually going to cry.
Your sir wave.
Oh.
That was so nice.
I mean, thank you.
Yeah, yeah, cause you didn't...
You didn't have to let her go.
That was so nice.
Oh.
Literally.
Oh my god.
Nice killers.
I had like...
Streamsaber, you think?
You get nice ones. You get nice ones. I think it was if it was one of you guys you'd be twerking into in 360s
I don't know you guys to be humpin strongies
I do actually get them pent up so much in streams though. I have to admit I'm a bit outrageous
Like sometimes I'll look back in a stream and I'll be like, oh my god
I'll be like did I really say that and then like I'll go in my marshmallows and then they'll be like mommy
I'm so XYZ and I'm like honestly. Yeah, I'm after what all the stuff I was saying. Yeah. Yeah, that's fair
That's real and true
Cuz literally I'm a bit outrageous and now the refunds are the exact date when to send you more so
That song and before everyone literally guesses my fertile window, thanks to you
Oh
I'm pregnant nation. Let's go
Well, do you want to know the tea? So I said if I get 20,000 subscribers, I'll show a pic of my butt naked
I hit fucking take a boat. You need to give me a few days lads. You need to give me a few days
Just you mean that
Shut up
You're making it so much easier to pick cells. It's natural at all. Your wings are showing me that
You've made this so much more cursed than I've ever seen a ladies. No! Oh my god
Oh my god
Actually, Mays was last week though. So was it? Wait, do you tell the imps when you're in your ketchup season?
Yeah, I'm like, sorry guys got shark bait in case the tides to get fucked. Oh, right. Okay. That's all right
I was just like yeah, I've got shark bait, you know
Because it's uncomfortable, you know, like it's actually tummy heart when you're playing games and I'm like, oh my god
I could feel it looking through the fricking chair. I just have painkillers and have a hot water bottle on my stomach the entire time
You just like you can't feel any pain if I'm literally burning my
I like the pain, you know. What? Hold on a minute. I
Like the pain. I like feeling that I have pain so like having pain and not being able to feel my pain. Yes
Oh
The trick my body into thinking oh everything's hunky-dory. No, you give me that so stomach baby girl
Put my tongue to you by the way because it's not me
I think what you're doing is called going on a model walking. I do love a little bit of female. Who did that?
Identify yourself. I'm sorry. I'm let you have your dough. Okay. I'm sorry
Oh, we're in the game with a person from you the last match Barbie is in a game again
Harvey. Oh Barbie. Of course Barbie goes down first practically. No, they just know Barbie's good. Barbie's good
Right if they go down instantly, we know it's a really hard killer
It's really hard killer that be every flume
You right. Okay. That was actually really smooth
I'm like trying to try hard on the skill checks. Oh crap. Oh, no, I think it's the zombie one
Where there's zombies on the map, so don't get jump-scared because I think it might be the zombie one
How did she know I mean I've got some eye contact, you know
I mean my favorite killer to play was Michael Myers. I like to just stare at people
Oh my god
It's a big technical guys not and they get them picture
He doesn't even know I'm there. Oh shit. Are you going for the rescue or no?
I
Guess I have to know that run away. I'm gonna go. I don't know. I hear her heartbeat. We need Barbie Barbie's good
I bet actually, you know what if it wasn't for that last killer
I would be thought so you know what fuck your Barbie didn't open another other door for me. How dare you?
This per guy. He's trying his best on the Jenny keeps popping it. Oh that hard killer
me
Literally between a rock and a heart are you saving are you saving?
You can I hook again wait. I saved the person. Yeah. Oh, right. Sorry. Sorry. I didn't realize. Oh, it's running away
Somebody's running away. Oh my god. Oh my god. Everyone's running. Oh my god
Oh my god, we're scouting like freaking cockroaches right now when you open a fridge in America
I'm chasing someone so time to get those Jenny's
Oh
Wait, oh my god, I don't know if he was one getting changed. Oh, no, no, no, the killer's right there
Oh my god, sorry, I need to find a gen to do or else that hatch. I'm doing one as we speak
Takes so long though and the zombies coming in trip check like that. Oh, I look they're like they do act as like another whole
like player thing
That applies more pressure on the I'm gonna have to get this guy cuz it's that black Barbies on like literally
That's why I hear a harp. I hear one too. I'm being chased so you're safe to do whatever you'd like
I'm literally going to the other side of the path. Oh
My god, my spine shell keeps going off because he's right behind
Oh
What does that mean? I just got whipped by tentacle, but it wasn't a refling school way
I don't want it. I don't want it. I ain't every flint. I don't want it
If I ain't a refling's I don't want it. I don't want it. I don't want it
Right, that's it
I'm taking them inside the house because I know the generator's been done in here
So I'm literally just going nuts going around in circles and again heels up again
Then he means me doing 360s around this house because I know this is the only gen that's been done
He's spanking me again refling stop. I don't know what to do. Right. Okay. Let's do this bye. I do you to break that fuck you
Beach, I'm so gonna be knocked down. I don't know how I've survived to hit slow
Um
I'm going around in circles. Surely he knows what I'm doing
Okay, I don't know right. Okay. It's fine
It's fine. It's fine. Oh my god. There's a there's a guy near me as well
He needs to find this cure. Everyone needs to find the cure before they become zombie
Don't keep getting inked on but it's not refunds. I don't like it. Okay. Let me finish my tea is it literally room temperature
Okay hydration check refling's an end. Oh no, I saw me. Impling fucking hell. Oh
No, I didn't. Implings have a mascot, don't they? Did they?
Yeah, just an imp in a suit
That's adorable
Yeah, cuz I got my little office outfit, so it's like, oh look date the office. You're under the desk
Also because they do
You know, we've got
Ones that do clips, you know, we've got one
He's whipping me. I literally hooked as well. I'm like, oh, yeah, that's been zombie-fied
Yeah, we're all zombie right now. We're literally all zombie
Don't stop licking me
So rude
Right, I'm getting saved. Hello. Thank you. I think it's connections a bit rough. That's okay. I forgive you
That's me screaming
Oh dear we're both coughing and I'm injured not gonna make it
When a guy she mass
Yeah, the white chest that are highlighted to you know, oh
My god, he took him to the basement. He passed the basement. Wait, what's going on?
That's where I live. Come on. How is he in the basement and not down right? I was gonna say sorry, but how are you even doing that?
Right, I need to be able to freaking take this medication
Did that just freaking close on me after I opened it you are trolling, right?
Inject vaccine, okay
That's really faking rude
I
I thought I was being so sneaky. I'm not I'm not being sneaky at all. I suck. I'm sorry
I thought it was being so sneaky. Oh
No, oh
My god, I'm so I'm infected again. I can't save that guy. I'm so sorry
I can't save the guy on the hook
I thought oh my god, he's normal. Oh my god
I wish spine chill gave you like a speed booster saw and if the killer looks at you for like longer than two things
Thanks, I'd appreciate that stop
Stop. Oh my god. I missed his tentacle. That's right. You're not refland only we've been through a tentacle me
Oh my god, I'm not gonna make it only go
Go men a story team go men a story, but I
I
Sorry to get generators done. We're all literally fried
Let's I don't know what happens with the vaccine like we don't cure the vaccine answering. We just succumbed to death
Yeah, so I'm just like that
Can you highlight your white chest?
Very the hell is a team I want you the entire team is with you apparently it looks like oh no big killer boys coming
I'm getting healed
You can break out of it with sprint you can break out of healing with sprint
Oh my god
Electrally healing me for ten hours. Oh, that was that was too risky. I'll ask me going on a hook
Oh, wait. No, he's okay. No, it's chasing others now. Oh, yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Oh, no, I'm getting picked up
I have to admit it's nice being able to see like
What the teammates are doing like I can see if they recover or they're doing a Jenner, etc
That is a very big quality of life improvement when it with a game that has no communication
Oh, it's trying is what you're doing and when you're doing it
Well, I'm in the basement, so do you this is what it's like to be in the basement
We're all coughing and dying
I don't know what to do
Are you a really healthy team?
Yeah, I was spine chills going off as well. Well, oh
Did he see me be honest? I think I just saw him. I
Think my days are not anyone's numbered, but they're fucking I'm the quality that's running to you
Is anyone further ahead than me?
Let's know
They're all coming for me. Are we all going for it? Right? Oh, no, they're not
Okay, I'm coming. It's me. It's me. I'm coming. I don't know where the entry to the frickin basement is though
And
No, it's not. No, you're not the dude or something got me now. What the fuck?
Okay, that's fine. That's fine. I'm just gonna do this just really wants to heal me
Maybe it's a street night, but are you every one are an infant? Oh
My god, the zombies are so nice. Where's the imps any imps called Jesse and Barbie in the chat
Hi, I'm Barbie
Oh, he's back
I'm a barbie get out. Oh my god, the insult
Life in plastic
All right means in cover when
Oh my god, we've all been on the hook twice it's over. Sorry, but we're not making this one out alive
No, this is even worse. Oh
Oh
My god, everyone dies when they go on I got impaled by a fucking tentacle
If everyone's gonna die on hook, I need to be selfish and look for the fucking thing
I'm saying that bad boy. No
I'm trying. I don't know if I can heal myself or my moans are gonna give everything away. I
Think my moans are gonna give everything away. I
Think I think this is a fool everyone dies for it. Oh, I just fucking stabbed myself
And how do you fail putting bandages on yourself, honestly
Getting chased back. I don't mind if I go down the mic
Here thing he got more expecting. Oh wait. They have a moray. Oh my god. There he is
Yeah, he impaled my fucking body. No, he just closed the
It was right there and he just closed the damn thing. Oh
That's so annoying
That is so annoying. Sorry, but this is really intense. I'm literally not making this out alive
Like if he comes over, I'm just except that I'm not making out alive. I'm gonna hear the heartbeat. Oh fuck. Well
Hi, can I give you this? Can I can you just let me go? Can I can I?
No, you're supposed to look away. You're supposed to look away
You're supposed to look away
And let me out you think you can you think he
He literally looked away as well like he almost fell he fell for it
Sorry, he fell for that look behind you and then I literally escaped
Okay, that was a GG. I'm not too mad. He played very well. I'm a pity to me in my name. Okay
I'm GG. Well play all good luck in next game exclamation mark. Oh my god. I'm such a nice dad by daily thingie. Um, oh my god
I'm gonna endorse you right now. Oh my god. Thanks for the endorsement. Oh my god. They came with a freaking moray
Oh, he never had any perks. I miss me very new
Right, I'm I mean business that I'm putting add-ons on. Oh my god. We were so serious and after hooking a survivor
All their survivors are revealed for five sayings. Okay, that makes sense why he was able to come straight for us whenever like that happened
He just picked her up and carried her like a sports bag, bro
Honestly, I got manhandled that that gay assault. I'm saying I got literally manhandled like
I just get put in his pocket
He just carries me
All right, put him in my pocket. There you go. Pop it. Lock it poke it off it
No, I don't hang the hat
That is kind of Montana. Yeah
Why do I remember why is that I'm looking the whole time? I just noticed that your weapon is locked onto your boob jiggle physics
That's actually really funny. The weapon's like jiggling with your bitch
John. Oh, yeah, you like me in that office. Oh my god. I'm so jealous, bro
I'm so jealous that you can just like right strong and get your glasses on
Oh
Oh, if you guys wait, wait, if you guys didn't know hold on
Let me make you bigger if you guys didn't know sin has this amazing toggle. Hold on
I'm making a bigger right do the toggle again because I put you like
Front and center if you didn't know sin has this amazing toggle watch one
It I just look your eye out. I'm sorry. It literally pops her blouse pops open
Is that no amazing or is that no amazing? Like I don't know how much I said
But and she can make them we are bigger right now. They're big
But she can literally be like, oh John. I'm back. I'm back. I literally humongous
Like if you guys didn't know literally her thing is pinned in the chat, but it is absolutely amazing
So but she has so many that's why the killer keeps getting me undead. I didn't hear my tits clapping against my kneecaps. Oh my
That all right
That's so cute
You hear me before you see me or you smell me before you see me. Oh my god. Maybe that's you actually
You don't you smell straya for you. Oh my god. I'd be pheromone max and every time I play a freaking game
I played halo and I was absolutely reekin. So she's fondle abysm. Oh my god. This is fondle abysm all along
Do you want to fonder my abysm?
If you want to
Or am I cat and beat?
A star that would like like it's not I can literally go and type in fonder right now and see all the other fucking
I'm like, I'm holding sin's hand. She's gonna support me. Oh my god. I'm so pale compared to you
Like the only toggle I have is literally
On all my talk with all the names. I said fondle a cock
Fondle a cock
Oh my god
Oh my god, let me pop you back down. I see bander. I see erection. I see erection
No, don't do that with ac's name because everyone's gonna call her ac erection there. No, I see a cock
My baby
All right, we found out that bend there is erection in french
And we thought it was brilliant. We did come on. We thought it was brilliant
And like then it come on. I'm a simple. I'm a simple thing a simple thing. I'm a simple creature
I like a funny one. I'm actually fan girl. I'm like, oh my god. I love it so much in capitals
Stop
Someone says AC I cock. What the fuck? No, I said you a message at 3am saying I can't sleep
I like the word play fondle my fondle and my titties are some fish
Fondle my bigos. Why did I wake up at 3am?
Bruh sin's.. I couldn't sleep for five seconds. I couldn't sleep. I couldn't sleep. Hilarious to work with. I'm not gonna lie
simple areas to work with. Hence why Strawni has all the brains. Are you joking? I'm brainless.
The little monkey like, like the wee symbols. The monkey with the symbols in the corner
like, Strawni hates her high IQ. She does, she does. Far from it, far from it. She hates
that juicy IQ. I'm telling you, I'm telling you. I don't know what you're talking about.
Her name's the Yandere Karambi that has absolutely nothing to do with a weapon. Okay, okay, how
did I do that? No, I was like, that's broken. I was like, that's absolutely broken. Lock
it in. Absolutely. Right, hold on. I'm almost level 50 on one character. Does that mean
I get another steam achievement for being such a good girl? I'm level 38. Sure, we'll
do hope three. Why not? Even though I don't use hope, I don't know what it is. I don't
know what it is. Combine everything. Yeah, that's true. Strawni's got the booty clap
and then my tits are clapped and so it's like, no, no, no, no, no, no. Wait, can I
do a sports bra on right now? Can you do? My tits are like, really tight. I was gonna,
for no particular reason, can you clap with your, right, for those of you who don't know
the lore, I'm flat chested, there is. I've literally have the smallest chest. Is it possible
if you have a big enough goober's that you can clap with them? Is this possible? Probs,
I don't have massive goober's. I don't have massive, I have my feature mode on this, but
I know you're trying to go for it. Hold on a minute. I'm pretty sure Shibi has massive
knockers. I'm going to ask her to record an ASMR real quick. Shibi's the expert tease
for that. Defo, we go to Shibi now for a whole trip. Hold on, wait, let me just DM her. Hold
on. I can't forget them on YouTube. I should be using other code names that come right out
of like, you know, Goobies. I'll call them Goobies. Yeah, big Goobies. Hold on right. Okay,
dear Shibi, I have heard through whispers that you have big, massive honkers. If in theory you
could clap with them in the ASMR mic, please do not hesitate to record said audio and I will,
I will edit it for you. Love you. I'm indebted. I've never seen a YouTuber clap to her boobs clip.
Oh my God, is that witch again that can, oh the, the Japanese. Yeah, she, why does she sound like
a popped air balloon? Well, like, so she got her, the lures, her dad was really abusive
and she got shoved off a balcony and she smashed into a mirror, which is like why there's mirror
all in her, her flesh. There's always a mirror involved with a scaredy girl with long hair.
A bruh on it? Yeah, what the fuck? You're, you know what, that's it. Oh my God, I found someone.
Is that you? I think I found you. Oh my God, I found you. Right, let's do this gen together.
Get it done. What was that? Did you hear that thunder? That thunder? Was that she be
clapping her boobs? Holy crap. She's fast. She's fast. You have one.
Okay, fast. We're doing this. Oh, we're so fast. Faster. Faster. Faster. Faster. Faster. It's a
boon hair. That clap hit round the world. Either that was my cheeks or someone's
feel or someone's. I've never tried that tech clap, honestly. I never really crossed my mind,
like, oh, I can't even clap them. Reveal the truth, momma. I mean, what's the truth? Good
bars, the big good bars. Have you called them? I say good bars. That's what I used to call them.
If you want some more, momma, cuddles, lures. My mom has fat fucking honkers and I have the
flash chest. I don't know where the fuck the genetics went because it clearly didn't.
I know where my genetics are going. Bruh, literally. Wait, what?
Wait, wait, wait. Oh, shit. Are they trying to slug? Why is my screen blue?
You're blue screening. Wait, oh my God. Wait, is this totem you can pick yourself up if you go
down near it? I've never heard that in my life, but I guess it's been years since I've played.
So they came out with this hex girl because obviously all the totem weave pull things are for...
Am I about to get walloped? Oh, I'm about to get walloped. Sorry. I'm being a cheeky bam here and
that. Oh, I'm so sorry. Do you want to heal? Is she chasing you? Oh, shit, come on.
Soz, Annie. Okay, she's fine. Right, you're on your own, mate. Soz, you're on your own. I'm letting
sin deal with the gen. Soz. Literally just one down. Four more to go. Right, so...
Oh, my God. Wait, our teammates are really good because I think they were teabagging. I can't tell.
Soz, but if a teammate teabags when they're getting chased by the killer, I'm like, oh my
God, we're in good hands. I know it's toxic. I know it's toxic behavior and I know it's not nice.
I'm sorry, but... I'm being a cheeky soz like that. I'd be a rage if that was the killing
fucker team. Oh, my God, but I played the killer before and I kept getting teabags in like the
torch in my eyeballs. I was human. I was absolutely raging. I'm getting exposed by my gen mate. Oh,
my God. Sorry. The whole company is imploding. You want to know the lore about my prego ASMR
video, soz. Yes, I had to use sheebie's heartbeat because mine was too fast.
Oh, what the fuck? Oh, there's a fake heartbeat.
What? Wait, is he cheating? How did he get off the hood? Why am I blue?
It's a totem where you can pick yourself up. Why is your heartbeat so fast? I have a very unhealthy
heart. I'm literally a hamster unironically. I can't use my own heartbeat because it's too fast
and sheebie recorded some and I was like, sheebie, can I use your heartbeat because mine's messed up?
And she was like, yes, sure. And I'm like, thank you. So yeah, the truth is it's not my heartbeat in
the prego ASMR because mine's too fast and uncomfortable. I thought the bail blocker fell.
But my fucking heart is pumping out after that. Oh, my God. Jesus. Supposing the company from the inside out.
Chocolate behavior, honestly. Who snitched? I guess sheebie question why? It's not a big deal.
Is it? It's not a big deal. That's absolutely a big deal. That's absolutely shocking behavior.
Be a blocker is to try and stop me. Me, we heart from pumping too much, but soz. I don't know.
Oh, it's snatched. They use each other's parts next, huh? No. Trust issues. They're typing your real
part. Is that your real part? Is that your? Oh, my God. Imagine if I'm a sound boarder.
Yeah, literally, literally. Oh, I heard a new thunder lies as your hair sounds are they real?
My hair. Yeah, that's my girl. I've given you my fucking hair sounds to use in an audience.
Are your are your slosh sounds real? Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Right. Okay. If you want the motherfucking tea, Alex, I'm in trouble. I'm in trouble soz.
I'm in trouble. Trubs. Forget the meme. Drop the memes. I'm in trouble. This is serious.
Never know. I'm not laughing. I'm not laughing. Sorry. I'm not here. I'm getting scared. I'm getting
scared. I need to feel. I'm still feeling. Oh, my med kit. No, it's over. I'm serious now. There's
no fucking lolly gag in this is serious. Oh, I just got jumpscoot again. Oh, my God. We're all
injured. I want to win one game where we both get out. I still feel so bad about that song map
because I thought you were on the different side, but I get so confused like I wish. I know the maps
aren't supposed to be easy. Like this isn't supposed to be like the easiest game ever to win,
but like, come on, the freaking both gates should go flying open or something. I don't know. It was
a fact that I went to go down to save that guy so you could get out, but something already saved
up and it's like they all got out and I'm like, oh, come on. Come on. Who's being chased? Are you
being chased? I'm just injured. Yeah, I'm fully saved. Oh, there's the enemy over there. Don't go
there. Don't go there. The enemy's right. We need to get the genies. Did we do one in here?
I don't know. I haven't even been in here yet. I'm looking for a gen. I'm looking for a gen. See,
this is a problem. I hate when it's not obvious where the freaking gen's are. I know they have
like big massive lights and all that, but am I going mental and I can't see them or...
Oh, no. Yeah, we're not even live right now. This is a sound board.
Stop. The refunds say that. They're like, oh, my God, this is all pre-made streams and that. I'm
like, what are you on about? Like, oh, my God, I'm literally live.
Yeah. Sin is actually voice acting and strong. Yeah, real. It's true. Real, real.
I practice. Hi, my big friends. Good morning. Good afternoon. Good day. Close enough. I'm
strong. Close enough. Bring her in. Bring her in. Right. I'm taking a break. Are you inking for me,
sweeties? Are you inking for me, darling? Good boy. Oh, shit. Oh, shit. Sorry. Run, run, run, run.
They're going to know we're here. She's been hired. Oh, shit. I hear the heartbeat. We're in trouble.
Wait, I don't, I don't hear a heartbeat anymore. Oh, that's why.
She's on my arse. She's on your arse hole. She's literally twerking on it.
We are reputable. No. That's your impression. That's my favorite. Darling, what's wrong?
Oh, the voice is fucked. I'll let you know. I'll let you know. Oh, what's wrong, sweetie pie?
Bleeding hearts. It's kind of there, but Azura naturally has that, like, pure six.
I don't know if I can save you. I wish I could have that voice. Bro. It's such a good voice,
honestly. I would never shop if that was me. I'd be like, yep, yep, yep, yep, yep, yep, yep, yep.
Oh, well, her tag is adorable. It's yet per corn, which is gracious. I think that's the cutest
thing ever. That's cute. We are real. The stream is just pre-recorded. It is. Thank you for doing it
at the right time stamp. Okay, I'm going to finish this gen, and then I'm going to
know I'm not because there is a random thing that stops me. What is everyone else up to?
Someone's claiming for windows and they just fell down. What do you mean everyone else?
It's just us. We're the only ones left. Oh, we're dead, but it's been.
We're doing really good. Oh, fuck's sake. That shows you how much I'm paying attention. I was
just so shocked over the heartbeat. That didn't pay attention. Half working her litches six feet
under. Oh shit, what's going on? I'm trying. Are you moving? Dane, I have botanino. Oh shit, run!
Run, run, run. She's here. Oh, for fuck's sake. I give up. That's rude. No, I want a new game.
I want a new lobby. I want a new lobby. I want a chance for us to win. Go and just let me and
my friend go. Sorry, go and just let my friend go. Go and just let her go. Go and just let her go.
No, no, she's mine. Let me give you my med kit or whatever. Look, I'm going to take, no,
stop it. I'm going to take her off the hook. You stop that. Right, and then take, no, no, take me
in her place. Wait, she's actually chasing you. No. Why? Bro, you're- Oh my god, she's like,
why does she want to break? She just want to break the fucking- Stop, why? No, you're going to die
Su-chara, what the guy? What a fucking Su-chara. I'm actually raging.
No, you're awake for it. Stop it. I'm healing. No, you're awake for it. What a wet wipe, honestly.
Literally, speaking of wet wipe, I can literally see her bot crack. You need to clean that better,
hey. Literally. I see that. I feel like starfish. I see that. That's it. I'm wiggling off, but I'm
like, take a chance on hook. Take a chance on hook. Can we touch hands? Can we crawl to- No!
No! She's doing it. She's killing me with her fucking- She'll let you just stab her.
Right, I'm dead. Mummy, your charisma check failed. We'll get a nice killer one day. Look,
I just want to win one game we're sinned before I have to go offline. Is that so bad? Is that?
It's her nip, so what the fuck? No, she is clothed, but like, it's very revealing, not-
Let's say I managed to fuck all that game, because it was like everyone was going off the hook.
We've got the bad ending yet again. Mummy, the negotiator. Literally, just let my friend go.
She's not even- I got a thing. Where did I get 17k points from? Just apparently
did an achievement. GG, we'll play all good luck. Next. Ilyu.
Excuse me. I'm actually raging. We both can't be killers. Like, what the fuck?
Well, there's a- Did you not see the blood point boost that said if you pick survivor,
you get 400% extra blood points, I think, because everyone wants to be the killer in
the game mode, that they can't find anyone. I mean, wait, hold on. Actually, you know what,
let's try it. Hold on. Let's go again. We'll try if we can do survive in the 2v8. Okay,
survivors is literally a 400% blood bonus, so I'll invite you in and we'll see what happens.
Have to do more generators. Maybe. Maybe, baby. I'm not sure. I'm just readying up,
and we'll give it a few minutes. We'll have a little cooldown. We'll have a little hydration
check in, please. All right, I got my Bepis. Cheers, everybody. Cheers. She's on the wrong
team, clearly, drinking Bepis, but whatever. Do you mean they're on the wrong team? If I say it
to my face? We can play the killers and make you two win. Stop. That was our 4% to get off the hook.
Yeah. Mummy, you can fill the melody. So we're playing until you win. No, unfortunately, I do
have an ASMR membership stream after this. I know. So, can you? Can you happen? Can you happen?
If they needed insurance. Try to be a killer in 2v8 yesterday. It took about 15 minutes for each
game. Right, we're going to give it a minute, and, you know, for can you? I'm just going to end up
a podcast waiting on the next game. Oh, bro. Anyway, welcome to the podcast, everybody.
Welcome to the pub. Doing the pub, that's our podcast name.
What is the topic of conversation on this podcast? I don't even know what we're talking about.
I don't have anything interesting to say, like, ever. I'm just like, yeah, hi. Same.
I don't like Coke, though, because Coke makes it look like my teeth are wearing
Ugg boots. Oh, because of the sugars. Yeah, it's like my teeth are wearing Ugg boots.
That's such a good descriptive. I would say, like, brush your teeth. You need to brush the
peas and poos out your mouth, that's what I say. Well, that's what it is. It's the germs
that do like peas and poos in your mouth, basically. Chicken Parma. Well, actually,
chicken Parma is on meat basis. So two Scots enter a bar. Oh my God, that would be what the podcast
is called. I'd listen to a podcast of these two for hours. We'd have to pick something to talk
about, though. But because I'm also Eastern European, you know, it's vodka. It's vodka as well.
Some are gone. Vodka and whiskey walk into a bar. That would be the name of the podcast.
Vodka. Oh my God, I love that vodka and whiskey. Oh my God. And they mix it together.
Okay. Yes, love it. Love it. It wouldn't be yet.
The tea, we just talk about all the tea. One gets so drunk and starts
suddenly talking in Russian. Oh, no. You need to teach me more Russian. The only thing I've
picked up off of her is literally Privyet, Cactella and Sika. Or you can be more like the colour
way. That's the colour way. The colour way. You can say like the cool Gopnik way to say
hi, guys. You say hello, guys. Hello, guys. Hello. Hello. Everyone knows Blyat. Oh my God,
you guys, you're listening to me. I'm surprised. I'm learning. I would have taught us instead, though.
Literally. I can't even turn around to be like, oh, let me teach some Scots. She already fucking
knows it. She already got the cheeks. She already got the regional cheeks on. I went to Scotland
to steal your jobs and ended up with this. I know, literally. End up with this local card.
Literally stole your job. I can't believe it. I stole your fucking job. What are you going to do
about it? Absolutely none. I ain't got a choice. Yeah, well, at least that's one thing would be in
a slag. Who's Jap the Dastille, huh? How do you say tentacle in Russian? Literally, I don't fucking
know. Let's look it up, lads. Let's look up tentacle. It's not something I really had to use in Russian
if I'm being honest. And before, it's like some vialing. I went to be an East lag, but Sin took
my idea. Literally got stream sniped by Sin in 14. Someone says bubuk. Oh, shupaltse. That's
pretty cute. Shupaltse. Me playing. Give me a shupalse. We got scotch whiskey in vodka.
Someone says feliz navida.
Close.
Puskagurva.
Yo, I'm trying. Yo quiero aprender el espaol. Si, en este momento yo aprendo, aprendido el espaol
porque muchsimo, mi chat, si habla espaol.
I've no got a clue what she's on about. I'm just glad she's happy.
Get in my lobby. Imagine me saying I want a KMS and you're like, oh my god, I'm so glad she's
happy. No, no, no, no. I like when you go and things. I just have no clue what you're actually
going on about. Are you here? I'm inviting you in. Did you get that invite? Oh my god, I just,
I just panicked. No, no, no, no, no, no, no. The game mode isn't. Oh, I just invited you back.
No. Ignore me. Ignore me. Why does sin remind me of that girl from Alia? Something. Oh my god,
I love that. Oh my god, I love Alia. What's Alia? Yes, this new anime where like she, she's like,
speaks Russian when she wants to say something, you know, like, like she's like tsundere and when
she wants to be nice, she says it in Russian, but the guy actually doesn't understand what she's
saying. Oh, that's such a cute quote. Sorry, those are my favorite. She's like, I hate you. She's like,
That's what she says. She says dirty, dirty enjoyer of women's thighs. Oh, that's what she says.
I'm doing a series called Turn Me Into A Weeb where we're watching like anime for the first time.
I'm starting it up this month and I'm hoping it's a success because then I can be like,
actually, yes, I have watched that anime other than like the literally main stuff. I watched the
main stuff. So I can find the, yes, I watch anime because I only watched like super popular stuff,
which makes me a bad anime fan. There's this like new deer one out as well, which is really cute.
And it's like, she got, she got. Oh my god, it's so cute. The deer one. Oh, I've done it. I've
got the name of it though. A deer. But yeah, we're watching that. Yeah. It's like a deer and then
it's just so goofy. It's just the good kind of brain roll. Have you seen Happy Sugar Life?
No, that's the first one of mine. I'm watching anime that only have like one
like season. Oh my god. Did you see the Vtuber one though? It's too relevant. I've not seen it.
Oh, maybe we should watch that one. They have three deals in the anime. Yeah, she gets like,
it's about like Vtubers and she gets like, oh my god, wait, but that's literally what we did for
the Veeler girls. It creeps me out. It's like, oh my god, that's literally strong.
Literally what we did for the girls are like, if you don't have this equipment, we'll buy it for
you because it's imperative that you have a three deal basically. Literally, she got like,
she reached a sub goal or something. Wait, no, that's, that's so weird. And then she gets the
Japanese ear picks out for her ear. No, I need to watch that. That's amazing. So good. It's so
good. I'm like, oh my god. Oh, it's like, and it's just like playing like, what is that one?
Getting over it. Yeah, she like plays like, all the major Vtuber games is wet. No, we're so
watching that refling. Sorry. That sounds so good. I feel like I'm going to get like a weird like,
is that me? Is this anime about me for one? Never related harder to an anime in my life.
That wait, there's no pair for me.
And then how do you pronounce the gate? Stop. Stop. I was there. I was there.
They're like, so we're playing fortnight fortnight. We like fortnight. So then I'm like, oh,
that's Goku. And then they all start laughing at me. And then they type out his name and I'm like,
Vegeta. And then they're all like, oh, I'm like, oh, how else am I supposed to say it? That's how
I say it. Like, oh, oh my god. In the Vtuber anime, no, like the check looks like, like one of the
succubus checks literally looks like me. I'm like, what the fuck? I'm like, who knew all the succubus
looked the same? Wait, they actually got red and silver like you? Yeah. It's a fucking milk, mommy.
Stop. It's you. You're literally in game. Literally, we're all in it. We're literally in
and it was, it was obviously based on us. Clearly that popular and famous in the anime.
And I was like, there's no other explanation for that. All right, go. They're dogs.
They're dogs. Can I pet that dog? Stop playing on my banjo. I'm strumming on my banjo for you, baby.
Oh my god. Cowboy Vtuber that uses. Yeah, literally, no. Cowboy Vtuber that says I'm
strumming on my, like I hear how it be already. Strumming on my, oh yeah, I heard that as well.
Fuck me. It's gone. Oh, it's me. No, no, it's me. Oh, well, I can't hear it. Yeah, you can get real
first. I'm off to do it again. Oh, someone got worked. She got, she got. Right, I hope I can do a
genuine piece. Someone says, Heyson, how do you flirt in Russian with someone? What would you say?
What did you say? Was it bad? I want to be a good mummy for you. No, what the heck? They dropped
the other person that they were. Oh my god. I've just put myself in a corner like a twat.
Oh my god. I'm such a twat. Sorry. I'm actually like, I'm really low IQ. I'm so sorry.
What is this? Oh, what is that? I don't even know what kind of killer that is or what he does.
Is he slow? I mean, like, it's not hot though. Like to say pee-pee, it's
chlen. Like, that's why I'd never make videos. It sounds like you're saying chlen. Oh yeah,
I want your chlen. I want your chlen so bad. Like, no, that's what I'm saying. What was that?
Something just came out of me. Oh, what is this? What is this? What is this piece?
Words for pee-pee in Russian. Stronny's like getting chased and absolutely shagged. I seem to,
I appear to have been reached the killer. What the fuck is this? Oh my god.
He looks like something of Elton Ring. Sorry. Elton Ring. What the fuck? He literally,
that is literally Radan. It is.
Oh, he felt brave going between that and that. Oh my god.
You just got on a hook from Radan. What the fuck? Why do you not dodge?
He's coming for you. I don't fuck his after me next. I do not roll over. Exactly, that's what I
thought. Getting on at me for no being able to dodge. She fell over. She fell over.
Okay, there's the, wait, because you're a girl, it's he fell over. He fell over.
Summoning the replants. That's the only, he's the only one for you. He's still chasing me by
the way, everybody. I just thought you should all know that. Oh, be la famo for people. Well,
the other two are still doing gen. Bruv, I think they're giving up.
Oh, she fell over. Isn't that an awesome little chant? It's just like, he fell over.
He fell over. That's it. That's literally the chant. There's nothing else. I'm living the
employees now. God damn it. That's what it's like. Oh my god. We have two gen. Oh my god,
you're in the freaking basement. I know. I'm in the worst place possible. Oh my god. We're
getting absolutely decimated. We're actually getting decimated. Oh my god. He had a tal,
what'd you call it, talisman on for Elden Ring, because what the actual frick frack,
crick croc is for that. Yeah, honestly, absolutely annihilated. Do you wear crocs? I've done, I've
never worn. Do you have a pair of crocs? I have one pair of shoes. One pair of shoes? I don't go
out with saints and I don't need to go anyway. I have one pair of shoes. They're trainers.
Well, I went to Tescos today. Oh, I'm getting saved. Oh my god, did you get the meal deals?
Oh my god, tell me how good Greg's is. It's been so long. I had Greg's a few weeks ago
and I went to Tescos today, got myself some bread. That was it.
Bet your bell jail, that's my link. If it looks like, tell me more about Greg, sorry, but...
Right, what was your go-to, Greg? It was the cheese and hamburger and then the cheese
bean and sausage toasty. Are you dying? I'm coming to get you. I'm coming, okay?
I'm more of a pizza slice kind of girl. Did you get a pizza slice from Greg?
Wait, did you die, die? I'm on the hook fighting for my life.
Right, okay, sorry, I'm coming. I don't know how to get you. I'm nearly over.
No, no, I'm here. I'm here. Don't give up. I'm dying. I'm feeling, even though there's a heartbeat.
Oh, well, we're off shit creek. Oh, she said Milashka. Oh, hello. Goodbye. Oh, dear.
Oh, dear. What does this mean? I don't know. I'm slamming that shit down.
Oh, she said, but it's herself for me. How cute. Oh, she loves me. Oh, my God,
he broke the pallet. I'm out. I'm out. All right, all right, all right, all right, all right.
I've actually got no points. I've not had a chance to do anything. Oh, my God. I have that.
Oh, my God, he won shots here when he's raging. Oh, my God. I'm going to be dead on hook, so you
might want to find the fucking A. Oh, God, he's going to find me straight away. I'm literally
moaning my guts out. Oh, my God. I'm already dead. Oh, I'm run. I'm already tracer.
What about the next? Oh, my God. We should make a dead by daylight parody of that song.
What about Huntress? I'm already Huntress.
I should have been the Huntress, God damn it. Look at you are saying her tunes.
Hemorrhaging. The other girl's getting chased right now. Oh, fuck, she's alive.
I was like, for the hatch. Oh, no, she's alive. Oh, great. I'm so disappointed. Can I hide my
disappointment? Oh, no, can't find the hatch yet. Is there a chance for more clubs in the future?
What was then? Always. Unless she keeps telling everyone that I'm on my high moons and, yeah.
See, I'm a cheeky. Oh, my God. Actually, little hats like an Eastern European week,
and I like what she bought everything. Oh, my God. Oh, that's so nice. I used to eat this Polish food
from Teslas all the time. It was like a wee wafer thing. God, the lag is awful. Oh, the
shock collar. Yes, we both do have a shock collar. I was going to do a stream called,
Are You Smarter Than A Five Fifth Grader, but I think it can only be streamed from one POV,
so I don't know if you want that on your Twitch, then. No, everything's going on your hint. I'm
the streamer that never streams. The streamer that never streams, real. Oh, my God. You're a V
Twitter. You've been demoted to a V Twitter. I can't believe it. Oh, my God. The shocker part is,
I think I asked my Twitter just like a month ago. What? Oh, no. I barely even tweet. I don't do
anything. I'm shocking. I just sit in my Discord like, Hi, bye. Hi. I'm a V Discorder. That's me.
A V Discord streamer. That's so good. I know. I'm sorry. I don't want to stream. Like,
Stroney. Like, hello, Stroney streaming. Hello. Do you think I want to stream? No, I'm watching
Stroney. Like, fuck off. You pop up so much. I'm like, Oh, my God. I'm getting embarrassed. I'm
like, Oh, no. She actually sits and watching my stream. I'm always there. I'm always there. I'm
always watching, you know? Don't worry. I just took over this week. I didn't get to catch you
as much as I usually watch you, sweetie. Oh, my God. So funny. I love you. I used to call me a V
girl. I'm basically a Discord kitten. That's true. I just... Wait, wait. Look for Jen. Look for Jen.
Look for... Oh, he knows I'm here. Goodbye. Right. Look for Hatch. I'm running and you can see my footsteps.
And you can see your bow. You couldn't. Oh, my God. That couldn't have gone anywhere.
What? No, you got the nook here. It's BS. It's BS. Bro. I've got smelly armpits. Oh, my God. That's
absolutely scary. Sin forces us. Oh, my God. Your pheromone maxing. She's becoming more like me.
Oh, my God. The more I talk to Stroney, the more I just close out, you know?
Sorry, but that totally... That's thunder. It shouldn't have got me. Fuck off. Honestly.
Can we actually have a GG? I want one win before we go. I want us to hold hands as we
exit together. Oh, my God. Celebrate our new friend freedom. Let's you get to fuck all that game. Oh,
my God. Shit. Absolutely disgusting. We keep getting worried. I'm sorry. I've been
worried about 20 times. Kill all survivors who've reached the second to stage. Oh, I'm getting
stressed. Oh, my God. They had no head as well. So is we were not making it out alive. That killer
knows what they're doing. So is but that killer definitely knows what they're doing. Can we get
something to do? Okay, mommy went on Elton. That's your guy's job. That's your guy's job to do that.
When are you playing Elton Ring next? Come on. Me? Yeah. I'm finishing it off next month at the
start of next month. I'm doing like three back to back endurance rooms. So 12 hours of me yapping.
I'm actually pure put off. Those spider scorpions are absolutely... Oh, my God. I know what part
you're on about that bit before you stream sniped me in that location. That was a nice surprise.
And then there's this new place, this village with them. And I'm like... Oh, no. And I heard
there was a scorpion temple. And I'm like, I can't play this. I'm sorry. And then I'm like,
oh, I'm going to play Bloodborne. And I said, oh, there's spiders in it, by the way. Yeah, I mean,
there's a spider story in Skyrim. But I was on voice chat with you. Oh, right. Okay. I'm going
to tell it then. Sorry. You literally thought you had to call an ambulance. It was that bad.
I thought Sin got murdered unironically or like someone broke into her house or something.
So we were just in a discord. Nope. We're in a voice chat on Xbox. And she was playing
Skyrim for the first time. We were just, you know, having a talk. And we were just talking away,
blah, blah, blah. And then out of nowhere, the most blood curdling scream comes out of her.
Like, I kid you not, you could not recreate that voice actors and actresses of all time could not
recreate the scream that came out of her. I had no idea what was going on. I thought someone had
broken in. I was like, Sin, Sin, are you there? It was literally like a movie when they hear a big
screen. It literally fucking threw the headset down on the floor and that I'm like, Sin, Sin,
are you there? Are you okay? Is everything okay? And then she comes back like a couple,
maybe 10 minutes later, five minutes later type thing. And I'm like, what happened? Is everything
okay? Is everyone like, do you need police? Do you need ambulance? And she's like, oh,
the big spider came down from the ceiling. I'm like, the big spider came down from the
ceiling. And that's what produced that fucking magnificent scream. Like spiders in real life,
don't bother me. It's like when they turn into like nightmarish looking creatures in the Scotland,
like then that's when I get the book. When I can, I could hear those scorpions in the DLC,
like Scotland above me. And I'm like, no, I'm like, I'm actually all over. Get me the fuck off this
game immediately. And the worst of it is I tried to summon imps to go in and kill the
scorpions and it wouldn't let me summon anybody in. For some reason there's like a glitch.
Right, well, they better fix that before I hop on the game where I'll be swapping the game off.
You're going in and murdering them. I want to see you murder some fucking scorpions.
No, I'm not getting my hand held through games. I'm so sorry, but it brings me so much. Like,
I just feel so warm and gooey inside when the reflins come and now they like protect me.
And then they do all this stuff and they point out where items are that immensely. It feels so
all lovey-dovey and ooey gooey in my tummy. For you, it's all lovey-dovey and I'm spanking
and like, come on, kill them faster. Scarfing. Literally, I love it. And let you just feel like
you're an army though, like going head in to danger and it's like, are we all going to make it out?
I mean, you have to kiss like this is the last time. I get so sad when a reflande thing. Oh my
god, they've given us ruin or whatever the freaking... They let you the romantic kiss before you go
into battle. Oh my god, I literally clam slam them all into battle. I think it helps. Clam slam?
That's, so there's this move in Elden Ring where you jump up and slam on someone. So,
what? Is it the doctor? Yeah, it's the doctor and I just got jumpscared. Oh my god. So before
the pre-ritual battle when we go against a boss, I clipped it and I clam slam all the
reeflings to boost morale against the enemy boss. I feel so warm and gooey inside when a
reflande comes. Oh, did I say that in a sentence? Oh, well, yeah, quite literally, yeah. I didn't
realize that was my sentence. I'm sorry, I didn't think that. Yeah, yeah, some evidence of that chair.
I can hear her heartbeat, but he's... I keep hearing it, but I don't know if this is like
a fake heartbeat. It's not going away. No, it's not going away for me either,
but I'm doing a gen. I'm halfway done one. Yeah, I'm doing that. Me and Big Bell are doing a gen
right now. And then Mummy dies three seconds in the fight. Literally, I got given the crossbow,
which is like the best DLC weapon right now or something, if you level it up. And I kid you
not, I'm doing like 12 damage from across the map while like reeflings are doing like a thousand
again. Whoa, what was that? It does seem so much harder, though, but what doing four of them,
because like the boss has more HP and all that crap. I'm like, I love they can predict when the
boss is something they're going to switch the aggro one to. Yeah, that's quite difficult. What the f
are these? Is he trolling? I don't know. My gen has just been taken off. Is that a refland? I'm like
off my gen now because I fucked it by accident. All the gens I'm seeing right now are like shot
at me into two. Well, the heartbeat's really loud right now, but
guys, you said you gave me the whips. All right, excuse me. Excuse me.
What is going on with him? No, I'm not an ace. Oh, my God. Thank you for the five.
Thank you for the five. Unfortunately, I do nothing. I just want strunny.
Collab, definitely have no issues with it. Well, I was in our ears like I like that.
Yeah, no, 100%. I could see me doing an ASMR collab with sin. No problem.
I don't know if I told you on my debut, my goal is to collab with a hundred v-tubers with ASMR,
and I've already got like 18 right now. I just need to actually produce the damn audio. I think
is this guy being nice? Is it a refland? I don't know. Whatever it is, we're not doing anything.
Oh, like all the heroes. Or is it like a troll build that when you're like about finish,
it like blocks the gen off or something? I just got it. I just got the gen blocked off again.
Is it every time we do a gen? Wait, what? I don't know what's going on. Maybe it's when
you let go, it gets blocked. I've got no clue what's going on. Maybe it's just a nice killer.
He's stacking insanity. What what happens when insanity is max?
Well, we're getting closer to him. He's literally right there.
I can see his red light. I can't even see him at all. Make some noise. Wait, I need to snap out of it now.
Is he going to like one shot us and go eight shots? I don't know.
I'm getting nervous now. This is as he got annoyed and he's about to one shot us.
I think it may be annoyed. I don't I don't. I'm actually in here. He's just making heartbeat.
And it's still slower than my heartbeat. Actually, you should take the heart piece.
Bro, literally just take it from dead by daylight then.
I remember the first time I played dead by daylight and I heard the heartbeat and I closed
the game down because I got scared. I was like, I'll get scared. I just literally all F4 out the
game. Do you play horror games at all? No, I'm surprised you didn't play that into the deep
where it was called that. I'm not playing it yet. I'm not playing that yet. I'll play it soon to
I'll be so funny. Oh my god, it's seven. I hate scary stuff. Well, I have freaking played Halo.
Turns out it's actually a horror game. When the flood comes out, I was like, oh, if you're driving
or what? Oh, did you see that? Okay. She saw it, bro. The driving at the end was like, I was like,
there's just a random barrier right before the end. Halo on Legendary. Yeah, we should play
Lethal Company. We should. Well, there's this game called Dead Space, which is co-op. It's a horror
though, but I would totally play it with you if it's just both of us screaming with our heart rate
monitors on. Heart rate monitors. Oh fuck's sake, I had this stupid skill check. Sorry, there was
like a skill check and it was bouncing. Are we going to any gens left? Wait, what's going on? I'm
sorry, I'm stuffed with it. He's not playing. Like, surely not. I mean, at least we get our victory
together. I'm not complaining. At least we both get to go. I'm just like, I'm stepping in. Could
we just end this already? I'm going in. Some stream stip it. I did get for the win. Yeah,
they're like, bro, hurry up and wrap up the stream. They really won that ASMR stream right now. I need
to do it. I need to do a thousand kisses before I'm allowed to kill again. Oh, for something
I meant to cut down. A thousand. I'm forgetting steak. Stop giving me these skill checks. I'm not
smart enough for this. Sorry, I'm actually not. At least stop giving me them. Right, I'm about to
pop it. So if no ed happens, Rick, I don't know if no ed a thing or not, but if it happens, I
can't even find where the actual killer is. I don't know what's going on, but that totally
counts, right? That counts as a win, right? Yeah, we didn't ask for this. This is a win.
Always count. Now I can hear his heartbeat. I have no idea. Oh, no, he's just standing there.
Is that a reflin or an emplin? Oh, not an emplin for it. Yeah, emplin is together.
No, no, I was saying emplin, so I didn't have to say reflins and imps. Okay, that's smart.
I mean, I guess. I'll call them fucking imps. Emplins are cute though. I like them.
It's kind of cute. You just like add in wings and then
if you give me your cockling. Oh, okay, no. I've done it like if you're British,
you call it like a tealing and all that. I could just do like a ling-ling-ling, you know.
Oh, it's a new player. Oh, wait, no. What? Is that a reflin? Gigi, well played.
It didn't even attempt to do anything. I'm sorry if you wanted to farm. We thought you had no ed.
Oh, he's calling the perks on and... Yeah, like I was saying, it's not like a
thrill of the hunt. Blood points, so he just...
I'm so comfortable. I'm comfortable. Because I've been writing anything.
Three genuine readers are blocked for a minute and two minutes at the start of a trail.
That's actually pretty OP, not gonna lie. I'm gonna get strung a band.
What? A band? Oh, no! He typed something back, but I never saw it.
What is that? Wait, what? What's this? Because I'm...
BDAFK League... What? What does that mean? Because I'm translating?
I don't know. I can't see it. You can see it on your end, but I've accidentally typed one.
Yeah, the literature wrote like... He was farming points stacking.
Oh, he was farming points. But he only got 4k. He could've walloped us at the gate, to be honest.
And he probably got more points to actually try to get us.
And no, that wasn't true. I'm rather confusing.
An encrypted message while CSGO joined my CSGO site for some woman skins.
Oh my god, I remember wanting that was all the rage. That was the big YouTuber news,
where it was like, oh my god, all these CSGO have Gamba.
I'm late. No, don't worry. Right, I think we'll make this the last one and then I'm gonna prepare
for my ASMR stream. Oh, big stretch. Big stretch. I'm excited.
So basically, every time I do a membership stream, I never actually do ASMR when I've
called it ASMR. So my punishment is 1000 kisses. So I literally have like a kiss counter and
everything ready to go. So I'm gonna do 1000 kisses and then I'm allowed to talk.
Oh my god, I need to open my window. So very sorry, friends, hear me in the street. It's not me.
Oh my god, could you imagine they walk past and they're like, wait a second, I know that voice.
I can't hear that voice. As soon as they walk past and...
Oh, I'll give you a wee wave. I'll give you a wee wave.
The butter be flown from your lips. Now, hold on a minute. Now, hold on a minute.
Like, we don't enjoy the yap in 1000. I'm sure it was 10. No, apparently,
10,000 is like a 10 hour stream. So I think 10,000 will be like a massive milestone because
I can't imagine me kissing like that. Oh my god, we're gonna get carried so hard. What the fuck?
Yes. No, he's back down. You're so stupid. He saw the default and he was like, I'm gonna play him
with these noobies. Oh my god. Literally, he was like, where's his skin? You...
Look at the state of the state of dead by daylight right now. And it's just folk that
there doesn't seem to be a park. So I'm gonna just buy loads of random things in the park tree.
Edinburgh, are you going to... Are you going to the Edinburgh Fringe?
We're going to the Edinburgh Fringe Festival. Oh my. Edinburgh. Edinburgh, sweetie.
Real and true, Edinburgh. Glasgow. Glasgow. Yeah, anyone been to the Glasgow event?
The Edinburgh event? You need drip to play with me. Honestly, that's exactly what it felt like.
They literally were like, uh, right. No, we're not doing that. It's like all things.
Honestly, I don't play. Do you replay the lyrics? Wait, actually? Shut up. Actually. Oh my god.
Right. You need to carry us. You need to carry us on ironic glue.
Strangely, if you don't want to click each item in the web, you can click the last one
in the chain and it'll find all the ones before. What? Oh my god, these guys, we join.
They spin it up. No way. Right, no pressure on this one reflin, but the entire,
the entire stream is looking at you to get us to win. Okay? You're watching. They literally said,
okay, we're all dead right. It's over. It's over. You represent all the reflins right now. No pressure.
Yeah, you represent all the reflins. You have to let us both
synonize. Right, okay. By the way, just saying, just saying, not a lot, not a lot.
He's changed so guys. Oh, lovely. All right. He's on me already. I hear his heartbeat.
Please let me play. Please let me play the game. Oh my god. No way. You're down. I just cheered
us up as the reflins. Don't worry. The reflin's going to body block and get you off somehow with
all his power. Oh my god, it's a reflin that's going on the hook. Oh no. I thought he was, you know,
save the reflin. Oh, come on. I'm in trouble. I'm taking him away. Are you in trouble? I don't know
if I'm being... Okay, I'll get your little precious reflin. No, you need to save reflin. Oh my god.
Oh my god, he's coming for me, but not in a good way. I'll heal this. We have to get the reflin
selfie. I'm going back. Oh my god, leave me alone. You're scaring me. You're scaring me, killer.
Oh my god, stop. Mummy can only do so much and he's... Oh my god. Oh my god. The hook is right
there. Right, save your mummy. The reflin heals out. Like reflin, like mum, I'm literally straight on
the hook right after he gets off it. Oh, he's running. He's running for years. Oh my god, he's running.
What is that? Why does chainsaw guy look so different? They have skins now, like everything
has skins. Okay, I got picked up. I got picked. I'm getting healed. I'm getting healed. Oh my god,
group healed. I thought I was being smart, hiding behind the barrels. Anyone's true for you.
I didn't know you could like go through it. I'm like, that's kind of rude. Very fat and rude.
You open the gun, don't. It's fine. It's fine. I got this. I need to get the fuck out of here
because he's going to come speeding up. All the way straight back over. Is he coming to get you?
Okay, we have a gen done. He is away. What the fuck does that noise mean? What was that noise?
They need to stop with all these mysterious noises. I need a big text on screen that said
that noise alert was activated because of the, the, the, because all the hair goes.
I'm not getting healed. Oh, I'm getting healed by speed demon.
Dave by D-like. I just flipped on my ass and I put it up.
No, the, you know, I heard the fortnight song. It's like fortnight. Oh, here it was that you
bled out your ass after getting chased and they want. No, no, no, no, no, no. No, it was overdraft.
You gotta check it though. They have, can the killer be faster? They're already faster than us.
They make them more faster.
Bro, this game, honestly, don't be a shite. Like, this game is so mean.
You just don't want to see us have a fair and square dog.
Right. I'm doing the one in the middle. I'm going to try to get healed. Please. Can you heal?
Okay. Gens are more important than my heels. Oh, no, he sees me. Oh, oh, no, he doesn't. Oh,
he's after speed demon. Has he been on the hook yet? So unironically, that might actually be the
best thing. I think I might be the next target because I'm in your morning. I can see you richer.
Damn. There's a perk that calls him to speed up. Hillbilly can run even faster, but he can't turn
properly, meaning you can dodge. Come on, use your Elton Ring skills to dodge. I guess it's safe.
Right. Reflin's going to his rescue. I'm just doing the gen. Oh my god. Thank you. Thank you.
But I didn't know he could do that. I didn't know he could do that.
Oh, oh, oh, oh.
I'm just can't believe doing a jet. Oh my god. If you finish that gen, you guys might be able to get
out. Oh my god. My little heart is beating right now. Oh my god. Thank you. Crow the Egypt for
becoming a member. And Egypt means... Oh my god. I can't believe I did that. That scared me so
much. You've got to break the line of sight with Big Billy. Right. I'll remember. Don't be silly.
My uncle Billy had a ten-foot belly. In the next door, he snuck into the door.
I can't believe you remember that. I hardly remember it myself. Classic. Classic. Oh my god.
Better be open in the door. Don't be silly. I didn't like your... Actually, don't be silly.
And object your willy. Something you didn't like. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god.
Reflin is down. I repeat. Reflin is down. Oh no. Hen, you know what to do. I'm self-healing. I'm
self-healing. I'm using my med kit, and then I'm going to save Reflin. Reflin's down. Reflin's down.
I'm at only... Oh my god. Why is the heartbeat getting louder? Reflin, I might have fucked
up horrifically. No, no, no, I got you. Let me save you. Let me touch your armpits. I'm
going to tickle you tickle, tickle, tickle. Okay, I need to self weak. Can you hear me?
Maybe not. If you hear me, it'll be faster. Oh, I'm tickling. I have bought any knowledge.
So my healing is a bit faster than the average do. And then we'll do this Jen and then that'll
be one done and since we've got the other one, and then we'll get out and we'll all escape
and somehow stay alive again. I had to stop because speed demon got wrecked. I had to
run. Wait, is this done? Oh, Jen is done. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. Mummy's special needs.
Um, rellis. Oh, that's not good. That's not good. It's not good. No, it's not. And I'm
dead when I go on the hook next time. Ripped. I don't know. You know what? Should we just
I mean, when were the reflins getting chased right now? Actually, not to be. I don't know
if I should go for the save. I don't know. Right. You stay on that gym. You stay on
the gym. I'll go for the save. She says she approaches this fucking table. Oh my God.
Oh my, I think it's too late. Oh my God. It's too late. It's too late to roll. If I die,
this might work out. If I die because it means you can get the hatch out and then it means
refling and I are together forever. You guys are just wait. He's right at your heartbeat.
I don't know. Is it going for you? He shouldn't you? He's. Oh my God. Refling sacrificed himself
for us. No, he's away. Oh my God. He's away in the sky now. Make sure it's not in vain
now. Hey, no pressure. No pressure. No pressure. I got Jen down. He's probably gonna go for
me. You got this one done. Right. Good. I don't know where the other one is. I'm running
from my fucking line. I'm scared. Yeah, he's actually coming. There's chainsaw. Oh my
God. Hide behind a rock. I'm hiding behind a rock right now. I hope he doesn't bite me.
Okay, I'm just starting a random generator. Although, speed demon's on it. Wait, is he
still alive? I saved him. I'm dead on hooks. Don't worry. I'm gonna die when I go on
hook. I'm gonna go join my refling in the ether. Okay, so we can be together. Whatever.
And then I'll spectate you. Is he dead? Is he away in a manger? Away in a manger. What
fucking soul is away in a manger? You're literally, it's you and the other guy's getting chased
right now. Oh wait, he's alive? Okay. I don't know if it's me. I just wasted my speed version.
You're screwed. All right, are you supposed to stay again then? Oh my God, wait, what?
He's doing the gen. Speed demon's a five head? Wait, so he's coming over to you now, but
speed demon's about to finish a gen. I'm not even kidding. You might be able to do the
gate. I'm not gonna do the gen then. No, look. Oh my God. And you get healed up because of
adrenaline. You five head. Is he heading? Or is he heading for me? He's going back to the,
I don't know. Oh no, I hear him. I hear him. Oh no. Yeah, right. Okay. Oh my God. Is he
purple? Oh no. Yeah, he's pink for you as well. Okay, that's fine. Speed demon's physical.
Don't vomit. It's okay. We need to root this in. Okay, so Dwight is currently opening
the den. One door. One door is currently being a little bit open. You might want to make
a move to find a gate. You can run. He's down here, but I know he's down here. Oh no, he's
in trouble. Oh my God, he's doing jukes. Call him Daisy because he's doing jukes right now.
I know that's not how to work. Wait, wait, he's sprinted away. Careful. No, no, no, no,
no. Pause. Hide. Don't. Shit. I don't know if he saw your track marks. I don't know if
you can see your track marks. Oh no, he's going back. He's going back. No, no, no. Open now.
He's going for Dwight. He's going for Dwight. Open now. I'm really nervous. No. Oh my God,
he's coming back. He's coming back. Hide hide hide hide hide. Oh no, no, he's not, he's not,
he's not. He's picking up the Dwight. He's picking up the Dwight. Wait, he's moved.
I can't see him. I don't know if he's coming back. I can't see him. I think he's coming
for you. I think he's coming. You need to move. I don't know. I need your yo... Oh my
God, you're YOLO-ing. Oh my God, you're YOLO-ing. Stop. I think you may do it. I think you
Oh my god, that's perfect. Oh my god, that was too close. My cheeks are clenched. Oh my god. I need to relax. Oh my god, that was too close.
Oh my god, we did it. What are we to end it? Sin made it. We did it. Did we win? We got the dub because Sin managed to get out. We got the dub. That's all we wanted. That was scary. That was terrifying.
Right. Do you want to plug yourself to The Reefland?
As what? What? No, plug it.
I don't stream. What's happening to show? I'm going to finish up for myself. I'll put you on the stream.
I'll catch you on Stony's chat next stream when I'm watching.
So, that's so true though.
Are you playing tomorrow? You collab with Ace, isn't it?
Yes, we do.
Ace collab week for me. I'm being so social this week. I'm not normally social.
I'll plug myself and see you tomorrow.
Alright, there you go.
Alright, there you go. There you go.
Thank you for surviving with me, even though the whole point of the stream was to play the 4v8.
Declenched, yes.
Declenched my cheeks.
Look how jiggly you are compared to me, bruv.
Jiggly? No, let's see. No.
Let's enhance.
And the fucking jiggle physics on that is way over.
How much did you pay? Am I allowed to insider knowledge? How much was the toggle?
I literally don't even remember. It was like...
Well, I wasn't the cheapest in the world, I guess.
Yeah, yeah. I mean, I can't even remember.
You got three infants or two?
Where's the toggle?
Oh, the toggle. Ah, there it is. I knew it. I freaking knew it.
I fucking knew it.
I knew she had another toggle.
I knew it. Yeah, there it is. That's what I remember.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Okay, let's wait a few overlands.
I'm de-jating right now. Oh my God, the buttons again.
Oh, oh, oh.
Oh my God, that's a good one. Oh my God, you got your tummy pierced? I didn't know.
Oh my god, actual tummy piercing.
That's so cute!
You can let my belly flint.
And you're we- oh, oh.
And your ears are pierced as well.
What can I say, my rebel? I'm an absolute rebel.
Can I just appreciate her model? It's just so good. I love it.
I love the hair toggles as well.
She can make her hair longer, shorter, and do the bunches and that.
Oh my god, did someone say symmetrical bunches? 10 out of 10 designs.
Those are actual 10 out of 10 designs.
I know, imagine having bunches, imagine.
Imagine, imagine having double bunches.
Imagine having like a bunch of bunches.
Imagine having to be fringe, bangs, bangs.
I have three singular bangs, I feel like I'm on design.
Oh, you have it as well though, you have three bangs as well, technically.
Because of the way you look.
Mine's also symmetrical though.
I hope you all enjoyed this stream.
Are you going to say a little collab?
Yes.
Did you enjoy it everyone?
And plings?
And plings, don't be surprised if we see Sin coming back on at all.
Please don't be surprised because I think we're going to do,
we're going to try and win at Who's Smart,
Who's Smart is in a fifth grader and we'll both have shot colors on.
So that would be fun.
And that would be a good thing.
Don't say I'm ridiculous, my milkers look though in this.
Wait, show us.
Oh my god, Sin.
You pick your salad.
Oh my god.
Wait, every time you go down and bring them up.
Bruh.
They get bigger.
They get even bigger when they go down and up.
Oh my god, that's ridiculous.
That is amazing.
Oh my god.
Split my chin open.
Bruh, how are they not smacking you in the face
and smacking down your knees and one face?
I know.
I was like, ah, something in my face.
Definitely because we can get it.
I can't imagine how you can be easy.
Remember to tune in to Strone's ASMR.
Member Streams.
I'm going to, yeah, I thought you said 10,000.
I was like, nope, I'm going to die of the 10,000.
Right, we little reeflings or implings,
we are going to say thank you so, so much for
Sin sister for showing up.
She does stream on Twitch when she does stream on Twitch.
You know what I'm saying?
So you can't fall into it once a year.
Okay.
But she does actually stream when she streams.
Which is a sentence, yeah, so it's technically not wrong.
She does have a Twitter, but she didn't use it either.
So if you want Sin updates, feel free to like and subscribe to me
when she pops into chat and blocks with her boob.
Literally, she almost like,
muted someone with her boob yesterday or something.
In the middle of the stream.
No, that was in the middle of the stream.
Yeah, my phone fell on my neck,
and then somebody's name was,
I was like, oh my god, I just banned something.
I'm actually, no.
Getting banned by a boob.
That only happens at Veiler,
so don't be afraid to like and subscribe.
Bye, everyone.
Okay, bye-bye.
Thank you so much for coming.
Bye, guys.
I'm going to end broadcast.
Oh wait, no, I'm going to redirect.
Is someone live right now?
Is there another Veiler member live?
If not, then user going nowhere.
Right, there's not another Veiler.
Sheepsters, come on.
Sheeby, Cotton, Boo.
Thanks for your welcome in the chat, everyone.
Thank you, everyone, to let me start
in your mummy stream today.
Oh, no, I don't.
Feature, featured, directed by Sun Sister.
Oh, she's not talking about me.
I should probably go now.
Okay.
Right, bye, Sun.
Thank you so much.
I'll message you after.
Bye.
Bye-bye.
Oh, no, she's going to be,
she's probably going to be in the Veature video thing.
You're going to be able to see her move around after this.
She's ended the call.
Oh, she's sticking her tongue out.
Oh, she's, all right.
Okay.
Yeah, she's moving about.
She's still hearing us.
Skyrim Co-op when?
Is there a Skyrim mod for Co-op?
Is Emi coming on later?
Emi Vee-joo.
I love typing in everyone's name,
so it's just a satisfying being a guy.
Just give me one more chance.
Oh, she's in ASMR.
She don't want ASMR in her new outfit.
She looks so cute in that outfit, seriously.
I can't take it.
She's so cute.
Right.
I'm going to redirect into Emi's stream,
which is two hours away.
In the stronghold, it's two hours away.
I know.
I'm aware.
But you're having to tolerate it.
Okay.
Because, ah, she's still dancing and gyrating
in the corner of my eye.
I'm trying to set-
Great collab love to see you both together.
Yeah.
Thank you so much.
Thank you, Tiny Spiny, anonymous,
bleeding, refilling Senpai, not Alessandro
and L Jeff for all the love shown.
I'm so sorry if I kind of patched it a wee bit.
Just, I'll try.
Try.
Okay.
But thank you.
Yes.
Definitely don't be surprised if Sen shows up on my channel
again because she's doing her thing.
Oh, she's done it.
Right.
We're going to redirect into Emi's thing.
For those of you who are a member,
I am going to take a five minute break to go for a pee
and make a cup of tea.
And then I am not allowed to talk until I've done
1,000 kisses.
Okay.
So there is a membership ASMR about to come up.
I will behave.
It would be sensational.
It would be.
Oh my God.
She has so many good toggles.
I didn't appreciate how good her model is until she's
like toe and toe right next to me.
No yapping.
Yeah.
See you in a bit.
So give me five minutes.
As I said, and then we'll get to it.
Oh, relax.
I'm listening.
Thank you for the game.
Bro, we both died.
Don't.
We both perished.
Okay.
Thank you so much.
Reluctantly same for the tip as well.
I can't believe you managed to stream snipe.
And honestly, I can't believe any reflin managed to get in
the game because I think it was picking Aussie servers.
She even has tonsils.
Does she open your mouth soon?
I don't have tonsils.
Open your mouth.
Wait.
Hold on.
Let me analyze.
I'm going to be her dentist for a second.
Oh my God.
What the heck?
She has tonsils.
That's amazing.
Oh my God.
She has hypnotized type.
It's like, God, look at the detail in her iris as well.
That's it.
Oh my God.
We both have fangs.
I look like the sinister sister in the background where you're dating her and I'm the big sister
that's going to make it hell because you're dating her.
That's fine.
I like you.
Oh my God.
Sorry.
Can we all appreciate her model?
I'm coming closer behind her.
She literally has a uvula.
How detailed is that?
Oh no.
I know what I want next.
Right.
I'm going to get going.
Thank you so, so much, Sin.
And thank you for the reflin and the impling.
Oh, imps and implings that showed up.
It's very cute when you two come together.
Okay.
I'm sure that collarbone is physics as well.
Fuck's sake.
She has such a detailed model.
God damn.
Let me ask her how much you paid for that.
Neurons activated.
Get ready for a whole lot of not talking.
Exactly.
Why is Johnny on Sin's stream real?
I probably reignited her flame for one to stream a wee bit more because she's so nice.
She's like, oh my God, when I watch you stream, I want to stream.
And I'm like, yeah, yeah, I inspire you.
Like I'm whispering in her ear, you want to stream so bad.
You want to stream so bad.
We're fucking talking.
Okay.
I will see you very shortly.
We're feeling in membership stream for those of you.
You can redirect it into Emmy.
And she comes up in two hours.
Yes.
I'm making you wait two hours.
Bye.
I'll see you very shortly.
Bye-bye.
I'll be two minutes to set up.
Okay.
Because I need to swap around the microphones and stuff.
Bye.
See you later.