I got the echo effect on, be honest right now. I like to sound like I got the echo effect on.
Oh my god, oh that was supposed to be a censor.
All right hold on, I'll down, I'll down, I'll down. I need to get my live chat.
Oh I haven't even got freaking stream elements up in case someone do knows. Hold on, start
that. I'm sorry, I apologize to anyone who does not like real body parts or immersion
bros as you all know. Oh I can hear myself. Oh get that, close that stream right now.
Hold on, hold on, let me cook, let me cook, let me cook. I'll get you up to date, I just need to.
I'm so upset, I'm not. Just to see, just so you know, I couldn't get to your freaking thing to work
so I had to draw it on a piece of paper. So it's literally on a piece of paper. This says,
oh my god, I get it now. And then this one says, I got lotion on my tinnacle, I got lotion on my,
mm-hmm. And then this one is just neutral B tier, it's a guy going, I mean, it's all right.
And then this one is, it's the biggest piece of ever. And then this one says cast it into
Mount Doom. And this freaking webcam doesn't, oh focus, what I told it to. So yeah, it's been,
it's been a bit of a nightmare to get here but Ken, what we're here now. So let me, let me just
check. Okay, I can officially see tips. So if you would like to tip, I will see it. And I can
actually read it out. Oh my freaking mouth, there's an calibrated hold on, let me, let me enolize.
Okay, much better calibration. Okay, the Gura sensor, true. It's big fish, look,
so I got Gura. And then, and then look who I got, look who I got, you ready for this?
Who's this? It's Pyro Pops. It's Cinder's plushie of Pyro Pops. And look, it, you came in a little
color. Look, look at that little adorable little Pyro Pops. And look, it's even got the hurt ears
and everything in the design. And then this one, are you ready? Let me reach, big reach,
big heel reach. Look, it's strawberry, darling straw. You know, darling straw, this is her mascot.
Got a little bowl, and got a little butt. Sorry, a bunch of the webcam's rubbish,
but it's probably, oh, it's glitching. But yeah, look, I got Pyro Pops and a straw,
plushie, and I got Gura, and I got a few other things on the way, but they're not here yet,
it's totally not over market. Check out the link in the description for the merch down below.
Your nails are so shiny, right? Right, right, before we get into the actual taste testing,
do you know how they freaking destroyed my toe? So if you didn't know, when you get a manicure
and a pedicure, you have to get cut around here. They like cut all your skin away here, right?
They cut into me, and this one doesn't have like all this on it. So I just, yeah, I got manicure
and a pedicure. I'm not beating the sweaty feet allegations because I don't know if you can hear
this, but yeah, like the paper's lifting with my feet. But yeah, I got manicure and a pedicure
for the monetization stream. However, it's not going to stop me. I mean, look at,
I'm a real girl now, huh? I'm so feminine. I'm so feminine. You're going to be eating
with your feet on the table. You sure you want to stick your feet on it? What are you talking about?
Okay, let's, let's get into the first thing. We are going to be trying there.
Okay. So basically, I have to manually freaking draw what tear I'm putting I am in as well. Like,
it's just, it is what it is. So we're going to try a little Nerdy's. Anyone else? I don't find
it nerd. It says pill tab here. I'm pulling and I'm ripping the box apart. It's not looking good.
It says one and two on the side. Oh no, it's a logic puzzle we're feeling. It literally says,
where's the webcam? Oh, focus on this is terrible. It says, okay, we can't even, it's a puzzle.
Okay, there we go. We're in. We're in. Yep, this is how you're supposed to do it. Oh,
there's two different colors. Oops. Wait, what's, okay, hold on. Let's just take
our part. You know, oh my God. Okay, okay. Okay, there's two little sections. We have two
clores. Choose your clore, any clore. Okay, we're gonna, we're gonna have pink.
Oh, oh, that's sweet. It's purple, the same flavor.
Oh, that's so sweet. It's almost sour. Oh, is this supposed to be sour?
Grape and strawberry. Okay. Um, oh, uh, grape is not for me at all. I will allow, I will allow,
um, uh, I'm gonna put it in a, I mean, it's all right. Hold on, we're like manually,
I don't know. Now everyone knows I can't draw straight balls. Okay, what do nerds look like?
I mean, it's all right. And then the packaging is pink and purple, but I don't have a pink and
purple pencil. Yeah, the grape flavor is very diverse. Yeah, strawberry is my preferred over
grape. Yeah, I'm definitely strawberry gang, straw, straw. Draw the little guys. Oh, they have like
a schnozer. Okay, hold on. And then they're butt and then their feet. And then their eyeballs.
And then their little happy face. What do we think? What do we think of my nerds?
That wasn't too bad. I love it. Oh, you want to see, you want to see the, oh, right. Okay, hold on.
There's like so much I wanted to show in this stream, like so, so much. I was originally gonna wear
this outfit for you guys, but then I was like, oh, I can't because YouTube is reviewing my channel.
But I got, so if you didn't know, the white on my outfit is pearlescent, like it's rainbow-esque.
Okay, it's pearlescent. So I got that. And then this is like, this is what the white on my costume
is. It's pearlescent. I don't even see it that well. I don't wear it. Be careful, American
sweets are super sugary. I'm not gonna eat like, eat, eat everything. But you know what I'm gonna
wash it down with? A fucking can of, oh no. Little, little ASMR moment. This is what,
I'm sorry if you don't like hand sticks. I'm afraid I have hand sticks.
With all my might as I shake car battery juice, the national drink of Scotland, Scotland is the
only country in the whole wide world, the whole wide world that has number one sales, not cola.
So cheers, come pie.
Insert bagpipe noises here. That's so good. I've not had that in ages. Right, let me put it down.
The reason why we're sipping into the iron brewers, I put it on the table over there because I'm
gonna knock it off. We have two drinks to try from America. Oh, if you have a can on your desk,
that's 355 milliliters, also known as 12 fluid ounces. This is what my hand looks like holding it.
My fingies don't even get like up there. I'm getting a lot of condensation though.
We're gonna try cream, soda, A and W as the condensation. Okay, ready. We're gonna try the
drinks first. Oh my, oh such a girl. This is not hand sweat before anyone starts making fun.
Okay, you guys, come pie.
Yes, that is a drink. Okay.
It's not, I mean, it's not right. It's not that, it's actually not that bad. I wouldn't reach for it.
Oh, I missed tips. I'm so sorry. I'm such a bad streamer. Thank you, tiny spiny for the tip,
just as a promise. I have some iron brew with me and I just had some. No idea how to describe
the taste, but it tastes better than it smells. Might have to get more of this going forward.
Yay, thank you for the tip. Zion, thank you for the tip. When you have to be a good Christian
man on Sunday but cuddles the stream and you do what you have to do and chin in with some one
earbud while Mass is going, when can the reeflings taste the Scottish sweets? Honestly, thank you
for the tip. I can't believe you're in church right now. Take me to church right now. I'm putting
all the drinks up on this little shelf because there's a 100% chance I'm going to knock over.
Honestly, that wasn't that bad but I wouldn't go out my way to have it. I feel like everything's
going to end up being neutral. Right, what was that? That was A and W and it's like on its side
like this. A and W, like that. And then it's got like a little logo. It's like two circles.
I mean, it's alright. Okay, now we're trying American Dr Pepper. 150 calories per serving.
So not for the full can. Oh no, the serving size is a can. Some things do that where the
serving size is a lie. It's a false profit. Okay. Get the aroma, that's right. Get the aroma in
your palate. Yes, yes, have it. Okay. Uh-huh. Oh, oh, it's going to be, you guys drink that stuff?
What is that flavor? I don't even know what the flavor is. There's something wrong with it anyway.
Oh, I should see my head bobbing up and down. Oh, that's my head there. See that? That's that's
the headset, Mike, but I'm going to talk to you through that, Mike. That's moody.
Dr Pepper Gaming, 23 flavors. Is that why there's 20? Oh my goodness. Right. I'm sorry to my Dr
Pepper fans. It's not cast it into the fires of Mint Doom. I'm more or I guess it's technically
correct. What does the front look like? A Dr Pepper. And then what's got 23 flavors? Oh my
god, 23. She's not the one she's talked to Pepper. Yeah, that, my brain was like nothing.
Right. Y'all want a kiss? Oh, sugar. I never thought this far ahead.
Oh god, I never thought this far ahead. No, the packaging. I'm getting trolled. The
fucking thing came open. It's not open. I'm getting trolled. Hold on. I never brought a knife. I never
thought to broaden what? No, your troll. Oh, there we go. Oh my god. These are like those kisses.
I remember there were so many memes online that are like, oh, you should, you should what?
It was like, oh, ask your crush if she wants a kiss. And if she says no and rejects you,
just pull out a Hershey's kiss from your pocket. And then all the comments were like, oh, what?
Is this a, is there a joke on the back? No, there's not. Okay, there's not a joke on the back.
It's not fortune cookie. Okay, gobble, gobble. Oh, it's hard. Wait, is it hard? Oh no, I had it
in the fridge. That's why it's hard. Why is it? I do have a napkin to remove food from my mouth
that I no longer wish to have in my mouth. So I do apologize if people don't like that.
It melts in your mouth. The cocoa percentage is a bit better.
I think I can swallow it. Oh, that's better. Oh, I'm fine. I'm chewing through it.
It stuck to my teeth. Okay, okay. Oh, I would not have a second one. I'm so sorry. I wouldn't.
All right, we'll see how it ambidextrous. All right, let me just draw in the second box. Hold on.
Easy, easy, easy.
By the way, I got manicure and pedicure. Did you see?
Oh, I also know the Vietnamese strats. So Boss Lady was the one,
there was two ladies working on me at once. What was that? A kisses. So there was two ladies working
on me at once and it turns out it was the boss and she was telling me about her visa and she was
like, oh, I had two children so they can't kick me out and I was like, you're smart. And she was
like, yeah, if they want to kick me out, they have to take me to family court. And I was like,
she's telling me the Vietnamese strats. I'm like, you're an actual five head for that. So we're
having to be giggle about that. So I definitely recommend what they call, I think they're called
chop shop nail bars when it's just like a bunch of girls and all that. So there was two women working
on me and the women that was kindly working on my feet, she didn't speak any English, which is fine.
So we never spoke or anything, but I spoke a little bit to the owner because she was doing
the manicure. And basically, so I paid and then I went away and I got some cash out so I could
give them a tip. And I gave the one that didn't speak English a tip and she was like, thank you,
thank you. And I'm like, yeah, you worked hard. I couldn't really use a lot of words because I
knew she didn't understand what they meant. But she was so lovely. Honestly, they worked so hard
in these like nail bars. And then I gave the owner a tip as well. And because I was like, just thank
you for being so nice because I walked in and I was like, I need French tip manicure, pedicure. I
had don't know what it is because she was like, do you want gel? Do you want this? And I'm like,
I don't know what any of this means. And she was like, it's okay, I look after you and her amazing
accent. And it was amazing. So I had a very good time. It was really relaxing. They started
like massaging my feet. And I was trying so hard. Right, right. This is the truth. Okay. So they
massaged this bottom part of the feet. All right. But with someone touches the bottom of my feet,
my feet go, I start to spread my toes. So I was like, no, stop, stop. She's trying to work on my
feet. But my toes were like, so I was like trying to sell my body. I was trying to tell my body,
stop moving. This poor woman is trying to like massage my feet and give me a relaxed experience.
And all my toes want to do is go, like, no, just relax. But anyway, it was a really good
experience. It was really relaxing. The chair started vibrating. I started sweating as well in
the chair. It was like vibrating me up and down. I was like, oh, right. This is all I hear about
from you Americans watching right now. I don't know what summer patch kids is, but all I hear
about it is how good they are. It says sour, then sweet. If it's a gummy, like chewy, I love chewy
sweets. So this is actually going to go quite down well. They look adorable. These are cute ones.
I like the look of these. So they're chewy. This will hurt your teeth. It is gummy. They're okay.
Ready? Bottoms up.
Okay, we had a good start, but...
Y'all eat this shit. Where did the flavor go? One earth? Wait, there was so much flavor
at the start and it's all gone. It tastes like nothing. It just like gels them.
Where's your flavor? Oh, it's so plain. I don't think I want to swallow this. Hold on a minute.
What the heck is even in here? Sugar, sugar, corn syrup, modified corn starch, contains less than
two percent citric acid. What the heck is the flavor in? Artificial flavors, titanium,
dioxide for color. There's literally nothing in it. What on earth? Wait, I'm not swallowing that.
Sorry, I don't trust it. I don't trust it. It's too suspicious. It's too suspicious. I'm sorry.
That tasted flavor. I'm sorry to anyone who like silver patch watermelon. You're done.
Your taste buds are cooked beyond belief. Nothing happened. You get the burst of sugar at the start
and then nothing happened. So I do apologize to silver patch kids. Right, we're just going to
draw this little mask out here. So he's got his little head and then he's got his wee arm out to
the side and he's holding the watermelon and he does this and he goes down and does this and
this and then he does that and then he goes like this and then he and then back to the head
and again the ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh. And then he doesn't really have features. There we go.
Silver patch kids, I'm so sorry but nothing happened when I bit into that which is
rather strange. It's odd. Sweet taste, the carcinogenic that a bloody old knot. Oh speaking
of carcinogenics, neon blue. I got access to neon blue peeps. Now I'll tell you this.
What's her face? Trisha Payes is an influencer and she ate these on camera and made them look
like the most delicious thing ever. Wait, why are you saying no to peeps? Are they bad? But they're
gleaming and green and fat free. Fat free just means it's all in the sugar. They're like neon
blue. I don't know how to explain to you how neon blue these are but these are neon. They're horrible.
Oh no. They look so adorable. I'm eating sheepsters right now. Oh, well come with me. Am I gonna,
all right, vote someone if I'm gonna spit this out or not. From your guys's reactions I'm getting
nervous. But look how cute he is. He's very sticky. Oh my. I'm scared.
I think I'm gonna gag. Am I gonna gag? I'm so sorry. I'm actually quite scared of it. I'm scared
of the bunny. I'm so sorry. I think I didn't spit that out. I apologize. Okay, I got taste. I actually
don't think it's that bad but I'm genuinely scared of it. I'm scared of this. Chewing on foam kind
of quality. Yeah. Does it taste awful as everyone? It doesn't taste bad but I'm scared to swallow it
but I never tasted anything that was bad. I'm just scared. Yeah, it didn't taste bad so it's
going in. I wouldn't eat it of my own violation again. Volition, violation. So it's going into the,
it's not, it didn't make it here. What does it, what does the box look like? Where's the box? Oh,
peeps doesn't really have much of an icon. It's just kind of peeps. Volition, vial, of my own
violin. I would not eat this again. Peeps. And then it's just got a circle. Oh, again,
I messed it up and an underling. Ta-da! Oh yeah, it's all coming together. Oh, pardon me, I'm burping
out. Oh, I never even thought that I could throw up this stream but it's now just occurred to me
the likelihood of me throwing up is actually very high. Can I get a TWS check if throwing up on
streamers allowed? Yes or no? Right, going on the back, sweeps, shriek-p-d-p-p-d's. I've got Twinkie!
And there's literally a zombie movie that's all about the dang twangie. So please, we'll
live up to the hype of the twinkie. Yeah, please. I mean, zombie land. Oh yeah. Okay, we're doing a
twangie. Oh, it's all coming apart. Uh, itadakimasu!
Okay, a sponge cake. We can manage that. What about the filling?
I've stuck my tongue in the filling, as you can see by the evidence of the in-groove.
Okay, I'm tasting it. It is going in the it's all right tier. Okay, it's going in the it's all
right tier. That's not bad. I wouldn't say that was bad. Twinkie is just sponge cake and cream.
It's going in the, well, anything. I actually don't know what the brand of Twinkie looks like.
And this just says hostess on it. We will create one, and then it stands for
two. There we go. New logo for Twinkie right there. And then we'll put it in.
We'll just do like the actual size. There we go. Twinkie. That's the new logo for Twinkie.
It'll be interesting to see how your hands keep on ticking. I've got Twizzlers, which is
Eric Cartman is my only exposure to Twizzlers. I'm pretty sure he was munching them in one of the
plots. Also, I got rinsed for all of this food. It cost me 53 zollas. Oh my god, they're sticky.
Wait, they're not? Oh, there is an artificial scent that has just came from this. Oh my god,
it's not come from fucking hell. I actually haven't used my strength, you know? Okay, hold on.
Oh my god, it's so sticky. Like, oh.
What is this? They're decent. It's very artificial scent has entered the room.
What is it? It's artificial cherry flavour?
Why does everything say a low fat snack that makes sugar turns into fat? Why is everything
marketed like that? It's so dumb. Oh, I'm tasting it. I'm tasting it. In my mouth,
those two little samples that were on my finger.
It's like edible scentless candle. These are sea bomb sticks. They're health candy because
everything in America is high fat. Big sugar. Americans believe fat is bad, but sugar is what
makes fat. Fat isn't bad for you. It depends on what kind of animal fat is good for you. For
example. Oh, everything is good for you in moderation. I'm still tasting that.
I don't think I would eat this of my own violin. Violin again. Okay, I'll say that. Do you guys
want that? I don't think I could finish it. Do you guys want to take over here and
you finish it for me? Yeah? Okay, there you go. All yours go. Yeah, the focus does not work on
this webcam very well. It's all yours. You can have it. I would... Oh, it's back again. I thought
I wiped it on the napkin. It's already back. Oh, you spat it out too? My pretty little baby bird.
I would not put that in my mouth again. No, I don't apologize to any Twizzler fans.
And then it says pool. Oh, I just noticed that pool and peel. Anyone else pooling right now?
Because I'll be peeling something back later. This joke doesn't work because I'm doing an American
stream and you guys get something stolen from you at birth, but let's not get into that.
How about some Jolly Ranchers?
Any Jolly Ranchers?
Oh, jeez, you need the freaking strength to open anything. My god, do you guys
even get into these? Right, what clore? Choose your clore. Any clore? What are the clores? Right,
we've got a red, we've got a yellow, we've got an orangue. Orangue. We've got green.
So any other colors or clore colors?
Okay, I think there's four colors. We've got lime green, hard candy mango,
and golden pineapple and fruit punch. No way, there's no blue. Wait, I've got Jolly Ranchers
tropical. Is that the wrong one? Did I mess up? Wait, hold on, hold on. No, there's definitely no
blue in here. Unless my elf eyes deceive me. And the wise words of Orlando blue himself.
Don't bite them. Suck them. Oh yeah, you want me to suck on the sweet? Right, well I do a pool.
Hold on, let me, you guys can vote what flavor I try. Let me, for those of you participating at home,
please feel free to use the starter poll. What's this called? Jolly Rancher? I've spelled that
wrong, but that's fine. We've got fruit punch and it's red. We've got mango, which is orangue.
We've got yellow, which is pineapple yellow. Or last but certainly not least green, green
lime. For those of you playing at home, folks, feel free to go into the comment section where you
will see a poll pop up on your screen. That's right, you, the viewer, can decide if what the streamer
eats. Let's see. Oh, fruit punch red. Okay, okay. Je comprende. I just realized it's using my old
freaking description sense or red gang raise up. Okay, so someone says don't bait it, just suckle on
it. Is it suckling ASMR? I'll suckle on something in a minute. That is so red. Holy crap. That's like
red of a pencil and that's the sweet red. I'm getting nervous. I'm getting shaky.
Oh, very strong, very strong flavor, but let it cook, let it marinate, give it a chance.
Yes. That is very strong. That is very strong flavor. I'm not even going to
be getting otherwise. What the fuck? That's so fun.
Is it sour? It's just overwhelming. I think my British, my British beans, I just want bread
and butter and cheese and ham.
How fried is America's taste buds? Are your taste buds fried at all? That is so strong.
They're all fried. Yeah, I like savory flavors. This is probably the worst for me.
American taste buds are 99% sweet. Okay. The British can't, yeah, the British palate
definitely can't. I can't. This is very, this is too much. I can't eat this.
Mm-hmm. I feel like an old lady sucking on a hard boiled sweet. Oh, you just,
you just be a good wee grandson. I'm bracing myself on my chair. I'm not even going to
pretend otherwise. My other hand is on my chair and I'm bracing myself for these sweets.
Well, if anyone else wants to take over, you're more than welcome to. I have had adequate tasting
and the aroma of the sweet has came through. So if anyone would like to take over, go.
All yours, baby. All yours because I like my fingers so they're not sticky.
Have a little, have a little napkin for dabbing my fingies. Meals and calls.
Right. That was overwhelming and I wouldn't put it back in my mouth again. I'm sorry. A lot of
things. I wouldn't say cast it into the fire. That's not like rejection, but I just wouldn't.
What's the logo of jolly ranchers? It's just a big J-O-L-L-Y-O and then a Ruh and then a Ruh
and then a N and then a C-H-E-R. It's so hard to like jump between the two. And then it says hard
candy. Okay, that's close enough. Our list so far. Do you think anything can even become
A-T here at this rate? I'm getting nervous. I don't, I don't think it's going to work.
It's not looking good. I will post this in high quality after the stream under the tweet because
I actually tweet for once. I just don't like Twitter. Twitter is for doing something very
nefarious on and then closing it 10 minutes after. We'll go that movie. Is this not in the Goonies?
That movie Babe Ruth. Right, because the guy wanted a baby roof.
We need some more, some Reese's. I never got Reese's pieces, should have. Reese's pup, Reese's pup.
Eat em up, eat em up, eat em up, eat em up. Reese's pup.
Oh, there's a big ass peanut bar. Thank God I'm not allergic to peanut bar. I had no idea what was
inside this. Thank God I don't have a nut allergy. That could have went terribly wrong.
Mmm. Honestly? Not bad. I can't believe it. I think we've done it. I think we have an A-T here.
I'm not bad. We're even taking a double bait ladies and gentlemen. That's right.
Oh, a peanut. Just for me. We have an A-T here. Okay. I can put that on the A-T here.
I hope I'm not choking. I better not be. Let's see. We've got an A-T here on...
Who are you? Babe Ruth. Oh, maybe I'm choking a little bit. Hold on. I better not be freaking
allergic to peanuts. Are you joking me? Hold on. Let me get iron bro. Not like I'm broken,
resurrect a situation. Literally, I don't need to go to A&E. Cheers.
Okay. I think the peanut was getting stuck in my throat. I'm not actually allergic.
Oh, that is farted. Did you hear that fart? I didn't fart. The thing farted before
reducing. We did it. We have... Iron bro doubles as an epipen. True. True. Right. We've got
mate and ache. Original fruits. Chewy assorted fruit fans. I like chewy fruit. Oh, push
here to open. Oh my god. Oh my goodness sake. How do you push it? Oh my... Wait. Is there like
an outline or am I being pranked? Right. Am I being pranked? This is push to open. I'm...
Look at the red on my finger. Tell me I'm not pushing right now. Tell me I'm not pushing right now.
I'm getting freaking pranked by these. What am I supposed to do? What... Oh, I missed.
What am I supposed to do? Push here to open. Well, I'm bloody trying. Right. Fuck you. Honestly.
That's... Right. Anyway. Plore is true to plore. Oh, these are jelly beans. Oh, I'm gonna like these.
Um, I'm trying. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. S tier. We've done it. We've done it. We've done it, ladies and
gentlemen. Jelly bean. We've got fruit flavor. Come on. What more do you want? Mate and ache.
Come on. I knew I was gonna like that. I looked at that and I knew I was gonna like that right
away. I mean, look at that. Look at that beautiful people. Should I just leave like little sweets
everywhere? Just a little chip. Oh, what's that? I'll try the green one. Okay, maybe not the green
one as an ache to your... You want the green one instead? You guys can have the green one,
but I'll have the other ones, okay? Mm-hmm. All right, green one didn't taste that nice.
Me singing the praise. Okay, we've got milk duds not to be confused with milk ducks. Okay,
don't get it twisted. It's instructions. Okay, we're going for it. Candy made with chocolate
and caramelia. Any caramelians? Oh, caramel... Wait, caramel dancing. Whoa. Wait, there's no
protective film? Like, at all? There's no protective film in the box or that the candy is in?
Monca S? Shouldn't there be a protective film? Question mark? Question mark? Oh, I'm scared to
eat this now. I'm going to take half, okay? All right, no, I can't. There's caramel.
You know what the British candy called rebels is? Rebels, maybe?
Mm-hmm. I don't hate it. It's not S tier, but I think it's A. I think that's the second
A tier. I like that. I would eat... I would put another piece in my mouth again. See, if I wouldn't
put... Or maybe it's B tier, I don't know. A or B. I've got lotion on my tentacle, or I mean it's
or... I've not got lotion on my tentacle right now. Sorry. Sorry for the milk duds. Milk.
It's stuck on my teeth, by the way. I just want you to know. Do you guys want any? Hold on. I got
it kind of hard. There you go. It's really stuck on my teeth. Holy crap. It's really, really stuck
on my teeth. I think I'm just gonna have to give up chewing and just put it on the...
But that isn't that bad. Not a good look, LaLa. Oh, that's really stuck. Where's my water?
I bought a water. I bought a water. I brought a water. Hold on.
Need it. Oh, please don't fall on it. Please don't fall on it. Please keep it inside. It's okay.
Oh no, no, don't. It's fine. It's fine. I'm okay. Wait, how fast am I getting through these? I think
I've like practically already done them all. Right. Mercy told me I'm supposed to finish on...
Oh, I still got the wires twisted now. Mercy told me I'm supposed to finish on one of these
flavours of crisps because they're so overpowering, but I think it's the tackies.
I can't remember. I think the tackies I'm to finish on, so we'll try chi-o's.
Chicky bit of chi-o's. They are flavoured. Flame it. Please don't, please don't throw up.
There shouldn't be this much trap wind. I'm getting nervous. Okay, I'm okay. I'm okay. I'm okay. It's
fine. It's it. That was the bag farting because my hands are sweaty if you heard that. See, little
my hands are nicest. Get the flavour up that nose. Big ol' sniff it a whiff. All right, hold on.
Let us take... They're like red. Okay. Bottoms up, yeah.
Is that cheese? Is that cheese and hot? High taste?
I think... Is that cheese? Yeah, that's cheese. I need to do the spice. Hmm.
Burning my tongue a wee bit. Not like flavour burn, like actual burn.
What do we think? That's honestly... Would I eat it again? Maybe?
All chi-o's have cheese. It's in the name. Oh, chi-o's. Am I saying them wrong? Chi-to's. Oh,
no, it is chi-to's. Cheese-to's. No, yes. Okay, they all have cheese and I've got it.
Honestly, that's not that bad. That's not that bad. I think I would actually eat that again. I
might finish this off. Hold on. That's gonna get an A tier for me. What are they? Cheese-to's.
Cheese-to's. There we go. Cheese-to's.
Living out. Did I put down the other ones that I just tasted? Yeah. I'll put the crisps on the floor.
Honestly, I could be that. Right, I believe this is the last
sweet I have to taste test and then I could just show you stuff around my room.
Because Shibi doesn't go live until two minus one hour in a little bit. Okay, are we ready?
Let's, let's see what's inside. Oh, these are like red as well, like chi-to's. Oh, they've got like
little tiger stripes. Are they supposed to have tiger stripes on them or is mine just carcinogenic
for free? Okay, ready, steady. Oh, they're like natural rolled over.
Oh, okay. Okay, my brain has decided. What the frick is even in this?
Oh my gosh, it's not even in English. Ingredients.
Yeah, I, I, that is so freaking, that is overwhelming. I think that might be a
Mount Doom. You know that. I don't know how that's edible. I think we have two Mount Dooms.
Love the Italian accent. Yep. I'm so sorry. That's a Mount Doom. I can't, that's inedible.
The flavor is overwhelming. There's nothing, there's nothing. Wait, what is the front?
The packet looks like, hold on. Oh, it's just a logo, geez. Has anyone got any? What does that say?
I don't even know what flavor Fuego is, but.
My heart, I'm so sorry. That, there's so much flavor. It's like not even pleasant.
Fuego means fire in Spanish. Oh, it means hot. Okay, je comprends. Sorry to any Italian,
Italian, sorry to any, uh, Espanol, you know, Viva la Mexico. Um, I think we're done. I can't see
any more sweets. I don't have any more sweets. I've eaten them all. Right, what did we rate?
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, 10, 11, 12, 13, 14. Okay, the only one that
made it was a chewy jelly bean, and then a baby Ruth, which is a peanuts, and then the Cheetos,
Cheetos, hot. Oh, I just completely skipped on doing that H. Let's see if you can see a bit better.
Yeah. And then we see, is that, I think that's from the Cheetos that I was touching. Nerds is,
it's all right. A and W, uh, creaming soda. Call me a soda because I'm about to make you cream.
Twinkie with their new design logo, milk duds, uh, and then in the, this is the biggest piece of,
it's not really, it's just I can't eat it. The Dr Pepper, Nacropeper with the 23 flavors,
kisses. Yeah, that was an experience. What the heck does that even say? Peeps. Oh, it says
peeps, but I hid the pee. Peeps, I was actually scared to swallow, but I didn't actually taste
bad. This is Twizzlers, pool and peel. And then this is Jolly Rancher's Heart Candy, that was
again overwhelming. And then the D, which is the mysterious, mysterious watermelon flavor
that disappeared the moment you literally put it in your mouth. Like you taste the flavor,
the moment it enters and then it's gone. And then unfortunately, Fuego, uh, Takis, uh, are just
overwhelming to the point that you do not even have any taste buds by the time you've finished
actually eating any of these American snacks. Did you enjoy the poison? I absolutely did. I
missed half the stream, but I'm gradually making it. We've got an S tier. That's all I wanted out
of this. We've got an S tier. Again, if you're wondering why I'm not using an actual tier maker,
it's because I was too pepego, so we're doing it by hand. That's right, ladies and gentlemen,
I'm so professional. I did this by hand. Okay. Oh, your voice seems better, by the way. It is
slightly better. Um, I did have a T before stream to try and hydrate. Oh, oh wait, hold on.
Oh, oh, excuse me. Sorry. I just need to get that pencil one moment, please. Just need to
grab the pencil. Oh, thank you. Oh, sorry. Thank you. Yes. Okay. I've got the pencil. That's what
I needed it for. Oh, did I tell you I got manicure and pedicure, by the way? Oh,
I can show you my little tism. I don't know if I've told you this yet. So if you look
right here, as you'll notice, these, all these red marks, and then you'll notice right here,
it's because I do this all the time, all day long. I do this. I shove my feet in the ground,
I sit on my feet. So I have a perma, like little indent on my, my toe bone right here.
And then right here, yes, because I always do this and curl my feet up, my little, my little feet.
I'm a toe curler, smiggle, literally smiggling out here. But yeah, that's all the food I have to
review. But I maybe have some fun, cool things to show you. Do you want to see the ASMR that goes
like it goes bloop bloop bloop? Oh my god, I didn't want to show feet. Oh, I did it
stuff for free, like and subscribe, by the way. But yeah, like I go, it's so pretty. This is what's
blooping in your ear when I do all my ASMRs. Like I put the, I did this, I put this on your ears
as well. If I put this on your ears and go, I woke up still in bed. I love you,
mummy. Your nails are so pretty. Thank you. You like that? You like that? Oh, I had a ruler. So
you guys, if you guys have a ruler, I got a ruler so you can, you know, if you want to measure your
hand and you can see how my hand matches up to you, you know? So if your hand from here to here,
okay, is, oh god, you guys do inches, don't you? Oh no, I never thought this through. What the heck
is this? That's centimeters. Oh no, this is centimeters. Oh no, I didn't think this, this part
through. Okay, so what size is your hand in centimeters chat for no particular reason? What
size is your hand in centimeters? Just if you ever wanted to know.
What the heck is a centimeter? My pronouns are USA.
Google translate centimeter. Go, go, go. Someone says 6.5 centimeters for no particular reason.
Wait, 6.5. Hold on a minute. You're, if you're 6.5 centimeters, you're here. Okay, 6.5 is here
and it's my hand. Maybe it looks nicer. Someone says 10. If you're 10 centimeters, you're here.
If you're 10 centimeters, this is outrageous, truly. Oh, you've got such big hands. Why has
everyone got such big hands? Someone says 8.5, 8.5 is here. Man, you guys got massive hands.
The width of you, someone says 21. Yeah, right, 21. This entire ruler is 15 centimeters, so I doubt
you're freaking 21. That's, that's a, we're hit, we're hit with a, if you are, so this is 15 centimeters
long. So if you're 13, your hand, your hand is 13 centimeters. We're doing this. Okay, we're doing
this if your hand's 13 centimeters. This one's it. So yeah, that's absolutely awful. Right, right.
So here's zero and here's 10 centimeters. You already knew it was coming. Let's go. Look at that
manicure. Look at that manicure. Wow. So there's 10 right there. Look at my toe. Oh my god. I look
so feminine right now. Are those my toes? Are those my toes? What else do I have to show you?
That I'm mildly interesting. I might be doing more hand cam streams in the future.
Because look what I got. I got fake nails that look like me.
Wow, little straw nails. Oh, look at the things. These are like, oh, hold on,
hold on, aim bot. These are like little fake nails that you do this. You just put them on.
Look, I'm, oh my god, I'm strawing cuttles. She's eating with her feet. I've already ate,
mercy. I'll finish the tier rating. I'll quickly catch up. Make an acme, oh my god,
I get it now tier. I got lotion on my tentacle is baby, Ruth and Cheetos, hot. I mean, it's all
right. It's Nerds, A&W, Creaming Soda, Twinkie with the new logo and Mike Duds,
Milk Duds, pardon me. It's the biggest piece that is Dr Pepper. Kisses, Peeps, Twizzlers,
Pull & Peel, Jolly Ranchers, Hard Candy. That was overwhelming. And then cast it into the fires
of Mount Doom itself is Watermelon Catch Kids and Tacky's Fuego.
I'm sorry, that's my tier rating. I was like so freaking
thingy. I feel like Peeps is rated too high, but yeah, I'm gonna, if you don't like
hand cam streams, I'm sorry, but I just, I'm gonna fuck a little bit. And this is the part where you go,
ooh. But yeah. So, why else do I have that's even mildly interesting? Oh, I like collecting
seeds of many varieties. Would you like to see my seed collection? Oh, I don't mind showing some
of it. I've not added a lot of seeds recently because I've been so busy with work, but I like
collecting seeds. I think they're really cool. It's my seed collection. Though it's not finished
or labeled, I need to go back and label them all. But I have loads of seeds and I like collecting
seeds. You know, everyone's got a weird hobby. Mine's collecting seeds. But there you go. These are
all my seeds. And there we go. All these sample sizes of my seeds. I do have other bigger ones.
I don't grow plants because I have to rent, but one day maybe I will not have to rent and then I
can have my CDs. But those are my seeds. And they're all super cool. So the thing about seed
collecting is you have to make sure they're dry or else your specimen will actually mold because
if they don't dry, then they mold. And it's not good for obviously you don't want moldy samples.
But yeah, these are pepper seeds. And sorry it's not labeled. Australians call them capsicum,
but these are peppers. The British call them. Like again, I can tell that these are wild Irish
seeds just from I and I just collect seeds. I like them. You can see the difference in the
seeds as well. It's absolutely stunning seeing what nature provides. Because look in this jar,
for example, look how unbelievable. Do you see those dots? Those are entire seeds that grow into
big magnificent plants. And then compare them to the size of this seed. Isn't that amazing the
diversity of plant life? And the seed as well. Also, some seeds can be the vessel that they carry to
the next location for the plant to spawn. So you can get these are wind seed carriers.
Which is crazy because obviously in comparison, these are wind carriers. And then these aren't
wind carriers at all. They have to be taken away via animals such as birds. Like when birds feast
on berries and the seeds inside it and they swallow it and then they fly away and poop.
That's how the new plant emerges because there's no direct competition. Whereas if you get seeds
that have direct competition with one another, that's how you lower the odds of success. Like
honestly, it's beautiful and fascinating when you look into the world of seeds. And yeah,
I just think it's really cool. And you can get some that are so similar. See, these are both
wind carrier seeds. They both get carried by the wind. They look very similar, but there is a
differentiation between them. But flowers steal each other's thing. As they develop in, you know,
the rising of emergence, it's really fascinating stuff in my opinion. But it might not be that
interesting from a stream point of view. But yeah, these are my samples. So let me just put them back
on the shelf real quick. The fact that I actually picked one up doing that, I don't know if you can
see that. Wait, let's see, I picked one up. But yeah, those are my seed samples. I am planning on
getting a lot more, but it's currently winter in Australia, which means my samples are very limited.
I gather these naturally by going through spring or by going through walks and just doing that kind
of thing. Like, for example, on one of my walks, I got a chestnut. If you didn't know this is, you
know, those big chestnut or conkers, you might call these conkers if you're old school British.
But I also have bigger sample sizes as well in these, where I just took an entire sample of the
stem with the seed pods inside. I can actually take the sample out because my hands aren't too
sweaty. I'm not going to ruin the sample. Oh, it's not even going to come out. I don't want to break it
apart. Ah, well, those brown bits are the seed pod. And then you can see where the stem it grew from.
And you can actually see where the flower is budded. So if you didn't know, seeds don't form
until pollination occurs. And that's what flowers are for. It attracts insects to come to the flower
and merge the pollen and the stem. And it's absolutely fantastic stuff. It really is. And it
helps with plant variety and genetics. Like, and the fact that the seeds you can't tell, I've not
labelled this one yet, but I know what it is. This turns into a big, humongous red flower. And you
would never be able to guess that from the sample of the seed pods. So you have to break open these
seed pods in order to get access to them. These like little bits that you see coming off, those aren't
the seeds, those are the outside of the pod. But inside is the seed housed right now inside these.
So I'm not going to break those open when I put them into a sample jar, because I don't need to do that.
But yeah, that's one of my hobbies. So it looks like little buds. Yes, humongous. Well,
education. Did he talk me plants? Yes, the ovum. And, uh, goodness me, I've forgotten the name of
the stem. Oh, I've forgotten the name of it. But it's very important to have plant genetic variety,
which is why pollinators do such a fantastic job, such as bees, wasps. Yes, even wasps are
pollinators and tons of tiny little bugs, so many tiny little bugs. But to increase genetic diversity,
which gives resistance to plants perishing, that's why it's really good for all these little bugs to
mingle amongst all the flowers and all of that. Bats to pollinators? I didn't know that. But yeah,
I guess they can be. This is the doorbell hoax sector I'm talking about. It's just in my...
Well, none of the food section. We've still got an hour to ramble, but I'm not even prepared
anything else. I actually thought it would take a lot longer, but I kind of steamrolled that,
didn't I? I don't really have anything interesting to show. Oh, this was the toy that makes the ASMR
noise really good. But if I go like that against the ear...
You did speed and run at it. Yeah, fun nerd now over hobbies. Just keep rambling, please.
This is what... What could we put this as a substitute for? Huh? We wouldn't say this resembles
any body part. Would we... Take the... I actually don't have anything else interesting to show. I
showed everything at the start of the stream. I showed you the outfit I wanted to wear. I mean,
I could open it up if you want. I thought that... Oh, I should have hit there. Oh dear. I can't
believe it. I can't believe I'm not ginger. But yeah, this was the outfit I wanted to wear,
but then I realized I can't freaking do it because it's not the... Oh, we can even assemble it right now.
Come together. Yeah. There we go. See, there's one little cuttlefish ear. It's not a cat ear. I
don't want to hear any allegations that it's not cat ear. I'm with the Pintis. Exactly.
But yeah, if I can get it in. Oh, that won't fit. Oh no, the fabrics ruffled up.
Squishy cuttlefish plushy merch when? I don't know. Soon, maybe? If the U-Woo market sales go good,
soon. If they don't go so good, maybe not so soon. There's my cuttlefish ears. As you can see,
I'm shimmering like my pearlescent outfit. And then this is the bow for the bow.
As you can imagine, it doesn't really leave much to the imagined. I can't even figure out what way
this goes. Okay, that looks like I'm supposed to put... Yeah, so that's the front. And then that's
where I put my... Wait, is that the front? Oh. Oh, that's the front. Yeah. So as you can imagine,
there's a reason why I couldn't put this on today. But that doesn't mean we can't do it another time.
I'm just doing the buttons at the gravitational area. Just do that, and I'm gonna assemble the
costume. Yeah. Okay, so that's the bottom of it. And this bit goes around my neck. So it's like I'm
collared. And then this, what is this? This is just extra fabric. Is this for my feet?
Is this for my feet? This can be for hands. There's no hand. It is! Hold on.
You know what time it is. There's no way this is for my feet, but I think it is.
Oh. Oh, that's a terror. Oh, there's no way that's for my... Yeah, that can't be for my feet because
they ain't non-six. But that won't look like a massive rubber. That's awful. No, that can't be
for my feet. But what would it be for? It's a dead end. It's literally a dead end inside. I think
it is for my feet, but obviously it's just cheap quality. Because yeah, this is not... This is my
hand in it, no. Oh my god, it looks like the Gryffindor. It looks like the Sorting Heart from
Frickin' Harry Potter. I don't know. Well, you're not twice. I'm cutting eye out. Yeah. Okay, maybe
it was good that I tested it out. That was not gonna work. Oh, but then I have... Oh, maybe I knew
it wasn't gonna work. Oh my god, past me. You've done amazing because this is what the other thing was.
I was gonna try it. It's supposed to be
pearlescent, but I guess just the top is the pearlescent charm.
Sleathering. You would have done well. Sleathering. Hold on. Let me just...
My feet are sweaty, so it means stuff gets stuck to them, which is not very pleasant. Hold on.
Yeah. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Let me kick. Let me kick.
You can kind of see the toes done too.
I don't know. I can like see the bit that made out. I'm supposed to do like that probably.
Who said our god is an awesome god? Are we singing Gospels out here?
Okay, that's enough giddy-fitting. Giddy-fitting? That's not a word at all. I will do that another day
for this costume, although maybe it might not be a live stream and it might just have to be
pictures or something if you guys want to take a Donothon reward. I don't know. I still need to
figure out Donothon rewards. Azura is the first to have a Donothon at the other headquarters.
I need to help her coming up with some stuff because we're going to be doing lots of group
activities. Wait, I just thought that was her hand, but it was her foot. I thought I just
been on a glove now. Take me to church. Have I done... I have eaten all the American food.
I have nothing more interest in the show. Oh, maybe... Okay, so this was my concept that I had.
Give us a soul flash, but it would be so wrinkly because I have to like turn my foot up in order
to give you a soul flash. So this was my concept for an ASMR series, okay? So we could do it on
Pyro Pups. Well, I was going to do it on the girls mascots first if we managed to get plushies of
them. And it was going to be like this ASMRs for Pyro Pups only, for example. And it would be like
because Cinder is on fire because she's so hot type thing, I would get the microphone. So you'd
see the microphone. So like, hold on, I can literally give you a live example. So the microphone,
like it would be a hand cam type thing, but I wouldn't do it live. I would make like an actual
professional video out of it. And it would be like, so because Cinder's always hot, Pyro Pups need to
cool down because of how hot she makes them. So I would do like with a little spray bottle and I'd
go like ear to ear. And then like that was and then whatever was related to and like, I would say
some lore about Cinder like, oh, Cinder started streaming last year on this day. And since then,
like she's had this collection come out and she's been able to achieve this and she's done that. So
it'd be like ASMR for those who are in the fan base. And I teach you lore about the person. And
then like, I would relate to it as well and be like, because Pyro Pups are such good boys, they
also deserve head pat ASMR and like pat pat pat pat pat pat pat pat pat pat pat pat pat, you know?
Like that. When did you do that? I've not done it, but this is my theory for like an ASMR type
series that I could do. And like, if a creator's come out with a plushie, so like again, this is
Darling Strobe's plushie. And I'd be like, oh, so Darling Strobe started her journey five years ago.
I think it was roughly five years ago. No, I don't think hers was as long. And like, I would just
tell Facts about the creator and I'll be like, oh, she's been making ASMR videos since 2021 or
something like that. And like, she's really found a good groove and she uploads like that kind of
thing. And then because Strobe's so cute, we would like, I would offer it a little strawberry and
then I would double over it and go yum, yum, yum, yum, yum, yum, yum. And then when I get the girls
plushies, I'll like all do like super maxed out. And then I can tell behind the scenes stuff about them.
And Mercy gave me permission to say this, but if I get the snippets plushie,
do you want to know what Mercy put on the end of her application that also helped strengthen
her application to Veiler? She put, I have autism and she went, she got in.
She put, I have autism. At the end of that application, it says, uh, is there anything you
want Veiler to know about you? And she goes, I have autism. And I was like, oh, and you come,
and you come. Gotta look after the fellow artists. So then she comes.
So yeah, please don't, uh, please don't think Veiler ain't gonna take a look at you because
you're autistic. Nah fam, the spearheads fucking got the combo of everything going on. So don't
you worry. Uh, but yeah, I was going to like do like a smart, that way everyone's plushies.
And then it also means if there's any creator that has a plushie that wants to send me it,
so I do like a, like a series on them as well. I'm more than open to it. I can get a PO box.
So if you are a creator without plushie that you can reach out, but obviously don't do it right
now because I'm not even started the fricking series. I was going to start the series off with
the girls plushies because like I would have to do like research on others. Obviously it's really
easy. I can just bomb the dns and be like, Hey, what do you want me to say? Uh, our type thing.
Um, whereas like for other creators like I have to do my research. Okay, I have to do my research.
And obviously like if it's she beats plushie, for example, this is the, this is the ASMR you're
getting right right on the, right on the face. I hope strobe doesn't jump in the stream. Oh my
goodness. She's going to be like, what are you doing to my plushie? Um, but yes, I can send you
but yes, um, I wanted to do it like really in character and all of that jazz. So I might do
a series like that. And I think the ASMR would be pretty Pog not going to lie. I think it would be
how one says a poke champ. Oh my gosh. I can't believe it. Darling strobes plushie knows how to
highland dance. Fogger is champed for years even. She's enjoying, I'm sure. Oh, well feel
strong and kill seas. Oh yeah. Not that kind of seed sample. Don't send that kind of seed sample.
That's a bio hazard for one. Did you know that swimmers can last up to 48 hours in the,
the womb? Which is why you need to be careful and wrap your willy. Don't be silly. You don't want
to pay child support. Don't give her the opportunity to leech your income. Be a child support. Don't be
silly. Wrap your willy. I'm just turning this into a mascot now. Well it's not my mascot, it's not
a re-film but. Was it a Mike and Ike? Just life advice, I know. Thank you for the message
plushie. I know Darling strobes plushie. I've completely forgotten. The fan base evades me,
the name of her fan base. Her darlings? Possibly? Very plausible, it could be her darlings.
But yeah, I know Senders is pyro pop. I could definitely do that series once we, oh my god,
what happens if they kissed? Oh this is boy slumber parties versus girl slumber parties.
I've not really been such a child. I've not like had a chance to actually play with toys
many a year. I'm sure that's not a surprise to anyone. But yeah, this is so cute and like
how much detail. Also, I didn't know this. When you order for makeshift, it literally tells you
like how lucky your batch is. Like Hellhound, I don't know if you can read that, hold on.
It says, oh hold on, where's camera? Hold on, find camera, find camera, come on, you can do it.
Hellhound, Wolf plushie by Cinder. Only 697 made, but it doesn't give me my number I don't think.
Just says it's official merch. Oh wait, what? Okay, they're called, if you're a darling strobe,
you are a Snickers? Like the bar? And you've only got 294. There's only 294 of these made and I have
one. So yeah, I was hoping to do an ASMR series like that. So it's kind of like ASMR and VTuber
orientated, which I thought was really cool because I don't think I've seen anyone do that before.
That's what her mascot is called, we're learning. But yes, I am hoping to be a cheeky cheeky and
possibly get the girl's plushies for their birthdays and then I can start up that series.
And it would be really cool because like I would literally open up a like form and other VTubers
if they wanted to be a part of the series, literally all they have to do is send me their
mascot, like a plushie of their mascot and I'll do the rest of the cooking. And I would think it
was like a cool way to get like more VTubers like involved and it's a way that I can kind of interact
with VTubers because I get like, not nervous, but I don't like reaching out because I'm a dirty dirty,
whereas I don't know if the girl is and I'd rather not like force that barrier. Like the barriers
being crossed between like Yumi Plus, like they're all super cool, honestly. Like I feel comfortable
with Yumi Plus and all that and the VNU girls, I'm all comfy because of all that jails. But yeah,
like I don't really want to reach out to creators in case they're like, I don't want to be associated
with you. Yeah, that's cool. I get it. I need mascot plushies and Fumos. What's Fumos?
Yumi Plus has been awesome so far. They have. They have. I would like the format and it would be
really cute. Yeah, like kind of like just like a little rundown on your mascot and all that jazz.
Just as a warning to the harem in T-minus 40 minutes, your supreme is live. Did you guys like
my hypnosis yesterday? Yeah. I didn't really expect to do any of that, but that was a very good
suggestion. I loved it. Oh, wait, sorry. Do you guys want to, if we're just talking, if we're just
talking, hold on. Let me just, if we're just talking away. Yes. Oh, yes. Kiss my feet.
You can literally see where I've been pushing in on my toe there. I do this all day, every day,
all day long. If I sit on my feet and all that jazz. Yes. This is my finished tier list. Let's
just, sorry, let me just point out the different sections of the, excuse me, excuse me, coming
through. So this right here, if you can point it correctly, so this is the S tier, which was
this is the A tier. Oh, no, it was Mike and I. Pardon me. Then the A tier, which is, I can't even
read my writing from here. Baby Ruth. And then the Cheerios, the Cheetos, not the Cheerios,
that's actually British food. And then for B tier, nerds. Do you guys, do you guys even have the
ability to do this with your feet or is this like, like, I literally have full ambidextory?
Like, I can literally have full ambidextory with my, my grippers.
Oh, shit. What happened? Oh, did something break? Oh, no, I didn't. I thought it did.
Okay, it's all good. Yeah, you can do that. Yeah. But can you write, hold on, wait,
can I write the refling's name? Hold on. Hold on. Let's see if I can write your names.
Well, I'm going to write refling, not your names in particular, but that could be a really funny
stream if you really wanted that. Hold on. Okay, it needs to be a bit longer. Hold on.
If you, if you weren't here at the start, the lady cut my toe so I actually don't have any,
a little harder than I thought. Right, R. Oh, that didn't even, oh, that's not even,
okay, there's the start.
And he used all my brain. Okay, hold on. It may actually be easier if I do this. Hold on. Hold
on. Hold on. I got this. Let me click. Let me click. I know you can't see the angle. Let me,
oh, it's not going down. This is terrible, honestly. Signed feet merch win, honestly.
Right. Oh, we're getting there. Oh, that's such a good R. I'm not even kidding.
Okay, that was an interesting E. That was an interesting E. Let him cook, let him cook.
Okay, that's the same problem with that E, but don't worry about it. Don't worry about it.
Don't worry. Up, up, and then down again. Yes, yes, and then an I.
And then up again, up again, gently, gently. And then an N. Okay, so down and then along. Okay, so
on the paper. Yep, and then up a little bit. Yep, and then along. Oh, and then down. Oh,
and then a G with all my might. Oh, and down. One big down, one big swoop, one big swoop.
There we go. Every flu. Oh, wait, we need to do the dot on the I. Hold on. Right about here.
Okay, there we go. Hey, replay.
I don't even know how I did that, honestly. Ta-da! Look, R-E-E. Wait, I didn't do the F on the...
That's about your name wrong. I did. That's about retelling. Wait, R-E-E-F. I forgot the F. Hold on,
I forgot the F. Let me try again. Let me try again. I was getting really distracted, but okay.
Okay, we need to just... Oh, hold on. Okay, hold on. You just hold that tight. Froggy likes that bad boy.
So do the F, and then it's got to be a flick at the back. And then, and... Oh, there we go. Oh!
Tell me that isn't like neat. I literally just drew cursive with my feet. Please clap, seriously.
I just drew cursive with my feet. Reefling. You can see that clear as day.
It is so good. Recovered F in the chat, which was right. I can't believe I did that. There we go.
That is amazing. I've got so much skill. I do. I've got so much skill in my little toes.
I was actually putting insert golf clap. Yes. But yes. That's me goofing around. That's all my
ideas. Oh, you can see my headset again. Oh my gosh, I am a real... I can't believe it. My immersion
is gone. It's out the window. I do not... I actually think for some reason my feet will probably be
better right in with my right foot instead of my left. I feel like if I wrote with my left foot,
you wouldn't actually be able to see any... Oh, I just dropped the pencil. Hold on. I'm just gonna
pick it up with my toes because I'm so... See, this is left foot right, and I'm not sure it's gonna work.
Oh, no, it's not gonna... Uh-oh. I don't see. No, you're not even gonna be able to see it.
Oh, jeez. No, that actually hurts to write on the left foot for some reason.
There, that's my R on my left. It's so good. If you can do this, what else can you do?
I don't know. Where's the ruler? Hold on. Where's the ruler? Where'd it go? Oh, there's a
sample here. Let me take a little sample at why not. These are called bendies. These are...
They actually use hook seat technology. I think there's four ways of seat dispersal,
and these bendies are called hook. They hook to the fur of the animal who's been near the plant.
Uh, don't be afraid to... Don't be afraid to focus in on the seed. Come on.
Oh, well, I try. They've got little hooks on them. It's pretty impressive, honestly.
Anyway, that's just me and my obsession with the seeds. What about you? What's your weird collection?
Look at the mess I've made. There's just chaos on this desk, right? I'm not even kidding. Let me just...
Like a huckleberry. Write in a feet script with feet as well. What, you want me to type on the
keyboard next? I mean, I could. You guys are going to see my gamer keyboard. You want to see my
gamer keyboard? It lights up. Hold on. Let me put the book on the floor. Our tier list is out the window.
Uh, excuse me, Giro. I'm afraid due to the nature of the medical emergency, you're gonna have to go up there.
Oh, no. Is the wire pulling? Okay, what do you want me to type in chat? I don't think... I can't
pull the wire any further, I don't think, and I can't really remove the webcam because of the way I've
set this up. Okay, what do you want me to type in chat? I've literally have chat open. What do you
want me to type? You want me to type PogChamp, right? Okay. Oh, I missed. Hold on. I think I'm
missing everything. Oh, shit. That did not work at all. That did not work at all. I thought I nailed
that. I'm not gonna lie. I thought I nailed that. I did not at all nail that. Like, not even close.
Not even close. Okay, give me another word that's short to try. I'll like really try hard it, okay?
The gripper. Literally, oh, you can't see it, but I like do this on the end of the table.
What do you want? You want cuttles, right? Really try hard. Okay, I can't even see it. Okay.
I can tell I'm like inputting so much other stuff.
Did that work? Did I miss? I did it! I freaking did it! Let's go, baby.
Just like that. Honestly, give yourself some practice on something new. If you've never
typed with your toes before, all it takes is a second chance and you nail it, apparently.
Oh, yeah. This is my keyboard and this is my mouse mat. Can you tell who's on the mouse mat based
on the hair? I ain't clean it, but it's, it's Jinx from, from the hit TV show, Arcade,
or League of Legends if you play League, but I like Jinx. It is Jinx. God, you guys are really
good at that. What the heck? No, I don't think there's anything else I can show really. Yeah,
maybe although, you know, look, look, it's the, the thingy. This is, so I bought the technology
that lets me do all this, but I never use any of it because I'm a bad VTuber. I'm a naughty VTuber.
This is what I'm supposed to do like mid-game. I'm supposed to be like,
let me change real quick, but yeah, it's not happening with me. Sorry, but I ain't not good,
but this is like how I control my hypnosis. So have you never seen like the behind the scenes
on a VTuber? This is what it looks like. This is what I'm supposed to do, but I never do it.
I've got a bikini toggle. Well, let's not do that. Oh, that's a tipper. I will hold you in
my hand. What did you say? Is Brian talking? I don't think Brian's talking right now.
There's no Brian in the stream. I don't know why. Oh, oh, I missed another tip from a random
refling, some random refling tip that said, I heart feet, narrow tip. Thank you for the tip,
said feet dexterity level 100. Just unlocked literally a little bit of a, but yeah, if you've
never like seen the behind the scenes of a VTuber before, like I'm happy to show like, I don't
mind. Like, you know how I always complain about calibration? This is why, this is why I calibrate
to and like, there's my spit pile. Look, this is very spit out all my stuff. Look, there's my half
chewed up foods, half twizzler. That's the caramel one. That's my peep. Yeah. And then that's James.
Hi, James. Hi, hi. But yeah, I don't really mind showing the behind the scenes of it.
It's just, just what it is. I don't bother me. No. So yeah, this is when I'm taken. I'm like, oh,
yeah. Oh, yeah, I took that. So good. Oh, my freaking, my preview of my live stream just died.
And I thought I just died, but I didn't. Indirect kiss on the food. Do we have the same desk? I
built this desk myself. I needed a really wide streaming desk and it costs like $400 to get it.
So I bought wood and I painted it and then I attached legs. So it's an extra wide desk. It's
like super wide, super wide, super wide. This is literally just turning into a handcam stream,
right? What game, what game we playing? You know the streamers that like only show their hands?
Oh, also, let's play also. Oh, oh, oh, let's get it. Actually, you paint wood, that could look
but yeah, she could build as furniture with a perfect way she'd be
playing the Binding of Isaac. Oh, my gosh, should we?
Yeah, maybe, maybe I should maybe not make the focus on the keyboard of this stream.
You know, let me just move that back over there. You go over there. There you go.
Oh, it's bumping on something. It's not. Oh, I broke the legs on this keyboard.
Do you feel in? See, funny you mentioned in a full Elden Ring placer with feet. I was actually
going to do a foot cam stream to show how much I don't have my feet on the ground. I'm currently
sitting on my feet yet again. And I thought it would be funny to play a game where I show feet,
because like when I get stressed, my feet also go like that with my toes. Like I have a lot of
emotion in my feet. Maybe. Oh, I do have something to show you. I can do this. It's a special shoutout.
I'm allowed to do it. So the artist is, I can't freaking, I need my glasses on so badly right
now, is LinkedIn Art. And I can also say this before anyone cries. I also say special thank you
to Dapper Bucket who commissioned the artwork. But for next week's streams, I have Elden Roll,
Elden Roll, nice enough. No, I have Elder Scrolls, Skyrim part one and part two. There's
are two back-to-back endurance streams for full achievements. We're going to get them together.
Hopefully I can do it on Xbox Game Pass and then we can get our first 1000-gamer score.
If not, then we'll play Vanilla. Then we have our classic ASMR stream which will be short.
And then we have the first indulge gen-mate stream. All six of us are going to be on Power
Watch Simulator and there's going to be a little plot line to go along with it, okay? You're not
ready for what that plot line is. But there'll be a reason why we're playing that game as our first
gen-mate thing. And then I am jumping back on Old School Runescape to beg you guys to give me
fish again. And then we're playing Crash Bandicoot Warped which is an old childhood game. I only
remember playing the China Mission when you're a cocoa and you ride the tiger. I used to play
over and over again. And I actually don't remember finishing the game or what it's about. I just
remember cocoa. So we're going to be playing that. And then Buckshot Roulette is my tiny, tiny stream.
I am aware that Buckshot Roulette is a very short game. So I might just do a foot cam stream if my
toes look good, if they don't. When are we getting a cavio play through? Not yet, but soon to end.
But yes, there are three Endurance streams which are the Elden Rings and Old School Runescape.
Crash Bandicoot, I believe, can be finished in eight hours. So it's technically not an
Endurance. That's just the average Joe's work shift. So Buckshot Roulette can be pretty fun if
you go for high scores. Okay, I've never played before. Someone says Veeler running out of funds
in the first month so the girls banded together to open a sexy power wash car company. You know what?
If you're just going to guess what the freaking plot was that I was going to make,
at least don't guess it correctly. You've ruined it now. You've ruined the collab. How dare you?
The whole point of that collab and the reason I picked that game first, I was going to start the
game with all of them lined up and I was going to be so serious. And I was going to be like,
look guys, the income that Veeler are making is not looking good. We're going to have to open up a
side business and we're going to call ourselves like the e-girl washers or something like that.
If you're going to guess it, don't you brand it. You brand the whole reason we're going to play that
game. How dare you? How dare you? How dare you? But only the reeflings that are in here are going
to know you're only you guys are going to know. You're going to know the secrets. But yeah, Buckshot
Roulette is going to be teeny tiny. I might add feet cam just to spice it up a bit and you guys
can tell me off every time I sit on my feet as I currently sit on my feet. Crash Bandicoot,
eight hour old school, endurance 12-ish roughly. My voice can keep up. Power wash, super short.
I don't know if I'll do a pop-up stream. It's plausible. It's very plausible. I might do a
pop-up short stream. I don't, I'm not going to ask for more than two hours from the girls
collab wise. I don't want to like force them to, you know, do that kind of stuff because they're
probably a busy one to do their own thing. Keep your feet on the ground. Literally, I can't help
it. Look how red my feet get. I don't know if you can tell but they're all red here because I've been
like doing that again. I can't, oh, oh, oh wow. Okay. All right. Just got a little sensor thing
going on that it do excuse me. Hold on a minute. Just, oh yeah. Yeah, you like that.
Look at that. Empty. It's true.
We love the story. There's a bandaid on one of them because unfortunately the nice lady that
was working on my feet cut it open by accident. If you didn't know, when they prepare your toes,
they literally take out these clippy caliber things and clip away the skin around your toe
and I started bleeding. So I said, it's okay, don't worry, but please don't do anything to it.
There's no point in putting this on it whilst I'm bleeding out. So I just said do, no, everything
else. It's fine. It's fine. Oh, it's terrifying. Well, I've heard some horror stories about people
like freaking losing their feet because of like chop, chop. So I'm probably not going to get this
done often. I do have what's called gel on it. If anyone is so inclined to know what this is called,
these are called gel and she literally baked my fingers. She put them under a UV light. So if I
get like any skin issues, it's because she baked my freaking fingers like to activate the gel.
You're supposed to go back to the place to get it removed, but I think I'm just going to grow it
out because I don't want any more chemicals like it was the smell of the chemicals that they were
using on my nails was very, it was rather pungent. It was rather pungent and I really do not
feel like any more chemicals after eating all those American sweets. I do apologize. I've had
enough chemicals for one day or for one week. So I'm just going to grow these out naturally. It's
probably going to look really bad. Oh, I've got 10 out of 10. Don't remove the gel at home. It's very
dangerous. Yeah, I was just going to let them grow out and cut it off. I assume it's fine to
let it grow out and cut it off because I'm not really going to be doing. Hopefully I'll get
monetization soon because the whole point of me getting this was to do a monetization stream
that's similar to this, but a bit different. That's right. I thought ahead enough to make it
similar, but different. Oh wait, similar, but different.
But yes, I love this. Are you squiddin' me right now? Oh, I heard that. Love all the streams
so far. So glad you're back. You and all your gen mates are on point. 10 tenths. I heard that.
Did you guys hear that as well? You did. Oh, thank you. Thank you. Eternity. What a name.
Eternity. Thank you for such kind words. Yeah, me and my gen mates are amazing. Oh,
also, this is how I make jokes. Right, someone quickly give me a joke that I can steal. Quick,
quick, quick, because this is what I do when I steal your jokes. Okay? That's what I do when I
steal your jokes. Brian's back. We did miss Brian, but thank you very much for the tip again,
Eternity. Eternity. A man walked into a bar. You think he would have seen it?
Wait, did that play?
Wait, it didn't play?
Okay, I don't think it's working right now. Something's not quite right. Something's not quite
set up. I'm not sure why. Okay, just imagine this one goes, and then this one, if it's a good joke,
then this one, if it's a bad joke, and then this one, if crickets. Okay? I don't know why. Sometimes
something's working. Sometimes other times it doesn't work. Oh, sugar. I'm going to make sure
I'm redirecting into Sheevee. Oh my god. Oh my god, you can see me typing. Oh my god, wait, hold on.
Is it cool? Like when you can see streamers' hands. Hello, reflings. How, oh, I'm getting embarrassed.
Is it going? And then that's right. I'm taping and streaming live. What are you going to do about it?
Nothing.
No, not really.
You're so silly. You're so goofy. Oh, that was right. You're so goofy. Are you challenging me?
I don't know how you learn how to tape in school, but in primary school, you had to do this. Like,
at first as a child, you do this, but then they teach you, like each hand takes over a certain
section, so you're just like, blah, blah, blah. Do you watch keyboard when typing? Right, this is me
not looking. The only way I can prove it is by looking up with my Vtuber model. Like, oh, okay.
Let me just get the star position. I am, oh, I pressed caps lock. Sorry. Wait, no, I didn't. Hold
on. Sorry. Sorry. I am not looking at the keyboard right now, but that's because I'm a dirty, dirty
neat that never left the house for two years. So I am kind of used to typing a lot. Sorry,
but it's just the truth. Oh, wait, I spelled the truth wrong. Wait, wait. There we go.
Yeah. Yeah, so I can tape without having to look. I don't know what it looks like, probably.
She's just like me. My gran always gets amazed whenever I tape in front of her without having
to look. She's like, hey, do you do that, strongy? I'm just like, I don't know. We grew up with
technology. You grew up with like coal fires. That's like as far as your technology went,
a little coal fire in the corner of the house. Main or grammar mistake. I went, no,
do a taping restream. Wait, I can beast you guys and taping?
How do I do a taping restream? Is there like a website for it? I was going to do, I was going
to verse you guys in chess. Like 1v1 me and chess. 10 fast fingers. All right, I'll check it out.
10 fast fingers. You should be taping up the dev overkill. It's hilarious. Wait, chess would be
so cool. Yeah, it would be a chill stream, a long stream, snipe day. I would love to 1v1 you guys
in chess. Before you're like, are you a chess champion? Oh, no, I am not. I suck.
But I also swallow.
But yeah, we probably 1v1 in chess would be funny.
I literally, I am a chess box champion. Right, let me 100% make sure I'm raiding into
sheepsters after this stream because I am rubbish and I'll mess it up. Hold on.
Come on, YouTube. Give me monetization so I can do my pop-up stream. I'm waiting for it.
Oh, she's playing vampire of masquerade bloodline. I might need to sit and count for that stream
on ironically. I'm doing collab study. I'm actually doing collab scripts. I keep saying, oh, I'm gonna
do collab scripts, collab scripts, collab scripts. And then I never do them because I get distracted.
It took, and oh, there's like literally food on the back of my hand right now. Oh my god,
and I knew you told me, how embarrassing, there's just food on the back of my freaking hand. Do
you like my, do you like my meat sticks? Do you like how you can see my meat sticks?
Some people hate that, but I don't know, it's just like, can you see your meat sticks at home?
YouTube, please. I want to use that most honestly. I want to use them too. I've got my
most waiting for that meat stick. What are they called? These aren't the ligaments, what are they
called? What are they called? What if I'm freaking name the tendons and the ligaments? Yeah, those
are my meat sticks. So hot. You like meat sticks? One potato, two potato, three potato, four.
Right, I have still not correctly redirected into she because you guys are distracting me.
Stop distracting me. This is terrible. I'm just going to start talking through my hands.
Stop distracting me. You're so naughty. Stop it. That's your end point. You're in,
getting closer to you. I'm getting so, you can see the chocolate on my finger again.
And there, this isn't even, get off me. Yes, you're right there. You're a terrible influence.
Terrible.
Did you lick my finger? Refling, you just lick my finger. You're terrible.
But yeah, this, this is my hand. I do apologize to those who,
get filler, get filler, get filler. Don't enjoy when a YouTuber has hands, but
I don't know what to tell you. Like I also got the, got the feet toes up. Look at that spread. Look
at that spread. Why does, why does that toe, my pinky toe does not come out very much.
Spread. Whoa, my pinky toe. Hold on a minute. Whoa. Wait, wait, why does my pinky toe not spread?
Whoa, wait, when I go to spread my toes, my pinky doesn't.
Ah, it like so crooked.
There you go. I, I must ask you a question.
Why is this one like having the time of its life over here? Holy crap.
Could you imagine the grip strength I would have on you? Where's the ruler?
I'll repeat my, imagine the grip strength. I'll snap it in half in between these toes.
What does that even mean? I don't know. I'm starting to lose the plot. I think the,
the American can die is getting to me. It's all, it's all the red numbers. It's the red 40.
It's going, it's getting to my head. I can't stand it. I'm being taken over. Oh, who say can, who say.
Red 40 strikes again. I can't believe it. I'm turning American.
I'm like leaving you. I can't believe I actually thought this was a, um,
a fortune teller thing. I was convinced there was going to be like a joke on the other side or
something. You're going crazy. I like, I can't believe it. All it took was a few American sweeties
and I'm going, the numbers. What do they mean? Right. I don't know. I don't know what you guys
want me to do for like these last 10 minutes. I feel, I feel a bit out of my comfort zone,
but not in a bad way. Just in a, I'm really unprepared. Like I thought we were going to be
at this for a very long time, but we're not. Do you want me to tell you what? I'll just,
I'll just caress this. There you go. Oh, little ASMR orb. Watch to do your orb, orb. I see. Yes,
yes. I'll just caress it. Oh wait, maybe I should get the second one so it's a bit more,
a bit more. Yes, we'll caress these. One week review of the company. You want me to review
via lure? How do I review it? Everyone's doing great. They're all having fun. I'm going to even
review it. Everything's going fine. We've got an exciting thing coming up, but I'm not allowed to
talk about it. Boom. But you know, God respect the, God respect the hustle. Spur the moment ASMR.
Employee performance report. Bro, what do you want me to say? Oh yes, all the girls literally
streamed every single day. What more could I ask for? Seriously? What more could I have asked for?
Visucky coming up. All right. Okay. You want the DLC expansion of Veila already? The Visucky DLC
to go live? Okay. Not enough burps, honestly. Lord's milk. Nice keyboard. Thanks. Thanks. Oh my
God. Wait, I can still type in chat. Thank you for being so kind about my keyboard. You're so nice.
Woo. I'm a real, I'm a real streamer. Totally not breaking a VTuber code of conduct.
I was at VTuber code of conduct 101. Don't show that you, do you see this little mark here?
That was from the toothbrush when we brushed our teeth on stream. All of the toothpaste leaked
down my toothbrush. Do you want to brush our teeth? Let's, let's brush our teeth. Oh my gosh,
that's like the perfect time to do it. Hold on. We need to go brush our teeth. We're helping.
All right. People are wondering why I mute when I leave the room. It's because the toilet is right
there and I really don't want to hear, like, I don't want to give you a chance to hear me,
like, do a big old, a big old job. I am not going to lie. I actually had a tick to hear you as a part
of this stream. And obviously the Americans have been bubbling up and help out. I'm currently using
my floor towel and I have a floor towel for how sweaty my feet are. Oh, has everyone got their
make tootie brush? Look, this is my tootie brush. It's so, so fancy. Oh, so fancy. I don't put it
on because it makes a really loud noise and I don't want your perspective to be, what we try and do
this thing together. I'm going to need to borrow your toothbrush. Okay.
Okay. Does it vibrate? Yeah, I like it vibrate. It's like, oh, that just put water everywhere. That
was very, oh, oh, rather silly of me about how, so I have to snap it in to put my thing into,
but we're just going to manually brush our teeth. Okay. So this is day two of 21, even though I've
not done it consistently. I'm brushing away the red 40. Red 40 ain't got nothing on me.
Oh, I forgot about the moment. This thing just keeps on getting fired. What do you mean? I've
been sweet and then I get, I have done. You need to get behind your teeth as well, like behind your
front teeth and behind your broken front teeth. Just after this stream, I don't want to get up. Okay,
even though after this move. Oh, yeah. We're brushing our teeth right here. Sing gangsters'
parodies. I don't actually know the words that well.
Okay, I've gotten wet everywhere.
What's your favorite American song? Something from Green Day, probably.
Uh, I like the schizophrenia Green Day song. I can't remember how it goes.
I like the holiday. What would the schizophrenia one be? He's in the scene as well, as opposed to a
scene as well. One, two, one, go! Lay down your arms, and through the sky, one, two, one, go!
Oh, there's a new single out by Atadashi Gakko. Wait, hold on, I need to spit.
This is my sweaty feet towel. Would you like it? Instead, it's gonna be my toothbrush. Oh,
shit, that just went everywhere, don't it? Oh, that wasn't the objective, but hey,
oh, it's like all over me as well. I have so much spit. I don't know if you guys like salivate a
lot. Oh, it's on my desk. Oh, sorry. Oh, thankfully the camera's actually out of my hairs in the way,
so you don't have to look at my freaking spit on the desk, clean, twat bag. Oh, well, here you go.
Oh, yes, oh, yes, the hood reads in the first place for the... Oh, it's all over the back of
my hand as well. My god, that really actually got everywhere. Jesus. Some of us salivate a lot,
some of us don't. It's fine, it's fine, it's fine. It's even on the keyboard, is it?
It actually is as well. I'm sorry. I get really salivated whenever something enters my mouth,
so teeth brushing with something. I've actually covered that other thing, actually. I'm sorry.
I just have to use my sleeve. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I know I'm gross and minging, okay?
Look, deodorant's optional. If I'm not going outside, I'm not wearing it.
Oh, I should probably do that smelly thing, because all my gen mates did that smelly thing.
Okay, we are soon to read into ShoeBee in two minus seven minutes. Cease your heresy.
Would be disgusted. Look, I was raised in a barn. That's all I'm gonna... I'm gonna...
Hear that chat? She's self lubricating. Oh, you can't say that. You made me read that out loud.
The AFK bubble. Yeah, you like my AFK bubble? Any AFK? Yeah, give filler, give filler, give...
In a barn, is she, Jesus?
She's...
I feel like I don't have anything else interesting to show. Like, this is it. I'm not that interesting.
I'm sorry. Okay, out of raw interest and no more. Where's my pencil? I've already lost it.
Excuse me. You're gonna have to move out the way. Okay. How many?
Right. What are... Right, this is four centimeters.
Four centimeters. Okay, then we'll do the next one. This is eight centimeters for no... Oh,
you guys can't see that. Sorry, sorry. I keep forgetting the camera's like, not my eyeballs.
I know that's crazy, but the camera's not my eyeballs. This is eight centimeters long.
Oh man, I think... This is 12. This is 12. That's ridiculous. I don't know why I'm...
That's 12. Oh, you can't see it. It's so freaking late.
Yeah. How many pickles can you show? What's she measuring? 16.5. That's all fours.
You guys are not out here for that much, holy shit.
16.5? Shut up. I'm sorry. What? That can't be. This... This ruler is 15. I'm sorry,
I refuse to believe that. What? No way. My reflins are packing. I mean, actually, hold on.
I don't know. The marshmallow's beg to differ.
19-0-5. No, I don't believe yours. I don't believe yours. That's outrageous. That is so much blood
flow. Like... I don't... That's... I'm still going. Like, I'm still going. There's no way. I refuse.
17! No. I'm... I'm still going. I'm claiming like a monkey with hands. There's no way. I refuse.
You guys cannot be that packed. How does that work? Don't you know, like, get lightheaded or something?
That is outrageous.
No. Why are we measuring our hands like this? Wink, wink. We're measuring our hands.
Like that.
How do you do this? 14. That seems more reasonable, but that's still a bit outrageous. I have to admit.
14 is that. That is still really...
I don't know. Hold on. I'll redo 12. I'll redo 12 so we can actually see it because I can't actually see
that with my eyeballs. Oh, why? What? Why did that not show up? I wonder because of the green undertone.
Hmm. Yeah. My goodness. Now convert that all into inches. I don't know what any of this means in inches.
So I love to hear you pronounce different words with your accent.
Apparently I say dual wield quite satisfactorily and strawberry is quite satisfactory and ghetto.
This girl. 2.5 centimeters is one inch. So two point... All right, hold on. Do it like this.
Do it like this. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Let me kick. Let me kick. So from here,
one inch, 2.5 so then that makes that two inches. 2.5. So that's three. That's two. That's one.
What does that mean? Five and then plus two is ten. It's four inches. Yeah. And then we'll
halfway. That's five. Then we'll halfway again. That's six.
Yeah, I'd say you're, you're, woohoo. Let's go. Woohoo.
You're good to go. You start. This is, this is getting painful. This is getting,
we've had enough at this stage. I will, I will teach you a very fun fact. Maybe a later date.
But as a woman, I had to go see a woman doctor and I got diagnosed with a clam. Okay, let's just call
it Tate Clam Syndrome. Okay. So this, woohoo. This, this is, oh, oh, you're hurting me. Like,
so, yeah, this is, so higher than this. Our lure. Yeah, I'll get to go.
Yeah. I mean, I don't mind. I think if we end up doing bands,
streams, I'm happy to show you my, my figurines and I will show you why I have a certain type of
figurine from a super underground elite video game that no one's heard of. Okay. And I'll,
I'll show you why I have a certain type of figurine and I'll explain it in a lot more detail.
But apparently, none other than Shibi Cottonbump has just gone live. So we're going to end it there.
Are we happy? Are we satisfied with the hand cam? Have I done enough fan services? Everyone happy?
Do you have any last requests? Any last requests before I go?
Remember a game. Yes. Today is trying to stream we learned. Yeah. Ending on a high note. It was fun.
Yeah. Everyone happy. Thank you for stream. Okay. I did everything. I did everything. No
requests. Okay. I'm happy. Everyone happy. Peace sign and stick out your tongues model.
I can do that. Flip me off. Yeah, you like that? See, some people, some people bring this in.
Wrong. This is wrong. It's, it's back to back L's. Okay. You need, you need to give them the L back
to back. That's how you do it. Okay. You want hand holding? How do I hold your hand?
I hold it like this. If I ever see you at a convention, it's over. This is how I'm holding
your hand. Oh, or like this because apparently you guys are absolutely humongous. So I'm just
going to hold onto your thumb. Do you just be walking around the convention?
I don't know. Got you. End with a heart. I'm, some do that, but then the fingers in the
background are in the way. So I'm, I'm all in like this. Okay. I'm all in some do this. Like it's
supposed to be the love heart from the bomb. I don't know if you can tell, but this is supposed
to be the bottom of the heart. And then it goes like, Oh, well, I ran out of room there, but you
get the point. Is there any other way of hearts? Do your middle finger if you really wanted.
I'm starting to make stars and stuff up in the touch.
Wait, that's a heart sign. This is a heart sign. It's the bottom of the heart here. So it's supposed
to be like bottom of heart and then tee tee. That's a heart sign.
You can do the hand heart. I do feel, I feel, full stack. I think there's another way to do it,
but I actually don't know. I did feel stack. I thought the thumb and the finger made the heart.
Like that? What? Like that? The thumb and the finger make the heart?
Well, no, you guys are learning how my brain is slow. It's not looking good.
But yeah. Isn't it because the two tips of the fingers form a heart? What? What are you smoking?
We've made a, we've made a, we've made a diamond.
No, the one you said was a bomb. Oh, wait, this is the love heart part. And then it like crosses
over obviously because that's how fingers work. Huh. Interlocked fingers. Yeah, you like that?
Yeah, they really do it for you. Like Flappy Bird. Oh, wait, what's that thing where
you do that and then spin it? What? Wait, hold on. I'm sure there's a thing where you spin it.
Oh, there it is. Diddy, diddy, diddy, diddy. You used to have a thing where it was like,
oh, it's a boy. Diddy, diddy, diddy. I can't remember. Can you do a shadow pop it?
Oh, wait, dogs have two eyes.
Boop, boop, boop, boop, boop, boop, boop, boop, boop, boop, boop, boop, boop, boop, boop.
Scuff dog. How else are you supposed to do it? Very big underbate. Look, he's a, he's a pug. Oh,
wait. Oh, no, that's what a dog looks like.
Boop, boop, boop, boop, boop, boop, boop, boop, boop, boop, boop.
Someone says, you're Australian chat, bro, you're about to be redirected in the
sheebie yeti-like. Yamest it. Hand shadow stream. I don't know. How would I do a rabbit?
So those are the ears. Where's its face? I don't know, how does its face feel like?
Wait. That's too hard. This is too hard for my brain. Okay, I am going to let you raid into
sheebie's pantalones. I've had a really fun hand cam stream. That's the first time I've
ever done something like this. I hope you enjoyed it too. And if I get monetized,
then you will begin something similar, not the same. Similar, not, not the same.
Similar. Okay. Similar. Yeah, you're like, I got my nails done. Did you see? You notice
it's showing off my nails? Got them dead. Okay, you loved it. Oh, I'm glad you enjoyed it. I didn't
know what to do, honestly. I was like, I don't really know what you guys want. Like,
we'll review these sweets. And now I have tons of sweets that I don't like. Do you think I could
send them to the girls and pretend that they're a cure package, but really I just don't want to
eat anything? Okay, that was so fun. Thank you so much. I'll see you all tomorrow for
oh wait, it's Elden Ring for Foostroda. And I'll teach you all the strats on how to get 100%
achievement playthrough. Whoa, is that as bad for you as it is for me when I see the preview?
My hand, like, just teleported. But I hope you enjoy my French tips. You know,
a ha ha, wee wee baguette for my, oh wait, hold on. French tips. Yeah. Thanks to the stream,
Elden Ring. That keeps saying Elden Ring. It's not Elden Ring yet. Elden Ring is the motor. No,
next week. It's Elden Scrolls. I keep getting Elden Ring and Scrolls messed up right now.
Yeah, these are French tip nails. That's what these, this is the style. They paint the white
on it, but it's like my natural nail color and everything. It's called French tip. You know why?
Because I'm French and I'm giving you the tip the night, boys. Right, enough, enough.
Sheeby's live. Please enjoy Sheeby to your heart's content. Thank you so much for watching me rate
American sweeties. Where the heck did that come from? That just flew out of nowhere. I got afraid.
I thought it was a spider. Thank you so, so much for stream. I will stop rambling because I'm
holding you up. I'm holding the line of command. Please enjoy Sheeby to all your might. I will
see you tomorrow for two endurance back-to-back streams. So get ready to strap in. If not,
I will get strapped on. See you tomorrow.