I'm going to do a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little
bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit
of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little
little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit
where's my game she's she's just she's just yelling I'm using a Zara as my
cover-up today hey let me let me let me let me let me do a little thingy how do
you do a little switchy to switchy switchy how wait give me a second wait wait I
broke it I broke it oh my god I broke it I broke it you guys say I'm the girl
failure and I'm scoff okay I got this
down I'm a genius wait no those wrong one never mind I'm just playing with my
fidget toy with this little slug one in my arms
that sounds nice keep doing it I know right I'm like this is good for ASMR I'm
like I'm gonna use this as a trigger I have never played fall guys hello
everyone I've never played fall guys Azura has but apparently she's bad I'm
trash at this game do not expect great things from me I'm absolutely dog water
so I was hoping she'd carry because you know she just like is great at every
game she touches but apparently not this one not this one but you guys have the
opportunity to play with us today yeah so I was supposed to have waited to show
the way how did I can't even show the code so I don't know how you did oh oh
it's right there on the top of the screen do you not have it on for yours no
isn't that up here for you okay I'll post it in my chat
great we're gonna have bleeding hearts and hair I'm like whoop our asses I hope
I can push people because I'd like to be able to push people to their deaths yes
you can push people but they could definitely push you back oh no I don't
even know the controls I'm I'm going in completely blind
are you alive did I lose you and I'm here okay me and Azura are very sleepy
I wanted that how many hours asleep I actually got in the past three days please
do tell four four days I mean three days yeah four hours three days four hours I
don't I can even math right now um yeah this will definitely be fun then cuz I
just woke up from a nap I think you just I don't know if you like slept at all
so I woke up two hours ago there you go there you have it I'm drinking a lemonade
that has like a shot of energy in it I believe it's called a very blast from a
local joy so I'm excited excuse me so sorry excuse me that damn mouse again
has gotten in my house it keeps keep phrasing its voice how many people can
be in a lobby I think 60 what the frick excuse me I'm so sorry I gotta put it
me it up she like cold off my sweatshirt I'm actually sweating anyway my
lower region is hot my upper region is hot
I can't take her like wow oh my god guys I'm stuck maybe I should take off my
headphones first hold on a second Azura don't say anything bad my headphones are
off I could hear that from my headphones while they were on my table
all right so hi chat I didn't say hi to you guys I'm sorry I'm gonna pull your
chat open to actually I was just reading it but I didn't say hi I'm sorry oh yeah
I could pull yours up too I know let me grab yours as well
oh no I can see both of you haha you could always you could do a pop-out
window like a pop-out a pop-out rascally wabbits wait right am I done I think I'm
on what did you do oh here we go I'm okay we are doing just fine thank you yeah now
there's two two cats now there's two mommies there's two chat look at your
because you don't oh my god she's
He's regressing.
Oh, I just took a twat.
And I took a twat.
Hi, twat!
Hi, everybody! Hi, twat!
Hi!
And last, your favorite, um, little sisters.
I don't want them to see me.
Hi!
I see me!
Why does my dog?
We should totally hijack.
I see it in me smiles!
That would be too funny.
Oh.
We could be cute and funny.
Yeah.
Alright.
Shall we wait for like, how many people?
people. Oh, no, as many as as as I can get in here since we did kind of tell them very
late that we were going to play with. That's a good point. Oh, I should tweet that on live.
Oh, I forgot to do that too. I always forget to tweet that on live. My manchurian in your
tweet. Come play with us. How we enjoying download the game if you don't have the game.
If you don't have room for it on your computer, delete something. Delete it. Delete it.
All of that porn off. You don't need it. You have us. It's fine. Delete it. Get that
terabyte of porn off your computer to download this game, please. Okay, let me hear you.
Don. Don. Don. Don. Don. Don. Don. Don. Don. Don. Don. Don. Don. Don. Don. Don. Don. Don. Don. Don. Don. Don. Don. Don. Don. Don. Don. Don. Don. Don. Don. Don. Don. Don. Don. Don. Don. Don. Don. Don. Don. Don. Don. Don. Don. Don. Don. Don. Don. Don. Don. Don. Don. Don. Don. Don. Don. Don. Don. Don. Don. Don. Don. Don. Don. Don. Don. Don. Don. Don. Don. Don. Don. Don. Don. Don. Don. Don. Don. Don. Don. Don. Don. Don. Don. Don. Don. Don. Don. Don. Don. Don. Don. Don. Don. Don. Don. Don. Don. Don. Don. Don. Don. Don. Don. Don. Don. Don. Don. Don. Don. Don
Don. Don. Don. Don. Don. Don. Don.
And my boy that's not for you.
really.
classify them like you.
Imagine. Imagine. No fairious.
Imagine. Imagine. Imaginate me.
Imagine. Imagine. Imagine that
imagine. Imagine that forever as
It's like a lot of fun.
Ah!
Sib is dead.
No!
I'm dead?
It was just the screaming you did, and then the boom.
I just go quiet.
Ah!
OK, I'm going to say 25 people will try to get in.
That's the goal.
A lot of some people said they were downloading the game now
in my chat.
Oh, OK.
Then, yeah, we'll do more than that then.
Maybe pin the message for the code.
I was thinking that, but once we start, yeah, it's going to get
to work in.
Like nobody's going to be able to get in for like a long.
Can you even join when?
Can you join while a game is already in motion?
Let's try it.
Is that possible?
Maybe you can join and queue up in a lobby later.
Download!
Where did I even drop?
Download for guys now and play with us.
It's all in caps.
Five and I can't see the.
Just copy, paste it.
Can you?
I don't think you can.
I just copied and pasted it from when you messaged me the code.
Oh, my brain.
Oh, my God.
Is there a longer than me sometimes?
I like that it compresses your screams and you just get real quiet.
Well, I can help you fix that.
I fixed mine.
No, I meant in our call.
Yeah, I can help you fix that.
It's mine.
It used to, and it was very annoying.
Wait, I have all the settings trying that for that off.
No, I think it's a different kind of setting that you could actually fix.
I think I know which one you're talking about.
What is it?
It's, it's either your.
Oh, my God.
The words left me.
Window settings.
Yes.
Yeah.
Oh.
How do you pin messages?
You press the three dots and click pin message.
Just hover to the right of it.
Okay.
I'm in system settings.
System window settings.
Mother guide me.
Oh God.
I was unprepared.
It's under sound.
Yeah.
Well, you got a, you know, the little gear thingy on this,
on the bottom right of your, like on the, the task manager.
And the thing that looks like a, like a volume, like the sound button
thingy.
Oh, is it in the sound mixer?
Yeah.
Yes.
Not mixer.
The other one.
Oh, I think I know what you're talking about.
Found it.
It's like a whole thing though.
So maybe you might have to.
Yeah.
You got to advance and then you have to make sure that everything is at 100.
And then you have to go back to your focus.
Right.
Then you've got to turn yourself down.
Turn it.
I'm not doing all that.
That's too much work.
Yeah.
Like you should probably do it later.
I know we're waiting for people, but like that, that's, that's too much work.
And I didn't do it all day.
It took me forever.
It took me how many days?
Like a couple of days to get it right.
Yeah.
It took a couple of days.
I can't, I couldn't.
Oh, okay.
Yeah.
Just like that.
I just just, I can, I couldn't, uh-oh, uh-oh.
What did you do?
It's fine.
How did you bring a microphone?
What's happening?
This deserve need to be turned up.
Anybody a sound good on my end?
I'm stretching behind mom.
Really?
Yeah.
drifted away sounds fine okay cool here i hear what is that i heard just a weirdest noise
what was it wait speak hello i'm speaking your goddess here your fertility goddess
okay i think i might be the game sound
yeah my mic fell fell my mic stand came off the desk
i fell i'm just falling so i had to fix it
okay you know i'll put the join code in my on my twitter as well as those
oh yeah i forgot to do that again did you not tweet no oh no you're like me you type it out and
then you get distracted and then you just um
okay yeah yeah retweet it i'll just retweet it
wait could we make is i hope there's not like there's not voice chat on right or party chat
it should be automatically off okay cool i think i think you oh i hope i hope not find out if
people are screaming no more words so
what if they say the bad words what if they say bad bad things and then i am pressing
ed broadcast immediately that's what i'm doing stream over stream over goodbye everyone and then
i will just cut the half the part that was said from the timestamp and you'll eat it into the sun
xbox gave richette i'm gonna say a swear frick
yeah i feel like i feel like bleeding hearts you can't swear at zara like you can only like
excuse me i feel like they would have they like feel like they have to be really proper
and like they'll make up like the silly fake swears
surprisingly my chat has been very good they're very yeah i think your chat is the most
highly caved out of everybody's i don't think anyone's really gotten like like hit like with
anything like time out much or anything at all i think those in these ices mine strawneys
mercies and yours yeah
by the goddess how do you behave you behave all you behave like you know like dogs like trash
you know i don't know what else you want me to say yeah you yeah you you you wine
you know sometimes you show your teeth and i have to you know put you outside for your
your misbehavior aka time you out
but uh
hey wait i behave hopefully yeah i bring you out from you know behind the shed
sorry i gotta put you out of your misery
well aren't you just the sweetest boy tipped one dollar america you're laughing face
america you're america you're america you're america you're trying to do my best shy
why you're so cute
hi no i can't do i'm still working on that
like you'll be a very quick quick
hello i need to listen to her voice
hello
she's just as there is being japanese
as there i can you speak some dutch for everyone no
no
oh my god why why i want to hear your beautiful dutch
i'm still learning and i'm i'm trash i can't really say like a lot of sentences full on right
off the top of my head all to say like hi how are you
you
i did if i if i had known because you put dutch in your in your debut as one of the languages
you spoke i would have put tanish french jammies and i literally didn't i did not put it in my
debut go back in the video and you'll see i only put english and then i mentioned that i am learning
dutch in japan you was that in the in the moxon i can't remember or maybe i'm gonna use no all of
it i have never put any other ones because i knew i knew someone was gonna be like ah you speak
it fluently then like that's why i didn't put it i am not fluent french or spanish either
my rest of my family speaks french too but i don't speak french i don't i just because i understand
it and sometimes and so doesn't mean i speak it so i don't put it
how are you
the one alert to be you
i'm your aftercare apparently
i'm your aftercare what
i
every time i go to speak spanish i end up speaking french though i only know how to like
ask what you want to buy in spanish and then my colors and then i can understand a little bit
you
you do not like french cb i can be french for you
hot
let me let me move this fan over here french made chibi oh that'd be a good asmr actually
i'm i'm i'm stuck around the back of my head
i
did you get hit with copyright because you sing yeah just just random songs
they're not even of the like the people that actually do copyright the song that don't belong
to those people it's fake i know that's so dumb
jesus i i used to i would also sing a lot like when i streamed on twitch i don't know i said
twitch like i'm
yeah i sung like a lot on twitch my favorite thing to do and i would play music too oh my god i'm
gonna do your mod job for them but the thing on twitch is that you could uh what is it what do
you do uh you could separate the audio like the complete audio so that when you should go live
on twitch they can't hear uh the music at all but they can hear the music when you're live
but it doesn't stay in the vod so the vod doesn't get muted yeah yeah the whole freaking vod gets
muted yeah so i can't do that on youtube are you allowed to join yes you're allowed to join you
think we just have 42 friends with us so i'm not used to uh not singing
um i gotta use for me i kept demonetized um because of because of my boobs so
and lily i just smacked so much like stronti was showing me her um monetization versus mine
and i was just like holy i was like ineligible ineligible ineligible copyright ineligible
limited ads limited ads limited and i was like but then i changed thumbnails and stuff
and i um i appealed a bunch and thankfully i was able to
i wonder if i'll get i wonder if i'll get hit with that after probably yeah like you've been
doing the right thing with the the bread you have to cover your whole boob crack
i mean if i you i change it to the bobo tea you change it to bobo tea oh that's funny i have i
just have the sign in front of my boobs and then you um yeah because it like it did make a difference
if i didn't cover it all the way if the boob boob thing was still there but hey i think we'll be
getting cover-ups anyways so very soon i cannot wait i know yay i can button my shirt and maybe i
can pop a button that'd be cool cool toggle oh i thought you just love bread yeah she loves
bread so much she's stuck it in between her boobs i love bread really man it's the best thing that's
why i chose it i need uh my son to cut out a picture of the harem um so i could stick it on
my boobs just have you guys just wedged in between as a cover-up
it's just funny how much the algorithm has changed because like evident by azura's song covering
pewdie pie uh boobs in the thumbnail that used to be such a main like thing like you everybody
i struggled so hard singing that song really i had to do so many retakes because i could not
stop laughing like i would say i would laugh i would sing it i would laugh and it ended with
me having to sing monotone because if i didn't sing monotone i would laugh i know like people
were like why do you sound like you're singing because you're trying not to wake up your parents
i'm like because i yeah i also couldn't take it seriously and i'm not a good singer so
so that's why i'm like and it's so hard to match up it's a hard to match a pitch of someone who
also can't sing yeah that's the like yeah pretty can't sing right william johnson can't sing like i
can cover i could probably like the next song i'm probably gonna cover is like stacey's mom
which i'll be able to sing because there's actual flow and yeah in most of the lines that that were
put in the song it's literally a few words mashed mashed together and i have a list so pewdie pie's
accent and my list did not mesh well i thought it really was good though i thought yours yours and
strongies were actually i like all of her things like i did a lot takes for mine and i was going
insane listening to the song over and over and over again um and then yeah i was i didn't even
like sent me the edited version i'm like yeah great because i was i'm like it's probably
cringey as hell i'm not listening to this i don't want to hear myself
um it was fun though a really fun experience yeah i like because of that i now i know what's
involved i really want to try harder and do a better cover you want to do what with me
what song i don't know that'd be cool though i don't know what i don't know what we could do
can you have a bunch of songs already on list that i want to do for covers
okay i have a big list yeah a little bit yeah a little bit i'm like i'm trying to think
a little bit it can't be like hard rap like like extremely like
i'm not i'm not i don't want to
well what song would you think um you sounded like you didn't want to be there
what's my song what song would you guys want us to cover little john we just do yeah
a little john is on the venue
in the club with my homies and then it's just
shots
yeah
i think it would be cool if we um did like an english cover of like i was like
like it's ears even singing i was like uh actually no i feel like i feel like k-pop
girlies will come for us because i was gonna say a k-pop song um i think because just because
you just find a girl group of six and just pick a person and do the lines flow right up
shawty got the apple bottom oh i'm gonna put a karaoke for next week
shawty got the baggy pants and the rebox with the strap okay we're gonna get
we're gonna get we're gonna get copyrighted you gotta do the cooking by the book
break it down bitch let me see you back it up
over 50 players
oh wow the number i was not looking at the number it went up yes it did ma'am we're just we're just
enjoying ourselves yeah so i could be can do like the stephanie portion and then i can do the
little john portion that would be pretty funny it's a piece of cake to bake a pretty cake yeah
she could do the high voices there are i can yeah i come no she can i can when we were like doing
little cutesy voices earlier uh which one right here i can do this
voice
backstreet boys that'd be good
everybody
yeah rock your body
yeah everybody rock your body right
be a lurks back all right
copyrighted
gotta get smited yeah
i feel like dying
do some parody songs i have one idea for a parody song i've already rinsed some lyrics i'm very excited
all right are we literally waiting for 60 people somebody just left they just
oh they came back
all right we could do like a like a like a countdown yeah like a countdown yeah like a
countdown like like a countdown
all right do you want to redoing it by what number
uh i don't know it just want to do 10 10 seconds we could do missus hippies
yeah but we're probably gonna both see mississippi differently how do you say mississippi
mississippi one mississippi two mississippi okay we'll do down from 10 then ready
yeah 10 join the game right now if you don't join the game this is it for you
i'm gonna count down right now we're gonna count down i'm ready ready ready
ten missus hippie nine missus hippie
why is it like not it is it like we're not in sync because you're like really
me oh we're in sync for me okay okay ten missus hippie nine miss nine missus hippie
eight missus eight missus hippie
are you from mississippi because you're only miss who's piss i'd sippy
um
what number were we on
seven seven missus hippie
four missus hippie
three missus hippie
two missus hippie
one missus hippie
zero
i was playing with my fidget toy just like okay
okay let's let's play i'm ready yay okay now how do you it's been 40 minutes you don't know how to
stop
hey
who the fuck is moaning rabbit
games like this
games i'm falling out of my chair wait how do you do like all of it like a random like a
like a mix i don't know
okay i'm gonna go to the bathroom while you figure this out uh i'm muting for
stream but is there i apologize if you can hear me pee
no apologies here
listening listening listening
yeah
you
It says 59 out of 40, though.
Can the still 59 people still join or is that like bad?
I'm back. I thought 60 people can play.
Wait, what the heck? Who just...
Aw, thank you for the 20 gifted!
Thank you so much, both of you!
W! W in the chat! W! W in the chat! W! W in the chat! W! W in the chat!
That's right!
Did she start? No, she didn't start it.
Yeah, say your thank yous. Say your thank yous.
Aw, that's such a sweetie. Thank you, Paul.
I don't... I don't... I don't... I feel kind of bad now.
Why do you feel bad?
Solo is only 40.
Oh, fuck.
Not 60.
Aw...
Wait, then what's the other... We could do the groups, then. It's fine.
No, no, no, no, no. The groups is group 60.
Do... Wait.
I think we could just... We could just take turns, right?
We could take turns.
If Solo's is only 40, why would it let us do 60 people?
I don't know. Maybe because I didn't choose the king, but I don't know. I don't know.
I don't know! Don't quote me! Don't quote me!
Maybe we could... Maybe we could... Maybe we could...
Like, after we finish, right? After we finish. After we finish.
We could restart the lobby, and they could all rejoin again.
And it's...
First come, first serve, right? First come, first serve.
It's first... Yeah, yeah, but the first come, first serve, we just gotta start it.
It's whoever gets in in this one.
We don't... We don't know who's gonna be in this one.
We don't know! We don't know!
We don't know!
Do what... Do what you must. Do what you must. Do what must be done.
It has almost been an hour.
We're fine. We're having a good time.
Sure. I usually gap for this amount of time, so we're good.
I usually gap for the longer.
That's the longest or the waiting period. Someone just said...
Alright, let's go. How do you start now?
Too many players. Oh no.
No! There's no way!
No!
What is happening?
Horror!
No!
What is happening?
Horror!
No!
They left me with the responsibility of having to kick people.
I don't want to do it.
Do what you must. Destroy them. Kill the younglings.
No.
No!
Mod, when you have to time somebody out several times and they're not taking the hint...
That's when you put the user in time out for 24 hours, okay?
Yeah, yeah, and please do that.
And please leave.
Because I don't know why.
What's happened there, baby cakes?
I'm talking to Azura is not mine for the Republic do it execute order 66
execute order 69 do it how about we just restart the lobby then we start the lobby
okay message me the code when you're ready wait you gotta hide ties your game as well
don't jump in before I get a true true true true how do you hide the game fuck you want me
to do no I got it I got it I got this that's more see look at that bam bam boom boom
Bambi boom boom boom Bambi boom boom boom boom goddess boom boom ha ha ha diara
ara ba ba ba zero so smart she's she's uh what do they what do they say they
she's wicked smart kids she's wicked smart yeah there you go now you join okay
all right time to update the thingy mabobber the thingy mabobber thingy mabobber
did you join yes oh oh you oh you changed the code I was like we're these people
coming from we're these people coming from yeah I guess I just pasted it I'm
like wait there's no point in hiding my game now that I'm going to be jumping in
there just cold now and then I pin this one yeah yeah wait there's too many people
again okay I'm gonna have to blindly just remove people okay
I close my eyes I just left I literally left I could join right now it's fine oh it's already
a maximum capacity somebody else out so I can join eight people have to leave eight
people eight people eight people come on why did you leave because I thought you're just
gonna remake the lobby before it's so sweet oh okay you get it you get a smooch for that
I still can't get in though so it's going down slowly okay I'm in I'm in respect thank
you thank you guys my heart everybody everybody gets gets a
membership you get a membership you get a membership you get a membership all right
for the last person come back in here have we all last person I'm about to start the games
we can finally start the point of the game is to get from point A to point B yes I know
that much of it controls I'll start it oh which one am I why do some of you look so you're
green what the heck are you going so for this one you just don't fall oh okay how do I okay I'm good I'm
golden okay okay you're gold I'm green this is fun I'm enjoying myself oh shit oh no okay we're
chilling big chilling narrowly escaped that one how do you jump okay that's how you jump you can
dive oh no okay I'm good good okay I'm good I'm like I don't want to be out in the first five
seconds oh wait you can just just keep running forward oh I took a point oh and then you can
jump am I gonna oh okay oh I can't jump that though
I'm scared we got this dude we got Kavulu we got a panhead we got this guy oh he's trying
I can't believe I died on the first level I don't I'm so upset I went for a jump that I
shouldn't have well enjoy guys I'll be over here oh shit this whole time I didn't have game audio I
just noticed now there's game audio
game audio see this looks so fun if only I could play all right coming out of the gate we have
love emmy bsu tailing the front oh wait how do I I wish I could get to the person the front
Vapa jumping up struggling just a little bit joyful Prince narrowly missing some balls like I did
what morning rabbit bringing up oh getting knocked to the side almost eliminated can't seem to
climb back up they are struggling crunchy killer being followed by Cthulhu took a shortcut very smart
Pentium going over oh it he falls poor Pentium Pentium struggling he's about to fall into the
slide I don't think he's gonna make it folks oh he died for it he got it look understand I
literally said under she beats post if there was a game that I'm bad at it's this one snowy
tour it was a game I'm bad at it's this one we already have four winners at the front super
rad man getting blown off almost off course completely he is so close trailing the edge
trying to avoid those donut ring things no step ease enjoyer getting launched back
Mako Tom chill sitting pretty with Cthulhu doing little victory dances Sarangyeh
Penton it making it and there you have it folks only three people
really only 13 13 they just they just waited at the end free and then Dudby and fan
shout casting let's go I used to want to be a CS go shoutcaster I thought she be was a gamer
platforming is literally my worst enemy blight town and lies of pee I wanted to not I wanted to
unalive tail tag this is cute everybody has their plugs at the ready love Amy B Sue is off
ooh snowy with the tail I don't know why the camera okay that's weird clapper heading towards
the center getting knocked by a hammer melting link searching for a tail to grab
super rad man hiding out by the side nobody seems to have noticed him yet oh he has two
eyes on him oh he's fine nope they didn't even notice oh wait they also have a tail super
man just chilling out doing some great exercises get those calisthenics in
Cthulhu struggling just lost their tail getting tap a tensile getting their tail yoinks that
butt plug was just ripped from their asshole that got her that's got her folks if you didn't
want to live during my speed we're a butt plug today and play fall guys we are sponsored by Adam
and Eve use code allure to get 15% off of all your butt plug needs I'm kidding that's fake
that's the fake sponsor wait what only works on bunny tails yep I never actually never I'm
gonna we are down to our final one two I can't really tell I can't count I didn't see
I think this is the finals yeah oh how many people are left like a seven or nine maybe
one two three four five six yeah well six people okay so people just died love Amy Bees you
start trying to stay afloat avoiding any sort of yellow hexagons oh super rad man still in this
let's go and Lord be the BDA big way I know yeah I don't know what that is like yeah is my sweat
clappers Lord Bada struggling trying to do some sort of strat almost I don't know how the heck
they just they should I feel like they should have died there what the hell staying to the edge
somehow I'm having a good strap Makatum on the edge of glory already got eliminated yep love Amy
Beesu oh running out of running out of of hexagons narrowly oh notorious BSG still kicking hanging
out with Makatum these two have been thick as thieves as seen from the last one oh amazingly
both missing the gaps also missing the gaps are down to our final three who is going to win
oh sweat clapper is running out of hexes oh almost oh they're trying to land on each other's
hexes to knock the other ones off it's quite an impressive strat is our however Makatum is
hanging out by the edge again oh is it oh is it from Makatum oh sweat clapper we lost sweat clapper
fucks Makatum is the winner good job what the fuck where do they just go to oh there I watched another
pen tie to see where this is going oh okay nevermind gg's gg don't read it's a code so same yes I think so
this let's remake the lobby and see who joins oh yeah people chance yeah you people turn now that
we're not an equal without the little bit I'll hide I'll hide the game I feel like more hair
members got him hopefully that could stay in longer why you don't like my shout casting
are you doing that with your finger no with my tongue oh why
can I please have a cold man
bum bum bum sleepyhead sleepyhead sleepyhead sleepyhead sleepyhead sleepyhead sleepyhead
sleepyhead sleepyhead sleepyhead sleepyhead sleepyhead sleepyhead sleepyhead sleepyhead satisfied
literally literally literally literally.
We release at, that's three. Okay. At three, at three.
What about a tree?
We release at three.
We're releasing at three.
yeah the code okay I'm gonna show it on screen first and then I'll type it in I'm
lazy typing it in though
ready tree I mean at tree okay now I'm three I'm ready I'm right now the
three and then I'm gonna type it in musty yours I'll copy your text
oh no no no please stop joining please I'm sorry please please please I don't
do the game please I'm sorry please leave leave I'm so sorry it doesn't sound like
quicker shells yep yep she's a best streamer NA I agree
get out just kidding if you've already played please consider leaving before
we are okay we're good hurry okay nobody nobody gets it slide down the
troll what I'm terrified she's so lower accurate my chat crashed they say
there once that I'm not ready mom oh wait how do I slide guys how do I see you use
press your mouse a button you're right click I think well I'm not using
controller oh I'm gonna lose okay that was fun this has been great
I don't know what you're talking about what do I have I don't have anything
I died so I did not survive I was not slippery enough Epson chat thank you I'm
gonna find Azura and and shoutcast over Azura how do I I need to make a new pop
out chat my tab broke literally says can't open this page and it doesn't let
me refresh it see what I like on this one this might have been easier for me
one of them who the fuck is Squidward okay let me find hair oh there she is
Azura in a big group getting smacked getting smacked again jumping she's doing
it folks in the middle of the pack doing well got a climb up oh wonderful
amazing form having to now navigate around these fans she gets bought
she's going the longer way an interesting strat however it might pay off for her if
she doesn't get bonked she's doing it oh oh barely dodging that little bonker
stick she made it folks seventh place incredible what a gamer she's an actual
pro Azura do lay more like Azura gaming more like signer to liquid
hey let me fix this chat everybody's very proud of you Azura do slay the
gasified version of you Azura do slay I hate this one oh this is great oh don't
fall into the slime cookie gonna put my gamer gamer mate my gamer face on okay
ready whoa like one at the top you can't even see those oh my god this thing
is stuff is being chucked at them the board is tilting side to side Azura is
trying to stay on in the middle for safety but these planets are just coming
out of left field oh oh she was taken out almost made it so sad
good job what are you doing step galaxy it was a good effort folks but not a
great god damn someone get by controlling I like how they're beans that's cute
eat them roll out eat them oh it's delicious oh yeah yeah how would you eat
them yeah you know put them on a ball okay big ball and then you put some milk
with the beans yeah okay okay all right you scoop them up and then what and then you fucking eat them how
would you eat them okay and then how would you finish it off and then I'll
hmm all of it like a good girl yeah I hope people are listening while they're playing and then just
I think we killed a couple of people because of that oh my god I'm dead
oh cute little banana cat thing what the hell
I like your skin there's no I like looking at them
it looks like a vibrator though Soros looks like a bullet vibrator
I think the cat the cat banana skin is my favorite oh of course it's sweat clap
oh that's a giant strawberry
what
gobbledy's nuts Squidward bear Squidward tennis balls uh huh uh huh
that's the most hard to look hard got clarded by a giant fruit what the fuck is clarded
me that's a new word I'll use that thumbs fun clardin get clardin
get clardin be honest did you die because of our amazing
of there's amazing talk amazing you got clardin on eating beans tactic
you got the squidward
flopjack is in the cardboard box whistle thing or bullet or whatever you are
go go go you got it
if you like your hexes come back go cool I don't know Vegeta oh I don't know
is that the wukong hair looks like wukong's hair wukong wukong
is that the wukong go go go burger with a burger on your head go I want to eat it
I'm gonna eat the burger oh it looks so good gonna eat it hard hard go banana cat go you got this
whoa banana cat
whoa uh cracking cracking dragon like a dragon but you're cracking dragon cracking I don't know
no you got this whoa
I can't even show cast because I think Azura is doing a better job than I could
oh box man yeah
it's bullet and banana cat go banana go bullet go bullet go bullet go bullet vibe you got this
bullet vibe oh no this is it oh no banana cat is disqualified eliminated destroyed
the bullet vibe has won everybody let's do a celebratory
gg gg gg boys
you don't suck you're fine look at look at me I literally die the first round each time you're fine
do it do it everybody come and join there's a chance I don't have to make another lobby
because 20 people there is the code is up in our pinned thingies it's the same code
that we tweeted out because oh I put it in the main tweet so I can't really delete
you
only time I ever played be she be both times are you really that proud of that how dare you
and don't hit the wrong way because this word has multiple conversations but do you know what's
scatting is
not the not the bad version I mean like the like the scab would have to do with the
dab but did you do that that's scabby do this can't be getting I'm not really a part of my
boat but my cheek really hard I'm a scott man
guys don't look at me like that
oh
did you press play no oh my god
I started it I started the game big fail great great I thought of that I'm gonna die
do I get a head pat mama yes you do such a good girl here's your head pat
how do you guys oh I'm so scared oh god okay I got this
no someone stepped on my head you got this come on she be you got this you're fine you're good
you're gonna run along the edge you're gonna whoo nice you're golden you're golden
you're doing it uh we're gonna go this way frick we're gonna go this way
we made it we made it
oh what the heck oh I didn't know you could
oh this is a lot easier oh let's go
almost made it we're almost there
whoo
I did it
I fucking did it oh my god the guys are
omogas the hell
I'm proud of myself
hey yeah yeah let's go we all made it I made it I'm amazing let's go I'm so good I'm so good
yeah yeah what's this navigate the obstacles and raise two laps around the course okay fine
this sounds fun oh it's the race it's a race I'm bad at this let's go okay do you is there a run button
w oh I don't know a controller okay I'll figure it out I don't know I think you just press you just
use your what do you call it joystick joystick yeah those stickies yeah what the hell is this course
I did you two laps of this yeah and I'm really bad at this so I'm probably gonna lose
probably not gonna make it bouncy as hell somebody just pushed me don't be a fucking dick it pushed me
oh
oh we're doing it oh we're fucking doing it bros oh we're fucking we're out here
we are doing that shit why am I moving so slow
oh well oh I'm not gonna step on that
there we go there we go it's okay oh shit it's fine move ahead oh Jesus fuck
I don't know how I survived that
out of my way out of my way I have three green dudes coming up behind me and I'm scared
oh
I'm gaming oh oh Jesus fuck oh shit oh no I'm stuck oh no I can't stop spinning
can you come
I'm stuck okay I did it
oh I'm sorry it's very front of me
we're almost there you're a combined we're almost there
oh
that's fucked go that's fucked guys that's fucked you get you I'm retracting my kiss from earlier for that
I can't believe you I can't believe done this
run from the fan
wish you'd be still alive yeah I am somehow okay I'm fine again ow
oh
she died never mind I think I passed her no I never made it sir she died oh fuck uh
it's like jump rope it's like jump rope it's like jump rope it's like jump rope it's fine
where is she oh there she is I'm in the back madame shibir that's me you want it only
oh look at the reflexes look at those reflexes
oh
oh it was the last person to die too oh fuck if I just held on a little bit longer
you were doing it just wait when we play mario car I'm wiping all of you it's all I'm gonna say
no I just noticed my starting BGM is still on
I got fucking yeeted the big scuff is real
you put up a nice fight shibir sir thank you thank you appreciate it
I just died at the last second it's you can empty-headed hair um demon demon demo pan
um sleepy phoenix getting hit by some balls balls to his face
yeah sweat clapper is zooming he is a pro fiorios that's an interesting name I like that fiorios
red sky kai notorious bsg of bogus okay so empty-headed very relatable
they willing no and yeah that's everyone that's in this one you guys got this I believe in you
I believe in you
the disrespect in my dono thank you joker my god damn
j willy nox that's a that's a name
willing nox turn your monitor on
fucking audacity oh uh j willy nox you are not doing so hot bud
willing nox you got this day willing nox I believe in you these two these two dicks at the end
waiting to take their spots
god is oh rip rip oh they're actually types of fall guys are downstairs one for action one for the names
yep uh azur just says the names and I do the
yeah he made it they willing nox made it congratulations uh you did so good everyone did so good banana
cows in your pool what is this place I like it yes yes yes it's like high-pitched domain
I was born in a darkness you barely adopted it you barely adopted it
raised
I literally just moved my controller like I was playing
let's go hair up with this weird eyes wonder why would you pick that
what is this I like this viking one I like the yellow oh that was lucky yellow on these
I like the yellow underpants with the horse on it
I like the beard I want to braid it I like I like to think that soup can who just has little arm cuffs on
it's just like shackled and I feel like they are a harem fan and they're just like shackled to me
rest in peace harem harem just died oh how could you do this rest in peace says
I would just stay in one of those things his butt and be fine
oh
and then they just oh someone just got yeeted
now let's fill in the house
who's still in the gaming who's still in the gaming where's it seven left
in the gaming
I
kind of want some toast craving some Nutella peanut butter toast
I want you want some one toast yeah
yeah
no no toast toast
there's slathered some peanut butter Nutella on Azura's toes gobbler toes up this is the same thing but with ice
I
let's go sweat clapper let's go notorious let's go furious
empty headed empty headed okay
I would make some toast keep keep them occupied
oh
Nah-Nah-Nah-Nah-Nah-Nah-Nah-Nah-Nah-Nah-Nah-Nah-Nah
okay
Yeah, I have a poster, so I don't worry about this like there it is.
JJ! JJ!
Are we taking our food break?
We're taking our food break.
Food break!
I'm hungry too.
Snackin', yeah.
Mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm, mm.
Haha.
I'm great, I'm great.
I think don't worry about me
It's not my fault. It's like a catchy little jingle be
Then I got the bass in the background
No
I
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry
I'm going to grab a snack
I'm going to grab a snack, I'm going to grab a snack. Should I grab one now or should I
wait?
I'll be back!
I'm so good!
Yes!
We're good!
Alright, what's up bitches? I'm taking over stream.
You should be scared. You should be very scared.
I got toast. I got some peanut butter and Nutella toast.
Usually I put some banana on it, but I don't have any banana.
I kept hearing about how people see her as mommy and all, but one of the first strings.
I went a person involved or being concerned about our new toaster.
Yes, Azur is cute as fuck.
All the girls have quite a bit of Gatbo.
Moe, sorry.
Nutella? Yeah, it's like a hazelnut spread.
Yeah, she's a cutesy, caring type, and then I'm the Sundari type.
Sundari, but you actually hate us. I don't hate you guys.
Don't say that.
Maybe. I don't know.
I just think about it.
Sundari, but you actually beat us to death.
Yes, let me beat the shit out of you.
Azur has got Meow.
I'll see myself out.
Meow way.
Oh, that was good.
Hate us affectionately.
Yeah, I gotta keep you guessing, guys.
I'm gonna sacrifice myself so Azur gets to the final round.
I don't know what she's getting as a snack.
I feel like she's getting some sort of fruit or crackers.
Or toast. She just burns her toast.
Eating animation under her mouth. It's actually just my mouth tracking.
I promise you, I don't chew with my mouth open, but like the model tracking picks it up as I'm just like being like.
I'm making rice ball.
You're making a rice ball?
Yeah.
That's not a snack. That's a whole ass rice ball.
How are you making it?
With salt?
No, but like rice balls are different in different places, but like what type of rice ball are you making?
I was like, for me, a rice ball, I think of Italian rice balls, but you're probably doing like a Japanese rice ball.
Most likely Japanese, just how I do a rice ball.
Yeah, but I don't have anything to put in it.
So you're literally just eating a ball of rice.
Yeah.
I try to look for something to put in it and I like set it up to put something in it.
And then I was like, I am, let me put something in it and then I don't have anything.
I could have put tuna in it, but then I would have to go get it.
Yeah.
I was going to say like, oh, do you have any tuna, like canned tuna and put some mayo in it or something.
Rice ball filled with air.
No, no cheese.
No meat.
My fridge is so empty.
So does mine.
I desperately need to go grocery shopping, but I'm just way too lazy.
Same.
Too much of an effort to get ready just to go to the grocery store.
Oh my God.
That's very relatable.
Let me go wash my hands.
I did this without a glove.
Gasp.
She wouldn't wrong.
Oh.
Reminds me of this one Chinese mythology I learned.
Basically the lead girl was supposed to slay a dragon.
She set up rice balls.
So dragon would be like, dude, snacks.
Rice is the best snack.
All right.
I don't, I think, I think I have some like Jasmine rice.
I'm chewing.
No glove.
Extra love.
Yeah, I love biryani rice.
Oh no.
I broke this.
That's not good.
My salt, the opening of my salt, it can only open one way.
It's completely broken.
How does that happen?
I don't know.
I think I stepped on it.
How did you step on it?
I don't know.
I'm lazy and I never put things back on the top of my fridge
and they end up on the floor.
Damn, bitch.
You live like this.
I literally have my toaster on the floor.
Why is your toaster on the floor?
I have nowhere to put it.
You don't have an outer.
We'll put it on.
Do you need to clean off your counter?
If anyone can see how cluttered my room looks, you'd be appalled.
I can't even look at my TV.
There's like things in front of it blocking it.
Things hanging off of the TV.
It's a little bit better but the little bit of clutter that's at my house,
I mostly picked up yesterday.
Squalor core, mama.
I literally just called you squalor core.
As there is a true knee, 100%.
It's true.
Want to hear my bag of bottles?
Please.
Kikimori azu.
Kikimori knee azu.
Can you hear that?
Can you hear this?
Do it again?
Do you just have a bag of piss bottles?
What? No!
Someone asked, do you have a piss drawer?
No.
Pretty sure Emmy has a piss drawer.
I wouldn't be surprised.
Yeah, your chat is not used to me.
They're just like, what?
Yeah, I'm used to this.
Don't worry.
I'm unfazed.
I don't want to hear these allegations.
Okay.
I told you guys, literally, there aren't debuts.
Did I not say that because the outrageous thing?
I'm sorry.
I'm just blunt.
I said it in my debut.
You were warned.
I became used to it.
The girls have been desensitized.
You should see our group chat.
We have a memes channel.
Although, is there going to be sending some very interesting memes in our memes channel?
I'm just going to say that.
Don't out me.
Don't expose me.
Don't expose me like that.
Should we increase the shot quality?
Okay.
Hold on.
I have to think of something inflammatory to say.
Bush did nine.
No.
This is a miss.
See me.
What the fuck?
I don't know.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Everything's fine.
If you don't know me, if you are unused to me, my content and how I roll, just watch
either my bunny garden play through or my class of 09 play through the first one.
Because those got demonetized for reasons, but they were so worth it.
I don't understand how you got monetized before me.
I don't either.
I don't think YouTube likes brown people.
I mean, for those who don't know, I am brown.
I am brown.
My birthday.
My family.
My family is brown.
I am brown.
music and I'm like why would they why would I get copyrighted on that so I
disputed it because that's fucking stupid it isn't fair it isn't fair and they
can't dispute the copyright strikes because they're the scammers yeah so
all you can do is like mute it and wait mute wait and hopefully YouTube will
like hit them for for being for faking up copyright yeah so even though Azura
doesn't have memberships open isn't monetized yet you could still support
her by once a month giving five dollars on her patreon and through stream
elements yes by her bird you know come support me please Azura's info is in
the description below please go to our channel like comment subscribe smash her
to giant brown like buttons
yeah you gotta ring her bell to make sure you ring her bell yeah do that
I have so many plates in here I got my bed frame in and I because I've been
sleeping on a mattress on my floor in my apartment for like almost two years now
and we've just like me and my cats in my bed and so I have to go downstairs bring
up this go to the mailroom bring up go up several flights thankfully we have an
elevator and then I don't know how I'm gonna move my mattress and then build
the thing and then put the mattress on top of my bed it is so f**king heavy
it's a lot of work just just the mattress on the floor and it's not good to have a
mattress on the floor because the moisture in this like the heat from your
body could f**k it because the floor is carpeted oh you have carpet I only I
never had a mattress before that I didn't have a mattress before that so I
slept on my floor and I don't have carpet oh ow did you have like a hole or
something no I just slept on a sheet and a blanket oh
somebody buy her a bed well get her out of her house right now she needs her own
place I have a bed now one of my family members lent me a mattress yeah but you
need a they lent it to you do they have to give it back no oh my god yeah
mattress please for for only the small amount of $5 a month you can support your
favorite brown vtuber is there a please get her out of that please please let her
have her own apartment so she could be as messy as she wants to
gotta put a bedroom set on through yeah so I have to figure out I might have to
ask my dad and my mom for help or maybe some friends because I cannot the bed is
way too heavy it's fucking huge you want to clean ASMR that actually be cool you
can do a Twitter space and you can just ramble and chat while you clean your room
that's actually that might help you I might help you my ADHD well they can
help you stay on stay focused for me I have to have something like playing in
the background otherwise yeah like music yeah otherwise I can't focus I feel the
jam we need a don't go back yeah is there a is there a need to make a don't
go on your throne saying get me out of my house and then just put like the first
to last month of rent forever you are for the goal maybe the donut on that I'm
gonna have true your birthday which it's August right yeah 24th August 24 mark
the calendars ladies and gentlemen come to my birthday I'm very excited cuz
you'll be the first one of us to have a Donald on yeah I think I'm gonna stay
longer oh and yeah I think mine's after yours cuz I'm September 28th so yeah
scary I might try to do a 24 hour I have to talk to strong about it like that
actual I think all of us are doing 24 hour though but not like 12 hours a day
but like continuous streaming on stop 24 hours yeah that's what I was gonna do
oh fuck yeah okay perfect sounds like so confused I would not suppose no
sometimes people say they do like a 24-hour donathon but then they break
it up over a couple days true so shit yeah so I think but I think but I think
we're kind of known for like we do a lot of endurance stuff like between me
actually everybody I think has done like at least one endurance stream I think I'm
not quite sure yeah I don't even know what I want to do for my donathon I have
a few plans to do but I'm gonna do a Zatsu we're all gonna chat about what
we're gonna do what they want me to do or what they do yeah ideas and stuff we
have a few already so what I'm going to do during the donathon is what I don't
know yeah there's somebody that's so far behind in your VOD and it's really
funny because they just responded with lent you like with the bed thing that we
talked about yeah VODs end at 12 hours so yeah we'll have to be two parts but I
think I think it'll be cool yeah I do that and then in the 12 part you could
take a break before the next one yeah I'm sorry I totally misheard I was like
imagine like a Zura dressed as like a beautiful 1920s flapper with one of
those cool cigarette holders in her mouth and she's like hey doll you want to
go out she was talking about cigarettes and I thought she was talking about
something else entirely oh are you
I'm like laughing behind you I was just like oh sultry cigarettes after
copulation always talk about you know grass like outside okay what I love
struggling to breathe the dank grass oh why I got it I understand now I get it
I'm smart ah the devil's lettuce indeed whoops I think I killed the wacky to
back the sticky icky okay I'm sorry breathe
the saw like pizza like I think a pizza like you want to grab a slice of
I can't tell if she's getting she's not so far away like she ran across the room to
cry she be here's blinker and think what's what the fuck is a blinker I'm
thinking about cars what I don't they call it what is that like I've never heard
of that I've never heard that called that when you hit a bit for long enough in
the light starts playing oh because I like I have friends that smoke vapes and
stuff I didn't know that was a thing I'm wait till you know I'm very I'll expose
myself more right now I'm I'm a part of me was very thankful that nobody recalled
in my past life that I sat during a stream for about an hour debating male
anatomy with my viewers because I thought I thought the little the little you
know beans in the sack were on like behind your legs and and that's why you
had to like man's and I remember just like complaining cuz I'm just like men's
anatomy is so weird cuz it's like why is it on the front like that and I thought it
was cuz I'm thinking about like in terms of like the distance of like a woman's
stuff and a man's stuff I'm like is it okay is the ball in between the leg like
and and so I remember I was drawing my example for people and they were just like
kind of doing what's happening now and I was and I don't know why I thought that
cuz it's not like I don't like I don't watch stuff so I'm just like you know I
was gonna stop talking
you need to look at the draw it again
guys she tryking it
I got to see this.
Hold on, hold on, I got you.
I'll show you what I mean.
I mean, I need to see this.
Let's people forget I grew up in a very religious Christian hospital.
Oh, I'm sweating so bad.
How about sex ed when I was a lot younger?
I didn't really remember a lot, but I thought so.
Wait, they actually taught you?
Like they actually taught you?
I thought like you were like in a religious household where like they like kept you away from it.
Because no, my mom, my parents were like, we don't want you getting molested.
So like here's some information.
And they're like, if somebody asks you to do this, don't do it.
I don't even remember my sex ed class in high school.
Like I'll be honest with you.
I think I might have like blanked that out for my own mental health and safety.
Yeah, pretty decent parents telling you that early age.
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah.
Being a girl and an only child, they didn't want me to get like diddle by someone in church or whatever.
Damn, every time she hits me with these like terms, it really shocks me.
So this is the head of the dude and he's just hanging out.
And then I'm going to do this from the side.
So I'm going to, this is his leg.
Wait, we can't see it.
We can't see it.
What do you mean you can't see it?
Oh wait, I'm delayed in a month.
Don't worry about me.
I kind of made his legs too thick, but don't worry about it.
I thought like this is the butt and let me get this one.
How do I make this bigger?
Damn, look at that cake.
I know, he's kind of, he's caked up.
He's caked up.
So I thought like a guy's stuff was over here.
Like that's where the peepee is.
And then this is where the balls are because they're like in between the legs.
But then come to find out, they're actually like weirdly at the front.
And I just think that's stupid because as a woman, you know, you have like,
there's like too much space between the asshole and the balls.
I just think it's dumb.
Whereas as a woman, your stuff is just like down here all chilling and then you got your asshole.
You know, don't you want to pinch it?
Like the space between a man's asshole and his balls?
Yeah.
Is there a what?
You want to pinch it?
I've heard it's called the Gooch.
Yes, the Gooch existence.
I think it's stupid.
I don't like that anatomy.
I feel like their stuff should be a little bit different.
But yeah, the women's stuff is there.
Like, I feel like I could just pop this off and just be like,
I'll make you a Kendall.
And then your asshole is all the way over here.
Like, I don't understand it. It's stupid.
Like, what? There's too much space.
There's too much distance.
I think the reason why the tack is on the front like that,
because it's the root of where it grew.
What?
I thought that prostate was like inside.
Yeah, isn't that inside?
Yeah, the prostate is inside.
Yeah, that's like you got the booty hole and then it's like,
well, like right above it.
Because the man's spot is literally in the booty hole.
Yeah. And then I know like,
I also get there with like sounding and stuff,
which is terrifying, by the way.
P is stored in the balls.
That's true.
You know, I remember when I was younger, mind you, again,
I was like probably like five when my parents taught me
about like how to make sure that I'm not being taken advantage of.
So I don't remember a lot because they bought me like a whole ass anatomy book.
And they also got me a little book.
I think it's called The Caring Keeping of You,
which was really cool for like girls who were going through puberty.
But like I also, it took me a while to figure out where my P-hole was
because I thought I peed out of my clit for the longest time.
But I discovered that wasn't the case.
Are you serious?
Damn.
I have to have a mirror.
Was I just that exploratory when I was younger?
I knew all of this from the get.
What do you mean Vod's cooked? Vod's fine.
This is educational purposes.
Educational purposes.
Precisely.
I'm getting educated.
Well, I've been educated.
But like this was probably a couple months ago.
What just happened? Excuse me.
I think I was just very exploratory.
Just overall with anatomy as a whole.
So it was very, very, very young.
But it's funny because like I would draw and stuff,
but I didn't draw like that stuff.
And then like I would read like,
yeah.
And like watch stuff.
Like a little Fuji.
There's no way that you watch.
Yeah.
And didn't understand the anatomy of the boob.
It was, I think it was like object permanence.
I don't know.
Like I just thought it like moves around more often,
but it's really just tacked to the front.
And I thought you could like tuck it.
Like that's why I'm like, oh guys can tuck
and I don't want to like show how much they're packing.
You know?
Am I just embarrassing myself?
Why am I in the horror corpo?
I don't know if it was out of me.
I was curious since day one.
I really thought that when they showed you the,
the, the, the, the, you know, the sake wacky.
Can I call it a sake wack?
The wacky to back.
When they showed you it in the pictures,
I always thought it was like an egg.
Yeah.
So I was very curious.
And, and like, because of like,
because like there's stuff is on the inside.
I thought it was like,
I didn't know that it was like holding stuff on the inside.
I thought it was like the organ itself.
Like I didn't like the sack is holding the testes.
I just thought it was like,
it was the testes just covered in skin.
Don't crack it.
Everybody is terrified of you cracking the nuts.
Oh, he cracked the nuts.
Yeah.
I always thought it was, I always thought you like,
it would actually crack.
Like when I was younger, I was like,
Oh, does it really hurt?
I accidentally kicked someone like a long time ago.
It was an accident.
Like for real.
I didn't do it on purpose.
Thank you.
Believe me.
I remember when I was younger,
I was playing tag with friends and at recess,
aka I don't know if any European friends don't eat recesses,
but just like a break time
from after lunch and stuff.
And we were playing tag and this one kid
jumped off of a
we had like these like benches
and he jumped off of it and I went
to go
tag him and I ended up punching him in the nuts
as he jumped off
and he just started crying
and I being a girl
called him a little bitch
because I'm like, why the fuck do you crack?
I've taken
shots of the pussy, you know.
There's no way.
There's no way because I remember
when I was younger, I fell.
You know those old wooden beds?
Oh, yeah.
I fell on one.
I fell on the headboard.
I was fucking with it
and I was like a badass child when I was little.
I was like running around jumping
on the bed and like on the board and like
do a flips and shit and then I flipped.
I slipped and I felt
in between on the bed and right in between my legs.
No, that shit hurt.
Like I'm like, I thought
I broke bone. I thought I cracked bone.
Does that mean my pussy can take more of a powder than yours?
I don't know, bro.
There's no fucking way
that you didn't feel shit.
There's no way. The only time
it hurt.
The only time it's hurt for me,
nobody really does that a lot.
The only time it's hurt for me
I draw.
This is educational.
So like, you know,
there's like the pubic bone like up here
or it's like your lippies
are right there.
It's like this bone. I had there was a girl
that like this looks like a bush.
There was a girl
to cut this out like right there.
There was a girl that
swung her music case
that had like her clarinet or something and it hit me
right at the bone.
This is what it nuked.
And I'm just cutting this out. Don't worry about it.
And it hurt so bad.
Like that was the only time it was like on the tip
like the bone
like right where your pussy lips start
to happen. That really, that really hurt.
Yeah.
I've bruised that before like going too hard
but otherwise
like
you know like
anyways
I'm Bob Ross.
These are educational drawings.
The Vaude
is not 100% dead. We can cut it.
We can edit the Vaude guys.
Archive bros, where are you at?
I'm tempted to leave it
in to be honest. I don't think YouTube will pick it up.
I tested it now.
I'm gonna test it.
I'm gonna fucking test it.
Because I didn't smash your pass with Tomo yesterday
and we said some foul language.
We just said some foul shit.
Oh my god.
And we were fine.
I can't.
Being in that
you like I haven't used that
like
my vocal range changes depending on my mood
right.
How I feel
my vocal range changes.
I haven't been in that vocal range in so long.
My throat fucking hurts.
I'm so sorry.
Oh my god.
I was laughing too hard in high pitch.
I haven't laughed that hard
forever.
My throat is fucking fucked.
Help.
I'm so sorry.
Did you need a break?
Did you want to end stream?
No.
It's fine.
We can play one more.
Thank you madam.
Educational lecture.
Body education.
Thank you.
Oh thank you for the five gifted boy.
I missed that one.
Yeah everyone gave me gifted.
I wanted to go through them but you guys send them
like back to back to back and Chibi was talking.
She just told me to shut up.
No.
Thank you guys after.
Thank you all the people that were gifted.
Yeah.
What did you want?
What did you thank the people that gifted them?
Because the people who were gifted.
Oh I don't have gifts.
I don't have gifts.
Remember I'm not monetized.
I know but I mean like on my stream.
Wait. Oh I meant mine.
Oh I get you okay.
Cause I'm like wait you're gonna go
to my stream and read out the gifts.
No.
I'm happy you guys liked
the educational portion of the stream.
Um.
I'll be good rid of this.
It was very educational.
Definitely.
We should do a deep dive
into drawing anatomy.
Maybe I'll learn how to draw.
Cause I can't draw bodies like Azir can't.
Uh.
I don't really try.
I don't know.
She doesn't even try everybody.
Look.
I'm not trying to.
I'm like literally don't try.
Everything I draw is literally the night before.
Like not even like an hour or two hours
before I post it.
I'm like this is a great idea.
I'll be honest.
I think it looks bad.
I don't know what you mean.
What do you mean?
I do have a question.
I did some art.
On your other account.
Yeah.
It was quite creamy.
What was laying?
Creamy.
What was laying in the cream?
There was like a ball.
My tail.
Wait.
Your tail popped off and.
It popped off.
No.
My tail popped off.
Wait a second.
Lay directly on your tail.
So it would like hold on.
I need to go hold on.
I'm going to send you the picture of the one that I'm talking about.
I know.
Yes.
Wait.
I'm confused.
You see the color.
I know.
I saw that.
It was like my tail popped off.
It was just like are you gay best?
Steve is going to kill me.
I'm going to laugh too hard.
I'm going to perish.
please don't die.
Hold on.
I'm going to your account right now.
I'm going to stare at this.
First I see some gorgeous legs.
Then we're gonna go to someplace else.
Oh, that is your tail!
It's my tail!
I thought your tail would be higher up!
That was it again! I was just shocked! We are so sorry for her!
My tail is on my tailbone, so I thought it would be behind.
Yeah, but it was mine!
How was your tail reaching all the way?
You lay on your back and if you pull your legs up, your tailbone sticks out.
Your tail would be out of your ass!
I thought it was just a pile of cream and there was just a small bleeding.
I'm like, oh, she gave birth!
My tail is a little longer than yours.
I'm not good with anatomy or perspective.
Oh no!
Now I'm just staring at this photo because it's very nice.
Now that I know what it's supposed to look like.
I'm so sorry!
I'm not doing it on purpose! I thought it was a pregnancy kink thing!
Oh my God!
This is my gen mate, everybody. This is my gen mate.
See, somebody eyes agreed with me in my chat, so...
You both need to get your eyes checked!
I'm wearing glasses!
Get new glasses! Even I don't have my glasses on!
Okay, let's play one more.
We got two spots left, everybody wants to join.
Three spots now, three spots.
Get your glasses.
I have to make these people leave me!
She's like, no thank you.
She doesn't even know where stuff is.
I thought it was a rabbit spot!
Oh my God.
I'm sorry.
Am I going to be bullied for this?
I just don't remember things.
I'm not good at remembering where things are and where they're supposed to go.
That's literally one of my issues with my mental Illinois.
The Dom has become a...
No!
Oh honey, don't get it twisted.
Okay, I'll still put you in your fucking place, dude.
Now I know where to kick properly!
I'm so sorry if she be was how allowed.
I know I got real close to my mic.
Yes!
I had you turned up on the score.
I had you like maxed out, like...
Because I couldn't hear you earlier, but I forgot to turn you down.
I'll still be dumbed, but man, that was unfortunate to hear.
Shut the fuck up.
You know where to kick for now until I forget again.
This is not the loot company, this is the...
It's fine, she be yours.
It's okay.
No.
I don't even know, I can't even defend myself.
She be is over for you.
I was right, I was right.
I told you for day one when she be was saying all the things.
I was like, no, this is the girl that's going to get everyone in trouble.
She's gonna be in trouble with you, I can see it now.
Trouble make her...
She's gonna say like the craziest things.
You're wrong.
You know, you're not wrong.
I was still even with me saying that, I was still surprised by this shit you'll be saying.
I can't get up.
What is she saying?
I'm falling and I can't get up.
Oh shit.
Oh, okay, there's water.
Guys, I don't think I'm gonna make it.
Oh shit.
Oh no.
Yeah, I'm not gonna make it.
Oh shit.
Forget I can dive.
Oh fuck.
Ow.
Oh my god.
I'm literally like last.
I made it.
I'm amazing.
I was like...
No.
She didn't make it.
Rest in peace.
Rest in peace?
I'm resting in peace right now.
Resting in peace?
Resting in peace isn't in peace.
In peace.
Totally fair.
I deserve this.
I'm responding to my feet.
It's not my fault that men are built weird, okay?
I'm gonna draw a sheebie.
Discovering a dick for the first time.
How did you know?
How did you know my plan?
That was my plan.
What is this?
Weeeeee.
Ow.
For not having our animal men are freaks of nature.
That's why they get dombed.
Actually no, the male and the female form are quite beautiful.
I just forget what they...
Wait, is that the one way?
What if we go this way?
Don't get it twisted.
I don't remember.
I'm not gonna make it.
It's because I fell.
I'm happy nobody heard me say that.
What'd you say?
Don't worry about it.
What'd she say?
What'd you say?
I forget what my own looks like.
Like that ass?
Yeah, I'm not looking at it all the time.
That ass?
What if you get something?
What if there's a mole?
Actually, somebody made me really look the other day.
Because they're like, do you have any moles?
And I was like, oh, I do.
I have one.
I realized I actually have three beauty marks there.
Oh, let me pull up a diagram.
Oh, you're gonna actually give them a diagram?
I'm just gonna say where it is.
I can't say.
It's hard to describe where they are.
Mine is on my lip.
Your lip?
I have...
I might have to look again.
On the inside of my lip.
I have one on the outside, and then one on the inside.
This again.
I have to look again, because I forget.
Capture?
Perfect.
Okay, let me take a peek.
Okay.
I have one right there.
One right there, and one right...
Wait.
Okay.
All right.
I'm ready.
Okay, so how do I make this thicker?
Make the brush thicker.
Yeah.
Get distracted, get distracted, get distracted.
Very much.
I have one on the inside of my lip.
Eggplant.
I need help.
One right there.
Go bullet person.
It's a duck.
What the fuck are you doing?
I'm not...
It was very abstract.
You guys couldn't tell what I was talking about.
It's a duck.
Yeah, she's just quacking.
I was drawing my interpretation of a duck.
Azir is quacking.
I'm drawing my...
My beauty marks.
That's everyone's phone.
The phone will be fine.
It's fine.
Relax.
Oh!
Is that a chili dog?
Oh, yeah.
It's a chili dog.
Look at that.
Oh.
There was two of them.
Girl, are you good?
It's a chili dog.
Look at that.
Oh.
There was two of them.
There are two.
They're just like hot dogs, though.
It's really grilled.
Oh, which is really grilled.
That's not sauce on it.
They sauce in?
They lost in the sauce?
I don't know why I said sauce.
They time Azir is a different breed.
Yeah, you guys get me at night when I have like no energy.
This is like how she is in all of our collabs in our meetings.
This is Azir.
It's a night she's chilling.
Azir really likes chili dogs.
She definitely loves wieners.
That's for sure.
I want to touch the eggplant.
Eggplants really taste the other good plants.
Is it?
Really?
I don't know.
I've never had an eggplant before.
The texture isn't for everybody.
I changed my mind.
I don't want to eat it.
Yeah, I don't know if you would like it.
At least like eggplant farm.
I like eggplant farm.
Maybe.
I'm very picky with some things that I eat.
My throat is so fucked.
I'm so sorry.
Because aren't you streaming after this?
Yeah.
Put some salt on it.
Don't worry, well I'm after this and you can rest.
She needs some milk.
It's undercat.
Fucking thing.
Or key man rather.
That's actually pretty cool.
It is actually.
It's kind of hardcore.
Oh ghost cat, congratulations.
Congratulations.
It was so fun playing with everybody.
And I'm glad
you got to learn a little more about me.
It's so funny.
It's so funny because
you were making fun of me.
You are making fun of me
earlier.
I'm going to tease Azura.
I'm going to tell everybody what happened.
I said, do you want to call me
50 minutes before?
And she was like, sure we can do that.
And I said, sweet.
And she was like, how do you want to play using vtube studio?
And I said, I'm going to do
foodie tech because it's easier on my computer.
And then Azura says, okay.
And I said, is that okay with you?
I can still pop open studio,
like have her model in it.
So we had a boyfriend model.
If you think it would be better.
Azura said, I don't mind either way.
But are you not using studio during live?
And I said, I'd use studio for my model.
Yes. And she's like, oh, okay.
I was confused. I thought everybody use a PNG.
And I said, no, use foodie tech
for you. And then she said, oh,
LMFAO.
And I said, ellipses, Azura, ellipses,
ellipses, ellipses.
And then she said, oh, I'm sorry.
And I said, I'm going to tease you for this. And she said, no.
And then she said, style up off saying, don't do it.
And that's the story.
I have to fart.
But she didn't say that.
I didn't say that.
Listening.
I spread my teeth so you guys couldn't hear it.
Oh.
Oh, what the?
What the hell?
Oh, hi.
Hi, welcome raiders.
Hi.
I don't know.
Let me look.
Sorry.
I can't tell.
Because I can't see it.
You highlight it.
Can you highlight it?
I have a chat very much
closed.
It is
Shantarelle.
I like your name.
Welcome, raiders.
Welcome, welcome.
Thank you. You're doing great. Thank you.
Yay.
You won't get away with this, right?
Whatever.
Are you still streaming?
Are you going to keep streaming?
I think.
I don't know.
Should I end it?
I think I'm going to end it and then start again.
I'm going to just chat for a little bit at the end.
With the tatters.
And stuff.
I'll chat with you guys too.
Well, I mean like my chat.
And I'll say bye.
Thank you for playing with me.
It was so fun.
Bye bye, cute-bye.
Bye bye.
Do you guys hate me?
Listen, everybody forgets
so that you used to be cute and funny
in my past life.
And I'm, I might be a little innocent and forgetful when it comes to male and female
bodies but I'm still here madam and you can't forget that I am the one in
control. I, I am close to graduating my DOM class. I am learning
expeditiously. I am still in charge. Isn't it hotter though? Isn't it hotter that you
have such a silly girl doing that to you? Doesn't it just tickle you a little bit?
It's a bit tantalizing is it not? Yeah, everybody has to learn somewhere.
The gap is getting wider each day. So you can't raise that? Yes I can. Bend over, spread your
cheeks. I'm going in with no lube. If you scream, we repeat the process tomorrow. If you stay
quiet, I'll let you finish. The game and Minecraft of course. Just as the fall guys beat. Oh, don't
you want to flick that bean though? I wanna be the very best that no one ever was. To
catch them is my real quest. To train my bitches. My harem is my cause. I will travel across
the land. Searching far and wide. Something, something, something, something. The dominatrix
that's inside. Madame Chibi. Gonna tame a mong. It's so true. She's gonna put her strap
in you. She fucks me. And my balls are blue. Dom Chibi. Chibi Dom. The boss is not
obsessed. It's him. I love it here. Gotta tame a mong. Chibi Dom. Take all that juice
out of you. What do you mean? Chibi streams are one of the, why would the bod is fine?
The bod is fine. This is the one I call my Oshi. I'm so sorry. I'm sorry I'm your Oshi.
My voice goes very high when I'm embarrassed and excited. Minas are a lot alike in that
way that our voices change. Actually, no, I don't want to do that. I'll tame it. Call
me Oshi. No. I'm so sorry. You guys have bad taste in women. I have to work on that,
I guess. I think, I think Strawnee would love that if I told her. I already pitched a couple
ideas to her about some content that I want to do consistently. And I'm going to start
planning for them. There's two segments I want to start doing because I think there's a niche
for them. I don't know if there'll be honestly a niche for one of them amongst men, but I
think you guys would still enjoy it. I want to do like a book reading club podcast of
Smuddy Books. I was thinking about it before, and that's why I like when Amy's like, oh,
I want to read this book. I'm just like, oh my God, please tell me because I want to do
it with her. And then my friend Salem and Strawnee said it was fine. And fanfix. Yes,
fanfix would be a thing. I'm going to do more. Don't worry, I'm still continuing fanfix
next week. Yeah, I'm turning Salem into a Vtuber. I hope you guys are happy. I'm trying.
I was supposed to go over her house today to see, to figure out a set up for a podcast.
Because, but like, it's this is something we've wanted to do since for a couple years
now me and me and Salem, but I'm trying. I'm helping her design her character, but she's
not in Villalur. She's literally only going to live on my channel. She's not going to
be like social media or anything or be like her own entity. It's only going to be for
a podcast. But I think it'll be super fun. What if Salem becomes a dominator? Oh, Salem's
100% a sub. I'm sorry. No, she she is not Dom at all. She is 100%. She is the she is
a bratty mess of Gaki type. 100%. She's short. I've choked her before as a joke in our store
and she screamed and it was like R2D2 screaming. It was very funny. She's not my sub, no.
She's more of a pocket than me. I don't forget I said she was way more base than I am. I
have to reel her in. She isn't even on the interwebs like that. Bad Omen's equal sub.
Got it. Very great man though. Um, I think it'll be a recorded thing just because for
like safety. Strawdy set me to get stepped on. All right, hold on. Hold on just a moment.
Prepare to be stepped. Thank you, Bob. Here are your stepies. Take a good with. My feet
don't really like step from side to side like some models do, but I hope to get that at some
point. My legs are so nice. Can we just talk about how nice my legs are? Imagine if this
was my skin tone. I wouldn't even be mad about that. Or is there a skin tone? Steppy,
okay, I need you to stretch out your neck and I'm gonna step on your windpipe. Oh yeah,
it's look at my thighs. You guys don't see my thighs that often. Okay, come come and back to
her. Imagine if she'd be to step to their feet. Oh, I have heels so I could do that.
How do you got the got thigh for the thighs? Everybody gets a treat. No, not my neck.
But I hope you guys enjoyed. Sorry, I was looking at Azura's chat to see if she got off or not.
I think you just did. Um, she's still talking. Um, because I wanted to see if I was going to read
into her next one, but I don't know. I'm sorry for my behavior. If there's any bleeding hearts in
the audience. Um, but sometimes I do misbehave and I do have no filter. Well, that's just how I am.
Vaughn is not being edited. Vaughn is fine. Why not step on the ribs or solar plexus? I could
break your ribs if you want. I can just like pile of drive my ass into it. Be like, watch out,
watch out, and then just like fucking slam my ass down. Okay, I'm a little, a little embarrassed.
I got my way is strong right now. I'm feeling like, I'm feeling like I see I'm in my little space.
I feel very cute and funny right now.
But um, uh, I hope you guys had a good time. I'm gonna play Azura, uh, and I hope you have a good
night or day. And I'm gonna go hide away and I'm gonna go practice drawing. Because somebody got me a
drawing tablet because I got a drawing tablet because I do want to practice drawing. So, uh,
maybe I'll put up a drawing stream for next week. And you guys can all practice and what
drawn out of me and fucking, you guys can laugh at me. Okay, I'll see ya. Stay for the raid. Bye.