I'm going to do a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little
bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit
of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of
a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a
little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little
A little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of more little bit of a little bit of
You're just so big and I'm kind of stupid wait what did you just say I'm kind of
stupid so far apart so I'm just gonna put you on either side of me I call
right I call right I call right boob give me off let me do my thing you now
wait I need your food to foodie should be automatic when you do the yeah I got
a copy that thing why is there is a square I don't know my god I don't have
a target I haven't set that shit up what a horrible vtuber doesn't have shit
stupid hope type my audience is no I just got out of the shower like two
minutes yeah and clean smelling good sec I was meeting on mine and I'm so
stop it hello what scent is your what kind of soap is your I'm using honey I
wash the kids from lush no not like that it's so many fucking soaps it's
just like the liquid I do I got a bath bomb from there
yeah I don't know what that is I do cuz you don't shower not yes I don't
I did shower today as well it took a lot of bravery it took a bravery shower yeah I
realize I keep slipping slipping into my cute and funny voice it's habit it's
habit I'll start talking like a mommy go for it can you
oh my god mr. frog hello we don't know what that is family I feel like a kid do
you know what that is mr. frog was mr. frog my link friends you know I can
remember the fuck oh that yeah no I don't even know it it's like does that mean
no I think I'm just an out-of-gen alpha that's the problem oh yeah small stupid I'm
kidding introduce yourselves okay oh my god I'm so nervous oh my god hi okay I'll
go first I go first you want to go for it okay hi I'm child with a four I'm a
devil doctor demon so cute vtuber and I just love mommy she be and I just am
here with my friend Noriko we're gonna be cooking
my name is oh oh shit my mic just fell off the table um my name is Noriko and
I'm an isopod princess and I like um then out on and I like I'm she be cotton
mom's number one fan you guys all think you're her number one fan no I am it's
her I'm sorry guys that place number one I know are you guys are lovely we've
never ever played this game together before I don't even know what this game
is yeah never played it in my life it's so crazy
of course I know it must be an order for the both of you it's alright hold your
applause I know I did the presence of a celebrity I'm just I'm just a dork I'm
just a favorite girl failed um oh wait yeah wait your audiences don't know me
hi I'm she I am your ever-demanding madam and mistress in dominatrix
velour and I do 18 plus contents and audio and other sites but don't worry
I'll keep myself contained my ropes will hold me back for this stream and I will
try not to I'll try to contain myself around your lovely girls yeah you can't
touch me I'm one like a kid
you're gonna be in big trouble if you touch us yeah
stop don't touch me there this is my no no screen so it's really inviting okay
I'll invite yeah you do all that I'm so smart and I'm not I don't know what I'm
doing half the time the nice discord noise this court I mean steam I don't
know where I am okay I gotta you guys are just gonna work to be someone said oh
my god when you're her eye patch comes off when she talks is so cool
why is this working just want to be I have so many okay I'm almost ready I'm
almost ready I'm a little bunny I want to be a bunny there's a bunny there should be a
bunny a bunny a bunny I feel my controller rabbit it won't let me use my
controller what the frick oh she's back me but I don't want this version of me
here okay now I gotta join you oh my gosh I'm so productive and really good at
things there's no rabbit there should be a rabbit I'm gonna freak out I won't be
the dog again you'll be the dog yeah what do you mean again yeah I just met
today it's fine I could change why are the brown people in this game like kind
of ugly to look at I was gonna say why are you why are you brown wait I'm gonna
wait wait wait wait wait wait I can say that wait wait wait wait wait leave on
expensive Ferrari hey haha I heard you like cute things I think haha I like
milk on my expensive cars spins my keys to my mansion thank you for the raid
is there love is there a love is there a love yes hey hey girl hey
okay I'm here now let's shift oh I'm the brown one yeah I didn't know I was like
how the turns have tables yeah I'm the most opposite but it's fun to roleplay
sometimes okay I love role playing as a brown person you have to reintroduce
yourself because now because I'm now here okay here before so make it make
it snappy make it snappy hi I'm Shibi cotton bum I'm your favorite madam Dom
mistress girl fail and I'm a rabbit and I'll tie you up and slap your ass part
of you later check me out hi hi who who I'm Noriko and I'm an I supplied and I'm
kind of like autistic see I told you you smell Wow I could smell you from over
here though I put Shibi in between us I wouldn't have to I also separated you
too thank you thank you so much I'll inhale the isopods stink yeah I smell
me I'm not my glory smelly and acoustic why can't I play I have to play with
keyboard I hate this yeah no it doesn't play with me I think this happened
before maybe never never ever you're crazy and insane I know I'm I'm I'm
losing my mind I'm so to Lulu I just hey guess what a little celebration I just
hit 1.4 1.4 K oh my god congrats what the fuck yeah thank you thank you please by
the way if you guys please check out Chai and Nori in my description below I
put their links from their Twitter and their Twitch they're really funny
girlies and hello I was cute and funny girlies so far I would reach people yeah
sorry they're from Twitch we usually you know keep them separated but you know
honestly please take me back YouTube is so hard I love you to thank you so much
corporal say it say it with your flat chest oh no you can't see it
horrible for before YouTube okay no I'm gonna cry I'm being bullied by a
child you took for the first time and it wasn't even terrible and I didn't want
to die oh okay the first time I did I was struggling I mean you can't be as
cool as me I guess she be playing with her two daughters so wholesome she be
playing with her two daughters it's funny Chai actually looks like she could be
my kid
like I found her in the garden I found her in the garden what I said garbage I
was like well I have a little princess crown
all right how do we how do we start yeah are we ready oh I had did I have to
do something oh yeah it's me all right so new game new game right there's a
continue button but the new game yeah oh you have to press E
but it's a new game right are can't or continue should we do a new game oh
continue oh wait continue whatever you played with before you know unlock some
stuff yeah get to pick a safe spot you guys have to pick a safe slot oh my god
it's Freddy hi Freddy Fazbear in my chat when I was Dia she be it's me for type
Freddy and welcome to the overcooked challenge I'm gonna I'm gonna punt you
across the route I'm gonna step on you and squash you and not if I call into
your teeth first excuse me nothing try did you pick a safe slot hi one just
pick any one two three four I up down left right I don't care I declare a
thumb war oh my god remember one time I did a thumb war with my dad and he like
cracked my my thumb oh that's okay and he was like I was yeah shit oh wow guys
look wait we are here that's one star do this again I think we should do this
again oh I'm sorry again I remember loving this before they're not my favorite
bug but they're up there don't tell Nori that'll get to her head
I'm gonna I'm gonna kill myself what do you mean up up there
wait I don't know how to pick shit up space we're way better than we used to be tomatoes
I feel confident in my job for the first time right I maybe we made a mistake
chop is left control chop is left control so left control to chop oh okay okay okay okay I'm
gonna read the controls left control to chop pick up his space um dash is left alt and to throw
oh throwing is also left control okay so here what the fuck how do you beat this pick up uh dash
throw or drop how do you drink let's throw um washing up okay am I constantly hold on
I'm gonna check the controls it's okay let me make the sauce go wait what oh I gotta cook this first
they don't first okay wait okay wait we could always go like even though we're in this safe we
could always just go back to the beginning and like practice again if you want to yeah
but sweet I need a plate oh let me get that for you pizza
stay on me okay it's not letting me throw it's I just said it's left control
ground I know I'm pressing left no no lady grandma yeah my mom is kind of stupid okay how do I
listen whatever oh there you go see I can throw okay I'm a tosser I'll toss your salad
I just can't hold in this still I don't know what I'm doing I think can we quit this
I don't know I just hear a control you guys oh yeah let's just quit maybe we should just quit
I don't know if quitting means like ending this yeah the ending of the stream
no and how do you get out of this this level I have no idea I'm scared you
stream than usual yeah it's cuz um nori streams late I'm sorry I'm sorry I stay up until five
and I don't like streaming wait where did you go wait did I just leave just because it sounds
wait do we all this this is so stupid at the level nori if I quit I ended it okay so we just
we're just gonna quit the game
all right guys good night good night
bye chai thanks for stopping by thanks guys bye wait did you guys oh wait no our ties is gone
yeah ties is gone she I'm just gonna keep quitting and re-invite okay yeah this is
I'm so stupid chai this is so stupid challenged no cuz I literally tried this with poof on my screen
it's fine I know she just like disappeared from existence okay and she was brown
it's for the better okay I realized here now I'm ready
continue but we go from the very beginning right yeah chat is destroying us stream is cooked
faster than the game I don't care I literally don't care I think you should I think you should
spit on your chat you think no they'll like that I'm not gonna reward them I patch off I patch off
I patch off
I feel like it's like fucking clap on clap off except it's just her eye patch
all right you're you're just we can practice wait we don't even have to be all the way
back it just has to be back to see yeah okay girl you're terrible at driving
I'm literally I'm literally like a centimeter tall what do you want from me woman
okay it's time for the foot pedals yeah let's do the tutorial again and then we just drive
the cup sounds good okay sounds good oh yeah I can um always just so loud
they can cook food just after tea time we gotta cook for our chats guys we gotta
can we skip this yeah I'm like I'm not dramatically reading this shit
it's very stupid shilling
this book holds a secret to everlasting culinary greatness
in a large bowl dissolving sugar in one moment with Jesus fucking
thank you thank you starring the yeast what's yeast isn't yeast like a yeast infection shut up
you said that last time I mean this is the last time she's reusing jokes mom it's killer
I'm not using jokes I'm just I'm trying
there was no last time the old ladies keep forgetting these things that happened that's
try I'm sorry
unoriginal getter boys I'm trying my best to skip I'm coming the yeast comes from your kuchi
and they use the yeast to make the bread oh my god there is one time there is a story of this
lady they used to use to make cookies and they got on their tongue and it was really gross and
white and crusty no that's fine anyways why am I on this okay so we're gonna take it out
and I'm gonna pass it to you it's all right I'm gonna tell you something this game it feels like
work right like it feels like painful and like excruciating to play but like when this game was
suggested to play I was like yeah hell yeah like I want to play it it's fun I have like a desire
to be in pain I find that interesting I want to like psychologically analyze why no why'd you do it
I'm not paying attention I'm just chucking shit here you go I'm the only one chopping I'm the only
one working in this place we should have gotten a horse man hey man you just fucking hit me with the
tomato listen I don't even I don't know enough to chucking cucumbers at me I don't get paid enough
to care don't you like that having cucumbers on in my face no I'm the one smacking with the
cucumbers okay hold on hold come here this is unless you want to I will only do stuff that you
consent dig my meals you're pretty slicers okay oh yeah we're cooking wait Ty keeps pushing me away
from me I keep trying to make my plate and I'm just getting shoved away I think it's funny because I feel
like I feel like oh sorry if there was like a stat you know when you like finish playing a game
and it says like you can see like your stats like oh who got the most kills or like yeah
like I feel like if I did it like my progress like my meals made or whatever or like any like
contribution would be like zero or like I know for a fact like I just can't my brain can't like I
know I just I don't know how to explain it I need a tomato okay hold on tomato and what do you
want tomato sigma meals give me slicer so oh my god I'm literally gonna beat your ass
oh you're just mad I'm a little bit sigma and you're just gonna be done to my baby gronk
I don't even know what the fuck you just said and you don't even know I'm thinking about
can you teach me tick tock I don't it's not it's not teaching it's a mindset
my chat one time I'm sorry does anybody does anybody notice you speak zuber
someone said shibbity toilet don't acknowledge them wait it's a real thing was that like
was that original I think it was so funny mercy mercy came up with this start calling me shibbity
toilet I love that I have it so my fucking mods nuke anybody who keeps spamming it in my chat
toilet shibbity toilet shibbity toilet great
I'm gonna I'm just gonna be on us it can't be on us
okay I'm ready I'm ready I'm ready to be good now I'm about to break in my new
so true chat so true
I'm sorry nori why are you so cute yet annoying it's because it was practically like an actual child
the same thing it's like the same vibe an actual kid gives you like you're so cute but you're disgusting
in the weird disgust okay now we know now we know what to do we have to actually talk why am I saying
shit okay and then I put this together they're not enough me to play
no no no we have to cook it first we have to cook it first and then we get to play it so then
cook it oh and then you have to cut the dough to make the dough why do you have to cut the dough
you have to beat the dough like when you make pizza you have to beat oh fuck
I'm gonna beat this dough I'm gonna beat this meat I'm gonna fucking what the fuck do I do now
and then okay okay like oh wait don't try it okay put the tomatoes on that and then put a plate
put this on a plate and then serve this I can't throw it but serve that pizza
I don't know I'll cut this I'm actually doing something I'm so proud of you try to keep it out
okay now put this what I was trying to pizza that I just oh I feel good I I swear I can't oh my
god I feel it's trying put that pizza yeah I'm doing things this is awesome stay on the
nach side I think I can I think I can you ready yeah yeah yeah yeah how do I know is this ready
put this down yeah yeah uh no I don't think it's ready oh wait take it take it take it uh no it's
not ready you did it oh can you get the dishes this is why we should have two people I got it
we're both trapped back here what do you do yeah don't don't put that on sorry I wasn't uh-uh I don't
pursue this never give in to impulse never give in to impulse no worry about keep mogging me she
always mocks me what is it mogging what does that mean oh it's like it's like being better
yeah oh I'm better than you like sigmo like I'd like just cool learn stuff
he's gonna get it oh my god this wouldn't understand my my reason okay I don't I don't think I mind
being mugged by a by a bug that's fun yeah I'm just at least I'm taller than her that's all that
matters okay fuck you if you guys at least I'm aerodynamic are you but you can't fly if you
if you can eat it if you could eat any bug what a bug would you eat like I mean you know I eat nori
okay oh wait no but I don't have stars and let me cook it I need a plate let me do this one
who put dough in the thing and didn't even put anything
look no someone just put dough in the thingy and then they didn't cook it they just put that in there
wait okay we're at 31 this is good I think I mean not 31 36
take this okay serve that serve that serve that serve that that should
up I think that would be a really splendid waitress I try try there's people being done in the oven
try to get it we'll put it on the plate no there's a plate over there uh it's a lot in my hands
okay I did it we need to cook a little wizard put that in the oven ma'am beep beep beep beep beep
gotta do the dishes we need a tomato
I'll wash it it's okay is this done okay it's done yes I need a plate
raw dough haven't eaten also I have eaten bugs before like chocolate bugs yeah that's
actually asking for real if you're here I've had a cricket it was okay it was a
I've had I've had I've had bugs before oh what the food I've never oh my god I think we're doing a good
job uh we're definitely doing better than why can't I put the shit down oh that dough is gone
if we ever did play this in the past we're doing better oh 100 we can't
put cheese on the pizza oh wait there's only two it doesn't even matter
yeah we did it I really hope we passed I really hope we passed okay fuck you you stupid fucking
onion stupid bitch fuck this fucking stupid onion hope your kingdom dies I hate that okay okay okay
we have a strat we have a strat no fuck this level I hate well we have to do this level
so we can continue I know we can do it we have the next level I think oh I unlocked a white dude
eel yay oh wait I don't know why is it eel
yeah what what is this a bratty child which one
raised mixing is impure I'm babysitting tonight I'm the angel child I'm a good princess although
she's the devil and then there's nori who's supposed to be the princess what the fuck is this what are we
making hamburgers okay um I have something very bad to say what I've never had a hamburger in my life
our cheeseburger you're lying you just push me out the way no that's a very obscure wait okay cook
that and then I'm gonna keep chopping these bad boys here I'm gonna oh they have no lettuce
I can't drop this okay
I was I was actually before I joined call with you guys I was
I'm gonna stay on this side I'm just gonna cut thing oh wait oh we can tell
oh okay that works out um I need this back
what the hell do I do with this meat
that one's burning get it
alright I can throw things please lettuce oh thank you lettuce oh thank you oh that's a burger
that's a burger oh my fucking god lettuce oh it's fine it's fine I got it lettuce put some cheese on
that shit oh oh fine we do need a cheeseburger so that actually works is it this is a cheeseburger
with no lettuce okay wait we need meat we need meat there's no meat on this side on the other side
silly goober mine I did it
go go beat some meat
yes ma'am oh yeah okay okay okay throw me a meat throw it to me you want to
throw me to me sorry hold on hold on hold on please hold please hold you I feel confident
okay hold on hold on please hold you thank you why are we holding
oh there's my meat throw me my meat okay oh no the plain burger oh god fuck I don't need this
there's me on the floor you do need it
oh no
I'm waiting for this meat I'm just gonna I'm waiting so patiently for my meat so wait
no he's doing all of this oh my god I can't pick that up if there is I got it did it burn
no what's going on try the stairs try look guys just come off the stairs there's
there case look oh my god teleport she was just screaming
is this chopped lettuce okay oh fuck me in yet
hate this stupid finish that sentence
I need a purd
I need one
do we need to be doing dishes is that like a thing we should be doing
oh it doesn't look like we need to put the plates
a little plate
we suck balls
oh I'm just looking bad
uh there's a fire uh do we have a thing
uh can you can you get that
um oh no no I can't I'm trying to put the shit down oh god oh god oh no this is bad
oh norish I was the cup drink no I didn't what's a cup oh that's a call back to be in um
Thomas stream I think we did pretty good for that
I think we did terrible no I think I think we need a plan okay okay I know no I didn't
what we should do in the beginning just throw all the meat to the side we have to pound it right
or cut it you know what I mean yeah yeah and then and then it's a bit easier to throw it so then
so I'll cut everything and throw okay the meat so okay I won't touch the lettuce because we don't
need the lettuce yet but okay just start throwing the meat almost like throwing bread oh wait well
we can I just walk it over for now she's just waving she's not here right now
one meat done here make a make a ham ham hamburger what that on why is it called
like what is it called a hamburger I don't know that's a great question yeah you ever thought about
yeah why ham hamburger try if you don't move out of my way out but now I'm not gonna give you a
like knuckle sandwich okay okay there should be enough meat on that side and then I'm gonna
cut some lettuce oh is this one ready a burger I teleported it's fine I can just go about a burger
okay okay I don't get that it's called hamburger but
oh fuck oh shit oh fuck oh shit oh fuck oh fuck oh my god okay I'm gonna get that thank you very
much wait you can just throw that off though throw that off though like the side oh my god wait we
gotta make a cheeseburger uh that's a meat burger that's a meat burger ham cheese okay you already
got some cheese okay yeah it's it no no this one is the last one oh my god shit's on fire can you
please grab the thing try it's right next to you try no it was right next to you
oh I fell with it it's fine order okay where am I where am I order thank you
oh this is good thank you order okay I'm gonna get some like please pick it up oh oh god
I'm coming back there's a plate there's a plate yeah I can't pick shit up because there's so much
shit in the way I fell again that's fine oh cheeseburger uh there's meat cheeseburger
yeah you can teleport over there I need meat okay cheese give me some meat ladies pick up this thingy
and then I'll give you some meat uh I need cheese for this bread bread bread meat helmet to me thank you
meat I blocked it that's why I'm not talking as much I'm trying for the hardest and it's still not
good enough out of all all games I think this is the one where like I at least meet me to meet
have the ability to talk and compete like your thoughts meat bread bread oh I have a question
have you guys seen dungeon meshi yes yes oh I love dungeon meshi who's your favorite character
senti I know I've only seen try pick it try get those meat I told you I told you that I can't
talk I can't stop doing it it's like actually possible my brain can't do it I didn't hold
this order just waiting uh okay
we got a little bit more tips than last time but I don't think it's gonna be enough
probably not
the first person to ever tell me about dungeon meshi is was she be oh was it yeah oh oh my god
that was so stressful do you think we did it holy shit no I think we need like 300
I don't know about you onion man I think he's yeah I don't I don't like this guy he's he doesn't
he doesn't look like an onion he looks like a wooden knob he's just a fucking knob knob
he's like it's a knob it's just a knob the bloody knob knob no no no hate on it no hate on the dough
no you're right it's a dungeon meshi talk with a little bit oh wait are we gonna rain
where are you going come back oh everyone thank you for the rain
oh rain hi strani raided oh hi mom oh uh another of your lord lady ha ha hey it means on the wall
hello I find you quite admirable this is nori and chai nori is the the seductive isopod who's
trying to do what if I told you right now I think my game crash okay no it's fine okay yeah I'm like
what's this happen um and then chai is your sweet cute little devil why am I not sweet and
curious I just like I said you are seductive I am not seductive I'm like I don't know you're
you're trying to raise up strani right now hey man I just think all women are beautiful
oh this is a good strap this is a good strap we got the buns ready
hell yeah get that shit look at us oh my god I did that by the way you you're amazing
chai and you guys can read cheeses like you're like put them through those things don't say anything
it's okay I almost fell how do you throw item control left control but you can't have to
stand on the edge tell me when you're gonna throw that okay um I think I can bring this over
don't fall no fall is this a thing nope it was wrong shit I actually threw that cheese oh
fuck me bro okay we're already we're already at 45 where am I oh excuse me excuse me what the
way excuse me excuse me excuse me cheese delivery no no no no let's not put that down
no chai chai come back there's no cheese
I'm gonna flick you in the chrome dome chai
I got it okay that's it that's it I'm locking in I just need to lock it ready to rumble
yeah need some bread I'm throwing some eat you fuck I'm not on that side yet
Kobe oh fuck he would be disappointed Kobe why is it hitting the fucking wall
this woman sucks a dude I don't know what you want okay it's fine it's fine it's fine it's fine
just throw through the teleport at this point oh I didn't even know those are things focus mode
well hi I can't let go oh fuck I actually oh oh I didn't I oh I'm so smart okay no don't fail
oh no no no no you just choked shit at me and I died I'm sorry okay guys let's get to 300
can we get to 300 yes we can I can't put this okay please oh my god there's so much shit everywhere
let's go ladies uh we need to grab the plates I'll do that
locked in locked in ready to lock in no
I feel like nothing is wrong just fucking eat shit I feel like something has gone wrong
no everything's fine we need like we need a fourth party to like commentate all right we need
commentate like it's like esports it's so awful
I you know it's like women in the kitchen I don't even think I don't think we should be in the
kitchen this is quite bad we should be in the kitchen either because it's a papa thank you
oh my god yeah I am not a woman I am a small brown man
oh small brown one do your job no she's trying to stop somebody stop her okay go
so many we are doing we did worse we did worse no no no no it's fine it's fine I got this
oh my god I just clutched I think I think maybe we need to play on easy
do you know anybody miss me because I don't know anybody
if Azura is still here do you want to play with Azura do you have this game
somebody's to slap us in this shape here Azura Azura would would would do so
oh
I'm gonna like mommy is sorry I already have mommy this should be auntie
oh yeah would she be auntie auntie Azura would she like me
would she like to be called she'd probably probably anything she is she is the goddess
of fertility and she gave birth to everybody in human and you know the universe so
god I think I want to fuck my fertility mom sorry my apologies that was inappropriate of me
it's all right uh all right
are we just gonna sit by the side of the road are we gonna do something these people are hungry
we'll try again let's do it again we need guys guys listen to me we need 340 for one star
why so we just need okay okay okay okay what about okay we're going to plate this
shit the fuck up okay so i'm gonna grab the bread i'm gonna grab the bread and put it on the plate
now i'm high i'm not being nice anymore i started throwing meat and cheese at me i'm
okay look i did it i did it i did it okay now i'm throwing the meat oh okay
guys i'm actually never i'm never taken up by some meat okay who's the
very unusual it's gonna be it's gonna have to be all of us we just have to practically um
cheese okay so i'm cooking that meat stay on my side stay on my side okay okay take it take it
can i jump because like i feel like i should be able to jump so i can toss this stuff over there
wait you're throwing it on the edge wait wait wait stop okay cheese thank you for cheese
okay look at this make the cheese burgers make the cheese burgers make the cheese burgers first
and i'm gonna start throwing the lettuce okay we need cheese burgers here's another one
here go serve it cheese i mean not cheese lettuce lettuce okay so i'll try grab the plate
okay okay i'm grabbing plate bread okay i'm gonna take some meat
wow look at this fine oiled machine we need we're doing so well lettuce oh give me that lettuce
cheese cheese okay start chopping yeah next one oh this one's ready oh no we need cheese
i just gave you cheese perfect perfect cheese i gave you cheese i'm going to chuck some meat over
here look we're almost at 200 we're at 200 look at us go we're zooming thank you
where's the dirty thank you dirty plate there's no dirty place to scrub the plates
i think they made that a little easier okay oh oh that's nice toss it toss the things of meat
through the teleporter please i'm gonna toss some bread now okay bread bread i'm gonna toss three
breads at a time and then you need to make two lettuce burgers here i'm throwing this two lettuce
burgers okay two lettuce burgers or cheese lettuce so here's some cheese
okay i'm gonna throw i'm gonna bring this cheese burger through
good job shy oh we need a plain one plain burger meat a meat line just a plain no it's gonna
yeah we just need one because that that that that first one's gonna go all in uh
uh
here's a plate here's a plate okay perfect grab it okay i'm gonna bring it i'm gonna bring it
nice job oh fuck i need to put this down three breads we're missing bread okay uh
me if you can toss it to me okay someone uh she'd be past the meat hold on i'm waiting for this
thank you chai here's another one oh sorry okay it's okay it's fine it's fine it's fine try that
try to try this meat next to you that's gonna be we can help i got you don't worry about it
okay here's more meat oh my god i was killed you basically killed tv
no this one doesn't have any i need cheese on this oh i got it thank you oh perfect there's
meat on the floor by the way want to be the first time sorry um don't worry about it wait
ma'am i'm sorry yeah i don't i don't know
i don't know what we need oh it's fine we did it oh my god we are fucking two
first try we're so capable we're stars we're not too proud of our efforts i don't want
christ is so proud of us thank you thank you chat oh no no i said holy crap they
mocked that level yeah we mocked that fuck yeah we mocked that shit out of that level
i can't believe wow we were just so amazing okay yeah yeah yeah yeah is that a tomato or like a
peary see a what
peary it's oh i don't know what you're saying okay what are we doing here pizza level pizza
pizza with sausages sausage we do have to wash dishes eggs oh these are gonna fucking lose
oh fuck me i'm just gonna i hate the wizards these take forever
um i can give you a pizza right now here put that on that plank that you serve
do we have to put it on a plate um yes we do here's a plate there's not enough choppy
okay i need i'm gonna make this pizza this one pizza and then you're gonna put it in the oven
i don't know what to do with myself okay okay she's gonna be okay she'll be okay can you
can you okay wait can i put that in the oven yeah okay there's how many ovens are there oh there's
two there's two put that one i got it wait what the fuck where i thought i was trying for a second
i was like wait why am i not going where i want i'm facing okay put this in the oven
this needs a plate that put that one uh fuck me no no no don't put that one in the oven yes yes
put this plate in the oven this one right here uh this one needs uh tomato
you'll see the plate we don't have plates we know okay
you only have fun oh wait there's a plate in my fucking hand oh why is this burnt
that doesn't make any sense it was totally fine that doesn't make any sense
why is it black that's that was weird i don't i'm gonna try to take this
understand this is this one bad like i shouldn't serve it this was bad um wait we don't even need
this why do we put this you need pepperoni we didn't make pepperoni what the heck wait what
what the flip i can't hold up why can't i wash these this hello help wait can we still put the
sausage on after it's cooked i don't think no because it's like a raw pizza
sorry we just throw my sausage at you we got two pizza what wrong no no no no no
chai chai we've made like like three so far
because at first it'll say like oh we want this and then it'll be like oh but now we want this
at all let's keep this weird okay this is a pepperoni okay there is a pepperoni there's a sausage
pizza that's fine so i'm gonna make some tomato uh oh no pizza i see there's also pizza with tomato
on top yeah it's it's weird okay whoa whoa whoa i'm getting stressed out we need more chop and
thingies wait so these are garbage no i mean maybe i don't know i don't know
i'll just throw them up what do we have we have 45
it's always a slow start but i know that we're capable okay and okay this is done look look
look this one's done oh beautiful yay we got one little pizza done oh wow we really only have one
i thought we had more here's the wasting
okay we we can redo it now that we know that there's tomato on top of the pizza
you need to have somebody like always near the choppy chops i can be near the choppy chops
i'm good at the choppy you are good at the choppy chops yeah i was gonna make a very
or no very fucked up joke but i'm very good at the choppy chops i kind of want to i kind of
want to hear the joke i don't want to hear the joke i can type i can type the joke in the in the group
chat uh okay so basically guys i'm right above the chat it says donas and soupas will be right at
the ends thank you all right my keyboard's in spanish another in here okay let's do this again
yeah i know yeah yeah we got this one it's gonna be okay we got this wait can you guys see that to me
it's gonna be okay yeah it's gonna be okay wait i want to see the good joke oh my god
yeah i'm happy this yeah yeah it's just joke it's just joke yeah yeah so i know i know my okay
i'm gonna chop chop so just kid chai we started chai chai's dead she passed away i thought that
that was a joke i wanted to see it whatever
we're on the wrong side already okay can you okay so wait no no put that there yeah yeah yeah
okay okay there's a sausage and then i'll put it on no put it on we're gonna make that tomato one
first because that's the easier one so move that maybe if we we should just do one at a time
there's no rush you pick up my tomato of doing tomato put the tomato down wait it will let me
what so don't wait i think for the tomato ones we have to put the tomatoes on after it's cooked
for only the tomato ones what okay we'll try we'll try them let me see try again yeah yeah okay okay so
we'll just cook it and see that theory okay chai chop okay wait it's not doing the chai so turn
it side so she doesn't get overwhelmed okay here chai here chai look uh tomato has been chopped for you
thank you very much i'll top it now yeah no no put something on this tomatoes or we can put sausage
i'll just find out i'll just give you sausage no you can't put the sausage on after you can only put
the tomato on after okay so put the sausage on that one i'm in cooking it won't let me it's already cooked
oh okay then try the tomato tomato at me please oh it's right there right here thank you
it won't let me do that wait what the heck are you supposed to do yeah i don't really get that one
because i but if i get cheese needs plate though oh wait maybe if you put on the plate put on the plate
oh no that just counts as the pizza oh because i don't know why the fuck is it labeled like that yeah
that this is stupid that doesn't make any sense i thought we were
okay this one's done so here this is a sausage pizza
okay i love an uh a man i don't even know what to say i'm so i'm so focused
oh this one i can cook
somebody's phone is vibrating
uh there's just the iris i think it was snorri's dad
oh
get the thingy get the thingy it's over there sorry
it's okay wait am i missing my mom came into my room and she needed something from you
yeah so my mom is super cool oh none of us are on the right side
oh okay we have negative time we're at negative time
pizza's hard pizza's hard to me it's hard to pizza i need cheese
okay we'll just fail this i think
i'm gonna have to be comforted we'll be happy yeah it only worked when you started yelling at us
i'm gonna have to be comforting and around you yeah i guess i guess nori has to
okay so this is what we're gonna do next game okay the dom gets domed by a little ice
okay wait a second yeah i don't should what if they made this game worth it as the levels
progressed they got easier that'd be so nice that would be so great instead of it being harder
if i got easy i got charged sent a bunch of periods sorry i'm sorry oh to the joke
i'm like why is my i'm sorry i'm sorry i'm sorry it was an accident
why didn't you ask if my friend was my phone number that's a really small phone number okay
ladies i had a similar area code so i was like oh listen to me ladies we need 440 stars okay
okay you see me on that side you're gonna you're gonna go back you are going to get plates
me and me and tyre gonna cut okay you're gonna throw things on us if they move okay okay got it
okay give me okay we're gonna make the first two the first pizzas we're just gonna ignore the
sausage pizza that's too stressful for us we're just only make so only make the pizzas with the
cheese right cheese okay and fucking tomatoes okay so i can put this in
yeah put that in okay yeah okay give me i need cheese get on that side try try get on that side
i need okay got cheese yeah you can get the cheese wait the pizza's ready oh get the pizza
and there's plate okay now go put this in yes ma'am next pizza
oh my god guys go ice coordination there's another pizza ready thank you
can you give me a tomato yeah yeah like cut one yeah yeah cut one pizza done and yeah go wash the
plates okay wait before i get trapped on the other side
okay plate washed go get that oh shoot oh thank you go get that plate that's done
look there's a plate that needs to be washed okay can i um
oh i can't okay if we all had a ratatouille on her head this would be easy i know i agree with
that okay can i get a tomato can you throw me a tomato try yeah thank you
yeah there's a plate go get those plates and clean them and then put this in put these
pizzas in hold on i need to grab a pizza oh my god we're doing good i think
okay let me get this top top top top top top top top i'm taking your cheese
we got this we just need 440 yeah to get a smile pizza pizza pizza pizza pizza pizza pizza
oh no fuck try i need a plate yes yes try give me please try i could wait oh okay
here you go
put this let me cook this it's already done try try cook this one because you have
okay hold on you have the pizza doesn't matter oh i didn't i didn't know i didn't know what she had
i didn't mean i didn't mean okay we need to clean this plate someone needs to clean that plate
someone 369 pass me the plate clean clean she's dying
you have like a horror movie scream tries anyone told you that no thank you i like i like when you
wait it's on the recent district that's fine that's okay nothing wrong with that
uh oh this is wrong with these uh plate plate plate here's a plate for this pizza
can i get some cheese for this one your cheese let that one cook a little bit more
i can do it wait we're doing it we're doing it we're doing it where's the plate no i just shoved me
oh i hate this fucking bitch game no this game just shoved me over here it's fine it's fine
yeah we can't do that now it's fine it's fine it's fine it's fine we we we don't have sausage
anymore yeah we did we met our quota yeah yeah yeah we met quota that's all that matters wait so we
didn't did we do zero sausages we did zero no no yeah we did no no we did sausages you guys
didn't know because i didn't tell you i just put it on let's see any sausages there were sausages
secret yeah there were sausages secret sausage there were sausage orders it was just like
when they were overwhelming i would just slap it on and then tell you to cook it wait the dog
isn't even proud of the one star the dogs didn't even care about the ones we got in this secret
raccoon
why is the raccoon like this stapled
wheelchair raccoon i am go blushing i gotta switch my chef
oh are you gonna switch it to the raccoon it doesn't want to be brown anymore
supposed to be disabled crazy
oh wait tight right so did you watch dungeon machine sorry i'm autism i've only seen like two
or three episodes oh who's your favorite so far i don't even i don't think i have a favorite i feel
like i haven't really gotten to know the characters i'm my favorite character i think is the the chef
but the moustache is chubby and she swears yeah yeah i like a lot of women like sunshine
women like a man that can cook the women like a girl
he's just coffee i just feel like he would tell me really great stories and
and make me good food yeah and give me a lot of life advice
you know i like we'll talk yeah it's pretty cool i think he's sexy you think she'll talk is
sexy i think she'll talk is sexy he's got big ears yeah i like i like the big ears it's the
big ears that gets me although it's my weakness fallen is pretty she's pretty cute oh my god
mars fallen in myself okay this one see like this one's easy 280 guys okay 280 we got this
smaller number i really hope we leave the wizard realm soon
realm okay uh what okay i am with you okay so i'm gonna tp
okay i'm gonna be up here okay this is okay
so before i go up here what i'm gonna do is that i'm gonna get these plates ready and you're going
to try to like toss it to me through the uh thing
i'm just gonna can you bring me that plate actually no i think you're fine i'm gonna go help you
try to try stop throwing try something i'm not i i stopped throwing oh i thought that i was crying
why am i covered in red the frick was that okay i'm gonna take this now
and what i'm gonna do is i'm gonna throw you this cheese chop that cheese and throw it back to me
and then we have one on you
uh
guess who opens randomly holding stuff
uh can you grab plates and throw them over here
no no i have the plates you have to okay so this is what i said you need to do me
oh hold on hold on i got it i got it yeah i am gonna put all the plates up here because
i have to literally go back down and wash them so it just makes sense to have the plates up
where the where we have to deliver everything yeah and then just throw in like a bun
okay i'm getting distracted by these floating candle bra i know this is so much
i can't do it my brain is too small okay i need lettuce and then i'm gonna throw this
unless it's on okay you can't throw it okay can you can you chop that lettuce for me that
has to be that has to be on this brother and then throw it back to me right here
thank you mm-hmm yeah this one's a little harder because it's like multiple spots it is
no dirty plate yet okay we have this one ready we just need lettuce for this one here here
chop some lettuce i'm gonna chop oh no it's not mine oh wait could you do the lettuce again
yeah yeah actually nicely yes it's a course
i'm gonna just start filling up that corner sorry it just has slides
and overwhelmed it's fine it's fine
um look we're close but we have a minute and 20 left i gotta go wash that dish
we have a plate for that oh oh oh oh there's the oh yeah that's why i said it's it's easier
88 we fucked up wait here here here uh wait it's not on these lettuce still
i got it i got it here here here here oh you got it good good good good here
i'm not even looking at the recipes i'm like uh i'm putting this we can still do it we have 49
seconds i need that plate i'm gonna go wash that plate i threw stuff there already i need a bun
up here okay if i could drop this meat we can do this one i know we can do it put that meat on
yeah yeah yeah okay thank you and then done okay done yeah
chai's chai's exclamations keep me going oh fuck yeah brother oh fuck yeah oh i got to yell at you guys
why do you feel like you're yelling by a toddler it's not even it's not even it's not even yelling
just directions yeah direction you know i've never played this game before so exactly
clutched up clutched up last minute got a last minute order in it's fine if you don't get this
whole it's fine could be surpassed okay yeah hi tolin is so pretty and it looks like we don't
get to see her more but i think that's like a very good detail to this story what do you say tolmo
did you say tolmo fallon fallon sorry oh i'm sorry i i have dungeon meshi like
hi tolmo do you say hi tolma tolma oh tolma hi tolma
yes we're having fun i'm going non-verbal because i'm so focused uh i i have i'm so sorry i have
like the big autism i've been i've been hyper fixated on dungeon meshi content that that's
totally fine it's great i'm sad that it ended well it all confirms for your season two okay
okay this is easy we're just grilling we've done this i mean we've never done this so start
throwing so don't always you ever throw that yeah throw that
try cut that okay child is gonna cut me i'm gonna cut potatoes that's easy oh yeah yeah just give me
a little radio you want me to pass you the meat don't oh oh my god yeah yeah so i'm gonna cut
potato no no i cut potatoes you cut me it's easier that way okay let's let's overwhelm me
and then we have to try to throw a plate how are you gonna oh i can just walk over here okay here
yeah he's gonna walk oh no don't you're gonna hit him yeah grab that grab the nuggets grab the
nuggets time why you come over here too chai oh i thought we're all hanging out on this one
no it's fine it's fine i we had enough stuff cut over here okay it's fine okay chai cut that cut the
meat again throw me a potato i want to let me these dishes okay i'm gonna i'm gonna go over here chai
okay i'm gonna walk over it you stay on that one yeah you stay here
why can't i put this in the fryer because you don't have plates here okay even if i
didn't have plates i should be able to put it in the fryer can you throw on me a potato
look there's some chicken look all you have a new potato order all you have is a potato order so
just just serve that i know i know it sucks no i'm just confused why i can't fry oh wait i need
the fryer thing oh that's you chai uh silly mommy
silly righty okay chai stay there okay i'm gonna stay like i'm talking like a dog you stay
have a plate
i'm staying have this
potato i can't stick that in this okay
okay take this meat no i was waiting for i was just in order that because i was in order that
was in order okay there's also single orders of just like potato and chicken that's why i did that
it's fine it's fine i like the music for this one i know it's pretty good there's so much chicken
over there we need plates i can't fry anything because i need plates okay go go go put it down
and come back okay for me i'll go take i'll go take that and be try to be quick what square
do we need for this one me it was me it was me i know i just witnessed you died i was quite open
um hey you guys swim oh not well i'm the best swimmer okay we need 280 we need like a couple
more orders you have to bring that plate to her i'm a lifeguard oh really that's cool
why don't i believe you wait why did it get bad it got bad oh it's fine i got it oh i was like
what the hell okay what is this okay oh fries let me clean it thank you let me clean
that's a champion i know we'll wait for the fries
yeah wait what do we need what's going to do 80 at least max
oh that's okay we can do it again no we're gonna win this oh bullshit
269 come on come on come on come on come on
oh
i think we messed up on the double orders because there there was a lot of single orders
in this game but it was just chicky nuggies and fries how do you fucking mess that up
maybe they were too apart maybe they weren't good you know you alligator
he's bouncing oh i like it i like them i don't like his nose he did look like he's a good
nose alligator nose he seems to be having fun i'm having fun coming by he's having fun
hey i'm having fun my hands may be hurting but i'm having fun
i've never played with you guys before and i'm having so much fun
261 stop okay we need 400 for this after this i agree i know i would totally
consider that yeah i would have so much fun being friends if you guys or whatever blushes
what in the fuck nugget butt what am i oh my okay oh i already i already don't like how this is
i can't i can't she already thought okay it's fine don't worry about it
how am i supposed to throw shit i'm so excited for this what is this rice here you cook the rice
in the big pot and then we cook the meat i can't even oh i bet you it's okay okay
okay wait i'm gonna go on this side of sheebie because you're just really cutting and cooking
okay i almost fell okay i just need rice and this one yeah i'm coming i'm coming
i think i'll travel you'll travel wait wait put the dumb check
and i'll serve it great now we're in a worse place
yeah i kind of miss the wizards yeah this is yeah what are we doing this tortilla
uh don't say that in front of me how dare you how dare you how dare you how dare you
desecrate my lands hurricane Katrina more like hurricane tortilla
i'm sorry i'm trying to hide behind you let's try this
sorry okay like that yep yep yep can i grab this thank you i'll come back
shot see me don't worry me see me throw me when it comes
which type of me either one just try to grab whichever one that you can grab
oh my god okay well that's fine just do a drive-by
okay i need some i need some plates
we're gonna i'm gonna bring a plate oh what
can i show up okay
okay
oh you can just cross i can't pick this up
why are they doing this to us i hate it i need even bad girls
okay look chai plate oh wait i was in order let her mine oh okay i need a right here here
Here here here.
Put down put down.
And then rice I need as well.
I don't know if I can go over.
This meat this meat is this one is for this order.
Excuse me.
Oh yay!
I can't throw this.
No it's on the plate.
Oh thank you.
What?
She's going to go back to the other one.
Wait it's a good squinch.
It's a good squinch.
I don't understand.
I don't even really get it.
Rice.
Okay you got 140.
How's that looking?
We need 280 or something like that.
Okay.
I'm coming with you with plates chai.
These are rice.
Is there meat over here that's cooked?
Not yet.
Chicken? Yes.
Chicken.
Steak.
Plates are here.
Oh my god!
Oh my god the plate.
Okay.
Any cooked meats?
Wait.
Oh we're doing well.
We're really really close.
If we could just serve one more.
I need the tortilla.
I just put the one on the plate.
Oh I see.
Oh it's 400.
I thought it was 280.
Oh my god.
Alright.
This is difficult.
Difficult.
My brain would just sit to great plates.
What would you put?
Topping, gaming.
I don't know.
I don't know about that.
I think I'm too epi.
Epi. Epi. Wake up. Wake up shower girl.
Wake up.
The showers make me epi too.
I'm so tired.
I was gonna blame it on me being tired.
It's because you're a mom.
You're a mom.
After I have to wake up early.
You know.
The job.
Mommy's having a very early bed.
On the streets.
No.
No you're right.
I'm a high class escort.
You're high class.
People travel the world to see you.
Exactly.
To my hotel.
I can't even get my lore right.
No more I am.
Where am I?
Oh fuck me in the butt cheeks.
We can just throw the meat thankfully.
Cut these chai.
Oh what the fuck.
Oh no.
Just try to throw it.
Grab the rice.
Grab the rice that you need.
Okay I'm gonna go take this plate.
Cool.
There's a plate on the thing on the edge.
Just grab it.
Oh my god thank you.
I delivered it to you.
Thank you.
I need rice.
There's some rice.
There's a rice there already.
Rice me.
I can't throw the plate.
It would have been so much easier.
I swear couldn't we throw it before?
I don't think so.
I mean in a dream I had
I swear we could have thrown this.
Oh my god.
I have a dream about you Shibby.
Remember?
I can't remember.
I don't remember.
I think he told me that we hung out
or something.
I had a dream.
Me, you and Nori
we had to perform improv.
Oh yeah that's right.
But then Nori didn't show up
so we had to improvise.
We had to improvise.
That is so not me.
I fucking love improv.
Yeah.
You were busy that day.
You had stuff to do.
I have so much rice over here.
I need rice so bad.
It's gonna crash, it's gonna break it.
And then the minute we converge
I'm gonna grab those two
boiling things of rice.
Move bitch, sorry.
It's fine, it's fine.
There's an order right in front of you.
Grab.
I fell handed out.
I'm just grabbing tortillas
so I can grab them.
Now that order is done.
No, this rice isn't ready.
I was like that is a lot.
Here's a plate.
I'm stacking them up for you.
Can I not stack them up?
It's fine.
I'm gonna plate these for you.
No.
Oh that's ready.
So those two plates have
tortillas.
Tortillas.
Where are you?
People need me to say.
No I need those plates.
I really need it.
Thank you.
I need rice actually.
I have rice over here.
That's a plate as well.
Can I like...
You should be able to...
They're not cooked yet.
This one isn't cooked.
This one's cooked.
See you little lady.
That tortilla has rice in it.
Oh perfect.
I'm gonna cook some of these for you.
It's fine.
You have them.
You have any rice?
I gave you some rice.
It's right behind you.
Oh perfect.
Here's a bowl.
Yeah!
That's cool!
You can also just drop it in the ocean
like this.
Oh really?
If I drop this?
No not that.
I meant the bowl.
Oh the bowl.
Where am I?
Oh my god!
We did it!
All these girls had a dream where they played the same game.
Isn't that weird?
I know it's so weird how that happens.
I'm so in that dream.
Psychically connected or whatever.
Yeah I feel like I'm like, you know,
so connected to Sheebie
in some weird dream.
Weird dream.
She's my mother.
She's my mom.
Watching this makes me want food.
I know I want like,
I want like her burrito so bad.
Yeah this is me.
I did not eat and I'm hungry.
Same.
I only ate a bowl of cereal today.
Yeah!
I know I had a salad.
I had a cookie.
I only ate a bowl of cereal.
Hold on,
Siri's talking to me.
She scared the shit out of me.
Siri stop!
Siri! Hi Siri!
Wait I didn't mean to do that.
No Siri!
Wait what?
This is a nightmare.
I didn't mean to do that.
Hi Siri!
Call?
Do we have to go back to the castle?
Call mom!
Did Siri just dox me?
I couldn't hear what it was saying.
It just said your full name but that was all.
Oh okay, that's great.
She be caught in one.
She be caught in one?
My favorite cereal.
Wait oh my god.
Wait we can read it this time.
Because we're as new.
We can't read.
Is he going to talk to us?
Oh we have to go.
Bye bark!
Who's there?
Come at me if you want to.
Fuck. Oh thank goodness.
It's you and look at you.
So united, so cooperative.
Yes.
You're going from strength to strength at a rapid speed.
But the unbred are still too powerful.
Unbred.
Bark!
You think?
Oh dear, it seems we must send you
through the haunted swamps to the south.
I know, I know.
No one ever returns from Texas.
But these are desperate times.
No, no, no, no, no!
Texas, no!
You're brave, you're bold like Batman.
You're the greatest band who ever lived.
Why are we a band?
I don't like that.
Nothing can stop you.
Why are you waving?
Except maybe the possessed baguette.
That's been chasing Kevin around
all morning.
What?
Baguette.
There's no need to take his meds.
We will hold off the horde.
Now go!
Okay.
The swamp.
We're going to Florida, guys.
Wait, I can swear?
That's my little character.
Yeah, yeah, you see like bits.
I mean, they're really like kitchen.
Kitchen people, they curse a lot.
They're like, bit.
Bit.
Okay, this looks a lot easier.
Except it's probably not far.
I can't take my meds.
Oh, we know.
Japan.
Sorry, where are we, Chai?
Wait.
Oh, we're making sushi.
That's right.
Okay.
Wait, what am I?
Fuck!
No, no, no, guys.
No, guys, guys, guys.
Don't throw it back to me.
I'm trying.
I'm chopping and it does it.
Shrimp, shrimp, shrimp.
Don't try, try to put it back.
You didn't cut it.
Oh, let's die.
Shrimp.
Um, can I have sushi?
Cool.
Shrimp.
Oh, I need rice.
Oh.
Is this correct?
Who do I give this to?
Oh.
Imagine?
Imagine working at a kitchen where you had to
cross the street to hand it out.
Oh, wait, I need rice.
I need rice for this one.
This one needs rice. This is almost done.
Chai's just standing there.
Chai's making the brown one.
I mean, no, no, no, no, no.
Look at this girl.
She looks just like me.
She does.
Okay.
So, what do I do?
Cut that.
Oh, my God.
No, I put something down in front of me
and I fucked it up.
Wait, this is an order.
Excuse me, excuse me, sorry.
Sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry.
Excuse me, sorry, sorry.
Oh, there's one with just
shrimp the hell?
Yes, yes, yes, yes, I got it.
I got it in time. I got it in time.
Oh, well, this is useless. I need to dump this out.
Where's the trash?
Wait, I got so much rice.
Yeah, yeah.
Wait, that's not, is that?
I can't. Why is it?
I don't know.
It's making me confused.
I don't like it.
Why is it a taco?
Have you guys ever had like, um,
shrimp burritos?
No, I don't have that one.
It's a big burrito, but it's like shrimp.
Oh, okay, never mind.
Or I mean sushi.
Oh, yes, I've had a sushi burrito before.
I've never had sushi before.
You're fucking lying.
What do you eat?
Grass.
Why literally nothing sometimes?
I eat like a meal a day.
I'll just go about my day.
I'll just have like a piece of bread
and coffee.
It's like, alright, I'm gonna start my day.
That's just, yeah.
Oh, no, okay, it's fine.
Everything's fine.
We need three.
What?
We saw, okay, this is weird.
Okay.
We also have plain ones,
like the plain shrimp and the plain tuna.
Yeah.
Yeah, is it that normal to be able to eat
like not eat sushi?
I don't know.
I've had like
spring rolls,
but that's not sushi.
Oh, we can all go out for sushi.
A collab for sushi.
Yeah, I'm gonna have a burger,
a cheeseburger.
Oh, okay.
Listen to me, ladies.
I am going to bring you the fish
and you will cut it and I will bring you plates.
And then you will plate.
No, no, listen to me. You're gonna put the plates here.
Okay, you're not gonna move them.
You're not gonna...
It comes on the conveyor belt.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, like a sushi thing.
I'm sorry.
What?
Don't laugh at me.
Okay.
Okay, I need
a chai.
Okay, I need, okay, that's an order.
Put it on this side.
Give it to me, thank you. I will come back.
Oh, great.
Yeah, don't do anything with the shrimp yet.
We don't need anything with the shrimp.
We just need things with the tuna.
So here.
Here, this is one. This is one over here.
She's using her mommy voice on us.
She's serious.
I'm gonna wash this plate. Chai this plate is washed washed, okay?
Move you fat old bitch. Sorry
My apologies, I don't mean you I meant the person the pedestrian walking across the street
Yeah, but I've never had sushi before me, I don't know I feel like people
That shrimp
Okay, oh, I know this has rice on it. I didn't notice that I died by the way
By the way, I got it
Oh, hi cut this uh-huh, okay, that's an order. That's delicious. Oh
What the fuck he's pushing me
They're fat fat bitches. Oh
Yeah, not the wrong way found bitches. Oh stupid fat bitch
I
Really
No, there's no there's no shrimp
I wish I could throw this away like but I can't walk over there
I have to walk all over here to do it
Is there a oh, yeah, oh, yeah, there's literally just like an order of cucumber
Here's the order of crew cup real fuck
Do we do good
We did way better that time
It is better like I think it's getting to our brains our frontal lobes are opening up with new information
Mine isn't developed yet
Oh mine. I've been lobotomized one too many times
Aw group lobotomy I am lobotomy
I'm trying to develop yet. So I don't know anything. Oh my god. My booty cheeks hurt from homesick
I'll massage
Oh, yeah
I can be you each can get one cheek
Honestly, how big they are probably yeah
Like a bag
Oh, yeah
Try wake up
Okay, okay, okay, what we should do what the hell?
Okay
Guys listen to me listen to me listen to me. We don't need cucumbers yet. We don't need cucumbers yet
We just need the bluefish and and rice. So what we're gonna do
Put the the seaweed on plates already
Right and then it's just easier. So then that rice that's an order at the bottom. So now that there's cucumber ready
We don't we don't need that the shrimp yet. So I'm sending or the shrimp
That's an order
Okay
Sorry, I was in your waiting waiting waiting waiting. Hey, this is a done
Now we need shrimp, but the shrimp is literally only one thing
There's an order. Okay. There's an order here
I'm gonna bring this shrimp
I'm gonna cut it and we're just gonna pull
It's all right, we got this we're we're living we're living like Larry I got
And can you see long
Iskene this isn't really got you by you if you're in out. Oh fuck. I should have made that. Oh shit. Oh, that's whatever
Um, we need to see me and we need to see me stacked
Stacked
There you go
This is bad
I need to dump this out
I can't oh let me what the hell. Oh, I did wait. No
Oh, I need that sushi
Put that sushi on the plate put that sushi on the plate put that sushi on the plate. That's an order
That's that's an order the sushi that hot the sushi that got cut. Oh
Oh
This sushi that that's cut on the floor is an order like an actual order. So I'm trying to tell you guys
What sushi?
I got this
I'm coming out. I want the way to know
Got to let it show
I don't know what that song is. It's okay
It's fine
Pick up them
No, sorry. I don't know what the song is my bad
Point in the road, point in the road
Oh, we don't have any clean plates. It doesn't matter
No, I got one in my hand
We need to see that clean plate
No
Oh, I think we did better that time though. We did. We did way better
It got messy when we started moving
That's the problem
Yes, please check the girls out. They are absolutely lovely. I love them to death
Oh my god, it's like smiling
Oh, we were 50 away. Okay, super close. Okay. Okay. Let's do this again. Okay, but this listen to me ladies
Okay, I'm gonna put my head next to your heads. I'm really close and personal. Okay
I imagine imagine my forge push against yours
You me and cb
Are gonna stay on my left side cb and me are gonna bring the plates to these orders
You stay on my side. You don't move kid. Yeah, you stay on the left. You don't move. Yes
Okay
Wait, we don't have anything with shrimp right now. So what we need is just we just cut this up
I'm gonna put this on a plate
I'm gonna bring in another plate and then you're gonna just start you should have one plate with seaweed one plate with no seaweed
Just makes it a little easier for us right now
Okay
Here this is just literally just a shoot a shrimp or a day. Here you go. Yes. So put it on a plate
I'm gonna you got it. I'm gonna bring it. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah
I'm gonna bring it because I have to bring in a thing anyways. Okay
This plate needs to be cleaned
Okay, there's no sushi orders
Peace what there you go right there. There's the order
I can't reach that tuna
Oh, no
Oh, fuck me. Yes. I'm just gonna bring it. Oh my cat's walking in front of ice cream. I can't see
Oh my god
Okay, here try three picks on the plate. Thank you. Okay, I'll be back
No
What is that
Sometimes when you press it it just needs nori. This just needs nori and
Nori is this good? No
Hi nori this too. This too. This too. Can I try to wash these dishes? No cat get out of the freaking way
Ah
We're kitty. That's boomy
Boomy
Okay, we don't need anything. Okay. Next order is just seaweed rice cucumber
We don't need this yet. Okay, so someone make a seaweed rice cucumber order. I'm gonna bring a plate
Cucumber there's rice rice wait, let's cut it just a little bit longer
Boom bam bam boom. Oh, that's ready
Okay, uh, this is another cucumber order. We need another cucumber order. Okay, I'm gonna take it. Too ready. Too ready. Perfect
Oh my god
Oh, we are on fire. That's not an order. That's not an order. Oh
That fish order isn't an order. It's just rice seaweed cucumber. Okay, don't take it out. Just put it over there
Yeah
Oh, let me wash these dishes
Um, we need two shrimps cut up cucumber
Where's the shrimp at?
I died
I died. I'm gonna go throw this away
Oh my god, I think you saved the game chai you clutched up
Chai, watch it all last minute. Let's go chai
Oh
Good job chai. Good job. Without your brown ass chai couldn't do without you
Yeah, brown ass. Wait, wait, wait, wait
Hold on a second. Good job brown ass chai
Japan, Japan, Japan
Japan
So do you want to do one more or do you want to just like wind down and chat?
We can wind down and chat
I can chat
Let's chat. Let's chat. Do we have to save?
Um, no, I should save. Okay. We can just I can't make sure it's finished
Okay
Okay, okay. Okay. Are we gonna chat now? Like like like yeah, we're gonna like chat like we're like hanging out. Yeah
Oh my god, I'll make you guys bigger
I don't like that yours isn't like hot it makes me so nervous to square lady
Oh, you know
I'm sorry. I need it. I do need to change that
You have a model. Just do it. I I drew mine. Oh, yeah. Yeah. Yeah, I that's how I did mine
That's how I did mine
I know I just need to do me being open and close like
Okay, I'm gonna bring you I'm gonna bring you guys over. Oh, I forgot to say hi to people chat. I'm so sorry
I'm gonna be on this really quick just to say hi
Okay, just be a concerted a podcast if they all yeah for an hour probably yeah a little a
Podcast we can just talk about whatever. I saw podcast
Oopsie. You ready here?
I'm funny somebody laugh at my joke, please
Thank you chai. Oh my gosh. Thank you
Oh, you're welcome. Is nori dead? She died. Yeah, what happened to her? It's probably her mom came in again
No, no, no, I didn't say hi to people
Yeah, I I have them
Oh, wait, I just realized this the audio is not picking you guys up. I just realized that
This whole time
I was like
Very funny
Do you have any questions you want to ask um nautical and chai
Oh my god. Oh my god. I'm Q&A. Q&A. Oh my god. I just hit my toes so hard. Oh my god
You're so brave. You're so brave. You're so brave. Don't forget about how I'm gonna kiss it better. It'll be fine
You got those. Oh my god. My feet in your mouth
Flushings
Uh, favorite pizza topping
pepperoni and jalapeos
broccoli
Yeah
I like pepperoni and jalapeos and hot sauce on my pizza. That sounds good spicy
I like mozzarella and basil
Oh
Oh, like uh margarita. Yeah. Yeah margarita
Margarita
You guys gotta try broccoli on pizza. It's actually I don't know what I like broccoli and I'm like, hmm
But I like broccoli cheese does taste good. Uh, they will also they also want to know why do you have a four necklace?
Oh
I was just talking about this earlier. So I'm really um
Insecure about only having four toes on each foot
So it's kind of like a confidence building thing. You have four toes. Yeah
Someone's like wait like legit or no, I'm just joking. Okay
It's because chai is full with a four and I'm a devil and four
Is also known to be unlucky for like she she means. Oh, yeah, somebody pointed it out in my chat
Oh
Death and kill
But you're so cute
I don't know. I'm just a sweet angel
I don't know my bad
But see what I just did. Do they get it? They're like, yeah, they got it. Somebody guessed it initially
Yeah, very cool. A
Do they know that part? I like that. I think they know that
I'm so smart. I'm very creative like that
So, I'm gonna ask you guys put mustard and or ketchup on hot dogs
One, I don't eat hot dogs and two. I despise ketchup. I don't like hot dogs either
I think ketchup is fucking disgusting. I prefer sausages and then I just use them. I usually have them plain
Yeah, I'm from we have like salami
Yeah, exactly tons and I prefer that over a hot dog, but I hate hot dogs and I hate ketchup
I
I don't like the smell of
What? Oh no, they I've been
I've been they sound like schizo. I've been talking. I can't hear you. I've just been talking about broccoli
I'm talking about hot dogs and everything by myself alone
It's a crazy little lady
Like a crazy lady. You despised ketchup. I think the smell of ketchup is very over
I'm very autistic guys. It's it's really bad. Do you like the vinegar?
Yeah, I think it's the vinegar because I can I can eat things with vinegar, right? But ketchup
I don't know why it just makes me like I want to puke
I think it's gross. I like ketchup. It was nice. Do you like tomatoes? I love tomatoes, which is weird
Interesting. Yeah, so it must be like the combination of like the ketchup. I mean the tomato and vinegar and all that like salt
Yeah, ketchup does have a lot of sugar in it too
Yeah, yeah, ketchup not even tomato it's just
It's like tomatoes are so a dash of tomato puree
I love tomato. I can eat a tomato or I think I love tomato
Like an apple you just be like yeah, I've done that before
There's one time I was really hungry, but I want to cook anything. So you just grab the tomato and I just eat it with water
A tomato and water? A tomato with water? Yeah
All right
Like drinking water or or like putting
Yeah, I usually do a tomato with a little bit of salt and pepper and balsamic
Oh, yeah tomato and salt is so good
Like tomato slices with salt
I'm craving tomatoes
I think we're just really hungry
Wait, we talked about pizza. We talked about hot dogs. We talked about
Not at all. Oh, I have a question. What's your guys's favorites. Oh, okay. Wait. No. No. You say first. He's right first
No, you you you. No, you. No, please. No, please. I'm begging. Try
Okay, what's your guys's
Favorite snack like go-to snack
Johnny's
Uncrestable
Oh, wait for real. The uncrestable thing is real
I like the crustables
I know, I know, I know, I know, I know
But I didn't know it was like that. Well, no, I don't usually have those
I haven't had an uncrestable in like maybe like a week and a half. So I'm kind of struggling right now
Um, my go-to snack
I've never had an uncrestable before
You guys are missing out. Um
What is my go-to snack?
I don't know. Probably like some mixed nuts. I like nuts
Oh, what's your favorite nut?
Honey roasted almonds
I don't have nuts. Oh, honey.
That's nuts. Sorry.
Ah, I know. I don't have one.
Jokes on you. I don't have one of those.
Fucking rude.
Tithe
I don't know how.
Wait, I'm gonna let you guys know that I'm a technological god
I don't like
Trashy nuts
Uncrushable looks like an empanada
I know. It's like a PB&J empanada
Oh
A little PB&J pasalito, you know, just like um, um, um, um, delicioso
Oh, okay
I'm just gonna pretend I'm looking at you
So, honey, honey roasted almonds
Mm-hmm. Those are pretty good
Okay
You aren't like a bunny. You're like a bunny dying. I like strawberries as a snack
And maybe like
Maybe like this yogurt. I uh
I buy like the little baby yogurts, you know, like the little baby smoothies is like a little plastic thingy. I eat those
Yeah, I love strawberries
I love I love suckable snacks
Like, you know the applesauce that comes in the little pouch
Yeah
Yeah, like yeah suckable snacks. Mm. Yes. I see a couple watching us today
You know go-go squeeze, don't you? Yes. I actually have some of my friends
I remember. Yeah. Yeah. When we first met, you know, you said something you like knew what go-go squeeze was and I was like
She's the one
I feel bad because I'm not Americans. I have to like, okay. No, I know what that is. Yeah, those are good
I call them something different. Those are good. Yes. Yeah. I'm like, I think you've had this before
Yeah, those are the ones I steal
I love smoothies. Uh
That's suckable. Hey Chief, do you speak Spanish? Uh, Un poquito
Oh
Kisses you sorry
Uh, you should you should speak Spanish
No, you know my Spanish is bad
But it's okay, I I would like be like you could speak to me. Spanish
You can speak Spanish is okay. No, no, no, no.
Nothing to worry about
Wait, your accent is coming out when you're speaking, sorry, no!
Am I Spanish?
Yeah, your Spanish accent just came out for a second.
Yeah, I know, I'm sorry, man. I'm fucking, you know, so, my bad.
My speak bad people.
I'm always surrounded by Spanish women.
Yeah, don't you like it?
They can't get enough of me, I don't think.
Oh, let me have more.
Yeah, yeah, you'd be like that.
Wait, do you guys want to have, like, a private call after this?
Like, an ASMR exclusive? She'd be so Spanish.
Oh, well, this was for two, I just, like, turned on my 3DO,
and then you guys just fall asleep to me.
I don't know, just, like, a random, that was just random.
Yeah, yeah, no, I'll give you a little treat, you know,
we can come up with a scenario, and I, you know, maybe,
maybe I can give you some previews to, um, my Patreon audios.
Wow!
Oh, hell yeah!
I'm sorry, I mean, yes, please, I'm completely normal.
Hola, preciosa, ti amor.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, I'm like,
Hola, mi princesas, como toda hoy, como estas, mi princesas.
Hola, mis princesas.
Ya, mi princesas.
Mi princesas?
Mi bebes.
Mi carios.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, cute, cute pet names.
It should have been me, it's never gonna be you, by the way,
it's always gonna be me.
I don't know, no, our second language in Canada is French,
so, like, I got zero Spanish skill.
I got zero Spanish game.
I don't know how to, I just know how to say my name,
and I was not gonna say my name in French.
It's just...
Xemaphone, China!
Xemaphone, Nauri, Kao.
Xemaphone, Shibi.
I can do a corn.
Like, can you guys do any accents?
Oh, it's hard to accent.
Like, what's hard to accent?
Like, I don't know.
What the fuck was that?
Australia!
Wait, wait, I got a word about...
What?
Down by the river!
Perfect.
What the fuck is this?
Australian!
I'm Australian!
See?
I can't, my cheeks hurt too much.
I can only do, like, a southern accent,
but then I get to really racist really fast,
so I won't do that.
Wait, how can...
How is a southern accent racist?
It just brings out the best in me.
Oh, I see what you mean.
Like, it just...
The America just takes over.
Yeah, America, the fucking...
American, I mean.
Today!
Should we normalize Peter Griffin ASMR roleplay?
What?
Peter!
Peter, I don't know why she's...
Hoss is here.
Chad, you should try Scottish.
Can you do a Scottish accent?
Yeah, do it, do it.
Me?
Yes.
Thank you.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, scrolling!
Just scrolling!
Does it sound like just mimic Shrek?
Don't care!
What are you doing in my swamp?
Yeah, I'm not swamped.
Or...
Let's go daddy to Pullman get some...
tall points.
That's right.
Yeah, that's right.
Kind of blends...
Yeah, yeah, I always slip into British
when I try to do Australian or Scottish.
The Yankee, isn't Yankee like the...
the...
New York.
Yeah, yeah, East Coast.
And walk in here.
I'm walking in, I'm walking in!
Yeah, wait me!
They need to turn into Australia?
It just keeps going back?
I can't control it!
Say optimize my performance in a British accent.
What?
Optimize...
Optimize my performance.
Oh, mommy, sweet Jesus.
If I...
If I was a boy, if I was a boy,
my weenie would be very wrecked.
It's a really stigma card, you.
My clip just jumped.
This is really deactivating you.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
What does that even mean?
Is this German accent?
I can't do it.
I can't do German.
I think I can do it.
I think I really have to focus,
and then it comes out.
It's like out of my control sometimes.
Who can make the most racist accent challenge?
I got you.
Probably Nori.
Right.
Actually...
I definitely can.
Southern...
Dad, I'm down in Texas today.
All right, that's pretty good.
I'm gonna get in my truck,
and I'm gonna go get some guns.
You're gonna get some guns?
I love Americans.
I love me and my guns.
I love being American.
My first amendment right is my pistol whipping guns.
I have a large gun point.
You know the Capitol.
Choo!
Yeah, let's go raid the Capitol.
No, no, Tommy.
Let's go storm that Capitol building.
Oh, yeah, let...
Yee-haw, let's do that.
Yeah, let's do that.
What gun would I use?
I would use an AK-47 or a military-grade gun.
I'll tell you what.
I'll use a goddamn military-grade gun
if I have to shoot down the goddamn...
Games?
Yeah, shoot down the range.
Take advantage of the second amendment.
I love taking advantage of the second amendment.
What's the second amendment?
I think it's like guns.
I think it's the right to bear arms.
No, America.
I love eagles.
Well, I love eagles and I love...
It's my sister.
What's that kilometer?
I don't know American freedom units.
Artificial flavors.
I'll go Alabama.
I'll go Alabama if she be right now.
I'll tell you what right now.
I love my mother.
K-Y-S, which means kiss your sister.
Don't mind if I fucking do.
I'll true, I'll true that.
True that, true that.
Someone asked in your chat,
what D&D race and class would you all play?
Necromancer.
And I'd be like the smallest class ever.
So a half-foot or a dwarf.
But I'd be a necromancer.
I was also going to say necromancer
and I'd probably just be an elf.
Wait, what's the question?
Oh, what D&D class and race would you be?
Oh, I would be a dark elf rogue.
I totally see that, yeah.
Gonna be black?
Are you black?
I think we've already established
that Chai has wanted to be black this entire stream.
Oh my god, he's not swear.
He loves you so much.
Chai wants to race mix.
It's a coincidence, it's a coincidence.
She wants to make many versions of me.
Ever since I was young, I felt like I was Japanese.
That's so true.
In every state but physical, I am Japanese.
Hi.
I represent Japanese.
I'm all level.
You're so dead to your heart.
I am a wolf.
Is that the CbCottenbum and Chai?
Oh yeah, I guess I'm fucking Rico, I guess.
Fuck me, I guess, man.
Fuck.
Fuck the person.
Well, I don't know where to look.
Someone went inside the CbCottenbum and Chai.
Yeah, please.
Why is there two of me?
Oh, one more moment.
Why not two of you?
There was two of me for a second on my stream.
What would Chai look like if she was white or Chinese?
Well, she's white now.
No, no, no, they think I'm brown.
Keep it up, keep it up.
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah.
This is what you would look like if you were white or Chinese.
Yeah, I only hang out with streamers that fake the rig.
Yeah, we're all beautiful, Aryan queens, blue eyes, blonde hair, pale, pale skin.
Like you can see our veins.
I'm actually pretty light-skinned, but you can see my veins and I get made fun of.
Now, I turn over my arm and my veins are like very matte.
People are like, good veins, little lady, your veins are so good.
That's when they draw your blood.
Do you have blue veins?
I have green.
I got blue and green.
Yeah, I have green.
Oh, wow, we got a mixture.
Maybe it's because I'm white and black.
Wow, that's all you're talking about.
You're a race, race mixer.
I'm a race mixer.
My parents, they, their loves surpassed race and segregation and they made me.
Disgusting, you're an abominant.
Oh, wait.
You're an abominant.
I'm so sorry, Chai.
What would you guys, okay, in like a casual way, like, what would animal do you most associate?
What's your spirit animal?
Oh, my, my hamster.
Hamster?
Yeah, because I think, I think hamsters die in the most obscure way.
So I feel like my owner would throw me at a wall and I would just go splat and like crumble and die.
I'd be like a pathetic excuse of a hamster.
I wouldn't be able to do anything.
So that's why it's your spirit animal.
Because they're pathetic.
Yeah, just like me.
What are you guys?
What are you guys guys?
I don't know what the fuck I was saying.
I'm just laughing too much.
I can't even answer.
Chibi thought she was the one who was edgy.
No, I know the moment I had, I was going to have Noria in my stream,
that you guys are going to fucking love her because how face she is.
And that's a great juxtaposition to Chai, who is so sweet.
You would think she'd be edgy with how she looks, but it's the pink one.
It's always the fucking pink one, isn't it?
It's always the fucking pink one.
It's always the fucking the pink woman.
Well, you're a purple woman.
I'm glad if you do.
Yeah.
No, I don't know.
I just think about it a lot.
Like if I was like, if I was a hamster, I would genuinely
I would genuinely die.
I don't know.
My owner would be too loud and I would just have a hard time.
I would just die.
My owner would bring a girl home and I'd kill myself like in my little cage or something.
I don't know.
Like I.
What?
What about you guys?
Dude?
Yeah, she knows this.
I want to pretend it.
I think on all levels, except physical, I'd be a wolf.
What?
I'm fucking a wolf.
I was a fucking role player for like 10 years.
I can't.
Wait, wait, yes.
I can't do that.
Yes, yes, yes.
Wait, I was a warrior cat's role player for so long.
Oh my god, no way.
Yes.
See, let's let it go.
Oh my gosh.
Can we start our own clan?
Yes.
I want to be Chai Pa or Chai Leaf.
I'm going to call you Chai Leaf.
That's actually really cute.
I guess I would be like cotton pick.
No, sorry.
I'll be cotton, cotton.
It's a perfect name for you.
Cotton bum.
Yeah, you just literally wouldn't have a furring.
What would my warrior cat name be?
I don't know.
Because when I was a kid, we role played like Naruto.
So I was like.
I also did that.
I also larped, you know, Naruto.
Yeah, I've larped enemies like a fucking loser.
Why does everyone have a membership?
Because they want to support me.
The.
Yeah.
Get out of here.
Gray name.
Yeah, leave my leave my leave my mommy alone.
Thank you for that.
You leave my you leave my mommy alone.
I love my mommy.
My sweet precious children.
Wait, so would you be a cat then, Chai?
Honestly, I think I always thought honestly.
I don't know.
I think I'd be a bunny.
Oh my gosh.
No way.
Be a bunny.
Yeah, I actually do think so.
I think I think a bunny.
That's cute.
You kind of almost have like floppy ears,
like like mine with your pigtails.
Yeah, too.
The floppy.
Because your hair is super long.
We're actually, I'm looking at us.
We're very similar, similar color palette.
Looks like a flat version of you.
My hair is just a little bit more blonder.
And I'm just going to canonically adopt you
and say that I slept with harem, a demonic harem.
Yeah, demonic harem.
That's why you have horns.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, mommy.
We're going to adopt you.
Flap is justice.
Speaking of justice, we overlapped with their diffuse today.
I'll have to go back and watch the VODs.
We are cute.
I want to, I want to, I want to,
I want to be adopted with a hat.
You're my pet, you're my pet bug from the garden.
Remember, I keep you in my palm.
From the garbage.
This, this pocket has a lot of lint
and like those cool little crumbs in it.
And that's okay.
Some moss and stuff.
It's okay.
You can crawl around and ride between my boobies and stuff.
I did that during your debut, by the way.
Yours and Azura's.
I sat on your top.
I think I actually saw that in the, uh,
when I watched your VOD back.
That's right.
I heard Azura's voice.
I'm so sorry.
She's not here.
Thank God.
I heard Azura's voice and good lord.
If I, if I was a man, if I was a man,
I'm telling you the things I would do,
I would do for that woman.
Oh, wow.
She does have like, when I first heard her voice,
I almost, I almost died and went to heaven
because it's just pure sex.
I wanted to lift those things up and just
look at the sweat between them.
I don't know, man.
And she just, she just makes me a different person
thinking about her.
I want a voice like that.
Right.
Like she's, I don't know, man.
She was cooler, whatever, but Azura.
That's true.
I can't really compete with her voice.
Oh, sure.
But her voice surpasses.
Now, but you're, but you're, but you're my Oshi.
I'm your Oshi?
Yeah, you're my Oshi.
You're fucking lying.
Don't say that.
Oh, I'm going to cry.
Toma told me the same thing and I'm,
I'm literally going to lose it.
I'm going to cry into my pillow because they
don't deserve anybody's love.
Yep.
Yeah, you're right.
Who's who?
The really white one either we go.
And the beautiful, sexy blonde here,
devil girl.
I'm really cute.
Devil boy.
Here's his tie.
Sexy.
I got sexy.
She's a sexy little thing.
My sexy, my sexy daughter.
Whoa.
Yeah.
And the pet bug, I guess.
And my, um, garbage.
No, that's worse.
I prefer, I prefer, uh, she's just my little,
my little buggy daughter.
Um, no, the vaude is not getting nuked.
The vaude is not getting nuked.
Woo!
The first one!
First one you can keep up.
Wait, do you have to nuked vods?
I, I usually have to like cut or edit vods
or delete them completely because I will
just say really dumb shit that I'm not
supposed to say on YouTube.
But I say even more worse shit than I did on Twitch.
The price you pay.
I don't even know why.
Okay.
I didn't know that.
Yeah.
You should watch, uh, honestly,
Nori, you should play Class of 09.
I know you'd like that game.
I'm a, I'm a, I'm a visual novel elitist,
so I don't play anything that gets like
touched by normies, I guess.
Like once it's in a normie scene, I'm like,
I definitely don't think it's a normie game.
I don't think it's a normie game.
I, I, I've seen it.
I like visual novels.
Maybe I'll play it one day.
Yeah.
I highly, I think you're-
I feel like if I play it, I start crying.
Yeah.
I would like to see the both of you play it,
or maybe we'll do a collab where you, we go through,
we go through, uh, the visual novel
and just commentate on it.
That would be funny.
You would love that.
What's an Oshi again?
An Oshi is like, it's, okay,
it's like a huge dork for people that are new TV to be.
It is idol culture thingy.
So you have like, kind of like in K-pop,
you have a bias.
It's like one person in like maybe a group
or like an individual that you really, really enjoy
and you are constantly keeping like up with.
So like, my Oshi would be Chibi.
You know what I mean?
Like, I keep up with Chibi,
but my Kami Oshi is like, Ina.
I have so much Ina merch.
It's so bad.
I made for Chibi to make merch.
I didn't know that, uh, your, your Kami Oshi was Ina.
That's actually cute.
I do have-
Make myself purple for like,
every Vtuber that I've liked so far is purple.
So I just make myself purple.
Now that I really think about it.
All my favorite Vtubers are purple.
You're the only red Vtuber that I like.
I was supposed to be purple.
Look! I'm leaving!
I'm leaving!
You're my, there's, wait,
but Ty, you're my friend.
And Oshi will never notice me.
You're the only red Vtuber.
You're in-
Oh!
I meant my Oshi's.
He's sitting there.
Oh, okay, okay.
She's like, I like you.
Um, but yes, I do have merch since you mentioned that.
My merch is in my description.
A wink.
You can get your own, own a hole.
I'm kidding.
That's not true.
What?
You know-
No!
I actually, I might, I might buy it.
See, if you make my keychains and pins,
just ping me,
because I'll make a bag dedicated to you.
Aw, thank you.
That's really, very nice.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'm like a really big j-
like fucking, what is it?
I don't nerd.
Sort of this like,
I'm, I'm sorry if I'm rambling.
I know.
Um, it's really, it's really cute when people have like bags,
like eat a bag.
So there's like a thing where it's literally the same merch
and one bag.
I didn't know that was-
I forgot what they're called.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So if you do that, let me know.
I have three for Ena.
That's really cute.
I didn't know that, Nori.
That's so adorable.
Hey, you just, yeah, this is just,
let me know.
I'm like, I like, I like pins and keychains.
Pick you up and smush you against my bosom.
You're so fucking adorable.
I would genuinely love that.
If you start feeling biting, ignore that.
Oh.
Don't say Ona Oshihou.
That's disgusting.
This is a safer work chat.
You hear that?
I may be screaming with a woman that does-
I might be a woman of the night,
but the other girls are not.
They don't do the sort of content I do.
So please do not think or assume or give them,
like, or sexually harass them or anything
because they don't make that content.
They're just, you're, you know, sweet, say-so.
In some ways.
Oh, yeah?
Yeah.
Oh, you're talking about us.
You're talking about us.
Oh, yeah.
I'm just edgy, ma'am.
What's the difference?
I don't know.
Once you get into the private chat in my Discord,
it's a little crazy.
Is it girl-central?
Once you get into VC with me, it's bad.
Groom!
Are you getting groomed by your moths?
No, you have to do the grooming yourself.
Honestly, Chai-Chai would do the grooming.
She just, like, she comes off as like,
I'm so sweet and innocent,
and then she'll just fucking groom the fuck out of you.
I'd be okay with that.
Same.
I'm here.
I'd be okay.
I don't know what I should say.
All right, Chai-Chai.
Uh-uh.
Let me, uh, look at the-
Oh, no.
Oh, my God.
And say thank you.
I feel kind of bad,
because I feel like I rumble a lot.
Oh, Chai-Chai.
You're fine.
I feel the same thing.
My-my chat knows-
Chai-Chai, this is our podcast.
You can say whatever you want.
My chat knows how much I app, so they-
They-
I guess.
Love you and Chai for the same reason.
Why do you act like I don't watch your streams?
Woman, I'm there.
I know that.
I'm there.
What do you mean?
I haven't seen your name!
Are you lurking?
Oh, I just look type.
God.
Okay.
Because I want to-
I get-
I get scared when people notice me.
I don't-
Actually, I feel the same way, so-
Okay, I'll never notice you ever.
I'll never perceive you.
No!
It's like, I don't want to explain it,
because then sometimes their chat starts talking to you,
and you're like,
oh, my God, please don't.
Please, I want to pee everywhere.
Don't do this.
You're gonna pee everywhere?
Yeah, I know what you mean.
Sometimes when you-
It's like, it's-
It's exciting when you talk in a French chat,
because then you're like,
oh, my God, hi!
But then you're like, oh, no, I'm like,
I don't know.
It's like-
Because like, you're taking away a pension from-
Yeah, yeah, yeah, right?
This was really bad.
I felt like, oh, yeah, oh, yeah, yeah.
That's why I usually only say one or two things,
because I don't-
Like, especially with my gen mates,
because sometimes people move the chat's focus on me.
So I'm just like, I'll say hi,
and then I'll be like-
Yeah, quiet.
Quiet.
Yeah.
You're gonna be like, yeah.
What?
Were you just underwater?
Oh, it's hilarious.
Someone in my mic panel kills itself.
Oh, so I just noticed-
Can you guys hold your arms?
Yeah, I'm Hispanic.
Try.
Sorry.
I'm so sorry you're Hispanic.
Yeah, my bad.
I'm sorry, guys.
I am-
I'm sorry.
I know.
I'm gonna hold the box and see.
Ha-ra, ha-ra, ha-ra.
Ha-ra.
Rrrr.
Ha-ra, ha-ra-ee-ba.
Ha-ra-ee-ba.
I want to learn how to purr.
Rrr.
It's the favorite word.
OK.
Hold on.
I'm gonna definitely say thank yous for Dota's and shit.
I'll be right back.
Okay, go do it.
Do it.
I love them so much there.
Oh my God.
I'm so thankful to have them as friends.
It's been a deep up too strong.
It's been a good present.
Yeah, that's what the conversation
will turn to with these two.
But thank you, Charlie.
She'd be pleased for giving me
from about to do bark, bark, bark, bark.
Thank you for the five bucks.
But thank you for the shibbity toilet.
Thank you for the tip, boy.
She'd be playing with her two daughters, so wholesome.
Thank you for the $20 two-tool, beep, beep, bless.
I haven't heard that in a long time.
Please let Nori know.
She has a whole paper set in her, your chat.
She can risen up.
Oh, she knows, she knows.
Thank you, Morgan.
But thank you guys.
I already know that you guys are having as much fun as me.
I don't even have to ask.
All right, watch, I'm an undefined
and they're probably me saying the most ridiculous shit.
It's like, oh, nice, happy, happy times.
That's exactly just how it feels sometimes.
Yeah, I had a nap.
I also had a nap.
I was scared I wasn't gonna wake up in time for the collab.
But I was genuinely like, if I sleep now,
I don't know if I'll wake up on time.
Yeah, I set an alarm.
I feel like, yeah, you know when you have those naps
where it's like you're, oh, home.
She back?
I went back.
I was just like, I was like listening to you guys talk.
Oh, cute.
To each other about her napping.
I'm talking about her napping.
I had really stressful dreams because like,
I feel like I went, I napped.
Like, I was like, okay, I have to like get up
after this stuff.
I have to, oh wait, raid, raid, raid.
Wait, oh my God, raid.
Hold on a second.
Oh, she's gone.
Thank you for the raid.
Oh my God.
Oh, she's muted.
What the fuck?
She's like, I disappeared.
She was shrimped.
What was it gonna say?
I take naps all the time.
I have a nap time schedule.
Like a pod board.
I've napped for like probably three hours today.
So that's why I don't know why I'm still so tired.
Yeah, I sleep at three or five.
No, in between, I'm just a child.
I know it's hard because I stream in my time slot
at the same time that I would normally nap.
So I have to nap earlier.
So then I sleep later or I nap later
and I sleep later and then I wake up at like 11.
I don't go to sleep until like five a.m.
and then I wake up at like 10 a.m., 10 p.m., 10 a.m.
all the time.
I have a horrible sleep schedule.
Don't nod.
I'm sorry, I've been yawning.
I'm yawning.
So I'm sorry.
Container.
You didn't go while you didn't go.
I'm boring or something.
No, I love you, stop.
Me, me, me, me.
Also, I'm so sorry, it's hair on my hair.
Yeah, hair on my hair.
Oh my God.
I made your, you're too much stream-solid.
It's the only time slot I'm available.
It's fine, they understand.
No, it's, you're guilty about it.
No, I don't feel guilty.
They're, I bet they believe that it was worth it
so they got to meet you and try.
So.
I hope so.
Yep.
I hope they liked it.
Yeah, I hope they did.
I'm just not, I'm gonna be all sad
when I lie being around you.
No.
Yes, I missed you.
I missed you a bunch.
All right.
No, you didn't miss me.
We just met.
What am I talking about?
We spent a little night.
You just met.
It's just the dreams.
You've just been in my dreams.
So it feels like we've known each other for months.
You've worked with me in my dreams.
What's happened to dreams, really?
I can tell you one of them.
I'm actually, I've had dreams.
It was weird though, cause he felt like,
you know, like you ever have like,
it's like we were an animic.
It was like in the real world.
So it was like you, but I was like a real person.
I don't know how to explain it.
Was I white or was I brown?
You were kind of tanned.
You were like tan.
Interesting.
You were like a tan.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
But, but there was like a weird dream
and we were just talking to me
and like you were holding my hand.
I was like, oh my God.
She's touching me.
Oh my God.
Yeah, like she's touching me.
She's touching my hands.
Oh my, oh my days.
Oh, good Lord.
Oh my days.
I would love to go to a convention with you.
That'd be fun.
There's, I am hopefully planning to go to one.
I don't think you are,
I don't think your place of work is very far
from my little, my little hole in the hole.
Hi!
Hi, Ty.
Oh, did you guys know that I quit my job?
Yeah, I saw that.
So I can, I can probably just
chalk myself across the states and go to you.
Wait, we're meeting in person?
No, I mean, like we're just,
she was telling me she had a dream
that we went to a con together.
And I was like, oh, I love what we're talking.
Koreans grind, Koreans grind.
Thank you for the follow.
Oh, oh, I was like, oh, good about Korean's that grind.
Oh, I love Korean's.
Wait, Noriko, someone said more,
Noriko, more like stinky co.
I just thought you should know that.
I learned them.
Who said that?
Give me, give me.
Their names?
Self mechanic.
I was going to ban them,
but they're a certified tune,
but I don't think I should ban them.
No, you should just
flick them really hard in the forehead.
Why in the forehead?
Because that's where I remember my mom was.
Oh, you said flick them.
I've heard something else.
Yeah, you flick them in the forehead.
I thought you said fuck them in the forehead
and I was a little bit confused.
Oh, I guess from like the lobotomy.
Oh, yeah, there you go.
Well, that's kind of like the eye socket.
Doll spoon.
Oh, that's such silly little names, huh?
Okay, are we going to a con?
I want to go to a con with you guys.
Do you guys like the cosplay?
I'm too.
I do like the cosplay.
I cosplayed myself.
They're so good.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Huge boobies.
You have pictures.
I just noticed that one of you guys
sounds like Ruby Rose from Ruby.
Which one?
I don't think it's me.
Huh?
I get told I sound like Mabel in Peridot.
Oh, you do?
Oh, that's actually true.
Oh my God, that's so true.
You sound like Peridot.
That's so real.
I know, I get to sound like Peridot a lot.
Wait, who do I sound like?
Who do I sound like?
I want to sound like you from Ruby.
I think they say, yeah, they think you
sound like Ruby Rose from Ruby.
That's cool.
Me?
Yeah, you.
Ruby Rose?
Is that the girl with the red hair?
Yeah, black and red?
Oh, she has some color palette, too.
Oh my gosh.
I got to hurt the typing.
Wait, like Ruby Rose, like Ruby Rose,
like the not like the Australian model in action.
No, not.
No, no, no, Ruby Rose.
You sound just like her when you do your Australian accent.
How do you do that?
Australia.
What?
My chat also agrees that they kind of hear the Ruby.
Who's Ruby?
Kind of, who is it?
Ruby Rose.
Oh, you know, oh, I send it to you.
It's a little like red girl, is it not?
With the red hair.
I never watch Ruby, so I don't know.
Not gonna go.
Guys, I'm feeling stupid.
Oh, that girl.
Also, wait, Chai, do you?
Oh, wait.
What the fuck is this GIF?
You cost, it's from the show.
The show sucks, by the way.
I didn't watch the first season.
Chai, did you watch the show?
I was really proud.
Have I?
Yeah.
I want you so bad, I beg and I plead and I pray and I ask.
It's just a lot because of the jacket.
I gotta get the jacket commissioned.
That's true.
But everything else I can figure out,
like 3D printing, like certain parts,
and like the cuffs and the chains.
You know how to 3D print?
I can, I have the ability to.
I don't have a 3D printer, but I know someone who does.
Oh, that's pretty cool.
And I get down on my hands and knees and say, please.
Please.
I think it would work out.
I do cosplay, though.
I just got back from a convention.
I cosplayed three different ladies.
I was freerun, freerun.
Oh my gosh, you would be so good as freerun.
I did her dinner, dinner.
Oh my gosh, I have to.
I can show you guys pictures.
Please.
Yeah, I think they're really appropriate.
I have a blue archive cosplay that just arrived of Hoshino.
And I also cosplayed a chopper from One Piece.
Oh, that's funny.
Do you have pictures of that one?
Yeah, I'm getting into One Piece.
I'm still getting into One Piece.
Yeah.
I watched the Netflix live action.
Yeah, that was pretty good.
It hooked me in like, OK, now I have to kind of watch the show.
Oh, yeah, I did watch the live action, too, yeah.
I would love to cosplay, but I have really bad anxiety,
so I don't leave my home enough to do that.
I haven't cosplayed in years at an actual convention.
It's been a very, very long time.
It's a whole other night.
Cosplaying at home is a lot less exhausting.
I don't know.
It's just like, I guess the fear of buying a cosplay
and then be like, I should have, like, work with you.
Oh, like, yeah, if it doesn't get all the money right.
My boobs usually don't fit into a lot of things,
so I'd have to play a very big, boobed character.
Yeah, I have that problem, too.
I have that problem, too.
Yeah.
My point.
Chai's body type is essentially her model, Koff.
It's really sad.
My model is taller, though.
I think my model would probably fit into cosplays
better than I could, just because of me.
I think I'm smaller.
She's so small.
It's like, sucks.
Yeah.
It's like, oh, cute.
There are a lot of really cute characters in my opinion.
I feel like you can ask me a lot of hard things.
Sometimes they make the small.
Sometimes the small isn't even, like, small.
I don't know.
I think I'm just, I'm just stubby.
No, I'm stubby.
For me, it's a lot of the time the cosplay parents
never go past my buttocks.
She's got a fat ass.
Yeah, my bag.
Yeah, yeah.
She's small with a fat ass.
Wait, don't be boob fat ass.
And let me have you.
You need to, man, too.
And then your little cute pet hunt.
OK, I'm also kind of, I'm also kind of pet-on,
so it's fine.
Yeah, you're also a pet-on, yeah.
Now we start that in sim.
It's just my butt.
That's the Hispanic jeans.
Just hit her there.
Yeah, it's just my butt.
I don't know why.
I don't understand.
I also haven't cosplayed in a long time
because people sometimes when you're brown
and you cosplay a white character.
Oh my god, it's so bad.
They just bitch and moan and I'm like, I don't.
Yeah.
You get called like the hard-art name version
of the character.
It's so, it's so, it's so mad.
It's like, damn, it's like they kind of got me there.
They'll be like, N-word, Shinobi or something like that.
I think I've seen that for like Gojo when somebody was
cosplaying as Gojo.
That's like the one thing that works.
No, no, no, I've seen somebody like a black Gojo
and people just fucking ragged on them.
It's ridiculous.
The cosplay community is like, it's just, you know,
like the cosplay community just kind of sucks.
Like it's very toxic and it's not warm and fuzzy
for the most part, but I can tell you.
Which is sucks because it's like, OK, this is not really weird.
I think when anime got mainstream and all the very
attractive people started doing cosplay,
it kind of ruined the vibe of like, oh, it's just a bunch
of nerds having fun together.
I agree, but it's like, when anime-
It's like Hot Girl Central.
Yeah, because it's like, in my opinion,
I appreciate like a more like messy looking cosplay
because like you can tell that they really like the character
than like a full blown, like full glam cosplay
because it's just for photo shoots.
Like, um, anime becoming popular sucks, it's so bad.
It's like retubing, too.
Like, it's so bad.
It's very mainstream, though.
It's sad. It is sad.
And it sucks to like say it because then you sound like
like a gatekeeper, like even gatekeeper.
But it's like, but it's true.
It is true because like the feeling of like the anime,
the community, the cosplay community and all that, like,
it was so different before like 2020, I'd say, like 20.
Yeah, 2020, like right around the pandemic,
when it did get really popular.
It was like, oh my God, yay.
All the people who bullied me, like finally, like,
now you guys can see it's cool.
But at the same time, like a lot of, yeah.
But yeah, exactly right.
Like, God damn, this is like, this is my thing.
It's like, yay, I know, it's supposed to be my thing,
where I was supposed to be like this little geek.
Like, they do it better because they're like hot and sexy
and like have a lot of.
It also sucks that a lot of anime is going to be very weird
and have very like obscure themes.
And then people are like, this is disgusting.
And it's like, even then, it's like, I could,
there's some anime that I'm like, you know,
that's a little too weird for my taste,
but I'm not going to show people that, like,
it's like the weird, like, puritan thing
people have going on with, and like just the anime.
Yeah.
And then like, oh my God,
so I could talk about this topic for hours.
It's like a different kind of like,
cause it's like initially, like it was like,
oh, I feel embarrassed that I like this stuff
because they're bullying me for liking anime.
Yeah.
But now that they know, it's like they have
all these things to say, like, oh, this is wrong.
You can't like this, but you can't like this.
You can't like this, you can't like this.
Like now that they're like, you know,
they're more familiar with it.
Yeah, they're dictating what's wrong.
It's like, no, no, no, no.
Happening with visual novels as well.
I have noticed that I've seen some stuff.
And it's really bad, cause in my opinion,
visual novels is the one medium
where people can be really weird.
There are some really like weird, disturbing visual novels
and people are like, oh, but the girls are cute,
but this game is so icky and gross.
You know, the place is weird.
It's like, maybe you look into the characters
before you're like, I'm in a cosplay-less character.
Yeah.
Saiyan Uta Kof Kof.
I think Afumo is,
Afumo should have never existed for Saiya.
I know, I was, I saw seeing a lot about that
on my timeline, just like Saiya blowing up and-
Yeah, Saiya's blowing up and people that hate the things
that Saiya talks about are like, I love Saiya.
She's so cool.
And it's like, you would not like the game,
but it's okay.
But then anime and VTuber are coming mainstream
was a mistake.
Gay keep it.
Push the little show.
Gay keep it, let's gay keep.
It's like, I don't want to gay keep,
cause it's like, I think it's fun to like
see VTuber merge in public,
but then it's like, it sucks when people are like,
this VTuber isn't talking about these things.
But VTuber does this thing, and it's like,
you know.
Everything feels so restricting, cause it's like,
oh, I feel like I have these rules to follow.
Or it's like, before I didn't feel like there was any rules,
I could just be like-
You need to be a little dork with other dorks
and having fun.
Be a little dork.
Yeah.
Yeah, you kind of put more under a microscope.
She's getting a figure too.
I know, that's like gonna be awful.
Plus Saiya's getting a figure?
Again, yeah, it's cause she got popular again.
It's such a hell of a lot of love.
What, what, what, what?
What, what, what?
That's the part where we all just like make weird noises.
Yeah, I know, I know.
Oh, I know.
I'm just very, I'm very passionate about my enemies
and my enemies' topic.
I don't know.
So all your enemies, I like weird.
Sunshine smiles, what about that?
Yeah, it's true, like fruit baskets.
Yeah!
Would they want more in this world?
No, they would want kindness and happiness.
Aw.
Happy, happy, smile, a little bunny cuteness.
It's real.
I watched Fritz basket in the longest time.
I literally, somebody snapped me back in to remind me
of like, Natalia acts as powers.
And I was like, holy crap.
Oh my god, Natalia!
Yeah, I know, right?
I think everyone can agree that Natalia did not age well.
No!
But Fritz could not admit that's one of the reasons.
No one talks about it.
Nobody, it's OK, it's fine.
I think that, I was really happy that Fritz basket got it.
Because Fritz basket was the first, like the original Fritz
basket was the first anime I ever watched.
So like, when I got a remake, I was really scared because I
was like, I can mess this up so bad.
I haven't watched the remake.
Is it good?
Yeah, I didn't watch the first season because I was like,
well, I feel like I already knew everything that happened.
But I watched the second season, third season,
and it was so good.
And I cried, and I was like, oh my god, happy.
I have to watch it.
It follows the manga a lot more.
I do recommend it if you have the time.
I will say, new romance anime for, OK.
I think you guys want to understand more.
Anime has become more for male, so it's
very hard to get female-centered romance anime.
Oh, like, so-so.
Yes, because if it's for men, no offense,
because there's some anime that are like, harrowing for guys.
And I'm like, oh, this is so great.
Like, 100 girlfriends that I really like you?
Great anime.
That was so cute.
Please watch an anime.
It's so good.
But I feel like we need more anime like Futsu Baskets
and Nana and Paradise Kiss for women.
I know.
That'll never happen.
I feel like I wonder if we'll ever return.
But then there's like, I feel like all the mangas that
would be the same, they're not going to get adapted
because they're so old and no one talks about them anymore.
Or they're too small and obscure.
They have no English translation, so it's no point.
I'm reading your chat, but I'm not this and guys
that like, show Joe, I don't, I think you misinterpreted.
I'm saying not a lot of anime's art, like, for women,
like, like, or on Host Club.
I miss Aura.
Things like that.
Oh, my God.
I miss Aura.
Peach Girl, like, we're missing, like, we're missing the female,
like, for the female fans.
And it's not the same.
You know what I mean?
You need some of the for the girlies, you know?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That is really scary.
Kimi ni todoke, it's the romance one.
She has, like, long, straight, black hair.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
What's that one about?
Yes.
I think she's like popular boy and she's like weird, scary girl,
but they end up together.
Oh, yes, I heard about that one.
I haven't watched it though.
It's literally the anime of fucking miscommunication.
They're really, she's so mean.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
My dress of darling is such a guy anime.
I am so sorry.
Oh, yeah, that one has fanservice.
Yeah, that's for guys.
That one's like, yeah.
So the difference between, oh my gosh, I look such a dork.
The difference between female and male-centered animes
is that male-centered animes will have a lot of, like,
unnecessary fan service for the girls.
And then, like, the girl ones are like,
oh, holy shit, the beach episode is your fan service.
But the beach episode is always, like, a part of the plot.
Like, in Oron Coast Club, they go into, like, the little water
park.
Or, like, I think of, like, animes, like,
do you guys remember Free?
Like, that was, like, a big one.
Yes.
Free was supposed to be a yowie anime, by the way.
Yeah, or, like, it played against it.
It was, like, a tease the whole time.
I remember fucking being obsessed with that.
But it's, like, usually.
Who did you ship?
Was it Rin Haru or Mako Haru?
Oh, no, yeah.
What did you say?
Both.
Both?
Yeah, I think I was Rin Haru.
Oh, Nagisa on the blue-haired guy with the glasses.
That was my, like, oh, chin.
Wait, wait, wait.
Who was your first character you shipped together?
Wait, what'd you say?
You're both first characters you shipped together.
Like, in general.
He could have caught him.
Wait, what?
He could have caught him?
Are you kidding?
Oh, so true.
That's a lie.
Yeah, I'm glad you're right.
I wanted you to ship them, though.
Yeah, but they literally, like, sleep together naked.
Listen, my young brain did not care.
And, you know, Twinsist is Winsist.
I do love that, I mean, I think it also
eats pretty bad things.
Oh, yeah, 100%.
What about you, Chai?
See it again?
The first two characters you ever shipped together?
First two characters I ever shipped together was Fruitsbasket.
It would have been Yuki and Toru.
OK, OK, OK.
That's cute.
And then Honey Senpai and Mori Senpai.
Oh, yes.
I also shipped a thousand, like, millions.
I'm going to tell you mine.
And this is the reason why I asked this question,
because mine's is really bad.
OK.
I want to know.
So mine's was SpongeBob and Squidward.
Oh, we're going that far back?
Oh, I thought we were in the context of anime.
Oh, no, no, I said first, not anime.
Anime is different.
Anime, mine's was SpongeBob and Squidward.
Mine's was going crazy.
They're very confused.
And I would always draw them kissing.
And I would, like, follow Japanese artists and, like,
things like that.
And then I went down the Tom and Jerry
pipeline of, like, Japanese artists.
And they still draw them together until this day.
SquidBob.
Yeah, I was like, SquidBob or SpongeWade.
Mine, if it wasn't anime related, I'm like.
It's just any media.
Any media that you, like, consumed so much,
there was, like, yeah.
I'm like, was it, like, Starfire and Raven?
From Teen Titans, I don't know.
Oh, that's good, that's good.
Yeah, I can't recall.
I'm too old for that at the age of 56.
Damn, sorry.
Cosmo and Timmy.
You know, I see, I was thinking that, too.
Like, first, when I was trying to think back,
I'm like, was that Cosmo?
Oh, yeah, Cosmo and Timmy, I think.
No, I got to think about that hard.
I feel like I wasn't, like, in the shipping mindset.
I was just like, yeah, TV on my screen.
TV on my screen.
I can tell you what moment made me ship them together.
Please tell me.
I know exactly.
It's so bad.
So when SpongeBob finds him eating a crabby patty,
and he's like, you like them, don't you screw him.
He's going on fairies with Lesley.
Oh, yes, I remember this one.
I was in, like, my anime phase, so I saw that,
and I was like, yeah, this is peak.
This is my OTP.
Yeah, this is my OTP, and I have, like, a fan page for them.
My friend Kumi, she's in chat right now,
and she said Mr. Krabson Plankton.
Oh, that's a good one.
That's a really good one.
But, no, it wasn't the inflation part.
It wasn't when he was fat.
It was like, he was just, like, eating it,
and he was like, oh, you like them, don't you screw him.
He's like, no, I don't.
And then I thought of, like, an anime
where they, like, kabadon each other.
And then, you know, last year, I was like, oh, my god,
what did SpongeBob was kabadoning fucking Squidward?
Oh, my god.
Wait, you remember?
There was that one scene where it's like,
SpongeBob says bye Squidward twice,
and he's like, yeah, I like Squidward.
He's like, I like Squidward.
Like, I like Squidward, I'm telling you,
they didn't even mention Squidward, so.
They teased it.
I loved it.
I don't know, I had, like, I don't know,
I was like, I was just a crack ship.
Yeah, I was like, yeah, I was just a crack ship.
Yeah, Gojo and Cinderella is the one that's like a thing.
Yeah, that's a thing.
How the fuck is that?
I don't know why.
I don't know, what?
Wait, no.
What's the bikini bottom horror?
Someone said blame Sheebie.
What's the bikini?
Oh, Sheebie, sheebie deal.
I don't know what they mean by that.
Oh, oh, it's not your fault, it's just your fault.
It's just my fault.
No, wait, I got it wrong.
It's Sakuna and Cinderella, and then it's Gojo and Elsa.
Elsa, I was gonna say it's 100% Elsa
because they like math.
It's Elsa, yeah, but Sakuna and Cinderella, I don't know.
Gojo and Cinderella.
Although, I do like those random edits
where they'll splice a bunch of Disney cartoons together
and TikTok.
Do you know, like, Vima, Bad Boy, Vima, Vima, Vima, Vima.
Yeah, baby, get it.
I think there's some shrek in someone from El Dorado
or something, I don't even fucking know.
Wait, what's El Dorado?
It's an old, lesser known Disney movie, animated movie.
You would probably like it, The Road to El Dorado.
Yeah, I know it.
Because you're Spanish.
OK, thanks.
Ash, Ash, catch them in Sky from Paw Patrol.
Oh, it's DreamWorks.
This Sky of Dog?
Sky's a dog.
What?
You don't know El Dorado?
Sorry, DreamWorks.
Next could be something you should compare and deal.
I did ship Gojo and Dio when I watched it,
but I thought it was a great ship.
How could you not?
Yeah, I did, too.
I always love enemies to lovers.
In real life, though, that'd be fucking insufferable,
but enemies to lovers, right?
Yeah.
Or rivals to lovers.
I like that.
Like, that's a more realistic trope, in my opinion.
Sky is a dog.
What do you mean it would make more sun?
Shut up.
Wait, what?
I missed that part of it.
She looked up Ash, catch them in Sky from Paw Patrol.
Ash, catch them in Sky.
Nothing came up.
I think that's just their personal ship.
What?
That's just their personal.
That's just their own thing.
That's it.
Yeah, that's their own.
What the fuck?
You freak.
Is this a pinkish dog?
Or like, has paint on it?
Yeah, that's a girl dog, I think.
Oh, my god.
The only girl dog on the team.
Stuart Little in Wreck-It-Row.
Oh, my god.
I had a huge crush on Stuart Little.
I had a really big crush on Stuart Little.
No, I made Stuart Little.
I ate him, I ate him, I ate him.
I think it says, like, in my brain, in my brain,
I was like, nerdy white guy, you know,
brown women attracted to a white man.
That's cool, lead balls.
No, I ain't doing it, I don't hate him.
I have to look up these movies in Spanish,
because I don't know what that, I treasure planet.
What is that?
I hate Stuart Little for trying to put a deep, rooted
personal reason.
Why?
I know.
I also, I could tell you guys.
I don't like Stuart Little because I remember watching
Mouse Hunt, and I hated the Mouse and Mouse Hunt.
And then, Stuart Little was also a Mouse, so.
That's fair.
See, somebody, I watched in Spanish.
When I see the English child, I have to Google them,
because I don't know what that means.
Why they do that?
Wait, what about Reckon Ralph's ex-fixit Felix?
I shit that.
Well, that's just, yeah, that's just, like, you know, again.
Like, I had a rival.
I like the, yeah, rivals under me.
It was funny, though, because he was, like, Ralph.
They weren't even mean to each other.
They were just, like, hey, Ralph, you just can't hang out here.
You break everything.
Wait, Reckon Ralph ex-merida from Brave is, like, a real chip.
It's a real chip.
If you had the chance to change your fate, would ya?
Oh, yes, I fucking love Treasure Planets.
OK, why did you give the cat lady to the fat ass?
Is this, like, an actual thing?
She doesn't have a fat ass in the movie,
but that's pretty cool.
Yeah, I like that image.
I like how she's turning around.
OK, I'm like, like, they just made her ass so big.
Like, why?
Like, in the group chat, I looked up Treasure Planets.
I was looking for things I saw.
Why is her butt cheeks so big?
I own Treasure Planet on DVD.
I'm pretty proud of that.
Oh, my gosh.
That's a pretty good reaction.
Reckon's rerun?
That's a thing.
Is there art of that?
I was looking it up.
How about Freerun?
No, if I did Freerun X, it's just going to be Himmel.
I own it on VHS.
I don't think it ever was on VHS.
Oh, it's a, oh, yeah.
I remember that little meme, the little meme.
I don't understand what's happening now in English.
My brain's trying to understand this fucking English language.
Oh, my god.
Look at this.
Everyone, look it.
Shrek X Freerun.
They're crazy.
That's a thing?
Wait, can you post?
Yeah, you know, there's, like, yeah.
Oh, yeah, I can post it.
It's all you have on your stream.
I just logged it.
There's this art.
Wait, no, no, no.
Ignore that photo.
Ignore that.
They just sent a white one in a very blue.
Mine's the color of a bubble.
It's really blue.
Ignore it.
Ignore that.
Okay, look at this.
Oh, that's actually pretty good art.
Is he picking her up?
I don't like that.
Her Shrek is super short.
Do you think she would like Shrek?
I think she would love Shrek.
I think she'd be.
Yeah, honestly, I think she would actually have a thing for him.
Oh, my gosh.
You should get art of you and Shrek, CB.
How about no?
All right, so I'm going to draw art of you and Shrek together.
Wait, do you guys have, like, a fictional character, like, like, crush that you, like,
push to be, like, silly and wacky?
Akira from Persona 5.
I actually don't.
I don't, I don't know.
Do you guys want to shit me with somebody?
Asking my, asking my hair.
Let me think.
What?
Oh, I know who I would shit you with.
I would shit, okay.
Wait, do you like, what kind of man do you like?
Do I continue?
Donkey, Donkey from Shrek.
Donkey?
You want to shit me with Donkey?
I can see you.
I don't like that at all.
You don't have the dragon that he, like, marries?
Oh, it's true.
I'm the dragon from Shrek.
I do like you guys.
I like guys who are funny.
That is true.
The main character from Golden Boy would love she be so much said in my chat.
Who, from Golden Boy?
Oh, yeah.
What is that?
It's a little old.
It's an anime, but some wacky.
It's wacky.
Okay, I'll have to look that up.
But mine is Akira from Persona 5.
I think guys are really fluffier and glasses really, like, get me going.
So, Senpai from Nagatoru.
I hate Nagatoru, but I, like, love Senpai from Nagatoru.
I think he's so cute.
He is a cutie pie.
Oh, floppy hair glasses.
Like, floppy hair glasses.
Oh, but right now, the love of my life.
Right now, the love of my life is Chilchuk from Dungeon Meshie.
I'm so in love with him.
You're, what a weirdo you are.
You got me here.
I'm trying to think.
I haven't, I haven't been watching a lot of, like, animated stuff lately.
I've, I've, I've been watching, like, the boys.
Nice.
Chilchuk, too.
I like, I like guys with blue, spiky hair.
What?
Sonic?
I'm like.
Oh, yeah, that's right.
You like Sonic.
Red shoes.
Sonic?
Yeah.
Oh, my gosh.
I mean, like, that's just, like, one, you know.
He doesn't have to be Sonic.
I don't care if he's Mary.
He's going to, we're going to, he likes blonde hair.
She's the other one.
I'm going to dye my hair blonde and he's going to fall in love with me.
I will, I will be married to Chilchuk.
Wait, who likes blonde?
Chilchuk Tim's likes blonde women.
Chibi and Johnny Bravo.
You know, I would approve that.
Johnny?
Yeah, that works.
Johnny Bravo.
Oh.
Who would they choose me?
Who would they pick me?
Who would you, who would you ship with Chai?
Who would you ship with?
I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I.
What the fuck?
She broke.
I just wanted to, like, give them something to, like, inspire them.
Wait, are you saying Poe from Kung Fu Panda for me?
Because he's funny and makes food, you know, honestly.
Johnny Bravo is my Chibi, absolutely.
Yeah, I see Johnny Bravo.
I do see that.
Yeah, me and Johnny Bravo.
Do you know the guy that plays the Riddler in, in the Batman, in the 2020 Batman movie?
Yeah.
This is weirdly specific.
Yes.
With Robert Pattison.
You know, no.
Paul, they know, but when he's specific with the Riddler.
What the fuck is his name?
I'm really into him.
I think Robert Pattison was sexy in that one.
Chibi X-Bugs Bunny.
No, that's, that's bad.
He's possibly my father.
Wow.
Oh, wait.
Oh.
What's your dad?
I'm also, I'm canonically related to every bunny character in pop culture.
Oh.
Yeah, Paul Dano is, I know.
Peter Rabbit.
He's, he's something.
I also like crazy fucked up characters.
So that's why I fucking.
Omelette?
I, yeah, I had a thing for.
Yeah, I figure it doesn't much.
Would you let him drink your Chichi's milk?
Yeah.
I milk him from a Zura.
Homelander?
First season homelander.
I don't, not, not later seasons.
Well, I'm a homelander.
Oh no, Chibi, not homelander.
I don't, I think it's like the, I can fix him thing.
Like, I'm like, oh, I let me mother you.
Like, I just want to take care of you.
Like, I like, I like to fix people.
I'm a fixer.
I have to stop watching it.
Cause I think once I saw the deep ass cheeks, I like tabbed out my brain.
Wait, I need to know more.
Tell me more.
So the boys has a lot of nudity and there was one time he like makes a person blow him
and then my, my, my mommy, my mommy walked into my room and then she walks in, his butt
she's on my screen and I just felt ashamed.
Yes, I would be Omniman's little pet.
Yeah, I bet you were, you freak.
I'll have another rare crush, but it's like from a really specific movie.
And it's like the way that what happens to the character is very bad.
The fucked up characters.
Yeah.
Nori at turbo.
Oh, I see that.
The snail.
I love that movie.
Herbie from Herbie fully loaded for a second.
Car.
I love, I love, I love turbo the movie.
That's a great movie.
I love YouTubers.
That's true.
Maybe I can get John Cena to follow me and I can, you know, hang out with Peacemaker.
Mmm.
I don't know what that means.
Oh, Chi X Hiccup.
That's pretty good.
Oh my.
I think Hiccup is so cute.
I didn't give it a go.
Hiccup is so cute.
I love how to train your dragon.
Yeah.
That's so like specific.
I feel like guys are fucked up teeth are so cute to me.
I don't know what that's.
I think that's exactly my type.
Like tall.
Why not?
To be a big ears and messy hair.
I like mentally ill or deep and brooding.
And that's why I had a huge crush on Robin.
Yeah.
I like either really like fucked up mentally ill guys are like guys that literally look
like they're like crack head teeth.
Yeah.
I don't know.
It just gets me going.
You guys.
Who's your ideal man?
Chi.
Which is your favorite trope that you're attracted to?
Um, charismatic and like, um, really fast.
Okay.
Let me think.
I don't even know you guys.
It's okay.
You can just keep saying Sonic.
But I will be on my stand completely.
100%.
Nori X fish legs.
No, it's just.
I do like British accents.
Not Batman.
I like Robert Pattinson's Batman.
He was good.
I think, I think realistically.
I don't know.
Really.
Actually, I lied about why it could be any skin color.
Yeah.
Fucked up teeth and big ears.
I'm kind of into it.
But then my first question is super deep.
I don't know.
My first cartoon crush was the cat baron from the cat returns.
And then I fell in love with howl from howl's we've been castles.
So I don't know what that means about me.
What does that even mean about you?
I don't know.
I'm sorry.
Let me look it up.
Cat Baron.
Can you spell that for me?
I'm so sorry.
Cartman?
Okay.
Okay?
Sorry.
I just, I don't understand.
Oh.
Oh, what the fuck?
Wait, I kind of to add that.
Yeah.
Right?
He's just like a gthon.
No.
Yeah.
I don't understand.
And then...
of liking. Do you guys ever watch? I really liked the Bolton, what the fuck is
his name? Bolton character from Game of Thrones that just fucking tortured people.
I thought he was Hoss. Fuck. I liked Joffrey. You liked Joffrey? Yeah. Okay.
I don't know what's happening. Yes, I like Ramsay, but I also liked him in Skins too,
so that's. Did you guys ever watch Little Bear? Little Bear? A movie with the two
bear brothers where they turn into bears. That's a brother bear. Oh, that's a brother bear?
Oh, I'm fucking restarted. I definitely had a crush on the bear, the older brother.
Oh, no, Chai wasn't a lie for this. What do you mean, shame? Don't shame me. Listen,
I think my first was like a little kid. It was Jake from Jake and the Neverland Pirates.
That's a child shell. Oh, that's cute. And I was my first crush. And then my most recent
crush is Chuchuch Tim's. I think my first human crush was Peter from Peter Pan, but like when
he was from Family Guy. No, the live action Peter Pan. Yes, with the kid with the freckles.
Yeah, he was cute. I don't know. I feel like I didn't have any like fictional crushes.
Except for Sonic. Oh, yeah, maybe I'm just very much. Oh, Jeremy Sumpter. Oh, yeah.
Wait, what's that word? Misogynist. I liked. Do you guys know Papyrus from Undertale?
Oh, I should Papyrus extends. I don't know what the fuck is wrong. Why am I saying this? No,
no, no, I agree. I had a big I had a crush on Papyrus. You had a crush on Papyrus?
Papyrus. Turning into Sean Connery. Honestly, I see it. I understand. I like I like a guy
who likes puzzles and tries to keep me entertained. I like the guy from the cow from Barnyard.
Otis. Yeah, Otis. I know my jaw drop actually my jaw drop. Our trans icon because he's a male cow
with otters. Oh, yeah, what is she? That's the joke. People just kept running with it.
I'm trying to think. Or is my like non human crush. I'm trying to think. Non human. You
guys watch Dragon Tales? Dragon Tales, Dragon Tales. Yes. The twin. I like the twins. Yeah,
the twin green. I guess I like twins. Maybe it's my Gemini moon. What the fuck? Non human.
Non human characters that are hot. I'm still trying to think. I don't know. I had too much of a
grind set. I didn't have time for crushes. Okay, I can think. I remember now. Bumblebee from
Transformers. Bumblebee from Transformers. And then when he spoke, when he spoke, I was really
into it. And then I really had a huge crush on Godzilla. I thought Godzilla was so cool. Spirit
the horse. Yes. Oh, yes. Yeah. Spirit that was Spanish. It was so sexy. I will lie. Yeah,
that's that's literally the whole movie. That's a seductive horse. And Balto from Balto. I don't
know man. You guys are weird. You didn't think this horse from Spirit is hot. Yeah. I don't
even know what that is. You never watched Spirit recently. I think it was a horse girl. Neither
was I, but I watched. Wait, show me. Show me him. Okay, that's him. Oh, there you go.
Long hair. Yes. Yes. Men with long hair. I think I just like incels. I'm thinking about it more.
I like I like incels and my old fat men. Yeah, I got a wide range. Yeah, I like a pretty wide
range. But if you're like a person, I don't know what my type is. Maybe guys like Sonic. I just
watched you put spirit. Watch them appear on the screen. You just corrupt the child image. One
gift was all it took. Spirit is a very charismatic horse. Yeah. And then we were like a horse. I
felt like I was being flirted with. No, it wasn't the size difference or the power. I think it was
Godzilla's like swag. I was like, holy shit. All of them. I have a problem. Oh, wait, no. And
my action I lied. My first human crush was one of the monsters in Power Rangers in Power Rangers
Samurai. I remember which one I just know is Power Rangers Samurai. I fucking I would do it with
show about Power Rangers. Every time I feel like I'm on screen, I was like, oh, yeah, this is
hot. I used to have a really big crush on Zuko too. I think everyone does. That's just basic. That's
basic. Yeah, it's pretty basic. That's my basic one. What about Uncle Irel? Am I right? I agree. No,
honestly would. No, I'm kidding. This is a safe space. Try. No judgment here. Try. Oh, yeah,
right. I don't even think she be kind to you. Um, not in the place. Oh, the cucumber from
Veggie Tales. No. Veggie Tales. I was forced to watch Veggie Tales. I didn't like Veggie
Tales. I have to watch it. I could watch it to learn English. That's a great show to watch to
learn English.
I don't know.
Iro in his prime. Buff Iro in jail. Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, yeah. Guilf, Guilf. 100%.
You guys are just listing off basically every character now. Not all. Not all. Not all.
Do you guys remember that movie Meet the Robinsons? Yes. Oh, the like black hair. Black hair? Yeah.
Okay, yeah, that's actually kind of real. I had a crush on Goob, the evil guy. I had a crush on
the evil guy. Oh, I had a crush on, um, what's his face? The enemy and the Incredibles?
And what was his name? Central? Yeah. Yeah. I had a crush on Goob, the white hair lady. You
remind me of the white hair lady. I remind you of the white haired lady? Yeah, I think she's really
pretty. Oh, you are like her. You are like her. Um, Goob when he was older, so like when he was
like all hunchbacked and like dirty looking and yeah. I like the one slur, but I think that was
pretty basic. No, no, that's a pretty, that's a pretty. I totally get it though. Like it makes
sense. Yeah. Mirage. Yeah, he's reminded Mirage. I don't know. I think it's the lowering appeal
with her. I don't know. I think, I think if I'm like trying to like,
hmm, it'd be like, oh, I'm, I'm kind of bad, but I'm, I'm like protective.
Like I'm like, I'm strong and I'm powerful. Yeah, maybe bad boy. Maybe like Draco mouth.
But it's like, but it's like, oh, but, but like for the one I love, I'm like soft and
protective and sweet. You know? Oh, so like Edward from Twilight. Oh, but no, not really. I
don't feel anything. I feel nothing. Quasimodo. Nori, people want to know if you like Quasimodo.
Quasimodo. From hunchback of Notre Dame. Um, I like the old man. Sorry. You like the old man?
I was, I liked the gypsy girl. I can't remember her name. Was it Esmeralda?
Okay. Cause I, okay. I wasn't in Spanish, right? Okay. I wasn't in Spanish, right? So in Spanish,
I have seen the Spanish version. I would get so. The voice actor was crazy for Spanish.
He just sounded so good. So I kind of just like fumbled everything. And I'm also like,
I'm kind of religious. So religious man, evil religious man. I was like, oh, this is amazing.
The creepy priest. Younger, little meaner than what I wanted. And I wanted the creepy old looking
man. Guys, I don't know who's that. I'm looking them up. Um, I can steal a Frollo from hunchback
of Notre Dame. Frollo, hunchback. Sakuna, like, well, that's like basic. Yeah, like, yeah, he's hot.
But like, we're trying to get to the fucked up ones, you know?
Oh, um, Pennywise. Pennywise? Pennywise? What was, what was the thingy from
I like the actor. The Demi Gorgon, but I never watched anything. So it was just the Demi Gorgon.
I've seen a bad dragon dildo of the Demi Gorgon. What? I don't even want to know what that is.
I don't want to know. I don't know what that is. I don't know what that is. You're not gonna
explain. Wait, can you link it? Link, it's a tie. Okay, I got you. Hold on. Not to me.
Oh my god. I feel like such a lame-o. Oh my god. Come on. Come on. You're even sexy even. Stranger
wrongs. No, don't curl chai. I just want to watch it. Don't curl chai. I want it.
I don't think this is gonna make any sense, but I did have, I do can recall that I had a big crush
on this cat. This cat? Get that out of my DMs right now. Get that out of my DMs right now.
Get that out of my DMs right now. I deleted it. You sick one. What did I tell you? I told
you no. I don't want to see it. What cat? Let's just change the subject. Now what kind of
you sick bastard? No, she's my friend. She's my friend. She's my friend. She's my friend.
Why is she your friend? Why is she your friend? Is that the cat from Franklin? No, this is a cat from
Little Bear. Oh, oh. That's not Little Bear. Chai. Chai. Why is it cat?
It was more, I think that's a thing. I think it's personality. I think I don't have a physical
type. I think that's the problem. They could be a cat. They could be a cow. They could be a cucumber.
Do you know the dog from Lady and the Tramp?
Uh, yeah. I had a question. The dog, like the lady's love interest, I don't know.
He went to do everything to be with her, man. I kind of liked it. Wait, what dog? Oh,
Bolts? The dog from Lady and the Tramp. Oh, I thought, sorry, I thought you meant Bolts.
Oh, but yes. Uh, Tramp, yeah. I thought he was very attractive. And he loved Lady very much,
yes. Oh, yeah. Very cute. There's the pure love that I like. Yeah, they were, like,
different classes. It was very adorable. Now I'm a sucker for the Juliet, Romeo and Juliet type
of trope. Someone's a sucker for that. I love there so much. Someone said bubble baths from Spongebob.
No. No, no, no, no. Okay. Who do you like from Spongebob?
I like the guy in the Spongebob movie that was like the bounty hunter that was hunting them down
with the really nice boots. Oh, yeah. I forgot about him.
Dennis, yeah. I didn't have a crush on the Spongebob characters. I was ship in Spongebob.
We were just ship in them. Maybe the robot lady, the wife. Oh, Karen?
Karen, yeah. I like the wife. David Hasselhoff. I don't know. David Hasselhoff.
There hasn't been like, oh, what anime characters do you guys resonate with? Like, what kind of,
like, oh, this is so- Do I kid? Yeah, like, who do you kid? Who do you guys see? Who do you guys
kid? Who's your kid? Who's your kid? Who's your kid? I haven't kidned a anime character in a very long
time. And I usually watch my first kid. I think my, my head always goes to tiger,
icica, icica, icica, icica, icica. Icicle, yeah. Icicle, tiger. Like, that's like always,
I can't, it's like uncontrollable, but I think like Toru, Toru Honda.
I'd have to think about mine. Yeah, I have to think. I couldn't really like kid myself,
because I have to, I feel like I have to relate to a character, and I don't really feel like I
really relate it, especially with the anime I watched. I usually used anime as a form of
escapism. I didn't want anything to remind me of my life. Oh, that, yeah. I usually watch like
super, I never watched like slice of life stuff. I watched like super high fantasy stuff, or like
sci-fi, or just like fucking, I was just watching Naruto and Full Metal Alchemist and all the time,
and I like, yeah, I can't. Oh, I liked Alphonse from Full Metal Alchemist. Is that your kid?
Suit of armor. No, he's not my kin, but like, I liked him. Oh, you liked him? Oh, okay.
Suki from Avatar, who I want to be. Oh yeah, I feel that. I don't know. I don't know who I can,
I'm not gonna say it all out though. I thought you guys would answer too. Is it like a weird? I don't
know if I have any like weird ones. I think most of them are like pretty, pretty, like sound like
pretty like normal. Um, I'm gonna keep her to myself. She's your, your anime Oshii. Um, let me see.
Oh my god. What is it, kin? It's just like a, it's a nerd term to me. I can't do like super
really, too. You're like, oh, this is me and I am them. They are me. We are one. We are Venom.
Of course, I'm Venom. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. What's the tongue do? No, no, not the tongue. It wasn't
the tongue. It was just the fact that he was like a symbiote. Yeah. And I was like, what would he
feel like if he was inside of me, but not like in a weird way and like, in like a, like in a symbiote
suit kind of way. Okay. I think, I think I actually might have kin death the kid.
Yes, yes, yes. Wait, me too, me too, me too. Because I have OCD and so I like really related
with this character because for obsession with symmetry and stuff. Yeah. Oh, I fucking love
Solator. Solator was my shit. I had so many OCs. I was very much obsessed with that the kid. I think
I related to him a lot. Yeah, I want to say that. It's like, I can always, I was like,
I feel like it's like, I like a character so much I want to be them or like, I'm like, that's so me.
Yeah. So me for real, for real. That's so me. That's me for real. Let's be for real. Let's be for
real. I can the dune worm. What the fuck are you doing? What's dune? You don't know what dune is?
No. It's a book. It's a sci-fi book. I don't know if you, I don't think you would like it at all
actually or even the movie. I don't only think it's your thing. Nope. Yeah. I like that. Also,
I don't even know how to read properly. I think I'm like genuinely dyslexic. So that's okay. Oh,
I know what my, my first, my first kid where I was like, really obsessed with the character and I
was like, Oh my God, I want that to be me so bad. I wanted it to be me. It was Asuna from Sword Art
on the line. Oh, I feel it. Mm-hmm. Yeah. Mine's with, mine's with Sasuke. Oh, really? Okay.
Yeah, that's good. Mine's with Sasuke. I'm on the line. What was an anime you wish you were in the
world in? Like, like, sword art, sword art. Yeah. Mine was, I don't really think it was an anime,
but I really wish I was in Code Lyoko. Wait, what's that? You don't know what Code Lyoko is? Am I,
I don't know. So Code Lyoko is this show where these kids go to like school,
but then there's this like this master computer that like tries to fucking kill them every day.
Why are there four heads so big? Yeah, they fucking use four heads. But they go into the computer to
fight, like it's like reset time. And so they just reset time all the time. I just fucking love Code
Lyoko. That was my shit. Wait, someone says I don't blame TV. I can understand that. I wanted to,
I, odd, odd was my, oh, I fucking was in love with odd, which was like the cat, the cat boy.
Oh, wait, I want to look it up now. How do you spell it? It was a really weird
art style, but yeah, Code Lyoko Ly, okay. Code Lyoko is French. Yes, it's originally French.
It's so interesting. But I love Bible Villaco. The thing that I wanted to be in, I'm trying to think.
I wanted to be in Code Lyoko and you know Naruto naturally. Either Yvonne Gellor the persona series,
yeah, yeah. I know I would die though, but um, oh yeah, I don't know, man.
Corks party, I'm lying, maybe Corks party, you wanna be a Corks party?
No, you could not, you would die so fast.
That's terrible.
Why?
Because Kauru isn't Eva, and I was obsessed with him.
But now, I'm gonna have a Corks party, I'm built different, I'm gonna fucking, I'm gonna walk out of there alive, not a scratch on my body.
I'm already very mentally disturbed.
Have you done a playthrough of Corks party on your channel?
Not on my channel, I've played it before though.
Oh, okay, cause I'm like, let me know when you do, cause I wanna watch it then.
Yeah, yeah, if I do I'll let you know, but if I was physically there, that little girl, that little girl was getting punted.
Oh my god.
Oh man, that'd be fun, aren't there making a two or something I've seen?
Yeah, they're redoing it, they're making a new game.
It's the buttered pooper, I totally forgot, cause I made the buttered pooper references before and I forgot it was from Corks party, such a great fucking game.
And Madfather, I loved all those RPG maker games.
What is your favorite visual novel, Nori?
Sorry.
Mmm.
What?
They said nori, they said Nori.
Oh, don't look it up, maggot beach.
What?
Don't look it up, don't do it, there's no better chair.
I think I've heard of that.
How do I spell it? Or send it?
I don't care.
I want to
You might not like it, but I won't like it
A clapjack just said, oh, mega beat
I've heard of that, what is that?
But if you want like a normie, a normie taste
Um, Totono?
Is it my one of my favorite ones?
I think it's very beautifully done
So I really like this one
Oh, I'm Sayushi! I'm Sayushi!
Sayushi's also really good
I'm going to mess up now
Wait, hold on, raid, raid, moment, raid, moment
Another one?
I'll try
Another one, oh my god, another one
Give me a second
She's popular, she's cool
I put maggot balls on accident
It's maggot beads
So it's maggot beads, Totono
Oh
And Sayushi is really good too
The girl's eye is being popped out of its socket
Yep
There's titties in this screen
What is this, it's like
Oh, why? I like it so much
I think it's just maybe like the art
And stuff is like really like
Interesting
I don't know, I'm like, I'm a huge sucker for like
Very unique art styles, yeah
Yeah, I'm not averse to like gore
And just like dark themes
So I'm actually like, I'm not
I'm not really a visual novel person
Really
You could just watch a play through of it
Yeah, maybe I might do that
I usually will just read manga
But I haven't even read manga in a long time
Yeah, consuming Japanese media
Has mostly been for me, just like anime
But I usually watch normie animes, so
I would recommend visual novels if you want like a little base tea
Some of them are pretty simple
You're just literally just reading and like
Picking an option
Yeah, it's like just
And you can also Google options
If you just want to like, if you just want to like
Have a specific ending done
Things like that
I think too hard
What is it?
Anyone here watched Food Wars?
Why did you say it like that?
Never heard of it
I don't know what you're talking about
What's Food Wars?
Yeah, never, yeah, exactly
Yeah, I actually don't know what that is
I'm so hurry
Hi son
I just told you I like the maggot baits
Why the fuck would I look at something that's called
Food Wars?
Do you think I'm a normal person now buddy?
I'm like an edged lord
Call me Sasuke Uchiha
Noriko Uchiha
Honestly, kind of a badass name
Yeah, it's my new name now
I know man, can you re-brand to that?
Visual novels often have late scenes though
Yeah, but if you get them through Steam
You're like centered so hard
So it doesn't even matter
I've heard that
Yeah, the stuff is centered
Yeah, but visual novels
I think are very worth to even just look at
So if you ever want a visual novel recommendation
I will
I can look and I'll send you some
Thank you
Alright, it is almost 1.30 a.m. for me
Call me Puppies, yeah it is
Yeah, I'm Epi
I'm also really a fucking piss
I'm waiting for Chyna to come back
Oh, she's here
Hi, I'm here, I'm sorry
I heard you say you're Epi and have to pee
Yeah, I need to run
I was hoping you didn't catch that
Hello
Hi
Welcome Raiders
Wait, Chyna
Yes, Raiders
More Raiders?
Oh no, it's the same
Yeah, I was saying hi to her Raiders
Wait Chy, are all the people you put on the stream right now
People you found attractive?
No, no, no
Okay, so the top left is apparently I sound like her
Yeah, yeah, yeah
Freeran Shrek, that's just like a visual image
For everyone to know
And then that's your crush
Right there beside them
And then this is Shibi's crush
And then it's my crush in front of chat
Okay, okay, okay
I'm so curious
I learned so much about Noriko today
Yeah
I'm a pretty open bloke
We learned so much about each other
I think we all have very similar but different tastes in movies
Yes
And same opinions, but I enjoy that a lot
Coral is a damn good villain
Coral is a very good villain
If you watch the movie, I recommend watching it in Spanish
It just sounds a lot better
There's some videos that are just better in Spanish than in English
Yeah, I think all of them don't chat
I'm trying to figure out who to read
Oh my god, we're gonna read
Read me, read me
I can't read
I got
Are you on YouTube?
No
You can't do that
I'm like, are you dual streaming?
Cause then I would
One day, one day, one day, one day, one day, one day, one day
One day
One day, one day
Alright
I'll read this person
Okay
Who are you gonna read?
I'll just read whoever you read on Twitch
If you're ending
I'm not even ending
Just read her
Okay, guys
I'm sending my pop horse to you
Alright, bye guys
Thank you for having me
Guys, you've been reading so much
I had so much fun
Love you
BGM is loud as hell
Hi
Hello, it's me
It was lovely
What did you think of the girlies?
Aren't they amazing?
I know how to pick them
But I hope you guys have a wonderful night
Thank you for coming to stream
I thought it was a really fun collab
I just blinked in like one eye
Blinked slower than the other
That was really weird
But yeah
I'll probably collab with those girls again
Nory is freaking hilarious
If you like little base bug girls
Go see her
And then Chai is sweet
And also super fucking funny
So if you like little cutesy
Cute and funny double girls
Go see her
So please check them out
Their channels and their Twitter
Are in my description
Just like a bigger booger
She really knows how to pick them
Exactly
I hope you guys have a wonderful night
Bye
Scum of the earth
I'll also say for the raid
Gonna raid some B&U girls
Thanks for watching