Oh my God! Hi, Haram! How's it going? Ignore my floating head. Don't worry about that,
sweetheart, okay? Are my goffs here? My goffs better be here. Thanks for watching. It's
your girl, Shibony, Darkness, Dementia, Raven, Cotton, Bumway. Today we're going to be starting
chapter 16 of My Immortal. I have it all nice and cute up for you. Yes, I'm a Dull Han. If you
don't know, I'm a distant friend of Shibi, but my name is Shibony. I am not a rabbit. I'm a Dull Han,
and I am your favorite goth punk princess who loves MCR. And I have a gun, but don't worry about
that. That'll come up later. But how are you guys doing? I'm emo. Yeah, I hate my life. I hate it so
much. The only thing that keeps me going is my dedicated fans, my harlots, my Haram,
a punk haircut. You'll what, my what? You also love, I said MCR, not NCR. This is not fallout.
Hey, that's us. That's you put in pop. Wait, what? I probably shouldn't have used that word.
Yikes. Voldemort gave me a gun. He did. Voldemort did give me a gun.
Oh, yeah, go back to work. Yeah, if you got to work, totally understand. If you need to sleep,
go to sleep. If you need to read your Bible passages, read your Bible passages. So, yes,
you can have me in the background. You can just totally zone me out. I love my lurkers.
I love my chatters. We all we all here.
Put in pop is like an off brand Harley Quinn. Yeah, let's let's pretend that's what that meant.
I'm already starting off strong, she be already I mean, shibony.
Okay, okay, okay. Wait, why am I my face in the wrong direction? There we go.
Yeah, we are about to read the Bible. How's that monetization going?
Um, I'm monetized. Or do you mean like my personal channel like shibonies chant shibonies channel
I can even pronounce my own name. I like taking over she bees channel so like totally don't worry
about that. But yeah, you can always catch up and watch part two and the VOD it was lots of fun.
So so far, if you don't know if you're first, if you're just tuning in now to the amazingness
that is my immortal. So my immortal is a fan fiction commonly believed to be satire, but I'm
the author just so you know, I'm claiming that title. It is a fan fiction of Harry Potter with a
self insert. My personal OC, ebony dementia darkness way. Yes, dementia. That's what I said.
This is my favorite piece of any sort of fiction. I mean, nonfiction ever written,
by the way, and I wrote it. So of course, you know, it's good.
Um, and it's about ebony, and she goes to Hogwarts, and she's in love with Draco. By the way,
everybody's goth. So preps get out like if you're a prep, if you're wearing Amber Convery and Fitch
right now, get the fuck out. We don't like you here. All right. Yeah. Yeah. Well, except if you
see on excites high school second place, I've never read Sonic High School, maybe I'll read that one
next. And then I'll dress up as a Sonic character. Oh, God. Oh, no. Um, no preps, no preps allowed.
Preps. Preps can go kiss your sister, you know, in Minecraft.
And my late how do you mean don't worry, we just started sugar tits. We're good. Don't
worry about it. You guys like my little meme. I mean, did you look guys like the meme that she
be made on her Twitter? From what I heard, it took her like an hour to put that together.
But she's very proud of herself.
Emo's only goffs only. So everybody take out your razor.
Everybody take out your blood and your your chokers, specifically my hands, my hands will
make a great necklace for you, by the way. And we'll we'll get into it. So where we left off
is that so Ebony just found out that possibly Draco and vampire aka Harry Potter are together
or were together and they're about to go to a concert. Can I make make this bigger?
My wings are in the way, but you guys don't need to read. There's some people that I don't
want to accidentally like show their face out of respect. So I'm covering them with my emote.
I mean, she visa emote. Let me let me switch the music. Let's see if this gets copyrighted.
The other time it did, but this said it was copyright free.
Is that too loud? Is it is it too loud?
Guys, tell me when do you get your own emotes? I don't know. I don't know if I'll ever get my
emotes. It's good. Okay. I'm gonna a little quieter. Do you like this spooky ambiance? Is that good?
I think that's fine. Also, I wanted to say thank you for you guys for your support lately.
Why is why did you just move up? Why the fuck? Why are you guys talking so much? Oh wait,
it's because I made this bigger. I'm actually stupid. Don't worry about it. It's small again.
Anyways, they actually have their own faces of profile. No, it's not that. It's just like it's
who the because this is like archived. It's not like on fanfiction.net, but it's easier for me to
read. There's also like cliff notes or like footnotes of like what she's trying to say.
I mean, what I'm trying to say. Because I tend to misspell things a lot. So it is what it is,
you know. Do we have anything gothic? What do you mean? We're reading stuff gothic right now.
But yeah, we're about to go to an MCR concert. Oh no, just kidding. We're about to go to a good
Charlotte concert. Wait, just kidding. I think good Charlotte and MCR there. So I think we're
we're just having a great time. I can't remember any of the voices that I did except that Ebony
is a Valley girl. So I will do that. Let me just but what I was just gonna say, thank you for people
supporting me. Somebody bought me I am the internal ear monitor thingies off throne and I thank you so
much because I can't I'm realizing that you really can't wear over the ear headphones. They're just
not it's hurting my ears, especially when I wear my glasses. Because yes, I'm wearing glasses right
now. How does that make you feel? It's because I'm fucking blind. I just I don't know what to tell you.
Vampires goofy. Okay, Draco was mommy. Vampires goofy.
Copyright free gothic ambient ambient music. It's called trick or treat Halloween slash
autumn lo-fi no copyright playlist. I like when I nod my head.
Also this like hoodie doesn't have a back in it. It's usually just like see through. So I stuck
like ornaments behind me from YouTube studio. So it looks like it's the behind the hood.
Wait, can I put on glasses? If I put on glasses, I don't think
they won't pin because my head is technically an asset right now.
It'll just be like, oh my god, why do I look so fucking cute? Hello?
Hi, hi, it's me, Shibani, Darkness, dementia, cotton bomb way.
How does this make you feel? Do you think I look cute? Do you think I hold on to make them bigger?
Do you think am I your am I the emo girl of your dreams? I better be the emo girl of your dreams
if I'm not. Your wrists are going to be covered in ketchup. That's all I'm going to say.
Nerd goth. Shibi nerd goth. I mean, yeah, imagine Shibi copied my style. That'd be crazy.
Bigger? Okay. All right, I think we're good.
I can't pin up so I moved six of the models, sadly. So it is what it is. Shibi would never.
I look so comically. Isn't there like a cartoon character that has like comically big glasses
like this? Who the fuck is Takane Louis? I think I'm cultured. I'm not.
When did Shibi go goth? I'm not Shibi. I'm Shibani.
How many times do I have to say my damn name? I'm Shibani, Darkness, Dementia, Raven, Cotton,
Bumway. God damn it. I mean, Satan damn it.
All right. But I hope you guys are ready. I'm gonna, this is actually, I think I might keep the
glasses on. Glasses are no glasses. You want glasses or no glasses? What do you think?
They won't be able to move properly. They'll just kind of be hanging out, but it is what
it is. Glasses? Okay. Okay. I'll keep the glasses on. We're very studious, you know, very studious.
Let me just adjust those glasses. Hello. These actually look like the glasses that I'm wearing,
except my frames are bigger and they're black, but I think I might get red glasses just to
not be cute. I'm never, it's not a phase, mom. It's a lifestyle. Okay. Get it, get it, get it
together. All right. Where is, what did I do with the window? Okay, there it is. Are you ready,
everybody? So I got some chips, chips and gold fishies, and they got some apple juice.
Um, um, um, um, um, um. That person over there has a border.
Make sure,
make sure you guys are comfy, cozy.
I have the tweet that I'm live.
This is nice. This is nice. Thank you for the reminder.
Oh my God, I'm almost close to 10K on my main. That's just so weird to me. Why are people like me? I
don't, you like this? You like what you see right now? Why? Why are you? Stop. I expected it to be like,
there's too many people. I'm getting overwhelmed. Okay, hold on.
I think, yeah, let's have the Dono Alerts turned on so you guys can
don't know and text to speech to your, to your heart's content.
What the fuck am I doing? Oh yeah, I'm live. I'm tweeting that I'm live.
I am streaming this right now. If you want to come watch silly voices, I need a burp. Um,
then my nose is itchy. Then get here right now, please.
Where is, I can't, where am I? Where am I? Where am I? Oh my God. Why does it never remember what
emojis I use when I'm on my PC? Because I hate having to scroll all the way to look for that one
red button looking emoji. Okay, we're good. And then I just need to retweet
that on my sexy account because everybody pays attention to that one more. But that's fine. It's
okay. All right. Real fans have noticed for JB's tweets. Make sure to spam that like button,
hit subscribe, ding that bell, ding my bell, all ring yours. Let's start. Okay.
Chapter 16. I'm not going to read the author's notes because they're kind of redundant.
We ran happily to Hogsmeade. There we saw the stage where GC had played. We ran in happily.
MCR playing Helena. I was so fucking happy. Gerard looked even sexier than he did in the pictures.
Even Draco thought so. I could totally see him getting an erection, but it didn't matter because
I knew we were only the true ones for each other. I was wearing a black leather mini dress and black
leather platinum boots with red ripped fishnets. Draco was wearing a black baggy MCR t-shirt and
black baggy pants. Anyway, we started mashing to Helena. We fringed. We ran up to the front of the
band to stage dive. Suddenly Gerard pulled off his mask. So did the others. We gasped. It wasn't
them at all. It was comma ellipses. Those some more into death dealers. What the fuck, Draco? I'm
not going to a concert with yo. I shouted angrily. Not after what happened to me last time. Wait,
we're already at the concert. Even if it's MCR and you know how much I licked them.
What? Cause we, you know, he got get it uncomfortably because guys don't like to talk about you know
what? Yeah, cause we, you know, I yielded in an angry voice. We won't do that again. Draco promised.
This time we're going with an escort. It's a Zara.
Hello, hello, everybody just coming in. We just started. So we haven't missed much.
Oh, MFG WTF. Are you giving in to the mainstream? I asked. So I guess you're a prep or a Christina
or what now? No, he muttered loudly. Are you becoming a prepper? What? I shooted
angrily. Don't worry. I'll put my gun at some point.
And no, I'm not. Please come with me. He fell down to his knees and started singing
the world is black by GC to me. I was flattened because that's not even a single. He had memorized
the lyrics just for me. Scroll down. Okay, then I guess I will have to. I said, and then we Frenched
for a while and then I went up to my room. I'm confused. I thought we were at the concert,
but I guess not. Maybe it was a dream. Bloody Mary was standing there.
Oh wait, this is Japanese. Not a Christina. I think they're like, she's talking about Christina
Aguilera. Well, let me, let me put up my feets. Put up one. Yeah, now I'm confused.
Okay, I'll guess I'll give her a kawaii weeaboo voice.
Hajime Masi did that. I can't read Japanese for shit. Hajime Masi did. Girl. She said happily.
She speaks Japanese. So do I. That means how do you do in Japanese? Wait, Hajime,
Hajime Masi. I don't, I don't feel like she's spelled that right.
By the way, Willow the fucking poser got expelled. Yo, what happened to Willow? Willow was my IRL
friends. I mean, yes, I said me. She filed all her classes looks like author had a falling out
of their best friend that she also inserted. And she's skipped math. Offers note. Raven,
you fucking suck. Fuck you. It serves that fucking batch of riot. I laughed angrily.
Well, anyway, we were feeling all depressed. We watched some gothic movies like Das Nightmare
before Chris X mess. Maybe Willow will die too. Jesus Christ.
That's not what that means. Yeah, I'm like, I don't think that's what that means either.
Oh, yeah. I have a confession after she got expelled. I murdered her and then Lupin did
it with her because he's on the field with a neck fillack.
Kawaii. I comment happily. We talked to each other in silence.
For the rest of the movie. How do you talk in silence?
Okay. Oh, hey, BTW BT dubs actually is what I'm gonna say BT dubs. I'm going to a concert
with Draco tonight in Hogsmeade with MCR. I said I need to wear like the hottest hot set outfit ever.
Bloody Mary knotted energetically. Oh my fucking God, totally. Let's go shopping.
And hot topic, right? I asked already getting out my special hot topic loyalty card.
No, my head snaped up. What? My head spun spoon. I cannot believe it. Bloody Mary, are you a prep?
She laughed. I found some really cool gothic stores near Hogwarts. That's all.
Oh, who told you about them? I asked. Sure. It would be would be Draco and Diabolo or
Vampire. Don't even say that nom to me. Nom. PTSD or or me. Dumbly door, she said.
Let me sorry. Dumbly door. She said, let me just call our Brahms.
Oh, M F F G. Dumbly door. Wait. Sorry. Oh, M F F G. Dumbly door. I asked quietly.
Yeah, I saw the map for Hogsmeade on his desk. She sold she told me. Come on, let's go.
We are going to a few punk golf stores, especially for the concerts in Hogsmeade.
The salesperson was OMG hotter than Geron, except not because that's impossible. And he gave me a few
dresses. Wait, what voice should I think this is supposed to be Tom Riddle? Um, what voice?
What voice should Tom Riddle?
Prep is starting to sound like a slur. Bloody Mary.
Yeah, they know ASL. We're just speaking in sign language when they're talking quietly.
When they're talking in silence.
I think because isn't Tom Riddle played by like, who is it? Robert Pattinson. So I do like a British
accent. I'll do that. Let me finish chewing my chippies. No, it's not going to be Road Man.
No, not Reddler.
Edward voice. I'm going to do my best. Edward, call an expert and press him.
Hello. Hello. Welcome in. Okay.
We only have these for the real golfs.
Double golfs. Me and Bloody Mary ass.
Yeah, you wouldn't believe how many poses there on this town, man.
Yesterday, Lupin and Snap tried to buy a golfer camera pouch. He shook his head.
I didn't even know they had a camera.
Okay, he sounds Road Man anyways. We'll just keep it like that.
Oh, MFG. No, they're gonna spy on me again. I cried running out of the changing room wearing
a long black dress with lots of red tool coming on very low cut huge slit.
Oh, my Satan, you have to buy that outfit. The salesperson said.
Yeah, it looks totally hot. Said Bloody Mary.
You know what? I'm going to give it to you for free because you look really hot in that
outfit. Hey, are you going to be at the concert tonight? He asked.
Yeah, I'm actually, you guys can't see, but I'm tucking my, my hair behind my ear, like,
like, you know, you know what I'm doing. Yeah, I am actually, I looked back at him.
Hey, BT dubs, my name's Ebandi, the darkness dementia tarot way.
I don't know why I added a name in there, but you know, you get it.
What's yours? Tom Rid, he said, and run a hand through his, his black dyed hair.
Maybe I'll see you there tonight.
The gopher is, I got dark gopher is.
Yeah, I don't think so because I'm going there with my BF, Draco, you sick perv.
I yelled angrily, but before he could beg me to go with him,
Hagrid flew in in this black broom looking worried. Wait, what was Hagrid's voice?
I think Hagrid had a fucking high pitch voice too. Oh fuck.
Was he a cowboy? No, that was Dumbledore. Dumbledore was the cowboy.
Oh my God, Abundi, I need to get back to the castle now.
Oh my God, Abundi.
Okay, okay, okay. Oh, sorry. Let me just cover your face. Fuck, sorry, Janice.
Yeah, I'm not doing Hagrid's voice.
Who is Scottish? I don't remember. I don't remember. Someone was Scottish and I don't remember who it was.
I live in Spain without the S. J.K. Rowling has written it enough already. It's up here for this one.
Okay, Tom, wait, hold on. Let me like move my glasses over because there's like a little bit.
I'm reading. There we go. And then I won't move my head as I read this next passage.
Tom Riddle gave us some clothes and stuff for free. He said he would help us with makeup
if he wanted because he was really into fashion and stuff. He's bisexual. Hagrid kept shooting at
us to come back to Hogwarts. WTF, Hagrid. I said angrily. Fuck off you fujacking bastard.
Well, anyway, Willow came. Hagrid went away angrily.
Hey bitch, you look kawaii. She said, yeah, but not as kawaii as yo. I answered sadly because Willow's
really pretty in everything. Oh wait, did they make up? Okay. Hell yeah. She's, they made up. It's good.
Oh my, oh my God, he was bisexual.
My scheduled guys are so hot.
She was wearing a short black corset thingy with bloodlet lace on it and a black or blood red
miniskirt, leather fishnets and black pointy pointy boots that showed up how pale she was.
She had a really nice body with big bobs and everything. She was thin enough to be in a
rexic. So what's she like?
So are you going to the concert with Draco? She asked. Yeah, I said happily. I'm going with
Diabolo. She answered happily. Well, anyway, Draco and Diabolo came. Diabolo, Diabolo, Diabolo.
I don't know. Let's do some bloat.
They were both looking extremely hot and sexy and you could tell they thought we were ought to.
What's ought to?
Big Bob's intersex. She got the nomi from one piece, Bonnie. Oh no, not the nomi. She got nomi.
Diabolo was wearing a black t-shirt that said 666 on it. He is wearing tons off makeup just
like Marilyn Manson. Draco was wearing black leather pants, a gothic black GC t-shirt and
black vans he got from the Warped Tower. Bloody Mart was going to the concert with Dracola.
Dracola used to be called Navel, but it turned out that he was getting after birth in his real
family who were vampires. They died. Died as in D-Y-E-D, by the way, not...
Shut up. Shut up, guys. Don't read my burp. Don't read my burp.
Navel converted to Satanism and he went goth. He was in Slytherin now.
He was wearing a black warped t-shirt, black jeans, and shoes with black hair with red streaks
in it. We call him Dracula now. Well, anyways, we all went to Draco's Black Mercy Benz,
get it? Cause we're go- gopific. That his dad, Lucian, gave him. We did pot, coke, and crack.
Draco and I made out. We made fun of those stupid fucking preps. We soon got there. I gasped.
Not the Navel. Average day. Yeah, it's just, you know, day in my life, ma'am. Day in my life.
I need some good chips.
Let me some cattle-cooked chips.
Yeah, they did hot pot, Coca-Cola, and crack.
A little bit of crunching ASMR for you.
Crazy meal set.
Minds me, I forgot to eat today again.
I'm just living off of chips and goldfish for a day. Okay.
Okay.
Gerard was the sexiest guy ever. He looked even sexier than he did in pics.
He had long, red and black hair, embarrassing blue eyes. He was really skinny and he had an
amazing ethnic voice. Uh, what is ethnic? What's an ethnic voice?
We marched to Helena and some other songs. Suddenly Gerard pulled off his mask and so did
it. Wait a second. Did she, oh, she must have like written the first part before in the last
chapter, but then decided she wanted to add more exposition. I gasped. It wasn't Gerard at all.
It was an ugly, preppy man with no nose and red eyes. It was,
I was, I was, I almost threw shade. I was not even like through shade, like in a mean way,
but I'm like, it'd be funny if I like rewrote this thing with actual VTubers names.
Oh, okay. Everyone ran away about me and Draco. Draco and I came. It was Voldemort and the death
dealers. I need to breathe.
You moronic idiots. He's shooting angstily. And Obi, I told you to kill vampire,
thou have failed, and now I shall kill thou and Draco. No, please, we beg sadly, but he took out his knife.
Hello, hello. Bealer goes to Hogwarts? Oh no.
My gosh. Strawberry pop tart. Why would you stick, why would you stick a pop tart in the
microwave? You're crazy. I forgot how dumbly word, dumb, I almost said dumbly door. Dumbly worded
this thick was. Should have been spilt knife. I know she spilt knife, right? I'm very impressed.
Suddenly a gothic old man flew as in the sickness on his brimstick. He had lung as in the organ,
black hair and a long black bread. He was wearing a black robe that said Abra Levine on the back.
He shot to the spell and Voldemort ran away. It was dumbly door. I don't know why I'm getting an
accent when I'm doing this. Sorry, Jacob, we're cutting your face off, Jacob. I'm sorry, bro.
There we go. No, your chin is showing. You cannot be seen. Be gone, Jacob.
He burnt his bread, just like Azura.
I woke up, done that, wait.
Did I just fall asleep? I don't. Anyways, I woke up the next day in my coffin. I walked
out of it and put on some black eyeliner, black eyeshadow, black eyeshadow, blood,
blood, bed or lipstick and black really low cut leather dress that was all ripped and in
stripes so you could see my belly. I was wearing a skull belly ring with black and red diamonds
inside of it. That's pretty hot. I'm not going to lie. A reference persona.
The night before, Draco and I rent back to the skull, get it skull because I'm
gothic and I like death. Dumbledore chased Voldemort away. We flew there on our brooms.
Mine was black and the broom stuff was blood red. The broom stuff. There was lace all over it.
Draco had a black MCR boom. We went back to our rooms and we had a, you know what,
to a Lincoln Park song.
Well, anyway, I went down to the Great Hall. There was all the walls, sorry, there all the walls
were painted black and the tables were black too. But you could see that there was pink
pants underneath the black pants and there was pastors of poser bands everywhere like Ashley
Simpson and the Backstreet Boys. They danced. Yeah, they totally, they danced.
My room is plastic and I bought a new Walmart.
WTF, I shouted, going to sit next to Bloody Mary and Willow. Bloody Mary, here we fucking go,
was wearing a black leather mini with a good Charlotte T-shirt, black fishnets and black pointy
boots. Well, I was wearing a long gothic black dress with blood red riding. That was all lacy
and came up to your thighs and black boots and fishnets. Vampire Dracula and Draco came.
Okay, totally unnecessary. We started to talk about who was sexier, Mikey or Gerard Way or
Billy Joe Armstrong. The boys joined in because they were bi. Those guys are so fucking hot.
Navel was saying a suddenly a gothic old man with a black beard and everything came.
He was the same one who had chased Voldemort, away Voldemort yesterday. He had normal tan skin,
but he was wearing white foundation and he had dyed his hair black, dyed as in dead and hair as in
like the rabbit. The old man came. My thighs, this is your thighs, up to your thighs, so I guess
you're wearing the so fit. Zombold door. Wheel gas. WTF, I shouted angrily. I thought he was just
wearing that to scare Voldemort. Hello, everyone. He said happily, as you can see, I gave the
room a makeover. What do you think about it? Everyone from the poser table and Gryffindor
started to cheer. Well, we got to just look at each other all disfusted and shook our heads.
We kind of believe you. What a poser he was. BT dubs. You can call me Albert. He called as we left
to our glasses. Why is it capitalized? What a fucking poser. Draco shouted angrily as we we
to transformation. We were holding hands. Vampire looked really jealous. I could see him crying
blood in a gothic way. Get it? Way like Gerard. Like Gerard. But I didn't say anything. I bet he's
having a midlife crisis. Well, I'm shouted. I was so fucking angry. I have to read the spelling
mistakes are what makes this. I don't I could not I couldn't go without it. You know, hold on,
let me fix my glasses. Perfect. It's because when I lean forward and lean back, it doesn't, doesn't
notice. Chippy break. How's everybody doing so far?
Are you guys surviving? Are you guys thriving?
You have questions? Okay, let's class raise your hand if you have a question.
Go on. Is mischief? No, he's not in the story.
I'm coming more gothic by the second good. Yes, you in the front. What's your question? I see you
raising your hand. You like my take on it. I'm glad.
What's going on? You don't need to know dying by a little of laughing. I just finished my second
tangerine. I'm so happy for you. How much more cringe would my immortal be if it were written
with brain rot? I feel like it wouldn't change. How old is the author of the time of writing this?
I think she was like 16. You're wondering if all of you alert girls are saline or Ravenclaw?
I can tell you.
Here's my Hogwarts house headcanon. I am Gryffindor. Azura is Hufflepuff.
Amy is Slytherin. Icy is Hufflepuff. Strawny is Gryffindor.
And Mercy is Ravenclaw.
I was thinking because I don't think Strawny would be
in Slytherin.
No, but they do know who wrote this. It was Tara Gillesbee. She wrote it for satire.
But just kidding. I actually wrote it. It was my real life account when I went to Hogwarts.
Anyone question? Who is Gerard? From the Witcher? You can picture him like that because that's kind
of hot. Like Henry Cavill Witcher or a video game Witcher. Either one would be golden. But no,
Gerard Way is the lead singer of MCR. My Chemical Romance. Gerald. I have the Witcher 1 and 2.
I thought I had the Wild Hunt. But I guess I don't.
Geralt. He'll be the hot teacher. He have intrusive thoughts about.
He doesn't even have to be a hot teacher. I would just have thoughts about him.
Geralt. Yes, Geralt. Gerald actually.
She be Witcher Marathon when? Like I was gonna like play in the games or like watching it.
Because I'll gladly watch it with you guys again. I like the the TV show.
On Netflix. What day is it today?
Hi, Siri. What day is it?
Oh, goodie. I have my members stream tomorrow. Or we get to watch the Master of Disguise together.
No, I haven't done anything. It'll be my first membership stream.
Yeah, we're gonna join the Turtle Club.
You're going to miss it. How dare you? Do I have to start being more possessive?
Am I being too nice? I'll be like, you guys better give me so much attention or I'm gonna die.
I'm like a plant. I'm gonna wither away and I'm gonna perish. If you don't tell me you love me right now.
Why do you guys have jobs? Jobs are to watch me. Give me attention and love and affection.
Because I'm lonely and I crave all the affection and attention in the world.
I tried to hold that one back and it didn't really work out for me.
You love me? You love me? But your name's in gray. You're a fucking light-nosed.
Most stable VTB. I can go real manhara. I didn't get real yandere. You ain't seen nothing yet.
You ain't seen nothing. You ain't seen nothing. But no, no, I'm gonna be good.
I'm gonna be good because I'm a responsible little streamer and I am...
My marbles are in the jar. None of them. They've all been gathered.
Manhara. That sounds like it should be a segment.
That actually is a segment where I just... I don't even know what it would be about. So give me ideas.
I had to fill the jar with something.
I love my madam because madam loves us wrong. But I need to make money to spend on that.
Am I like a cat? I'm like a... I'm like an independent cat that just like roams your house
and I give you love and affection sometimes but on my terms. And then you just give me lots of treats
and you buy me lots of toys and cat trees and you just hope one day that I'll just be able to
speak and tell you how much I love you back but I never do because I'm a cat.
As someone who has two cats, this is already a reality. Perfectly explained, see?
Makes sense as why I was a cat in my past life.
Agon, she's here. She be scratching the door, you open, then you stare and you walk away.
Yeah, pretty much. I'm gonna sit on your desk while you're playing game and I'm gonna knock
your g-fuel, your gamer sups off your desk because I want your attention and pets.
You did own a cat once. What happened to it? Why? Why are you saying that so ominously?
That's what happens if we touch your belly. You know, I don't like belly rubs. It just...
I'm not feeling... You give me headpats, you can scratch my booty, but belly rubs.
I'm gonna have to use my claws on you, sport. I'm sorry, you know?
Some of those cats can bring a serious income.
I must be the only cat owner who's never had their cat knock shit off their desk,
actually, my cats don't really do that. I'm trying to...
They don't, yeah, they don't really knock things off my desk. So usually just like,
Boomi will just like pick it up in his mouth and just run away with it. He doesn't knock it off.
Stretch. Ignore my delahod head being contained by only...
Uh, what's it called? My hoodie, flying off into the distance.
I don't use a desk. Yeah, they just sit on the floor.
It's in me to face it. No, I'm kidding. I'm teasing you. I'm teasing you.
Oh, she's touching this. Okay, rest in peace. Good cat. I've had several cats.
Growing up. So I totally get it. I don't even know where my cats are right now.
I think Boomi's laying in his bed. I cleaned my house today.
The cats were terrified by the new vacuum. Boomi, I don't even...
Like Reina just sat on the couch and was chilling and she was just watching it because she's
keeping an eye. And then Fia was hiding under the bed. Now that she can do that, there's a little
spot in the cat stairs. It's like a bed. And so she like goes inside the cat stairs and then
just like sleeps in there and hangs out when she's chilling. And then Boomi was just walking around
with his... The hair on his back bristled in fright with this little... The base of his tail poofy.
And then just like... But then like wouldn't walk away from the vacuum. And I'm like, dude,
if you're scared of it, just like, why are you keep like... You're just staring at it. I'm like,
are you like someone who likes to watch like horror movies because you like the adrenaline it gives
you? Like you have every... Like your fight or flight is non-existent. Like the cat. I don't even...
Boomi is just a dork. He climbed into my fridge for the like 50th time today. Boomi likes to chill
out in my fridge. I don't know why he does. It's not like he's hot. He just likes to go in there.
I took a picture of him in my empty fridge because I went to go get some juice and I left it open
for a second. And then he... It's a cool vibe. He just wanted to vibe in the fridge. And he...
I can't really explain it. But you know how there's like a little like side... Like when you open the
doors, there's usually like in the doors, you can like put like condiments and stuff. And usually
like in the bottom, there's like a place where you can stick like a juice or like a water thing.
So I like... Mind you, I couldn't... So I was like half closed. So like one door was open, one was
closed. And I go to close the other one and I see Boomi's head sticking out. And I'm like,
dude, what are you doing? So I open the door so I can get him out. And he's just sitting in the bottom
thing. And then so he just like slowly comes out of the fridge, but like sitting in the shelf
from the fridge. And I was just losing it because it was just so funny how he just slowly was like,
I'm in the bottom. I will post a picture. I took a picture of it, but you guys can't bully me.
He wants some sauce from the fridge. Hey, shut up.
I don't know why he gets in there because then I have to wipe it every time he gets in there
because it was... I don't want his dirty paws in my fridge, you know, my refrigerator.
I'm the sauce lady. I come out and I throw sauce everywhere.
All right, let's continue. Hope everybody enjoyed that break. Let me move my glasses back.
Make a comfort. All right.
I'm sorry. That was one of my favorite memes when Batman came out.
Anyways, why can't I get my glasses to work? Come on glasses.
Come on. Oh, fine. I'll put them like awkwardly like that.
Why are they big? Let me make them smaller. Let me make them a little smaller.
I can't find... I can't find the window to the walls. My favorite version of that song.
Okay.
Next chapter. Chapter 19. The last thing you want in your Burger King break. Sorry. Anyways.
I'm not okay. I promise. I'm not okay. I promise.
All day, we sat angrily thinking about Dumbledore. We were so fucking pissed off.
Well, I had one thing to look forward to. The MCR concert. It had been post-phoned,
so we could all go. MCR postponed their concert so that everybody from Hogwarts could go. That's
pretty sick. Jill's ASMR roleplay. Just joined. Can we get a recap of what we've read so far?
I've only read like three chapters because I get distracted easily and I like the app.
But so far, Ebony and Draco went to a MCR concert, but it wasn't really MCR. It was
Vulsamort and the Deaf Dealers. And then Dumbledore scared him away. And then Dumbledore is trying
to pretend that he's goth. And so he changed Hogwarts into a goth academy because he's a poser.
MCR is so pissed. Okay.
Where the fuck?
I lost my spot.
We were so fucking pissed off. We already said that. Anyway, I went to the common room sadly
to cut classes. Draco was being a little secretive. I asked what it was and he got all mad at me and
started crying all hot and angsty. Aren't sensitive by guys so hot. No one fucking understands me.
Oh wait, sorry. No one fucking understands me. He shouted angrily as his black hair went in
his big blue eyes like Billy Joel, Billy Joe, and Boulevard of Borkin Dreams.
I was wearing a black leather low cut top and chains all over it, all over it. A black leather
mini black high held boots and a cross belly thing. My hair was all up in a messy, really high
bun like Amy Lee and gong under. Email me if you want to see the pic.
I'm gong under, gong under Billy Joe. My dreams are Borkin.
Accused me. What about me? I growled.
Oh no, my head.
Bye, butt, butt. He grunted. You fucking bastard. I moaned. No, wait, it's not what I'm fucking,
wait, no, wait, wait. No, wait, it's not what it fucking looks like. He shouted. Why?
He only said no one understands me. Why am I getting so upset?
But it's too late. I knew what I heard. I ran to the bathroom angrily, cring,
Draco banged on the door. I whipped and I whipped as my bloody eyeliner streamed down my cheeks
and made cool tears down my feces like Benji in the video for girls and boys.
Raven, that is so our video. I took out a cigarette and started to smoke pot.
I took out a cigarette and started to smoke pot.
I'm joking. Oh, okay.
Suddenly Hagrid came. Sorry, Hagrid came. He had a pirated.
You gave me a fucking shock. I shouted angrily, dropping my pot. What WTF you think you're doing
in the girls room? Only it wasn't just Hagrid. Someone else was with him too. For a second,
I wanted to be Tom Rid or Draco, but it was Dumbledore.
Hey, I need to ask you a question. He said pulling out his black wannabe
gothic purse. What are you wearing to the concert?
You know who MCR are?
I gasped. No, I just I can't maintain the accents. No, I just saw there was a concert
that a lot of goss and punks were going to. Yee-haw. He said, anyway, Draco has a surprise for you.
Is it his pee pee? I don't know.
You're at a cool concert. Your teacher shows up. Yee-haw. Everyone says to me Yee-haw, but nobody
says, oh, yee.
Anyway, chapter 20.
All day, I wondered what the surprise was. Meanwhile, I popped on a black letter mini,
a black corset with orbo lace stuff all over it, and black gothic compact boots.
MCR were going to the concert again, since Volxamort has taken over the last one.
I slipped my wrists while I moshed to MCR in my bedroom all night, feeling excited.
So wait, she's just like in her bedroom, you know,
using it, making ketchup packets, and then she just throws her body around her room.
Just moshing. Didn't Draco die? No, he didn't die. He just took out a knife,
and then I guess, and then Dumbledore just like showed up and didn't kill.
Yeah, and so he didn't die. Draco's alive. He's fine.
Dumbledore has his priorities straight. She sleeps in a dorm. Well, she has her own bedroom with Willow.
So it's her and her roommate Willow, okay?
Where did I lost my spot? I'm excited. Suddenly someone knocked on the door while I was trying
some black clothes and moshing to fang you for Da Venom. I got all mad in turn of, but scarredly,
sacredly, I hopped inside that it was Draco, so we could do it again.
What the fucking hell are you doing? I shouted angrily.
It was Lupin. Are you gonna call me? Or what? I yelled.
Are you gonna share some grape juice with me or what? I yelled. I was allowed to say that
because Dumbledore had told us all to be careful around him and snap since he was a pedo.
No, actually. Get it, hell. Can I please borrow some condoms?
He growled angrily. Yeah, so you can fuck your six-year-old girlfriend? Huh? I said this
sarcastically. Fuck her, he said, gong away. Well, anyway, I put on some black eyeshadow.
That sounds bad. Black eyeliner and some black lipstick and white foundation. Then I went. Then
I gasped. Ellipses, ellipses, ellipses, ellipses, ellipses, ellipses, ellipses, ellipses. Snake
and Lupin were in the middle of the empty hall doing it and Dobby was watching.
Oh my god, you ludicrous idiot. They both
shooted angrily when they saw me. Dobby ran away crying.
They got up though. Normally I would have been turned on. I love seeing guys do it.
But both of them were fuking preps. By the way, Snake has moved to Gryffindor now.
Why does she hate Snape so much? You'd think he's like the ultimate goth icon in Harry Potter.
Why would you make Snake Snape a non-goth?
WTF? Is that why you wanted condoms? I asked sadistically. See, I spelled that.
Yeah. She still doesn't. Only you wouldn't give them to me. Lumpkin shouted angrily.
While you should have told me, I replayed. You, you, damn it. Snake began to shoot angrily. And then
Ellipses, I took out my black camera and took a pic of them. You can see that they were naked and
everything. Well, excuse me. They both shouted angrily. What was that all about?
It was to blackmail you. I snarked. So now next time you see me doing it with my boyfriend,
you can't fuking rat me out. I'll show this to Dumbledork. So fuk off you bastards.
I started to run. They chased me, but I threw my wound at them and they tripped over.
Wait, so translation. She threw her wand and they just tripped. Two grown ass men managed
to both trip over a like six inch wand. Well, anyway, I went outside and there was vampire
looking extremely fuking hot. WTF. Where'd Drake go? I asked him. My nose is itchy.
Could be packing a bigger wand. Yeah, maybe her, her wand is just thick. She got a thick
um's wand thicker than a snicker. Um, sorry, I just read the next line. Um, garsh. Oh,
he's being a fuking bastard. He told me you wouldn't come. Huh? Vampire said shaking his head.
You want to come me to the concert?
Then he showed me his flying car. I gasped. It was a black car. He said his dogfather's.
Wait, is that like a joke because Serious Black is a werewolf? His dogfather?
Is that a thing in the books? I've never read the books or seen the movies really. So
um, has given it to him. The license plate on the front said MCR666 on it. The one on the back
said a no be on it. I gasped. We flew to the con. Like, okay, I just didn't say anything about it.
I just gasped. Where is everybody getting these vanity plates? You know, these vanity plates are
very expensive. Um, at least in America. We flew to the concert hall. MCR were there playing. Vampire
and I began to make out, moshing to the music. Oh, so she just cheated on her fuking boyfriend.
What a bitch. Andy Arbrose are going to eat this shit up.
I gasped looking at the band. I almost had an orgasm. Geron was so fuking hot.
He began to sing Helena. And that's the only song she fuking knows by MCR. I swear to God.
And his sexy, beautiful voice began to fill the hall. Ellipses. And then I heard some crying.
I turned and saw Draco crying in a corner because he saw me cheating on her.
Oh, please. If somebody, did she be cotton bum for their license plate? Somehow I would,
I would, I would do a backflip. I'm not even joking. I'll do a backflip if that happens.
No, actually, no, I can't do a backflip, please. I haven't done a backflip for a long time
since gymnastics. Please, no.
I was sitting in the cock corner. He was in the cock dirt, in the cock chair.
All right. Chapter 21. Is there a cat on my chair? I feel like I hear scratching.
No. Okay, I'm just making sure that my cat isn't like being like, hey, pick me up.
Oh, my head edges. She be CB. Well, you don't have to, you can make it, you know, different.
It could just put she be bum. But how do you backflip with your back problems? I don't know.
That's why I said never mind. I was like, my back hurts so bad while I was vacuuming. I'm like,
wow, I'm really, I'm really getting up there in age. I can't, when I hit 57, I'm probably just
going to explode. Later, we all went in the skull. Draco was in the common room. Draco, are you okay?
I asked him, oh, sorry. Draco, are you okay? I asked him the gothic voice. I guess my gothic voice,
I guess. No, I'm not you fucking bitch. He shouted angrily. He stated to run out of the place in a
suicidal way. I shouldn't have said that word because of fucking YouTube and on the live and
Minecraft way. I stated to cry because I was afraid he would commit seppuku.
She cheated on her and she has something to ask. I know I'm like, dude, what's wrong? You only saw
me kissing your ex-boyfriend because this is a weird love triangle. Don't permit the suise doll.
That's actually pretty good, the suise doll.
Oh, okay.
It's okay, you know me. Vampire said comfortably, I'll make him feel better.
You mean you'll go fuck him, won't you? I shouted, girl, you just kissed him in front of Draco. You
literally just cheated, you have no right to act this way. Oh my god.
Then I ran to get Draco. Vampire came too. Draco, please wait. Who's talking?
I'm just gonna say it as a nobody. Draco, please come. He began to cry. Tears of blood came down
as pale as in like a pale you put sand in face. I was so turned on because I love sensitive
by guys. If you're a homophobe, then fuck off. Yeah, I get so turned on watching men cry. Tears of blood.
And then ellipses, ellipses, ellipses, ellipses, ellipses, ellipses.
We heard, like heard as in like cows, by the way, some footsteps. Vampire got out his black
invincibility coke. Like, is it a drug or is it? Or is it the fucking? Or is it like a Coca-Cola?
Oh, I apologize if anybody donated. I have my, I don't mind wearing my headphones.
Um, wait, nobody told me that nothing, no music was playing.
Video, why is the video pause? Has it been up and playing this entire time?
I'll just replay the same video. Let's go. Okay.
Okay. But thank you, BlackSilence26 for the tip from earlier. Here's a reward for cleaning your house.
Madame, thank you. Thank you.
I thought silence is for ambience and drama. I'm so folk. Okay, okay. That's good at least. That's good.
We both got under it. We saw the janitor, Mr. Norris there, shouting angrily with the flashlight in his hand.
He shouted angrily. We saw Filth come. He went under the invisibility cloak and started to meow loudly.
Wait, is it Mrs. Norris, the cat? Does she just get the characters messed up?
I thought there was like a teacher that could turn into a cat. It was a cat's name, Filth.
Chuck Norris is here. She messes up the names. Okay.
Um,
Hey, shout out to you one day.
Y'all, Mr. Norris.
No, fuck you, you preppy little loser-poser son of a fucking bitch.
Y'all, vampire senator, is breast in a disgusted way.
Oh, that's a bit of a gongal. Okay. I don't fucking know. What is the cat called, Filth?
What is the cat called, Filth?
Um, excuse me, excuse me, who said that? Y'all, Mr. Norris, then he heard Filth meow.
Filth, is there anyone under the cloak? Wait, he knows the cloak is there.
It was like, is anyone there? Is there just a random invisibility cloak?
Then nobody can be possibly under, although I heard something. Oh my gosh, hi, Reina.
Reina, what's up, girlie pop? You coming to snuggle? Oh my god, you're coming to snuggle with me?
Really? Oh my god, yes, queen. Thank you. Reina has joined the fray.
She is rubbing against the microphone.
She is rumbling. She's headbutting the mic. Her chest is wet because she must have just
decided to swim in her water bowl.
She's purring so well.
All right, she's sitting on my shoulder now. Let's continue.
Filth nodded, and then ellipses, ellipses, ellipses. Vampir franched me.
He did it just as Mr. Norris was taking off the cloak.
What the? He yelled, but it was too late now because we were running away from him.
And then we saw Draco crying and busting into tears and slipping and making catch
of packets outside the school. Draco, I cried. Are you okay? I guessed. I guessed, though.
Draco wept. We went back to our coffins, frenching each other. Where the fuck did vampire go?
Draco and I decided to watch Lake Placid see isn't that depressing on the gothic red bed together
as I was about to put on the video in the video. What? What is happening? My eyes rolled up and
suddenly I had a vision of something that was happening. Now there was a knock on the door and
Fug and a mystery of magic walked into the school. Draco as in Soldier Boy? Sure.
Okay. Chapter 22.
Draco couldn't hold his edge in bust. Here's 44 chapters of this.
Um.
All day, everyone talked about the misery of magic. Well, anyway, I woke up the next day.
I'm scared. I was in my coffin so I opened the door. I was wearing black lacy leather pajama.
Who wears leather pajamas to bed? Who does this? Then I gasped.
We're gonna do the gasped noise.
No. Okay. She's just gonna burn to the microphone.
Real gobs too. You're right. You're right. I'm gonna start wearing leather to bed.
I'll get some latex leather. Just be like only in bed like that.
Standing in front of me wear Bloody Mary, Vampire, Diabolo, Draco, Dracula and Willow.
I opened my crimson eyes. Wait, were they close? How did they know? Willow was. Oh, great. Here we go,
everybody. Buckle in for the outfits. Willow was wearing, I'm saying this in my normal voice.
Willow was wearing a tight black leather top with pictures of bloody roses all over it.
Under that, she warped a black poofy skirt with lace on it and black gothic boots that was attached
to the top. What? Vampire was wearing a baggy simple plan t-shirt and baggy black pants and vans.
Draco was wearing a black MCR t-shirt and black... Why did a Windows thing just pop up? I don't care
about Windows 11. Remind, why did that just pop up randomly? Sorry. Windows had something to say.
Draco was wearing a black MCR t-shirt and black jeans and a leather jacket.
He looked just like a Gerard Way and almost as fucking sexy. Vampire looked like Joel Madden.
Bloody Mary. I just thought of like, like, like e-sports. I mean, not e-sports, or just like,
um, what the fuck? Just like, one of the football games are just Madden. Yeah, just just Madden,
the game. Bloody Mary was wearing a tight black poofy gothic dress that she had ripped it,
so it showed all of her clerage with a white apron that said, bitch, mother swear words.
She's so, she's like essentially dressed like Alice the Madness, but then just has stuff written
all over her apron. Um, mother swear words and MCR lyrics on it kind of like, kind of like one
dress I had seen Amy Lee wear once. Darkness, who is Jenny, was there too. She was weaving a ripped
gothic black dress with ripped stuff all over an lace-up top thing in black pointy boots.
So were Crab and Goyle. It turns out that Darkness, Diabolo, Crab and Goyle's dad was a vampire.
He committed, uh, Suisse doll by making ketchup with a razor. He had given them grape juice and
stuff before too. They all got so depressed that they became gothic and converted to stanism.
Not enough all thank you, yeah. Yeah, they became K-pop stans.
So basically everyone in Slytherin has the same backstory, essentially, yeah.
Oh, I'm FG. I yielded as I jumped up. Why the fuck are you all here?
And no be, wait, and no be something has really fucked up. Draco said, okay, but I need to put
on my fucking clothes first. I shouted angrily. It's all right. We have to go now and you look
kawaii anyway. You are so fucking beautiful. Draco said in a sexy voice.
Oh, all right. I said smiling, but you have to tell me why you're being all erective.
I will, I will, he said. So I didn't, Reyna, why are you, she's like in the weirdest position right
now. Reyna, why are you sitting like that? Okay. I brushed you this morning and you're shedding
so much. Let's do some brush ASMR. I literally vacuumed and there was so much hair. Oh, there's
now you're getting cozy. Oh, okay. Perfect. You just hang out just like that.
She wants to listen. She was like, Reyna has this weird thing where she'll like
sit her butt on me, but then like stand up. Like, but it's like uneven. So like, okay, imagine you're
like on a stair and this cat is on a stair, but the butt is on the top stair and their feet are
just like standing on the bottom stair and she just like uses parts of me as like a little shelf to
put her ass on. So I just don't understand why she sits like that. She was doing that on one leg
to my other leg because my legs were uneven. But yeah, I hope that makes sense to you.
So I just put on some black eyeliner, black lipstick and black and red eyeshadow and white
foundation. Then I came. We all went in front of your friends. Come on, girl. There's a time and a
place. We all went outside to the great hell and looked in from a widow, a fucking prep called Brittany.
This is supposed to be Brittany Spears, by the way, from Gryffindor. Brittany Spears is canonically
Gryffindor was standing next to us. She was wearing a pink mini and a Hillary Duff T-shirt. So we put
up our middle fingers at her inside the great hall. We could also see Dumbledork. Cornelia fudged
was there shouting at Dumbledore. Doris Rumbridge was there too. This could not be. She said it
angrily. The school must be closed. The barclaw is planning to kill the students yelled Cornelia fudge.
You are not fit to be principal any longer yelled Rumbridge. You are too old and your Alzheimer's
is dangerous. You must retry or Voldemort will kill your students. What the fudge?
Very well. Dumbledore said angrily. But we cannot do this. We cannot close the school. There is
only one person who is capable of killing Voldemort and she is in the school. And her name is
Anoni Darkness Dementia Raven Way. Draco Crabgoyle Darkness Willow Vampire and Bloody Mary and
everybody else at the fucking school apparently looked at each other. I gasped. Alzheimer's
Yeah, I don't know. They just they just say he has Alzheimer's.
Oh, this is what she looks like by the way. If you guys didn't in the corner right over here,
you can kind of see the hair. I'm going on.
Chapter 23. The door opened and Professor Rumbridge and Cornelia fudge. That's an awesome last name
stomped out angrily. Then Dumbledome and Rumbridge sawed us in half because not like saw as in like
saw you. Sawed as in with a hardware tool, by the way. Chow's in one. She looks like a prep. Yep,
yep, she does. Mr. Way. What the beep are you doing? Rumbridge. Wait.
Why did she call him Mr. Way? Is Dumbledore's last name
Way? Is he secretly Jared Way's brother? No, Reina, don't leave. Okay, she went and hopped in her bed.
Okay. Okay.
Oops. She made a mistake. Sorry. Dumbledore blared at her. Not glared blared. Oops. She made it. Wait.
What the fuck? I totally. It doesn't matter. She means hi. Everybody come in. See you and by the
way, everybody has to come. There's a mistake. I have to make sure.
My chair squeaky. I need to burp.
Well, we all came in angrily. So did all the other students just in this big ass office.
I sat between darkness and Draco and opposite Bloody Mary. Crab and Goyle started to make some
morbid jokes. They both looked exactly like Vile Volo. What? Who's Vile Volo? I don't know.
I ate the number. Some Count Chocula and Drake some blood from a cup. Where is she getting this?
Then I heard someone shooting angrily at a school. Come on. Put it away, bro.
I looked behind me. It was vampire. Great vampires.
Doing stuff at the school. Oh, okay. Got you. I have never, I had never seen the person. I don't
think I've heard of that band. I have to look that up. I probably listen to their songs, but I just
never heard of the meme. Here, Draco, we're shooting at each other. Why are they shooting?
Vampire Draco WTF? I asked. You fucking bastard. Y'all, Draco had vampire. I want to shit next to her.
No, I do. I'm a vampire shouted. No, she doesn't like you, you son of a bitch. Y'all, Draco.
No, fuck you, motherfucker. She laughs me, not you. Y'all shouted vampire. And then he jumped on Draco.
No, and not in that way, you perv. They started to fight and beat up each other.
Dumbledore yelled at them, but they didn't stop. All of a sudden, a terrible man with red eyes and no, no.
I want to say someone's name so bad as a joke, but I don't want their pants to come from me.
Insert with a vtuber of your choice. He had no nose and was wearing a gray robe.
All the glass in the window he flew through fell apart. Britney, that fucking prep started to cry.
Vampire Draco stopped fighting. I shopped eating. Everyone gasped. The room fell silent.
Full Zemort. Do it, Shibani. No, Shibani. Shibani doesn't. I don't want to. I don't want to get
Sheebie in trouble. Eboby, Ebony, Darth Vader. Wait. Where did Darth Vader come from? Why is Darth Vader here?
I thought it was Voldemort. No, it's Darth Vader. Said it in his evil, in his raspy voice.
Thou hast failed your mission.
No, I shall kill Thou, and I shall kill Vampire as well. If Thou does not kill him before,
then I shall kill Draco too. Please don't make me kill him, please. I begged.
No. He laughed crudely. Kill him, or I shall kill him anyway.
Then he flew away cackling. Dirt Vruder. Made it as an impure new day to day life. I guess not.
I bust into tears. Draco and Vampire came to contort me.
Oh, let's do some contort. Suddenly my eyes rolled up, so they all looked so cool and gothic.
Am I cool and gothic?
I had a vision where I saw some lightning flash and then Voldemort coming to kill Draco. Will Draco
made some ketchup packets on his wrist in a depressed way?
Hey. I'll contort you. No. I screamed sexily. Suddenly I locked up and stopped having the vision.
Ebony. Ebony. Ebony.
Excuse you honking your horn outside. I don't know if anybody else heard that.
Ebony. Ebony. Are you all right? Ask Draco in a worried voice.
Yeah. Yeah. I said sadly as I got up. Everything's all right and no me.
Vampire all senesitive. No, it's not. I shouted angrily. Tears of blood went down my face.
OMG. What if I'm getting possessed like in the ring too?
It's okay girl. I said Bloody Mary. Maybe you should ask Professor Sinister about what the visions
mean though. Okay bitch. I said sadly. Okay bitch. I said sadly and then we win.
Chapter 24.
Well, we had deviation. Deviation. Divination. Deviation of a septum. Next. So I got to ask
Professor Travolry about the visions. Konnichiwa everybody come in.
I'll use another kawaii voice for everybody. Yeah, it's Sinister.
What is it I need to do? I'll give her, I'll give her like a, I don't know, like what does she have
like a northern UK accent? I don't, I can't, it's essentially Scottish or she's Scottish. I can't
recall. Konnichiwa everybody come in. I said Professor Sinister in Japanese. What was that in
English? She smelled at me with her gothic black lipstick. She's the coolest fucking teacher ever.
She had long dead black hair with blood red tips and red eyes. Her mama's a vampire. She's also
half Japanese so she speaks it in everything. She and Bloody Mary get along great. She's really
young for a teacher. Who is supposed, who is this supposed to be? Who, who teaches divination in the,
in the books? She's Russian but moved to Scotland. Oh, interesting. Okay, I can't do
Scottish accent but I'll try my best. Today she was wearing black leather top with red lace and
long gothic black rip dress. We went inside the black classroom with pastors of Emily the Strong.
I don't, who is that? Emily the Strong? I raced my hand. I was wearing some black naipolite Polish
the country, the, the nationality, the ethnicity with red pentagrams on it.
What is it happening? Yes. Hey, I love your naipolite. When did you get to talk topic?
Yeah, I answered all the preps who didn't know what HT was gave me weird looks. I gave them
middle finger. I wish I had my hand cam on because then when I, I would just, I would just flip you
guys off. Um, well, I have to talk about to you about some things. When do you want to do it?
How about now? She asked. Okay, I said. Okay, class fucking dismissed everyone.
Professor Trevoree said, and she let everyone go except, except for you, Brittany. She pointed
up Brittany and some other preps. Please do exercise. Get it. One on page three. Exercise.
Wait, is Professor Sinister and Professor Trevoree the same person?
It's not too late to hand cam. Yeah, I'd have to set all the shit up.
I'd be like, do it. Like, no, it was actually due as in like a paper is due. So yeah. Okay.
Please do exercise. One on page three. Okay, I'm having lots of visions. I said in a worried voice.
I'm so worried. Draco is going to die. Well, she gave me a black crypt tall ball to lock in.
I looked at it. What day to see? She asked.
I said, I see a black, she got like some quotes like she's saying that
black gothic skull and a pentagram. Suddenly there was a knock on the door. I looked at it.
It was Draco. He was looking really sexy wearing a black leather facet.
Is that supposed to be jacket facet? A black gothic Lincoln Park t-shirt and black
Congress shoes, not converse Congress. Okay, you can go now see a con.
Professor.
Bye, bitch. I said waving.
I went to Draco and vampire was sitting next to him. We both fall drink.
I like a hiccup yard at the same time. Draco together and I was so exhibited.
Congress.
Wait, Congress shoes are real? It's not the Jedi way, no respect for her teacher.
Well, she, the teacher said, okay, you can go now see a con. So
all right, chapter 25.
I was so excited. I fellow Draco wondering if we were going to do it again.
We went outside. Wait, isn't, I thought vampire was also following us.
We went outside and then we went into Draco's black car.
I've been in with the fuck did Professor Trivalry say?
Whispered Draco potting his gothic wit hand with black nail polish on mine.
Polish. Hold it. You get it. He was painting her nails. Yep.
Oh, wait, no, he's, no, he wasn't painting her nails. He was just putting his painted hand,
his nails, his nails are painted and his hands are white because he is a white boy.
His nails are black and he was holding her hand. Okay, I get it.
It's so black.
She said she would tell me what the visions meant tomorrow.
I grumbled in a sexy voice and he took out a heroin. What? Cabaret and spiked it and gave
it to me to, what? He started to fly the car to the tree and to a tree. We went to the top of it.
Draco potting his eyes. Are we doing heroin?
What is happening? I don't even know. What the fuck is a cabaret? Like I felt like cabaret is a show.
Oh, I knew we weren't filming.
Okay.
And all the things that you never ever told me and all the smiles that are ever gonna haunt me.
I don't know the song saying Gerard's sexy voice. Then we started tilling off each other's
clothes fevently. He took off my black thong and black leather bar, not a bra bar. I took off
his black boxers. Then he put his traubing, you know what, in my tools. Oh my fucking God, Draco,
I screamed having an orgasm. We started fringing passively. Suddenly I fell asleep.
Dick's so good. He put her ass to sleep. Now they call in him Nyquil.
I started tapping a tree.
performer
okay okay
Okay, uh, isn't it a black guy who was shooting two Gothic men with long black hair?
No, no, please don't fucking kill us. We're one direction.
Just kidding, it doesn't say that. They pleaded, but he kept shooting them. He ran away.
What is this racism? What did he run away to run a car?
No, my fucking god. I showed it in a scaring movie.
Ebony, what's wrong?
Draco asked me as I woke up opening my icy blue eyes. I actually didn't know her eyes were blue. I thought they were red.
I started to cry tears of blood out my face.
I told Draco to call Vampire. He did it with this black Lincoln Park mobile.
But two T's. The worst thing was who the people were shot in the dream were Lucian and Ciri.
Are there any black people in Harry Potter?
Why is there a red and black dude? Just kidding.
What is this?
Should I get my gun ready? I don't...
I think I just heard Boomi like meow to myself in his sleep. He was like...
Do you think double four is black?
J.K. Rowling said there's no black people in England.
Is that a real fucking person in the books?
Kingsley Shackboat? That's terrible.
I hate the way J.K. Rowling names. It's so bad.
Didn't she give an Asian character the most racist fucking name?
Sorry, racist.
This is gonna get... This is totally gonna get fucking demonetized.
Oh, Kingsley Shackleford.
Cho Chang. Yeah, who the fuck? That's a stupidest name.
Like what? That's so bad.
Oh, anyways, continuing on.
Chapter 20... Wait.
Chapter 26.
A few mutates later, Vampire came to the tree.
He was wearing a black leather Jackson, black leather pants and a good Charlotte t-shirt.
Hi, Vampire. I said flutterly as I started to sob.
Go hug me sexily. How do you hug sexily?
She's crying. Stop trying to pull a move on her, dude.
Triants to come frot me.
Frotting?
I started to cry tears of blood and told them what happened.
Oh, gorse. Oh, fuck it.
Vampire shouted angrily. He started to cry sadly.
What fucking dick did that?
I don't know. I said, now come on, we have to tell Dumbledore.
We ran out of the tree and into the... Wait, we ran out of the tree?
Aren't we like 50 feet up or like higher?
Dumbledore was sitting in his office.
Sire, our dads... Why did he call him Sire?
Sire, our dads have been shot.
Drake Cousin will be whipped.
Whipped some tears from his white face.
And nobody had a vision and a dream.
Dumbledore started to cockle.
What? Started to what now?
Um...
How do you expect me to know Ebony's not divisional?
I cleared a Dumbledore.
Is that supposed to say delusional?
Divisional.
Look, motherfucker.
He said angrily.
As Dumbledore gasped, see is that toot of cracker.
You know very well that I'm not decisional.
Now get some fucking people out there to look for Ceres and Lucian Ponto.
Okay, he said an imitated voice, an intimated voice.
Where are they?
I fought about it. I fought about it.
Then all of a sudden, long done.
I said, I told him which street.
He went and called some people and did some stuff.
After a few mis-tunes, he came back and said people were going out looking for them.
After a while, someone called him again.
He said that they have been found.
Jesus Christ, that was fast.
You know, good on Dumbledore for that.
Draco, Vampire, and I all left our rooms together.
I went with Draco to wait in the nurse's office.
Why? Well, Vampire went to make some catch-up packets in his room.
We looked at each other's gothic, depressive eyes.
Then we kissed.
Suddenly, Ceres and Lucian came in on stretchers and Professor Sinister was behind them.
I like how Professor Sinister never, like, explained the vision we had.
Clip that, clip that.
I need, I please, can someone make a compilation of me reading my immortal?
Please, please, please, I beg of you.
Everyone in the room, Chapter 27.
Everyone in the room stated to cry happily.
I had saved them.
Draco, Lucian, Serious Bond.
Serious Bond?
Like, is he James Bond?
Vampire all came to hug me.
The nurse started to give them medicine.
Come on a nobie, said Professor Sinatra.
She was wearing a gothic black leader dress with a corset top and real vampire blood on it.
Wait, why would she?
So that means she killed a vampire and put blood on it?
And fuking black platinum boots.
I have to tell you the fucking perdition.
I locked at Lucian Serifs.
Like the font.
Drake?
Drake's here?
Where did Drake get here?
Didn't you get your ass beat by Kendrick?
What the fuck are you doing here, bro?
Vampire, they nodded.
I smelled happily and went into a dark room.
I had changed.
Professor Sinatra took out some black cards.
That's a lot of sentence.
She started to look into a black crucible ball.
She said, Terra.
Who the fuck is Terra?
Oh wait, no.
We did, I think we said our name was, we added Terra before Way before.
And like when I was introducing myself.
Okay, Drake Bell.
It's Drake, Drake and Josh.
Nah, I'd like to think it was Drake, the rapper Drake.
Um, Terra.
I see Drac times are near.
She said badly.
She peered into de balls.
Drop your pants.
You see, you must go back in time.
She took out a time toner like Bloody Mary had.
When Voldemort was in Hogwarts before he became powerful, he got his heart broken.
Now do you think he would still become Voldemort if he was in love?
I shook my head.
You must go back in time and seduce him.
It is the only way.
If he is still evil, then you must kill him.
I don't know why I lost the accent.
You can come to my room tomorrow and you can do it.
Okay.
I said sadly.
We did death touch sin.
What is death touch sin?
Death touch sin.
What is that?
I'm picturing her like doing like devil horns.
Hold on.
Where is it?
So I'm picturing two hands.
Just like doing this.
Hold on.
Let me grab another.
I don't know why I named this straight jacket.
Oh, I forgot to flip it.
It's fine.
You get the idea.
My computer is just like, why did you add more assets?
Rock on.
Homie G's.
Poor PC, yeah.
Okay.
Where did the thing go?
Where's it?
What the strike working?
Go back in time and seduce him.
I'm going back in time and I'm seducing it.
Okay.
What fucking happened as Draco and Vampire?
Yeah, what happened?
As darkness willow and bloody Mary, question mark.
I need to drink the water.
I was about to tell them, but everyone was there.
They were celebrating Lucy and his serious being fond.
Everyone was proud of me, but I just wanted to talk to Draco.
They were teasing my name and some reporters were there
trying to interview Dumbledore.
A banner was put up.
Lots of fucking preps were there.
Obviously trying to be gothic
wearing the hymn sign on their hands,
despite not having actually heard of him.
Even Mr. Norris looked happy.
A black and red cake had been brought out.
Crab and Goyk set up some fireworks
and the shape of skulls from Wesley's Wizard Wises.
I put on my invisibility Coke with Vampire and Draco
and we sneaked outside together.
Damn preps.
Thank you.
Okay, eight out of 10.
All right, I'll take that.
I'll take that.
Wait, why is Shaggy in the top over here?
Is that supposed to be?
Oh, sorry, that's Diabolo.
Okay, probably Ron.
Okay.
Chapter 28.
We went into a black room.
The walls were black with portraits of gothic bands
like MCR, GC and Marilyn Manson all over them.
A big black coffin was in the middle.
Red velvet.
I said in the middle, but it says the.
Like that's how you know how messed up I am reading this.
Red velvet.
Oh, cute.
Okay.
Lined the black box.
They were, there were three chairs made of bones
with real skulls in them.
I was wearing a black, did I spill water in between my legs?
Why am I wet?
Um, that sounds bad.
I was wearing a black corset bar
with purple stuff on it.
Fishnet suckings and a black leather thong underneath.
Was I wearing clothes?
My, am I just wearing a thong and fishnets in a bra?
That's pretty hardcore.
So she looks like the average Vtuber.
I love it.
I sat down and wanted to chairs dispersedly.
So did Draco and vampire.
Are you okay?
Wait, are you okay?
Vampire asked potting his alabastered hand on mine.
He was wearing black nail polish.
I was wearing black nail polish with red crosses on it.
Yeah, I guess, I said sadly.
Draco also pot his hand on mine sexily.
I smiled sadly with my black lipstick.
The problem is, I have to seduce Volzemort.
I'll have to go back in time.
Draco started to cry sadly.
Vampire hooked him.
It's okay.
I know it bo, it boby, it booby, it boby, it bobby.
He said finally, but what about me?
You're not gonna break up or anything, are you?
Of course not.
I guessed.
Really?
He asked.
Sure, I said.
Refrenched sexually, vampire looked at us longingly.
Wait a second.
Sorry, I just read ahead.
Mom.
Then I took off Draco's MCR,
shrift, and seductively took off his pants.
He was hung like a Stallone.
He had replaced the vampire tattoo that said Ennobe on it.
Black roses were around it.
I gasped.
He looked exactly like Gerard Way.
Vampire took a video camera.
I had said it was okay before.
I took off my clothes.
Then we were in for the ride of our life.
We started freching as we climbed into the coffin.
He put his spock in mine, you know what?
Impassively we did it.
I love you Ennobe, it boby.
Oh, let me feel you, I need to feel you.
He screamed as we got an orgasm.
We watched vampire filmed everything perfectly.
Suddenly, what the fuck are you doing?
It was Snoop and Professor McGoggle.
One, one, one.
No, vampire was just a cock.
Everybody points and laughs at the cook.
Point and laugh at vampire Harry Potter, the cock.
Chapter 29.
Are you ready?
Oh, my Satan, we screamed as we jammed out of the coffin.
Snap and Professor McGoggle.
McGoggle.
Started to shoot at us angrily.
Come now, preacher McGoggle yielded.
We did it, killed the way.
We left the room.
She just, she just came out of them to come
and then they just came and I'm impressed.
We left the room putting on her clothes.
Snoop, Snoop dogs here.
Garved the caramel and put it in his pocket.
Hey, what the fuck?
I'm a vampire shooting angrily.
Yeah, Buster, what the fuck are you going to do
with the fucking camera?
Draco demonded, all protective,
looking at me longly with his gothic red eyes.
Look, Dumbledore knows your little secret
and if you do this again, then you will go to St. Mango's.
So give back to camera.
The mystery of magic thinks he is crazy.
There's no way a day will believe him.
Snoop laughed meanly.
There was no, there's no quotes.
I couldn't tell who was talking.
Yes, so shut your mouth, you m-m-m-m-poof.
You in-losent fools.
Yelled Professor McGoggle.
She made us come into her room with white stones all around it.
Looks like this is happening before.
There was all these wh-what, we read tools in it.
Draco started to cry all sexy.
Oh, oh, oh.
And sexative, get it?
Cause he's a sex bomb, LOL.
Tom fell not rules for life,
but not as mugs, as Gerard,
your sex on legs.
I love you, you fucking rock, marry me.
I don't know why I slept with you.
I'm really bad accent when I have to read a lot of misspellings.
I started to cry tears of blood.
It happens in Vampire Chronicles, Raven said.
So okay, so fuck you.
Um, they actually, they cry,
Vampires cry blood and true blood.
One of my favorite guilty pleasure shows.
Um, although I stopped watching after season six,
cause it was just so bad.
Um, Vampire took out,
took out a black hunker chip chief
and started to wipe my red eyes.
And then he and Snoop both took out guns using magic.
They started to shoot each other angrily.
Hold on, I need to, I need to make sure I'm strapped.
I need to make sure I'm strapped.
Perfect.
Uh-huh.
Blau, blau.
You like that?
Um, none of the bullets got on each other yet.
I took out my wand.
This is my wand, as you can see.
Cosio.
I shouted snap, started to scrum and he dropped the gun,
but it was too late.
Both of them had run out of ballots, of bellies.
I stopped to curse.
Professor McGoogle did a spell so that we were all chained up.
Ooh, she took out a box of tools.
Then she said,
Okay, Severus, I'm going to go now.
She laughs.
Snap started to laugh evilly.
Vampire started to cry.
It's okay, a nobie, said Draco.
Evergreen.
Who?
You know what?
I think she will be all right.
Remember the city you took of Snake.
Snape laughed again.
And then he took out some whips.
Bro, I hate this fucking dog, bro.
This dog is always, like, always walks by yelling.
I'll wait.
I can wait.
Teacher voice.
The bell doesn't dismiss you.
I do, sweetheart.
I can wait.
I think the dog barks because it knows that there's people in their apartments.
Oh, my God.
Are we done?
Is he done?
Please, is he, is he done?
Please let him, please.
Okay, I think we're good.
Bro, is he yapping?
I think as he heard my voice, usually when you, and dogs have better hearing than humans,
but you can kind of sometimes hear people if they're talking loudly.
Okay.
And took out some whips.
Bark, bark, bark.
Chapter 30.
Oh.
No, we screamed sadly.
Snap stated loafing meanly.
Are you fucking serious?
He took out a camera, Anvilie.
Then he came towards Darko.
Tony Darko's here.
He took some stones out of his pocket.
He put the stones around Draco and knit a candle.
Like, knit as in brightness.
So then I guess that applies.
What the fuck are you doing?
I shoot it angrily.
Pew, pew.
Bow, bow.
Put that away.
I shoot it angrily.
Uh.
Where I lost my place.
Snoop laughed meanly.
He pulled down his pants.
I gasped.
There was a dark mark.
A dark mark on his, you know what?
What?
I don't know what a dark.
That's like the little like snake symbol, isn't it?
I don't know.
He waved his wand and a knife came.
He spelled, she spelled a knife wrong.
He gave the knife to me.
You must romp here.
He said to me, if you don't, then I'll wrap Draco.
No, you fucking bastard.
I yielded.
But then Draco looked at me sadly with his evil,
gothic red eyes that look so depressant and sexy.
He looked exactly like a pentagram.
I'll get it cause I'm a Satanist.
Between Kurt Cobain and Gerard.
It took me a while to figure this out,
but she meant pentagram as in like cross,
like a cross between,
but she says pentagram instead.
It's actually pretty clever.
But then I looked at vampire and he looked so smexy too
with his gothic black hair.
I thought of the time when we screwed, wait,
wait, she fucked vampire.
And that's, wait, I thought they just kissed.
Holy shit.
She just straight up anyways.
And the time I did it with Draco and Dumbledore came
in the team where Draco almost,
Suisse, Dald and vampire was so sportive.
Snipe laughed angrily.
He started to pray to Volzemort.
He started to do an incapacitation dancing
around the stokes whipping Draco and vampire.
Suddenly a idea I had.
I closed up my eyes and using my vampire powers.
I sent a telepathetic mess massage to Draco and vampire
so they would destruct Snape.
Dumbledork will get you.
I'm sorry.
Draco's shooting.
Yeah.
Just wait until the mystery find out.
Vampire yelled.
Meanwhile, I took out my wand.
You ridiculous dunderhead.
I can't do the Snape voice right now.
Snoop.
You ridiculous dunderhead.
I can't do a Snoop Dogg voice either.
He took off Draco's clothes.
Just as he was about to grape juice him.
Crucio, I shitted, pointed my wound.
Snoop scrimmed and started running around the room
scrimming.
Meanwhile, I grabbed my black mobile
and sent a text to Sirius.
I stopped doing Crucio.
You dunderhead.
I'm going to kill.
Shooted Snape as then suddenly Severus came.
Wait, but they're the same person.
Snake put the whip behind his back.
Oh, hello, Seth.
I was just teaching them something.
He lied.
But suddenly Lucian and Professor Traveler came into
room and Sirius unlocked the chains and put them
around Snape.
Then Professor Traveler said, hold on.
Come on, Neboni.
Let's go.
And scene.
How wonderful.
Oh, I'm over here.
Let me take my glasses off.
Let me put those away.
Let me flip myself back.
Beeping, beeping, moow.
Wait a second.
Oh, yeah.
All right.
What did you guys think?
How do you feel?
Are you feeling good?
You feeling lovely?
of all time yeah I agree how did you listen to a masterpiece it's a to be
continued we're gonna we'll finish the rest next week I have to make my
schedule for next week I didn't think about what to do next you know what I
don't why'd you guys hang out with me while I make my schedule how about that
you give me suggestions cuz I haven't done that yet let me just go to the
stream schedule oh I got to log in okay
a stream planning stream wait what's today
why did I think it was I don't know what day it is half the time world conquest
yes that's a given though
Tuesday I'm gonna have I know I have a sketch
strawny takes up so much space on our schedule that we have it's just all all
strongy it was 12 hours of strongy okay
keys a trinket again part two that'll be a eight on Tuesday
huge giant it's starting to build different she is my hood what about my
head what happened to my hood how did my hood go down wait is there a toggle
what I didn't know the second fucking toggles yo are you kidding me oh I'm a
devil now hand over your peepee or you're going to hell
I'm gonna play play give me a hand it over I'm gonna I'm gonna pierce it on my
pitchfork
I'm your little devil girl ooh ooh say chic so sorry um sorry read the Bible so
we have a Bible reading stream for a membership stream I don't even know I
don't even know what passes I would I would want to do what Bible story would
we even do oh wait no I don't have to do that cuz I wanted to do like a nun
confessed stream but I don't have maros right now
ooh but I could still do a nun role play let me do that I'll do a nun ASMR role
play let's see let's see I like to do ASMR on a day that not anybody else is doing
ASMR so you guys get like ASMR at least like like every day okay
shawnee's doing a lot of ASMR
your list oh yes I want to do a tier list okay okay okay Monday we're gonna do a
tier list cuz I want to do that yes she be
member stream can you guys so again I'm not used to YouTube how often do people
do membership streams is it like once a week is it like twice a week I don't I
really don't know how it works just so I like I want to make sure I give you the
right amount if you expected like once it varies okay what do you what do you
um at least once a month Jesus I want to do once a week who's doing membership
stuff once a month depends on the life one maybe twice a month what okay once a
week is common okay okay okay then I'll do I'll do one a week maybe I'll do like
a gorilla every now and then some memberships are more than you know
that's a good point that's a good point that's a good point that's a point I
can't I can't speak on that again member stream and tag tier list and then you
guys are gonna see how fucked up I actually am I can't wait for that I'm
like I've been like dying to do that stream cuz strongy and
and we did no shut the fuck up you bitches oh my god I didn't die for this
oh shut up shut up shut up you can match my freak um maybe hope so okay Monday
4 p.m. actually what would be a good cuz I want to make sure you guys can all
make it what would be a good time for you I can just slide into any slot cuz she's
not here I'm my my beloved but like cuz I stream normally at 4 p.m. Eastern time
okay I think as a you as in the UK be any time alright okay cool okay they'll
keep it up for I just want to make sure like cuz I want people to be able to
make it especially cuz it's a member stream and I don't want people to get
like cuz it's usually funner like to do that sort of stream when you're there I
don't have okay what games have I been playing I've been playing cult of the
lamb sometimes I could probably beat that I could play Elden Ring but like again I
wouldn't we're not gonna get far cuz I'm a slow gamer and I haven't played
Elden Ring in like a year so I'm not gonna be good but I do want to play the
DLC okay you like the adventuring part okay alright I just like cuz I like I
literally just like wander for fucking hours but maybe cuz um you can have the
hair and help but I don't want you guys to help like I don't I don't want my hand
held for that I'll just have to think of a build beforehand and then remember how
I get my runes before cuz I usually do a certain thing to get more runes off the
bat like a level up faster um I'd never really to be honest I didn't really use
spirit summons a lot except for mimic tier hardest soul's game DLC attempted by
shivony darkness dementia bum Raven Way I don't do I have to play through the
entire game and get an ending in order for me to play the DLC because again I
beat Elden Ring on my PlayStation I didn't I only just got it for PC not as
beat Moog okay okay okay so I yeah okay then I'll probably speedrun and beat
Radon and Moog is such a fucking bitch to fight um to she bees to she bees okay
what day would you guys like me to play Elden Ring what's a good game for
everyone
we're done oh we're done I can just cheese we're done that's not hard although I
can cheese Moog too but
my face when I spread misinformation
I've got a free schedule all week you just want to you just want to Elden Ring
fucking all week marathon I think you scheduling your days off first makes the
most sense yeah but I don't really care about my days off because I just want to
hang out with you guys about time
sorry
my little sister is
people on the 4th oh that's right July 4th I forget holidays exist
um
I think I was invited by Salem to go over her house
that's what we look cool that she has let me see
Salem
okay I'm sure she did all of can't make it because she's in the middle of her family
I'm not really used to celebrating holidays I was brought up and I did
celebrating holidays so I forget the holidays exist sometimes
um so I'll do
I'll do Elden Ring okay it looks like Azura has a membership stream at 4 p.m. on
Wednesday so I'll do Elden Ring on Wednesday after her at
6 p.m. and I'll probably just like play until
oh wait no or she's not even streaming well okay well we'll just do an Elden Ring
run she be
Elden Ring
let's do it okay just play cool cool cool and then okay I'll guess so I'll
probably I might do a gorilla on the 4th before I
go maybe just like a zatsu um
in the morning
face is itchy
I'm like breaking out I think it's because of the fucking heat and the sweat
and I feel so fucking gross and you get some like those acne dot things
more mad at me I have time yeah I'll probably in the morning
one time
I'll do like 11 a.m. or 10 a.m. I don't know
not sleepy sleepy ass
I don't think I see fitter schedule so she's probably gonna stream at 12
the damn girl is beat yeah I won't add it to my schedule but Thursday I'll
probably stream in the morning and do like a zatsu
um but I don't want to hold myself to it if like Salem needs help getting
stuff done because I also have to talk to Salem with a podcast we might be
starting and I have to get her all vtuber shit I I'm turning my friend into a
vtuber I hope you guys are happy um why can't I
move to the side okay Friday no yes
what games have I been playing I haven't played vampire the masquerade but
vampire the masquerade keeps getting fucking claimed
so I might not play that which sucks because it's it's like the music in
there is copyrighted for some fucking reason
this is me on
why do I have a pitch for because it's going up your ass
um what do you classify as morning uh I classify 9 a.m. to 11 a.m. is morning
or like 11 a.m. is like early afternoon
forced vtuber vacation it's just awesome because like I told strongy this idea
and like no me and me and Salem have had this idea for a very very long time
um since we started becoming friends for several years
and then I get to live out this cool podcasting dream idea and then get to
invite other girls that like smutty books because it's going to be a
smutty book podcast but I have it's going to take such a long I might take
like a year to get that together though because I have to help
Salem come up with a vtuber persona then I have to come up with all the branding
I have to get stuff made I also have other projects that I wanted to
so uh like another super secret project I'm not going to talk about
but yeah I'm excited I'm excited I'm actually going to be able to get some shit done
I have both quests but I'm probably not going to want to play that the next week
description oh I need to do an ASMR let me do
Friday we'll do a little cute ASMR
my face track oh it died because I was out I was on messages
okay um
ASMR is a surprise so I'm not going to say what it is no title
so
because you guys will go rapid if I tell you
he
I'll be at the normal time and then Saturday and then Sunday
rated rapid what they said you guys I got rated I was like what I'm out of
and leather chewing ASMR yes that is the secret ASMR um
let's see let's see let's see
let me pull up steam so we could think of a game to play for you
I was thinking about playing hit man
you guys are very well behaved you're too well behaved are we being taken for walkies no
something better well at least maybe some of you will like it
continue with bunny garden get absolutely nowhere
okay some counter-strike I'm kidding I'm kidding I'm kidding I'm kidding
okay play the princess I do love slay the princess that's a great game
that's tight and full
I'm really like brats yeah I'm not I'm not a fan of brats
I'm I'm not I'm not in the mood to tame brats
play some apex legends just kidding I fucking hate that game
I have Bioshock remastered I never finished Bioshock when I started playing it
when did I get buckshot roulette
why don't I remember buying buckshot roulette
maybe I mean in general like I can tame a brat
like you've seen me like put my my gen mates in their place during streams
Bioshock you think you might be have Bioshock yeah you want Bioshock
this baby want Bioshock
hmm yeah that's true I didn't I didn't tame you guys
I also have oblivion in Skyrim but I know you guys just me and Strani like the same
exact fucking games like anytime I like go to find a game to play like she's playing
stray I was like I was gonna play a stray uh I don't have shadow mortar though
I'm trying to like
oh you guys want me to play armored core but I don't want to do two souls likes in a week
so
chat terraria screen
she's literally you know I'm literally her
what is I've never played terraria
no it's crashing stream I would just crash my computer just explode
because I'm looking at
I'm looking at what they have for the weeks ahead and I'm like oh
oh
Hades oh Hades I need to buy it but yes because I'm like I don't want to play call the lamb again
but people have said that call the lamb is like Hades so yes I'll get Hades I'll buy Hades
because I know they have been paid as I'm poor I don't know I'm living off tuna fish and rice
and many friends will do that on Saturday I'm going to beat scrawny for overlapping with me every day
I'm looking at the schedule I'm like scrawny please give me a chance
oh okay let me just fucking
he
Hades facade oh my god I fucking love facade not scrawny stop stealing my viewers I'm like scrawny
let your viewers come watch me because I know they like me too
what does it doesn't really matter in the end as long as as long as we alert successful is all I care
about
actually no because she's I'm gonna I'm gonna do that one a little bit later because that's
a membership stream and I don't like overlapping with membership streams I don't want to force people
to choose I don't like that
the fair because she overlaps everyone you're not wrong mercy's the only one that doesn't get
overlapped but sometimes she does and it's hilarious to me
she's already streams 12 hours every day it's more than a full-time job she's doing overtime
consider it mad up yeah I try not I don't like overlapping but I end up doing it myself because
we are just the overlap corpo because we just love hanging out with our fan bases
okay then so did I give myself sunday off I don't know
again I might like a lot of like the days off I can't see me I'm doing air quotes but the days
off like I'll usually just do a unless I have like some pressing errands to do I'll usually just
do a um a gorilla stream a gorilla stream
I do feel like there's quite a distinction between fan bases like not that many watch all
oh I would have to disagree with you I um I have to disagree because I feel like
yes there's there's definitely like fans that are like die hard like oh my god they're my oh
gee but then I think there's people that are like you know I don't mind watching scrawny and then
she be and then I see and then you know get cozy with the zura and then blah blah blah you know
so I I have to disagree with up I have to disagree all right I think that's good
probably we'll do a girl in the morning on Thursday and probably we'll do a girl on sunday
but who knows maybe I won't feel like it maybe I'll be dying my body has been hurting me lightly
I've got a five bro flare up and I don't know why
all the girls are great exactly how could you not want all of this sweet heart you got all
these cute girls for you and the next year you're gonna get more holy shit can you believe that
um yeah I hope you guys have a good day
I see streams at the worst time for me to watch river yeah and then like it's sad because like
I totally feel that because it's like people you want to watch and then you're like ah far
after like look at the ball and the ball it's like it's fun to be like there in the moment
to be able to react or interact you know I totally get that it would be interesting to see you act
as a senpai me
oh well I am senpai and senpapi you can call me papi
mi amor
if it was dream you're welcome you're welcome ho okay hopefully my manager won't attack me now
because he was just like why haven't you done your thing and I'm like I'm like I didn't I didn't know
you okay let's find somebody to raid
add redirect okay I'm just gonna raid strawnee
let's do it let's raid strawnee cuttles
corporate unity
gen unity all right later nerds peace out cub scouts
tell tell strawnee I love her I'm gonna go nap and try to find something to eat
yes I know my mic is still on hi bye
I can't place a smell this time I think it you smell a little bit sweet what's going on there
what's going on there too